Hey, sorry. I was on my phone. I was looking on my phone. I was looking at stuff.
Hello everybody, uh, happy Saturday. Hope you're having a good Saturday. Hope you had a good week.
Hope you're all doing very, very, very well. How am I? I'm doing good. I'm doing as good as I can be.
He loves his phone. Not really. I mean, I- I like FaceTiming my mother. That's fun.
That's something you couldn't do five years ago. When did FaceTime- okay, when did FaceTime
become a thing people were doing? When are you like 15? 2016? When did FaceTime come up?
It was 10 years ago, was it? No, it wasn't. The iPhone 4 and the iPhone 3 couldn't do FaceTime,
could they? No, no, it was like 2015. One sec. It was 2013. Anybody else have this problem?
Is anybody else- is anybody else permanently in 2013, 2014? It's something- what happened in 2013,
2014? Like, I feel like 2014 is like- it's- that's just every year. It's not 2021. No, it's 2014.
Time loop. Well, I don't feel like it's 2021. I feel like it's at most 2015. Because in 2012,
the world ended. And what, like did our planet got like detonated and we all got uploaded to
the cloud or something? What do you mean? Unironically, yes. Oh, unironically, yes.
And maybe it's because you peaked in 2015. That's not true at all, by the way. Oh, you know,
at 20- every year kind of feels like 2014. I wish it was like 2015, 20- remember when I was
getting like a million views a video on YouTube? Oh man, like every day feels like it should be
2014, doesn't it? By the way, I inflated those numbers. It was like 600 or 700k.
But you round up, especially when you're marketing yourself. Anyway, today we're gonna play
Barn Finders. It's a game that I played very, very briefly for about 15 minutes while I was raging at
Fall Guys. During that like Fall Guys week where the game just came out and the servers were all
fucked up, I was- I tried to play it. I couldn't play it. And I was like, well, I gotta pivot. I
gotta do something else. And I had Barn Finders installed. I was like, I guess I'm gonna play this.
And I didn't give it the proper time and respect that I think it might deserve. Because Fall Guys
servers came back online. I wasn't even paying attention to this game. I was just raging about
the servers. And somebody like- it like baited me into thinking that like a Fall Guys dev was
talking to me. Remember that? Like that- that- I couldn't give the attention to Barn Finders that
it deserves. So what is Barn Finders? Barn- this is a game where you go search for antiques. You go
to auctions. And you sell antiques. It looks like it's gonna be right up my alley. That was
peaked, Jerma. Well, that was like a year ago. Not even. That was like seven months ago. If I
peaked- here, listen to me. If you're telling me that I peaked- I peaked career-wise like six months
ago? Holy shit, that's awesome. I can ride this shit for the next 10 years. I could put up trash
can content for the next 10 years and just slowly go down. If you tell me I peaked six months ago.
I've been doing this for 10 years. Wow. You peaked at the imposter is sus. But you're already doing
that. You have no idea what I have for this year. No, I- I'm- I'll- you know what? I bet you I peaked
this year. All right? I'll be honest with you. There's like three streams that are gonna happen
this year. That I- that absolutely I've peaked this year. Like this- I- there's nothing I can do
that- maybe next year. The next one to two years is the peak of my entire online internet thing.
So, you know, I'm not- I'm not- I'm not there yet. I will be soon though. And I- and I know- I know
when to see that. I know when to accept that. It's probably this year. It's not gonna be Catboy.
Imagine peaking at Catboy. God. All right, are you ready? Let's play. Let's do this. In a movie this
way. Foreign Finders. All right, something- wait, what's wrong with the audio? Is it supposed to
sound like this? Is it supposed to sound like that? Is this copyright? Oh no, it's- my connector is
fucked up. You wanna know something funny about how much of a lazy idiot I actually am? I have had-
now remember, these things are like a dollar fifty on Amazon. I have had a busted, um, you know,
like the- those little jacks that you plug in, like a headphone jack? I have a headphone jack
extender that I've had for four years and it has never worked. It's bad. There's something wrong
with the insides and I have to like juggle and jostle around the cord inside of this thing to
get it to make audio come through it. It's- it's probably two dollars on Amazon. I just- I just
won't do it. I don't know why. Are you sure you want to start- what do you mean, am I sure?
That just scared the shit out of me. That just was fucking terrifying. Juggles is back. All right,
so let's give this the actual time it deserves. I think I kind of look like this guy right now.
What do you do in this game? You buy and sell antiques. What? Are these characters?
Is that an Oscar? That was just an Oscar. Oh, can I get an- that's probably worth a lot of money.
Oh shit, this is DMCA. Somewhere in America, 1991. No, largely similar to the real America,
but not quite. Imagine being concerned about DMCA with America. Wake up. Young and our generator
is down. Get a battery from our truck and fix it. Let's work awful hard. Our vacation awaits. Okay,
I might need to turn the sensitivity up just a little bit. 90 FOV. This guy didn't even play
Quake. Shut up. Okay, movement. Jump, look around, interact. Okay, so that's crouch.
So take a battery from your truck and place it in the generator. All right, you got it.
Do a funny voice. I just did one. Okay, I don't- well, I'm not gonna pick up the briefcase. Let's
go do the battery. This is a beautiful game. This looks good on my fucking 3090. Welcome to
Barn Finders. Get car battery from the car's trunk. Put it into the generator. Use your computer to
find jobs and travel all over America. All right, cool. Let's go get the battery from the truck.
Move this shit out of the way. Wait, you can throw? Hold on. Can I hurt anybody? No,
you can't hurt anybody. Never mind. It's a 1080. No, it's a 3090. Extra large. Okay,
so let's get the battery. Open the trunk here. Battery developed by Miku. This battery was
designed exclusively to power up Miku generators. Did you guys know that I thought that Miku,
like the singer, I thought that was a person up until about like three months ago, two months ago.
I thought Hatsune Miku was a person. I didn't think it was- I did not know that it was a robot.
I thought that was a singer and it was like a gorilla's scenario. I did- I did not know that.
I thought it was an actual human being singing songs. Wait, mark- to mark for transport, enter
study mode, rotate item, zoom in and out, mark for transport. Okay, place it in the generator.
She is real. She's real. All right, but I'm just saying, like, I thought it- I thought it was a
person, like somebody in, like, the booth. All right, check your computer for job email.
Are those guns? Why are there guns in this game? Oh man, the 3090 really brings out the
fucking foliage, let me tell you. All right, computer. It's better than the gorillas.
I just- I don't know if I can agree with you. Well, hold on a minute. Wait, wait, wait. Do you
mean like gorillas from like 2000- gorillas from like 2000 to like 2015? Or do you mean- what do
you mean? What are you talking about? Like, which one? It's a dirty computer. All right, email.
On red. A naughty stag for a friend. Hello, barn finders. Can you help an old friend?
So I heard there's still a naughty stag at the old red barn. Maybe you could find it there for you.
There's money in it if you do. 300 bucks to find an old stag? Okay. At the old red barn. Barn hub.
Okay, there's the old- there's the red barn. Travel is one gas or by gas. All right, so I have
to go to the red barn. Barnhub.com. Why the- why do people do this? This is- like, everything has
to have like a Pornhub reference. Okay, barnhub.com. All right, let's go back. Right mouse button,
log out. Travel to red barn, look for a naughty stag. What's F1? I can drive the truck, right?
How much is that brick worth? Wait, big- build big shelf. This is my store, I think. I think you can
sell stuff here. Not fall guys. Yeah, no, it's not fall guys. Sorry, I'm not playing fall guys.
Okay, go to the truck. Do I have a map? I don't. Do I not have a map? Is this basketball? Basketball
challenge? How do I play the basketball challenge? It's that turkey over there that's fucking me up.
I'm sorry, if you have a basketball court here and every time you're about to shoot you hear
oh my god this is fucking hard oh my god this is hard this is hard oh my god i have to do this
before i move on did i get it your score why didn't go i didn't get it what the fuck man
i don't think you can even this isn't even the right physics all right at some point if you're
looking out the window do you come out here and like give me the ball give me the ball give me
the ball and then swish and then leave and be like i just had to do that got it how's that not your
score time left oh oh let's go what do i get for this okay i'll tell you a true story when i was
in like middle school i was on like a bath the basketball team like the after school basketball
club wasn't real like it was just like middle school right it was like before even like junior
high school so they never gave me the ball because i was not very good but i always so badly wanted
just to like drain a three so badly it was like the good player that got the ball every fucking
time and he was the person that scored like 40 points because all the kids don't you don't
score more than like fucking 30 points a game 40 points a game and you're like 11 12 so finally
i got the ball one time and it was the only time and i got up selfishly like there was a big rebound
off the um off like the the backward and i just it came to me and it was like oh pass it to the
guy that will absolutely get a fucking three point shot no no no i just stood back i got to here
and i got behind the three point line and i just did a huge like i was just trying to be um what
was this just his name we were in the celtics he was awesome he drained threes every time uh ray
allen this guy drained threes every time he was like the best three point shooter pretty much
ever lived so i tried to like mimic what he was doing and i just it just soared over the over the
backboard it was horrible and then i don't think i went to the next meeting i think i like quit
after that like i just went like oh here we go give me the ball i got it and it went like over
that and like nobody laughed either it wasn't even like that was funny it was just like oh yeah like
that would you just you fucked up the game like i know nobody even cared it was like it didn't
even happen it was actually as if it did not happen but this actually i don't understand this
what the fuck this is i don't know i don't understand this what the hell why this music
doesn't help who plays weird old-timey music when they play basketball this is way harder
than it looks i'm just gonna tell you you do what you're good at i'm not good at this i'm good at
fucking like haggling and like making people give me more money for stuff that i i'm not going to
do that kind of thing let's go to the car can i get in the car your car travel to red barn how
do i get to the red barn wait is there like a shit joke oh there better be oh my god oh my god
careful what you wish for i didn't want that i didn't want that i i like wished for it the
devil just fucking gave that to me i didn't want that what the fuck oh my god i'm not doing that
again that was disgusting that was fucking revolting and i'm i'm sorry and i'm embarrassed
okay oh my god what do i what do i go oh my god okay here's one guess that was i hate to say this
but i think that was real oh i'm done talking all right i need to go to the computer right
i'm so thrown off right now i didn't think that was gonna i thought it was gonna be like a jokey
cartoon fart sound okay travel right 500 million off the dead if you do it again
i think you might you might be one of like maybe up 100 people here that want to see that again
okay so what am i looking for looking for the stag the red barn and dwayne's love nest
okay looking for the stag exploring abandoned barns as a barn finder your job is to find
requested items look for other valuable items you can sell them in your shop search for additional
items and secrets maps are full of them okay let's go boy thy famous red barn let's explore
around stuff whatever all right i gotta find things i'm gonna find the stag and then i'm
clicking on any bathrooms ever again let's just be clear about that what's this valuable trash
oh three bucks to recycle it i love this already okay you've got that clean i get money how much is
this worth can i sell this valuable trash is your stream oh you're wicked funny oh break hand all
right i got 13 bucks let's uh let's clear let's clear the shit out can i break this stuff is this
stuff in the crates if there is oh boy i need to do a hillbilly voice no i don't i'm not going to
go into a hit wait this is tv pick up that tv what did what the fuck just happened did i get it oh
dvds that's a cool picture why can i not take that no it's not valuable you gotta clean up you
gotta oh gas all right let me spend time in each room because i love this already i love just
cleaning stuff and like making money with cleaning i can't get over that like shit sound it's it's in
my head now oh what's this worth 30 bucks study mode all right this is a classic rocking chair
from the early 20th century handmade from beechwood and protected with a clear matte varnish and wax
yeah i'll take it you don't have a key you know the song i was gonna sing
i'm not doing it that's an antique that's the whole point is you find antiques
i look for hidden shit do i have flashlight i don't have done it i can crouch though all right
recycle we got a number one victory recycle the books why why can't you sell the books
grandma please be quiet i'm trying to watch tv what is possibly on tv at 12 30 pacific right now
that's not a game show or a soap opera what are you watching sponge bob no television there's
nothing on tv anymore all these networks it's just it's so weird i don't even know why cable
fucking tv even exists anymore every network now just plays shit that people liked 10 years ago
and has one or two shows that are actually in current airing schedules at like eight o'clock
at night what's the point of having a tv network what's that key i really just don't get it now
that's what is that thing no no no study it study it i want to see it it's like a frog on a bike
i want to see it whatever because you know everybody wants streaming services and i saw
this coming from a mile away i'm the only one that said this i'm the only person that made this point
i'm the only one that you know that said this i knew that every single fucking company was going
to make their own streaming service so it used to be like one two hundred three hundred plus
dollars a month to have like all the cable channels oh i want hbo i want showtime i want
uh food network i want the big package so now to get the big package everybody has their own
streaming service so what ends up happening is you have like seven active monthly subscriptions
to get the shows you want to watch so it's just one to two hundred dollars a month anyways because
all the cable companies decided oh let's make our own apps and charge 12 dollars a month i'm the
only person that said that all right wait there's probably something valuable in here all right i
still need um don't block the door get out of the way you're a genius every expert predicted that
no i'm the only one and you missed crypto no i didn't what are you talking about i got involved
in crypto back in like 2015 2016 what are you talking about missed crypto i missed crypto
he's angry you sold it well i mean that doesn't mean i excuse me just because i sold crypto and
got out of crypto in 2018 2017 does not also mean that i lost all my money what are you talking
about you don't know when i got it you don't know when i bought cryptocurrencies you don't
know what i had what do you know you all you know is that i sold it what do you know whoa a fantastic
sunny cat life-size phenomenal taxidermy craftsmanship whoa i guess i'll take it i
sell the sticks all right more more more more more i need more stuff i don't know why i want
to throw that off the window so bad is it painting oh it's a painting collectible poster oh wait it's
my poster it's the imposter cat black magic manual um 18 bucks all right i'm gonna buy it
is he gonna be this furious every stream we're didn't we already went over this last week
every saturday you're getting me i i i you this is like you're gonna hear me talk a bunch of a
bunch of shit that i've been bottling up for a week before you got a slow trickle of my irritations
and now it just just dumps on you every saturday oh shit yeah i take that every saturday i just
covered rant to you guys no it's not gonna be like that why would i get that annoyed and upset
today this is barn finders just hanging out playing this game i've been looking forward to
all right where's the stag uh a poster i don't want it i don't want that i don't want that
this game's a little this game's a little uh a little much um i don't want that how much does
it sell for i don't want it i don't want that oh there it is he's gonna have a meltdown about
crypto let me tell you about crypto okay there are 300 bucks yeah definitely here it is all right i
found it all right we can go back to the pawn shop tell us about crypto please no i'm not gonna go
over to cryptocurrency rant wait what what's wrong is it you okay oh shit what what's wrong what
happened oh i don't like that i don't like this i didn't kill it no i didn't yeah look she's fine
is that who who just pooped why is this shitting why does everything have to go to the bathroom
all right hold on i'm not done this uh this wheelbarrow definitely a good wheelbarrow oh secret
oh fuck does this explode this is oh for oh it's a wall okay it's like wallpaper shoot it
i don't have a gun wait hold on 82 bucks so far there's got to be something else over here for
this bucket what's going on over there uh i need to know what that is it's time to investigate
there's an alien that was an alien i think it just teleported um okay here's moonshine
oh don't drink it i wanted to sell it moonshine delirium theater what the hell is going on
i got a poster for that okay no no no no clean nice all right oh floor i can't open this
sing it oh what's this high five wolf what is it it's like a wolf statue
oh it's a high five wolf statue okay i got it i got everything
it's car all right i'm ready let's get to work all right i got gas we can leave
travel home interesting the human specimen shows great potential it's just stranger things the
theme song i will spawn random earth objects continuing the plan would barn finders be the
ones to save us unlock barns will now have some items when you visit them again okay
i missed a golden paper apparently comic sans okay unload your truck by hand or use the storage
station okay how to run your pawn shop unload the truck by pressing the button on the storage
station use secondary action button to place items on the shelves automatically open the shop during
the day to start selling items to clients okay try to place some items on shelves okay i don't
have any shelves this is all i have medium shelf what can i put here the replenished shelf
no shelf behind you one nico it's great gun all right 230 but wait axe oh all right hold on
wait wait wait later partner balls equip upgrade gun to change an upgrade gun shell for medium
transfer from store transfer form storage station or drop items by hand do i have to wait go to the
storage station oh here we go okay all right i need a tv take out item all right i want the tv
right in the front all right that's 70 bucks i want that over here okay um what's puzzle mean
what's the puzzle pieces mean unsellable unsellable what about the high five wolf does
it have to be on a shelf we're gonna just put it like out front oh he's too big it means it's part
of a bigger thing okay i can't just put them down put the wolf as the cashier all right we'll take
that back i'm gonna put this wolf back in how do i put him back in oh fuck okay okay um we're gonna
put this stag can't take off special item you can only sell it via email okay i think these things
are dirty those are the bugs mean all right let's sell the spell book okay i'm not no i'm not doing
oh what about the wheelbarrow rocking i need to build something all right let me let me turn this
one in let me turn this one via email because that's gonna be 300 bucks and i'll be able to
build something all right here we go i can send 300 bucks that it okay now i got money i got 394
dollars okay upgrade gun build and customize your home illuminate dark areas chance to find metal
scraps and wood slow speed tool for digging spots and lock picking or miko chicken sonar scan for
nearby items i'm gonna need this okay so i have an upgrade gun now with upgrade gun you can
customize your pawn shop use it to customize shelves wall floors and posters build stations
to clean and repair and assemble items oh shit build a big shelf upgrade slow emperor i don't
have enough money for this is this free 265 dollars what the fuck oh this i already have one here
i can put the wolf right there can i oh nice okay how much is he 75 bucks that's you're gonna get
way more than 75 for that one all right there's another one i could put the i won't put the tv
over there no i want the tv front and center right in front whatever i don't like that explosion
okay fable 2 oh shit i was supposed to play fable 2 that's right i was supposed to play fable 2
go is there enough how much is the wheelbarrow worth all right i'm not all these are crows but
i mean how much can i sell this for it's a fucking i don't want i don't even want this up here
this is a medium item or is this a little bit i don't know i don't want it i'm saying throw it
away i don't want this i actually really don't want this thing in here he always does this we're
used to this by now i know i don't want this i don't i don't want that i'm throwing it over
the fucking fence i don't want it i swear to god i don't even care if it's money
shit come on get it over there you don't even want it i don't want it i don't want it you're
a fucking liar i'm not a liar i'm a forgetter i think that's all i can do oh wait the cat the
cat go can't fit here are you serious come on what this thing is it's not a medium item
i need to clean it how do i clean it i need to clean it clean it cleaning station oh shit
what's that wall upgrade added to the collection cleaning station use upgrade you have to clean
the area from overlapping items what what do you mean clean the area how do i get this fucking gun
off zero i take this off build cleaning station fuck i need to build a cleaning station i okay
all right all right all right open the store how do i turn the store on i have to go to sleep
you don't have anything in it i have a tv a spell book a high five dog and a rocking chair that's
enough how do i how do i go to bed your first auction i haven't done that yet
maybe turn sign off closed go to sleep in the hay hold on what's this very cool do i just
go to bed sleep in the truck i don't think i sleep in the truck do i have like a house somewhere
go to the outhouse no no no no the doll in the chair wait hold on do you tell me what to do
oh okay here we go recycle everything just you get money for it why not just recycle everything
in the house do i have any wait i might have some stuff here that i can sell can i sell the chair
no all right let's go time for bed okay time to open the store i'm ready for my first day on the
job open the shop using the shop sign otherwise customers won't come come on in we're open look
on the client to start selling you can sell decline or haggle for the better price when you haggle
don't be too greedy or you might lose money whoa all right what are you looking at the tv you want
the tv i'll give you 18 dollars for the magic uh it can go better than that two more bucks all
right let's take it you just it's like a golf minigame okay you want the wolf i have an offer
83 haggle i-5 wolf do it again guys keep doing this i don't know he's talking read your pc
computer email were you just in here personal computer computer what the wait what oh i have
to talk to them oh yeah that was easy why am i so good at it it's that's not hard to do
and did i sell everything oh nothing there's nobody wants a chair oh you want the chair
33 bucks you come on i'll get it every time i'm so confident in being able to do that oh it's all
right cool man okay i don't have any more stuff okay hey kid a new tournament of mico's bid wars
just started let's go to the bridge storage and win this the final round will give us tickets to
hawaii if you find a car engine there send it to cousin kevin okay barn bridge oh this is auction
all right we're gonna auction cleaning station i know i know hold on all right let me go up here
the cleaning station how much do i have 495 no no no wait wait wait wait i need to be able to
bid on this thing not yet all right close the shop everything's sold close the store
i know i want to close it all right well like whatever it just there's nothing here to steal
if anybody comes in here who cares hop left oh we're closed okay it already is closed all right
let's go i'm ready don't go to the car a car doesn't do anything buy one gas for 50 bucks what
disable the motion blur the motion blur is disabled motion blur off it's off it's off look
the motion blur is off turn on v sync turn off v sync he said yeah v6 on because
are you new to streaming what because i have v sync turned on all right let me if v sync is so
listen i have to ask this question because it seems like i need you to help me if v sync is
stupid and sucks and everybody turns it off why is it in every game why do they just why what's
the point of having it in if every single person turns it off why is it just enabled people are
idiots germa don't listen you set him off somebody somebody set him off somebody set him off he's
one of these streamers that you jump into and like oh my god he could go off on like a rant
and he and he just goes oh it's so funny i love watching him he goes off about like
fucking nintendo and like nickelodeon no i'm not a go off streamer i'm a realistic streamer
okay there's a difference i'm being realistic with you i'm not going off i'm being realistic
i'm just gonna buy the gas whatever it's too gas to go here what the fuck you think you gave a
pretty good answer probably okay so we have to bid on one of these like storage wars do i get to go
why can't you just say me what is that that's gonna be your thing
it goes to be the highest bidder at the auction use small and big bid buttons to increase the
price after waiting feel free to explore and take all the items all right so where do we start
this is us you live in back with your uncle that's some what are you ready to lose kid gonna
smoke oil live okay i'm ready miko is the real face of america i'm ready let's go let's open
it just just let me in just can i go in there just let me in it let me inside
well just open it and let me see what's in there how do i start this
travel to bridge storage look for a car engine oh okay let's go 600 dollars i owe you kick their
eggs all right here we go i 150 225 up here 300 now it's mine 300 350 450
that's probably really loud i'm sorry what the fuck 600 destiny will teach you
this is 600 bucks yup is copyrighted i forgot that was me wait yup is copyrighted is that is it i
can imagine that being on a t-shirt like yep is on a shirt it definitely is if it exists i'm gonna
get it and i'm gonna wear it on stream one day all right i won the auction that was 600 bucks
what we got in here oh let's take a look around
hmm do people actually do this so you you you have a storage unit and you like you just like
don't go you what do you just default on the payments so could you go to the auction and
just like pretend like you knew what was in there you know yes like what if i went to the auction
and i like knew what was already in here and i what if i just told people what was in here
there's the car engine why would you pretend i don't know because you like you can just be like
just discourage people from wanting to bid on it all right here we go let's start let's start the
bidding yep a hundred dollars you're at your own the auction and just wait for it wait for it to
get to like 1500 fucking bucks i think there's something good in here i had 900 yep a thousand
910 950 980 yep and then you can just take off the fucking mask you have you take off like the
glasses with the mustache and go i this is i this is my shit in here guess what it's like old shit
from my grandmother's house it's worth probably 50 dollars and then leave there's like two rocking
chairs in here that they're missing legs and they're not worth anything you just spent a
thousand extra dollars than you had to you know what i would do you know you know what i would do
you know what i would do this is what i would do if i ever had one of these and i i would just get
a shitload of like baseball cards like i'm talking like 50 000 packs of baseball cards i know they're
worthless they're not there's nothing worthwhile in them i would just put i would stuff it with
fucking baseball cards so it would they would spend months going through these knowing that
like wait a minute look at all these baseball cards there's probably a wicked expensive one
and i know that there's not that's evil what i mean that's evil this is my storage unit this is
my stuff in here but maybe i wanted to maybe i was a collector of like a bunch of shitty baseball
cards what's what is that your business this is my unit this is literally my unit i can put
whatever i want in here what is he talking about i'm talking i look you must do you not understand
like what we're doing here somebody this is somebody's like storage unit you can put whatever
you want in here just don't tire buy an axe this thing goes down well that's kind of weird
can i get in here why is there a car down here oh i wait a minute i got it okay now turn it on
oh shit okay did i just get a car oh my god there's expensive stuff down here what's this stuff
unmetal oh what's that it's 150 bucks i actually can smash the boxes sometimes this stuff in them oh
minus 150 bucks this is a car there's a lot of stuff in here radio oh shit look at this
well this is doubt this is worth spending 600 bucks for this there's a big ass storage bin
yeah you guys like probably live down here there's another left there's another layer why is this so
big whoa cool like a bike thing hold on get this out of the way are there any more saw games coming
up um i'm gonna tell you unfortunately no considering uh they made two games both of them
were absolute atrocious they were awful horrendous video games that no nobody with four brain cells
that had any sort of capital working capital would have given money to make a third one
well that's just gonna be there oh there's another get i got how do i like collapse this
when has a shitty game ever stopped you saw 2 did saw 2 was awful it was like
is it blood i do need that axe you're right you just sucked at saw 2 i don't know i i have
this opinion that if you if you if you have if you're gonna defend the video game saw 2
you got it at christmas one year and like your friend got mario odyssey a mario galaxy and like
you just have to you you like have to find a way to make it like that is not that bad
dream of saw stream huh my best tool is the engine there's so much stuff here when you're
gonna play what is it we'll get saw 2 as a christmas present yeah that's true i don't know who would
be giving saw 2 to their kids that's a pretty bad parenting if you yeah well i don't know why that
would happen in fact you probably that i people would probably be like wait you got saw wait a
minute is that the game where you've been like but people get their heads chopped off
yeah oh my god oh can i see the couch get the frog please i'm gonna get the frog what do you
think i'm not gonna pick up the frog what's the fart for it's because i hit crouch give me a break
this is actually a fart button uh i mean take this tv erin erin no don't do that fart funny fart
funny all right i can leave ah suckers it was two thousand dollars worth stuff in there
well done there barn finder see you next time bye we kind of put it in the trunk oh
get the axe i i don't have the axe i have to buy it i don't have enough money to buy it
isn't like 500 bucks he's gonna miss every single toilet roll i don't know what that what that means
okay now let's get that item that i was supposed to do 430 bucks i'll take it
the new cyberpunk is looking good why is this cyberpunk i don't know i don't know what that
means cyberpunk we gotta when are you gonna do resident evil 8 uh the plan is well i was
supposed to fable shit um resident evil i want to do resident evil oh fuck what do i do here um hold
on let me figure this out resident evil 8 not resident evil 8 what a resident evil village
i want to play that game next weekend saturday and sunday so that's going to be a saturday sunday
stream uh i'm still working on the ipad stream which that's gonna happen too and then fate yeah
all right we got that we have the next like three weeks blocked out resident evil village i'm gonna
play i'm gonna beat it next weekend and then the weekend after that uh either fable 2 or ipad
insanity stream and then the week after that whatever it is we got this we got that that
that's quality video content over the next three four weeks when it's cat boy you don't have a
release date on cat boy you don't have a release date on anything all right give me the axe
probably never see you later partner okay uh let's make it i want to make another big one
yeah so what's the difference between why would you get this one why not just get the standard
one but why would you make this why would you upgrade this how long until he tries to axe
someone well you can't so don't worry okay so uh let's put these stuff let's put the stuff up
what did i get i got all right the wheelbarrow i need to repair oh the cleaning station cleaning
station repair and cleaning station right how much does this cost to make 358 dollars what the
fuck well i'm just gonna just put the tires out on the medium shelf right i could put three up top
38 there's b to clean this doesn't work i remember i also have this stock market game
thing to play today too because if you were not here for pre-stream i had a little bit of problem
um why can i not put this oh there we go uh the problem was i did a poll to see what people would
rather see this or this stock market game and it was like 50 50 it was really close for a long time
and then somebody boughted the poll and it was ruined everything and then somebody boughted the
boughted poll to fix it um does the internet don't the internet then nothing's on the internet is
fucking real by the way can we just just be aware of that like you can't how can you trust anything
like when you're online and you see like people talking to each other those could just be two
fucking bots talking to each other to get a response from you you could be you could just
be surrounded by fucking bots and have no idea what's going on you could be literally surrounded
by them right now tumor admits most of his audience are bots i've no i have no idea who
any of you are half of you could be pets at the houses that you live in that have somehow pressed
the right combinations of buttons to duo emote i don't know i have no idea you like left your
computer on and your cat walked over your keyboard you might not even actually be here how do i is
this a medium i need a medium shelf all right well that's good that's fine my cat wrote omega
lull rant andy that would be something now wouldn't it oh my god rant andy yeah but you're
here i don't know this needs to be repaired all right open the store i don't want this i seriously
don't want this i'm sick of looking at it all right let's sell open no go to bed wait yeah go
to bed open the store tomorrow sell it so it's gone yeah is it it's a large yeah you're right
just get rid of it is this the imposter is sus guy you know i have to answer that question probably
every stream now until until i quit oh is this not a big item that is it this is a big item why
i don't get it to hang it i don't understand it's big so why won't it oh because it's dirty all
right just get me the hell out of this all right open the store let's go you have to embrace it
you're the sus guy for the rest of your life yeah i wonder is the spi guy now tf tf2 is not
as relevant as among us is at the moment right now i may have been oh shit no i'm not doing that
okay build immediate now all right open the store let's go i'm gonna speed run this
i want to build more stuff open holy shit you're that erin guy yes well no i'm not
this isn't worth the time what i got it right wait wait wait wait wait i got it correct twice
no that sims character just that dick was treating this sim like shit and they went out
with like zero energy zero comfort zero bladder and zero hunger and they just got fucking furious
for no reason i didn't do anything treat your sims better all right what am i doing video
turn off v-sync before everybody freaks out this is audio too loud allows the audio i feel like
the sounds are fucking really loud in my ears now it's too quiet no but this looks awful without
v-sync oh are you guys seeing this this looks horrible this looks really bad it's an alien
are you gonna be better than that okay sell it i'm getting tons i'm getting an insane amount
of screen tearing it's gonna make me throw up are you guys not seeing that i have to put the
v-sync back on it's this is really really awful looking i have to i'm sorry i'm gonna like get
sick right now i don't think it's going through through my program here sell sell sell i really
want it okay so v-sync andy u extreme what does it look like for you guys right now why
v-sync with it on i keep hearing the thing like somebody's coming in here but nobody's actually
here letting the person thank you for where is this person where i don't see anybody what's
going on there's nobody here shit sorry car oh the car it's the car okay car car car hello
sir i can sell that to you 1200 bucks you can do better than that thank you very much you can
take that for 1,320 bucks i'll take the 1200 dollars thank you very much haggle twice no
that guy the last time i haggled twice they left twice i can't i have i love that sound so much
i can't stop doing it it's a v-sync voice agent nice shop i mean agent is this illegal is like
an fbi agent did you see anything suspicious yeah what yeah what you you you just disappeared
bye bye bye bye bye my cat just started purring because of the alien noise
go go go go sell sell sell sell cleaning station i know i'll do it it's still like four items to
sell or three items to sell then i'm gonna do an upgrade spree upgrade the outhouse shit all right
fine fine fine just take it imagine haggling with the guy there's a guy just swinging an axe
around in his store but why does your objective say to read your pc computer i don't know because
it just does because it's a personal personal computer computer personal pc computer i'm blowing
the place water fire extinguisher two and a half gallon pressurized water fire extinguisher 20
000 2000 i got money i know no one would take this job besides you guys some birdie told me
that a classic the classic butch model can still be found around quiet woods what about it uncle
billy you still owe me 50 bucks is a squirrel a squirrel boxer okay quiet woods let me upgrade
first do i buy something hold on what else can i buy uh the shovel and 6000 what the hell
and a headlamp okay cleaning machine and cleaning station all right dirty items have the dirty icon
put them in the cleaning station and clean it with a secondary action button all right let's go
let's get this over with before so people can like get over this oh it's dirty over there hold on oh
i hate this i hate this i don't want to do this this is stop saying erin stop saying erin
stop doing that i keep seeing it somebody just wrote omega lol haha erin like what are you doing
why are you i don't know why are you still doing this stop saying that omega lol huh do it say it
this is not a medium item so what how do i mark for transport did i not what why
i'm curious i'm so confused all right i can't do that let's go and find this uh squirrel please
explain the erin thing to me all right i'm gonna i'm gonna explain this one more time no i don't
even need to explain it why would i explain it there's no reason to explain it i need gas it's
just i i there's no i can't even there's nothing for me to explain i thought that was gonna explode
and kill me please explain it is this can i dig in here oh nice a tennis racket okay is it dirty
no it can just go up explain it or suffer the consequences what is for me to explain it it's
from attack on titan it's armin very concerned about erin and it's like the way he says it every
like three episodes every every single episode i don't do i need i don't need to if you don't
watch the show how am i gonna explain that to you you watch it dubbed yes i do and oh
oh he watches a show dubbed oh he doesn't watch it in subs listen i have such hard time paying
attention that reading while watching a show is hard for me to do because i can't pay attention
to what's actually going on on the screen i'm too busy reading the text at the bottom so i'm just
kind of reading and not watching that's it i know the subs have probably a million times better
but it doesn't matter for me it's like if you had the book of the show you were watching
and you were reading the book at the same time that the show was being played at the same point
in the story like looking down reading like you're reading the same dialogue look up okay that's
happening read down look down read the same dialogue or look up it's like just reading the
book while the show is happening i can't do it my brain is not smart enough that's a bad analogy no
it's not because i'm literally reading what's happening on the screen all right let's go i'm
gonna buy the other gas are we almost at the two hour mark is it time to play stocks game
uh quiet woods you're watching a play and you're reading the script yeah it's the same kind of
difference is the stocks game invisible hand yes so i'd pop up today i was like oh what the
hell is this clean your keyboard my keyboard's pretty clean actually watch out youngin there's
this lady i don't even know what you said the actors are reading straight from the subtitles
yeah oh okay they're reading the script
they're reading the subtitles imagine if they just had their eyes down like looking on the
bottom of the screen reading like the actual animated characters agent i'm detecting strong
paranormal waves here i'm detecting strong paranormal waves okay austin powers joke did
that happen in austin powers they read the subtitles that was like scary noises oh it's
a miko console in the woods at night this is worth 260 dollars 260 dollars 260 dollars anytime my
grandmother that just scared the shit out of me okay anytime my grandmother heard a price for
anything didn't matter what it was she would always say the price again very very shocked
and confused it doesn't matter what it was how much is that thing how much is that coffee uh it
was four dollars and and and 30 cents four dollars and 30 cents yes 60 dollars is that
that's like my coffee machine and anytime yeah anytime that i would like be in trouble if i
something that was potentially going to go wrong and it looked like that i may i might be in trouble
she would say i don't know i don't want that she'd say
erin jeremy jeremy erin it was bad that was not funny i'm sorry that was not funny but it was
relevant to what we were talking about i'm sorry somebody said it in chat and i just repeated it
that was not funny that was really not funny at all there's a worst joke ever i think
it was not even close to being even remotely funny to any of you stop the erin i'm gonna do okay
hold on a second oh shit what happened did you guys not hear anything i said i've just been
talking this whole time oh anyways what was i saying right oh so i need that i did not know
i'm sorry i was i didn't mean to do that what was the last thing i said you've ruined the peace and
quiet boy oh man resident evil i'll say it's so scary i'm so glad i'm not actually playing
right now i'm in such a jumpy mood at the moment all right we're gonna do a poll okay we're gonna
do a poll is chicken flying over here okay interesting all right next week do you want
to see me play through fable 2 or resident evil village which one and you better get the answer
right because we're not changing it okay i'm gonna put let me put a poll up let me do this right now
draw poll dot me okay re village or fable 2 this is for next weekend and this will be a
multi-day stream this is going to be saturday sunday either one of these i'm going to put it
in there here it comes please if you would vote on this poll do a twitch poll oh well
let's see i'm not sure you can finish village in two days i've heard it's less than 10 hours
i've heard it's like eight to 12 hours we can do that in two days mods can just do a twitch poll
really quick um oh yeah oh yeah yeah all right don't click on that one we're gonna do do a twitch
poll yeah that people can fucking game that one do a twitch poll next week resident evil village or
fable 2 we have somebody bought the fuck out of that thing and yeah i know i'm not no we're not
playing around with that one okay i need to find strength for this you didn't like the result i
didn't even look at the result i don't know what the results were why why is it in the game
what should germa play next weekend all right let's see what do you guys want i'm happy with
either one of those outcomes i did see something weird where else can i go can i go this way i hear
the simpsons intro up there can i get up there how do i get up there oh what the hell how do i
get that oh there we go all right well it's a golden toilet paper the thing that somebody
was talking about we found a golden paper okay what does that does that is that money
able to will happen anyway i mean they both will probably happen anyway it's just what do you want
to see next weekend i dig i gotta be able to dig here right no resident evil is going to be monka
s yeah i mean i i'm i've played pretty much all the recent resident evil games on this stream
so i'm gonna play it toilet all right agent what are you doing here play on the hardest difficulty
i don't play on hard difficulties not anymore the only thing you're ever going to see me do
that's hard is like if elden ring ever comes out which i have no idea when that's going to happen
i'll be waiting for that one for a very long time okay so what i'm where else can i go here's the
car holy shit okay i couldn't handle nicktoons baseball next to nicktoons baseball is not the
same as like playing resident evil resident evil village has won okay
recency bias recency bias racy racy's bias i need this like whatever this wheel is all right well
i'm playing resident evil village next weekend saturday sunday where is everything there's only
this one house but i can't get up there i need to get up here yes i do have a bias to rices they're
probably the best chocolate candy imagine thinking of something imagine actually thinking that
something is unironically better than rices just standard regular rices well rices eggs let's make
that clear i need to get in this house i'm so confused as to where to go this half the items
are still here but i can't i need to find something the cats are pretty good yeah they're there all
right this is the second house oh fuck wait that was this is the second house oh it is the second
house i thought it was the same house chocolates the devil's candy um chocolates good for you
you know chocolate improves your mood yeah am i getting question marks for
actual analytical science chocolate is supposed to improve your mood you guys don't you guys don't
actual bad opinions chocolate is supposed to scientifically improve your mood it has
mood improving compounds and i didn't just make that up somebody somebody else made that up and
i've read it and i'm repeating it to you so you can think it's real now i don't know that's what
i've heard it's suede science it's not it's so does heroin you don't even know what you're
talking about it's pc cd rom computer all right still no study a study can done by hershey's
you're fucking full of shit chocolate improving mood chocolate improves memory chocolate improves
mood scholarly articles for chocolate improving mood dark chocolate stimulates the production of
endorphins chemicals in the brain that create feelings of pleasure dark chocolate also contains
serotonin an antidepressant that can elevate mood says scritch field in addition to feeling good
this is what happens to your body when you eat chocolate that's a study done by a medical
scientist why is chocolate good for mood dark chocolate and cocoa contain an amino acid called
tryptophan that your brain uses to produce the neurotransmitter serotonin which can increase
feelings of overall happiness serotonin is the feel-good chemical influences your mood
okay self-published not peer-reviewed no it is peer-reviewed because when i eat chocolate i feel
fucking great how many times you eat a piece of chocolate and you go like oh oh my god decadence
oh and you feel happy it's real that's a fucking real study i don't even need to study when i take
a bite into the middle of a Reese's egg i just oh i just disappear and i go into my couch and
i sit down i put my legs up on the couch i take a big bite and my lips go around it and then it
goes it like transitions into my brain and there's like i'm on like a cloud like floating around
and it's like talking about how rich and delicious it is and i'm i think i'm describing a commercial
that i watched for like dove chocolate bars but you get the idea it's the same thing i got the
key to the house those were edibles no they weren't oh shortcut who cares what is dove chocolate
you never had like a dove chocolate bar like the dove chocolate ice creams
dove chocolate what are you guys talking about not shampoo why are you guys making me feel like i'm
insane dove chocolate yes this is a real different dove not soap okay i got the key which that what
was this law there was a locked door somewhere what was it right here right shit oh oh oh single
google searches i have a key for the second house i think this is for the second house
off eating soap of chocolate is so good yeah i know the person sitting on the couch
they're in pajamas they take one bite and it zooms into their face and then it tell them
it goes to like a part where they're like on a cloud and they're floating around and then it
shows them how relaxed they are up in the clouds and then it comes back and they have like the
chocolate and they just have this big smile while they're sitting on the couch all right let's go
all right found it still items here coaster microwave or whatever it is
i've been brainwashed by big chocolate you know it's also interesting to think about
so back like 60 or 70 years ago they would do commercials like i'm sure a lot of people know
this already but cigarettes were seen as not a big deal at all they were seen as like a healthy
snack there was a commercial i remember watching where it was like a doctor writing a note about
how like i think chester uh what was the name of the company chesterfield cigarettes are the
healthiest of all the cigarettes they don't produce any throat irritation it was a doctor
sitting there writing a note talking it was like a doctor's note about how they were healthy and it
made me think about people like 50 60 years ago thought like cigarettes were just like fun like
candy that didn't hurt you what are we eating now what are we doing now that like a hundred years
from now people are going to watch old youtube ads for like some product and go holy fucking
they were eating this all the time they thought this was fine what's wrong what are they insane
i wonder what that thing is going to be where it's like it's it is unbelievable to think that
we were eating this chocolate fast food sugar i don't think it's going to be sugar because
sugar is like sugar has a function it's like one of the most it's like the building block
of a ton of things everybody already knows sugar is really not good for you at all
we already know that people thought cigarettes were fine and they're like horrendous for you
what's the thing that we all think is fine right now or good that we're like no everything that's
perfectly fine but it's not at all oil like vegetable oil probably micro plastics interesting
i even use the key i don't know what do i even care i got the golden paper it's going to be
like the fake sugar is like stevia you know actually i would not be surprised like i don't
know something about that right it's like wait okay what if like 100 years from now it's like
wait they were making fake sugar garlic hmm now that would be very sad caffeine i could see
caffeine having some kind of like wow i can't believe they were doing that garlic oh man imagine
if it was garlic that would be sad because we think garlic is wicked healthy for you and there's
like studies about it i've seen a doctor write a note about garlic before oh i want another big
one here these old cigarette commercials they're so fascinating i recommend you go watch them
they used to say that like having the filter on a cigarette like filtered cigarettes filter out all
the disgusting stuff it filters out the tar so you get a clean smooth drag those things those
things don't even do anything the invention of the filter cigarette was so it's such a huge
advertising thing clean smoke yeah 105 anything dirty oh i need to wash it no i can't watch a
cigarette commercial i'm not 18 yet why you what are you doing here you had to click the button
that said you were of a mature audience to watch this stream what are you talking about
why are you here now you're in big trouble uh 155 this thing's 380 180 or 65 i gotta repair
it though okay we'll put this one up remember you aren't mature yes i am look i can make
fucking attack on titan voices in the shower and be mature just a little odd okay that's 100
false oh okay so you can't have you tell you can't have like a humoristic outlook on things
and like just have be having fun but i guess you uh can't be mature adult what mature is not caring
what people think no it's not say it please i beg you all right do a poll right now do a poll in
chat if people want to hear they mean do if people want to hear armin arlott the the answer the
question is do do you want to hear armin it's very simple yes or no question by the way it needs to
be at least 75 yes for me to do it okay i can't i can't see it so someone's got to relay what it
says it said wait hold on 77 yeah but it's not done yet that needs to stay over 75 until until
this is done i think of how loud and annoying it's going to be you're going to have to turn
your volume down some of you i'm trying to get you to change your answer it's going to be like
oh he's doing the errand thing i have to turn my volume down because it's so fucking annoying
i hate when he does this you know even if like two percent of you guys decided like to change
your vote right now think about it's gonna be loud you it's not funny you don't think it's funny
you hate it so switch your vote over like it's not you don't like it don't make yourself hear
something you don't want to hear hey yeah i mean like see think about it think about i'm looking
out for you your well-being 76 come on we need to hold no you don't you need to
the door holy shit that's ancient that is an ancient reference i feel like that was a hundred
years ago hold the door the door all right i got all my stuff here i'm gonna go to bed
this has got to run out i don't close it early this has to run out oh come on oh man oh i hate
that sound that sound sucks i can't believe this many of you guys are clicking on this
that's shocking to me it's got to be remember i said over 75 if it's 75 it's not happening
no fuck okay okay hold on let me wait wait i'll do it in a second
i thought this is a person i was about to talk to them all right all right you get hey you get
what you get uh see when i have to do it i don't want to i can only do when i want to do it
erin erin erin run away erin erin erin erin erin erin erin okay there you go stop i know you said
shut up you must be one of the two you should have voted no why did you want me to do that at
76 percent of you told me to do that i told you i didn't want to do it and you i told you i didn't
want it and you made that happen it was almost all of you it was almost all of you that's most of you
you lost 500 viewers of course i did of course i would have left the stream if i saw that yes came
through i would have been like well i'm gonna come back in five minutes i would have left they'll be
back in five minutes now do the erin impression now that's easy just go
sitan i'll do that one for free sitan no it's too bad he turns into he turned he's i'm erin
actually it's too bad that there are titans done did you see those titans sitan
i'm not doing every character on the show i'm not gonna do every character on the show that's not
how this works do mikasa no that's me because it makes us like armin armin armin armin erin
erin there that's as best as i can do
do hercule oh i can do that look that's i love that character in attack on titan
oh right i love when that character shows up and says i am the strongest person on her
uh what do you know about that goku erin erin erin no god darn it erin erin run away erin
run away goku i didn't even start how to haggle i just sold it do a poll about goku what are you
talking about new kenny from south park okay that was so easy like how how dare you give me
something so simple i got 2,600 bucks i think i sold everything i did close the store dude
jimmy stewart well i don't know what you're thinking there get down from there stop jimmy
stewart like the half a tenth of you that know who that is i'm not doing a compression what
do you want supposed to goku for i just did it i already did that i want a super lockpick yep yep
goku but yes sir i don't know what that means i'm not gonna do the mr satan like hercule impression
goku goku one three hundred eighty dollars for this clock 150 plus dollars all right let's go
bus guy i can't this is what happens when i'm so glad i got to do erin though erin erin it's been
two hours jeremy well hold on is this an auction for this house i only have 580 dollars glad to
see you again mary would be proud zoe this is to buy the house wardy are they doing another season
rick and wardy i just was i'm like asking i don't care that's just stupid like uh like reddit humor
is that when's the next season coming out don't tell them tell me i'll just look it up it's not
a hard thing to do oh can i move this it looks like i can dig there right all right i only have
595 dollars i need more money for this this is not good i bought too much stuff i can't buy this
what happens if i don't get this can i come back later and auction it again i just don't get it
it's going to be way more than 600 bucks i i just spent all the money to come here though
can i go in the other houses next game not yet i'm not finished with barn finders why is it
everybody want me to do the impressions of the stuff that everybody hates i think you secretly
like rick and morty and you want me to do morty because you like the character more do you think
it's funny in fact i would bet a certain amount of cash that most of you well i don't know about
most of you a lot of you probably actually really like that show and you're just pretending to not
like it i bet you a bunch of you actually really like it i think it's funny probably uh first two
seasons maybe what is a funny show that's right now i think have i asked this before what do you
what is like the collective like twitch chat hive mind opinion on what's a currently airing good
show that's funny that's really funny sopranos has not aired in like 15 years probably erin
currently erin invincible is actually a good show is it okay i want i want everybody to remember
this i want you all to remember this clip this and in like two or three years i want to see if like
everybody hates that show now okay remind me in like three years if like everybody thinks the show
is not funny because it looks like of all of you most of you are saying it is this dipping sauce
yeah just wait for the just wait for the dipping sauce episode young sheldon uh i have to like
i have to try to get this whatever i'm gonna lose it though i'm gonna try whatever let's go
just wait till the last second to do a 50 dollar bid wait 450 nobody there's so many how many
people there's so many people here and nobody's bidding why would you come to the auction did i
just get this house for 450 i did why did you even show up oh god damn it no what do you mean i
can't do this level now i just wasted a bunch of money the secret is to let them bid and then
come into the last second no the secret is to go to the auction go there kind of late and disheveled
because something just happened crazy and you sort of irritate everybody in the room you sit down
you're like oh sorry about that and then your character ends up sneezing like three or fourths
of the way like about maybe two-thirds of the way through the auction and they see that as a bid
and it's like oh my god that's so much money i can't believe what the heck oh my god it's sold
to the man in the funny hat and then i have to pay like five million dollars because i i didn't
mean to bid that's what you meant to say did this happen no this is every this is i don't have the
clock that happens in every tv show that has an auction one of the characters like sneezes and
they they put their hand up accidentally somehow that's mr bean yeah it's in every tv show that's
ever had an auction if you have an auction in your show the main character is going to accidentally
do something and raise their hand and have to buy like the 20 million dollar painting
can i even continue to play the game i have to like go to sleep this guy loves slapstick comedy
i do i really don't it still wants me to go to aunt mary's house i don't have any items did i
get soft-locked all right we need to go back to the red barn and find items right yeah it's free
where's our gift subs germy you owe us oh how do i owe gift subs from what what are you talking
about 500 million and i'm slowly shaving off that number it's not going to be an accurate number
yeah i i decided to pay with fun tokens you guys said that was okay
pay up now no i'm not going to problem is there a problem there one errand is ten dollars from
the debt no that wouldn't be worth it it would have to be like a million but it's tf tf problem
tf does it mean the fuck like the fuck ef what is tf there's something on top here how do i get up
there troll face oh okay can i get on the roof i gotta get on the roof you don't have uh bt yes
i do i just don't have it through like the stream labs thing yes i still use stream labs obs i know
didn't i just tell you that i have a cord that hasn't worked in like four years and i
still haven't replaced it i want every item slobs is so much easier to use i understand that
well theoretically theoretically i love stream labs obs but in practice i hate it having the chat
baked into the window here is like is is is the only reason why i still use it it's such a good
feature okay i need to get some items come on saving window space and monitor space is huge
i'll give them credit where i'm gonna give them credit i hate every single thing else about the
entire program i don't i have nothing else to say but that's the thing about streaming software
there's no like streaming to a service nobody has really made it there's like three products
that do it and i've tried some of the other alternatives and they were just a huge pain in
the ass is something funny you got it uh let's see what would make you in particular laugh i
don't know i don't know what you think is funny see anytime you guys say say something funny what
you don't understand is i don't know what you think is funny i don't know what your favorite
routine is here so if i try to say something that i think you might think is funny and you don't
you didn't like that particular routine then it's not going to be funny so i can't help you you
just have to watch until you see something that you like if you don't like what you see and you
know goodbye see ya i can't my hands are so sweaty i can't snap hold on and you know goodbye can i
jump from here there's gotta be a way i can get over there on top of the screen directly into
the mic for several seconds no that sucks i don't want to do that that's not that sucks
i don't i gotta get on this roof that's definitely how i do it all right i'm up here
and go here all right i got the golden um all right i got the golden paper how much is that
worth wait this apparently where's this other item there's another item that's like worth a
lot of money apparently i don't see any items i can't walk what the hell is going on i can't
i'm trying to walk well that was weird i find i was screaming in the bike ah where's this other
item there's one or two significant items that are still here that's making me annoyed that i
can't find them whatever i got enough that was so cringy yeah there's something about that fake
screaming that oh it just does something i agree oh they're buried shit parents are asleep dude
what the fuck dude they're gonna do a fart okay fine let me repair the thing let's make some
money where's the repair machine this is cleaning the generator where's the repair station i can't
believe you guys think that's funny oh there it is okay 800 bucks god damn it all right well i can
sell some stuff i will sell i should have enough to at least make 800 dollars and repair all that
stuff and then bring it back okay i have a few wheel barrels it's all i can sell i can't put
anything else up there even if they puzzle pieces does that i can't sell them well i should make
like 300 bucks i think all right get to 800 build a repair station and then repair all that
stuff and sell it and do another day all right and then i'm gonna buy the house all right and
then we're gonna play a stock game okay sound good to you sounds good to me did you watch the sub or
the dub of king of the hill i watched the uh sub all right sell hurry up remember my brother's
watching can you make him laugh he likes mario sure did he just like clap and scream i hope he
did remember he's 24 so i would have clapped and screamed if i heard that and i was a big mario fan
customer no i don't there's no i didn't see an alien come on i need 130 bucks 100 100 100
no okay that's fine that puts me in 937 good close the shop repair station go all right
allows you to repair broken items broken items have the hammer icon fix damaged spots using the
resources from the smashing the junk with the axe i don't i've read that so wrong now i can refill
the shop go to sleep do it again yeah let's look at this 465 dollars you kidding me that's so much
money i'll be able to buy that damn house i'll get it okay on the damage to oh i said do it really
fast okay edit got it nice all right sell this thing for 500 bucks at least there i got a lot
of repairable items this old television television that's better get over here i have so many um
fools let me say something unfunny i don't know like maybe 20 to 30 percent of everything i've
said this stream i don't think i need to say anything more i think you could probably pull
something is that an old chair that's not 90 it's probably like 30 it's like 20 i'll make
a i'm gonna make i'm gonna get that house i'm getting invested in this game even though i
don't i'm not but i am please the thing with the spring goes on the wall i think i thought
i tried to put it there it didn't do anything you ready for this one look at how fast that was
check this out ignore chat i'm not really ignoring them but i'm not paying that much attention to
them at the moment it's not a bad thing i'm just trying to get my store ready to sell objects
all right somebody said put this on the wall i tried to do that before it didn't do anything
all right sleep wake up open the store yeah that's it i don't have anything else i'm gonna make
probably two thousand dollars and then i'm gonna go buy the house and after the house has been
purchased go in there and wait i can't sleep it's too early can i open the store oh shit okay
customers thank you i'll take it you find any alien stuff i've found the alien the aliens
themselves i've drank the moonshine and they do weird stuff in front of me get rid of that sweet
this actually is kind of cool i would probably want this this would be kind of cool to have like
your front door or something like in a like your study all right the oh yeah i want you to take
that is a hundred and nice you this thing's expensive make up your mind next time what
are you talking about i just i just talked to you what because i walked away i didn't mean to
have you flashlight on oh whoops 500 bucks do it twice again yeah that's a huge hit right there
that's 675 dollars there's no way i get out bit at that house next time come on somebody get it
oh again yeah 674 dollars i am now ready to go bid you want that bear all right let's go
gravel i got money if you're my goku day is trending goku depose i'm glad we got to see it
all right 2000 bucks let's go i'm not going to do any bids until the last second there's the time
left is wait hold on all right here i come 850 hold on all right i'm coming in i'm coming in 950
burning hell is what i said what the fuck how is this more expensive than last time 1350 that's it
no one's gonna go more than that what the fuck no 1550 1750 no the last time the house went for
half of this that's it give it to me 1750 i got it that's way over what i i didn't want to buy
that much but it's mine whatever let's get let's get a haul here what do you say yep just because
you say yeah if does not mean it was a good deal you're gonna get sued all right because i said
yep what's this i'll take it it's trademarked you know what else is trademarked probably like the
and i do that every other day i do that like once a week to you guys i'm still fine
can't dig assuming for saying yep yeah now i'm gonna be saying that in the shower that's my new
thing i think that probably is gonna be my new thing can we get a doi doi doi no no i can't just
be like the guy that just does fucking three jokes i don't want to do that i already repeat
myself so much you want to do that more i don't want to do that more i know i but i know i do
that already i don't want to add to that can i pick this lock how do i pick the lock i have a
three star lock pick how do i use it oh well i don't know face camera i break my desk well i
know ikea has some good ones for your replacement oh this one's expensive okay what about this one
lock pick why is it scary move up pins in correct order to open lock i did it i just i guess i did it
oh computer lemon white unsellable oh wait i have the uh i have the monitor i have the monitor the
tower and now the mouse maybe i'll be able to sell it it's a dog photo 150 that's it for a huge
dresser like this there's a dick on the wall they might be that probably is i don't really i don't
care though still a lot of shit left here all right what about downstairs there's a car under
there car that's gonna sell for quite a lot i would assume so nothing any of these any of these
is
oh that's a big one megaphone give me that the trumpet i i did didn't i yeah i got it all right
what about this thing the road toaster i'll take it whoa i don't have a key to get in here where
would the key be no it doesn't matter it's just in the backyard stop finger on the back right
i can't go back here where's this key e i don't see key is there a key e the mailbox
that's not a bad idea wait all right that did something oh shit what is this oh my god that
was like that was that was a statue of like michael angelo i didn't want to break it i wanted
to pick it up there's no key in here i want that key i found the clock go check the mailbox all
right i'll check the mailbox not in here i can't leave without the object i can't go in the
backyard unless i have the key i'm missing it in the garage or something where is this thing
what about the shovel yeah replace the dig go into the twin peaks room did you just spoil the
show did you just spoil the show for me i've twin peaks like to show twin peaks so now when i watch
twin peaks it's gonna be a room like that and i'm gonna know exactly i'm gonna be ready for it i'm
gonna be waiting for that fucking room with the with the red curtains thanks a lot thank you i
can't watch twin peaks now thanks a lot i'm fucking believable you have no idea how much
that pisses me off that was all my list of shows to watch eventually you know i have that as well
the new alvin and the chipmunks 3d cartoon but they're desperately trying to make alvin and the
chipmunks something that people want to watch by making them like little kids they're not even
chipmunks anymore they're like as big as small children and they have like people faces the both
the movies sucked i don't think anybody cared nobody watched either one of those movies they
did horribly at the box office i think and they were very very poorly rated we have to have like
a show on nickelodeon about them i can't think of anything else i don't i can't think of anyone
that watches that show like alvin and the chipmunks is one of those old nostalgia things that
no one cares about and now i have to watch that show instead because you've ruined twin peaks for
me thank you you have no idea alvin the last episode that i just watched simon was on his
computer and he had a big report due that was due for his class because they're like in school i
guess and simon was complaining about the professor about how i can't do this this is way too hard i
gotta do all this code and alvin grabbed the computer and wrote an email to the professor
saying like simon said this and that and that and like hit the send button
and like he's like yeah he should know and simon's like what are you doing alvin are you crazy
i don't want him to know that spoilers yeah yeah yeah yeah spoiled sorry thanks for ruining twin
peaks now you got fucking spoiled your show got spoiled now i don't see any mouth i i where is
this key in another house is a second can i go in either one of these this looks like i can go in
mobile users reacting to a bit that happened a minute ago that does happen where is this key
can i go on wait can i go on the roof i can't break this ah check that dirt thoroughly no
the hell is this it's the tip of the hats picture
all right where is this it's pretty on a hook on the wall between the windows
oh my god it is up here oh jeez tip of the hats picture okay let's get to it
can't play the game because you're spoiled that's fine
oh
where the chipmunks you think it'd be embarrassing for the people that do the chipmunk voices to have
their voices like slowed down and we hear what they actually sound like it would sound like that
it'd be like where the chipmunks alvin siden and deardor they don't actually sound like that
yeah i've heard the christmas one i hope i get a hula hoop i've heard it yeah i'm i'm old
oh a necklace there's still something out here you want me to be in the next alvin and the chipmunks
film and why do you think they would want me in that movie although it take would be about 10
minutes of like a vetting process for them to see that i've talked about how stupid that that show
is and how awful that whole franchise is you you want that person to be in the next movie
oh that was fun the sus guy is a big draw not really why do you think that carries that much
weight can i take this hey auto stop he's just like digging into the ground over here stop it
because it's funny i don't know what this last item is but it's the clock it's the actual item i
need how have i not found the clock seems impossible as do you guys see a giant clock
somewhere i don't listen for it seesaw go to the seesaw oh oh nice thanks guys it really helped me
i you know i appreciate that you really helped me here so i'm gonna buy that i guess
clock go auto no i can't show auto because then i have to show me and i don't want to show me right
now all right i got i got everything yeah that's everything
i'm doing that what's wrong with me i'm leaving no you're not you liar you're still here because
you've been waiting for the stock game okay send this complete that quest why are you singing i
don't know why can i not sing why is it so out of the ordinary well i mean what is this app comic
it's like a comic book i don't have the whole thing all right i need to get stuff out here
how's the computer doing computer mouse computer and do i need a keyboard maybe a keyboard
i like this is my favorite part i want to play is that all right is that is that
isn't there power washer game now i want to play it is it any good it's getting terrible
how can i not get this okay finally jesus power washing game you should know if it's terrible by
now just play it next week um i don't am i should i play it next week no i'm playing resident evil
village next week i'm playing resident evil village 400 no resident evil village then fable 2 then
ipad stream then um then something else i don't know whatever you said
do a mini rumble between stream game choices that's actually a really good idea i'm going to
steal that from you and use it that sounds really funny maybe eventually megaphone give me that
megaphone or whatever this thing is a gramophone done on the wall oh come on hang it do not play
lisa i'm not i do i have to i'm not going to play lisa you're not going you i do i have to
keep saying this you are never going to see lisa on this stream it's never going to happen never
ever it's never going to happen it will never it's never going to air ever it will never air
ever it's never happening i mean unless like i think it's good i'm kidding no it's not happening
why not i still want to play it i don't want to play it i have a lot of items don't play dragon
rampa i'm not going to play that either i don't think i don't if you have a suggestion please put
it in to the suggested recommended channel on the discord and that's it thank you so much thank you
you want to see me play dragon rampa i'm cool i'm glad you do but if i'm going to play it it's my i'm
going to make that decision when i make that decision thank you all right sleep get up turn
it on i'm gonna go read homestuck no no no i it's not that i don't i just don't i don't have time
for like a big immersive series right now open the store read that email first no i don't have
time for that aim the bid wars wait what i want to go to the bid wars oh i need money first
is fable 2 going to be a two-part stream that's probably going to be yeah probably saturday and
sunday resident evil will be two streams and then so will the other one able to is going to
definitely take more than one stream to do what about the diablo 2 remaster well i plan on playing
the diablo 2 remaster um on my own to i don't think i'm going to stream that it depends i
don't think so resident evil village is like four hours well if i beat resident evil village quickly
then i'll just play fable 2 i don't think this is going to happen if a game says four or five
hours it takes me about 10 it's like took me about nine yeah i would imagine it's like the other ones
i did how is it i didn't even ask how the game is it looks like it's getting good reviews so
resident evil 2 the remaster was probably my favorite resident evil it was my it was my
game of the year how can that is it first person or is it third person it's first person oh shit
okay that's actually all right that's cool so it's like it's essentially resin it's essentially
resident evil 7 oh shit all right just so lots of sex in the game which won't allow it to be played
major t.o.s violations don't risk it what i mean don't risk it how many isn't it like a hundred
thousand people streaming that game right now it's like almost all of twitch is streaming that
i think they would probably you're fine i know i'm fine i didn't have a i'm fine i'll be fine
don't listen to that guy okay they all got banned t.o.s timmy's you're not gonna like
resident evil 8 don't play it i liked resident evil 7 well i liked resident alien i liked some
of resident evil 7 i liked portions of it the first hour the first two hours of resident evil
7 was a nine out of ten second like four hours was like a six oh like the last four hours was
like a two so i mean i don't know the first like few hours of that game were some of the best
i think they've ever done that house was scary that was terrifying and then resident evil 2 just
nothing can be better than resident evil 3's remake it'd be hard to do because resident evil
3's remake was very much uh like very lackluster they're gonna remake resident evil 4 i'm really
scared of that that terrifies me because resident evil 4 is still really good the reason to remake
2 and 3 makes sense because they're like old tank controlled top town just go turn turn turn
go go go resin evil 4 is still a great game doesn't really need to be remade what do they
have to like change remake 4 in first person i don't think i would like that i think i'd want
it to be in third person they're adding tomato town to resident evil 4 you know there are so many
there's so many zoomers now i wouldn't be surprised and that and that would be like okay i guess
they're adding like tomato town there's a lot of zoomers i mean and they love tomato town i didn't
say uh tomato town is dumb fortnight is dumb zoomers stupid i didn't say that i just said
zoomers love tomato town would it be that surprising if tomato town was in something else that wasn't
just fortnight our zoomers love tomato town all right let's do it again yeah that's a lot of money
how much is that 1800 i don't even know what tomato town looks like all right i got 4200 bucks i'm
going to bid wars let's go bid wars i have five thousand dollars let's go bid wars you're missing
out on tomato town beware of thieves why am i still playing this well i'm about to stop playing this
and move on to the stock game let's see what happens here are we bidding on this car oh shit
we're bidding on the car you said that an hour ago here you can show off your skill in a series
of small auctions the winner is the person with the most value of stuff found in storages
winner of the bid wars get a special prize the big machine the most value you have to find valuable
stuff in the storage units and come on it's we all know what we're doing here limit the amount of
snacks that somebody can get two bottles of water per person storage wars is staged is it oh no
i can do better than that only the best are invited for the bid war what i just do i tried
okay so i have to open these all right open this up oh shit hold on this doesn't make any sense
it's way too much this doesn't make any sense you can't get it in holy shit that was perfect
wait what was that where was i yeah i gotta get four i got three what i get for prize
oh a can of soda i can do better than that this is cheating get up this is cheating get it come on
28 points holy shit this is free money hold on put this away why don't have 10 points pick up the
fucking ball oh it's because i'm too far i'm not wait how many points do i get if i go all the way
back here that's that was pretty good fuck come on please come on what hold on yeah you ever watch
those guys that make the youtube videos where they throw basketballs off of a boat into another boat
that has a basketball hoop on it they're driving by each other and it goes in you know how long it
takes them to do that one point that was across the whole court whatever all right i'm done fine
fine fine fine fine fine whatever i'm leaving i need to win all right how do we do this start
bid wars no no i don't i don't need items how long has he been playing basketball i don't know 10
minutes all for a old Subaru which are great cars by the way they last a long time all right okay
hey wait oh shit okay do i which one do i take that one or that one i'll tell you no i'll tell
you Kevin i'm telling Kevin there i think there's an old game console in there not that one
construction stuff there's probably copper in here i want this one 50 this person eternal
fame's burning to hell is it oh come on i'll take it thousand 1050 got it okay what's in here that's
an old uh i don't know are you up can i sell these it's got another guy oh that's a power tool that's
a power tool hard hat there's gonna be copper in here what's this oh 200 bucks for that thing
forklift this is uh i don't know it's a wire there's a huge there's a there's a saw back here
need tuber commentary i mean am i doing tuber commentary i didn't think i was yeah that's a
good that's a tool okay so hold on a minute if i just buy every unit don't i just win i just win
so why wouldn't i just buy every unit things empty wait okay nothing else in here that unit is done
nice all right 827 i lost i lost some money but it's okay i'm gonna go for this one there's
something behind those there's something behind those green uh dumpster bin things is it me am i
winning no don't all right me 850 i'll take it yeah none of you guys are gonna even compete i
came here with like five grand your character looks like tiger king all right something valuable
here we go nails oh this is looking like a dud an old typewriter oh that's not that wait hold on we
got furniture honey this one's a dud yeah it's a dud this is less than probably a few hundred
dollars it's okay i can just screw up everything and nobody can compete with me oh you obviously
thought it was a dud you guys thought it was a dud nope there look at all this shit up here i
almost didn't see that belongs in a museum there we go all right i'm currently in the lead okay
how many more units are there two more units to bid three more units to bid on oh wait am i just
like blowing all my stash too quickly what's that in there yep i want this one too shumanji
why is there a portal entrance in front of this 1,100 bucks oh man this is going high did i
let it go i'll take it well i i can't afford to buy all of them i think i brought the axe because
i wouldn't be able to even go in here okay it's this thing that's a yeah 385 what else is in here
what was this oh that's four almost 400 crossbow yeah all right i made money this one was a going
oh yeah another crossbow up top as well this is a big ticket this is about 13 or 1400 bucks 15
1500 i don't want to miss anything nothing else right don't think so trouble we're good
okay there are two more to bid on what's in there a bunch of fucking trash in there
yeah this one sucks unless that like unless like captain america shield is worth a lot of money i
don't know dig in the dirt there's nothing in there what was that what was that what why even
let me dig if there's nothing there all right uh this one looks promising as well but this one
is a huge treasure chest all right if that thing is a skeleton bar i want this one let him have
this one i don't even care i don't even want this one good spend your money don't want it pass pass
this is the one i want here wait let me check this there's one more no just this last one
yeah this is a huge treasure chest right here i want this one that's small nobody wants this one
why i'll take this with 325 this is a giveaway did anybody else even come here with money besides
sebastian i got this for 325 bucks whoa i win what do i win are you gonna play the other game
yes i'm gonna take a break i'm gonna go pee i'm gonna get some water i'm gonna find out what was
in here lock oh i can lock pick this container it's in it let me play the binding of isaac music
i don't think i can get out okay i good thing i get out there's a bunch of chests in here
anything interesting oh what about this one maybe dig oh necklace i don't think so all right what's
in the last one there's nothing in here that's why there's only 300 bucks it was done it don't
matter i won the car anyways i won the car who cares nice all right i wonder how can i sell that
for how much can i sell that for hopefully more than four thousand dollars i spent like 4200 bucks
what can i sell this for i just want to see what it's worth and then i'll take a break i'm not
doing that sleep and then i want to sell the car there it is all right what's it worth just base
price 800 bucks that's it i spent i didn't need to spend that much money oh well all right that
just like annoyed me i'm done all right we're gonna play the stock game for a little while
i will be right back i'm gonna go take a quick break i'll see you guys in like two three minutes
and i'll be back with the stocks game see you in a minute