Hey, let's change the game to Hitman. It's worse than Quiet Man.
Hitman. Just for fun. Everything's just for fun. Go back to Quiet- I'm sorry, but you've-
We've made the lasagna. I made it for the whole company. You have to eat this.
Like that's like I did a poll in my company. Up in the chair.
What do you guys want for lunch tomorrow? And 60% of the people vote for lasagna.
And then all of a sudden the truck pulls up and a fucking kiddie pool lasagna comes over here.
And nobody eats it. Maybe two people take like- like as if you go to a birthday party
and somebody eats one slice of the gross cake that nobody wants.
No, no, no. That's not happening. That's not happening in my company.
You're eating this lasagna. Because you voted for it.
51%. Well, 51. They better be half lasagna.
What am I going to do with this lawless lasagna?
What am I supposed to do with lasagna?
Everybody likes lasagna. You'll eat it, right? Like you'll eat this.
I didn't even change- Hitman. Hitman...
I don't know. I think it'd be an hour to make a title.
Look at chat. I'm looking at chat.
What if you're allergic to lasagna?
Well, they'd be- they'd be a gluten-free fridge with a bunch of stuff in it.
Hitman lasagna.
Hitman lasagna. How do you spell lasagna?
I was going to spell it phonetically.
La-zon-ya. Lasagna.
That's going to be called Hitman Company lasagna.
There. By the way, I mean, we're not stopping right now.
I just want to make sure everyone's aware.
Tomorrow, there's no stream tomorrow because it is Thanksgiving.
Happy Thanksgiving if you celebrate it.
We're not stopping. Don't worry. We're not stopping.
All right. Let's eat some fucking lasagna.
Wait, why am I- why am I using the controller?
I was keyboard and mouse last time.
He's doing the end of the stream voice.
Okay. So, okay.
But I think, right? That's how it is.
Okay. So, I think I just got angry.
I just got fucking angry looking at this.
Like I have to get it off the screen.
All right. Let's see. What do we want to try?
Let's go back here and let's try a different scenario.
Planning. I'm not playing ghost mode.
Absolutely not.
Florida suit.
All right. Event. Let's try- we can go here.
We can take- obviously, I'm taking a fish.
Everyone would scream at me if I didn't.
All right. Stream was good. See y'all later.
DM me if Quiet Man comes back.
You just didn't take a piece of lasagna to go.
Don't just leave it.
I mean, I know I'm losing half of my viewer base here
because I made everybody eat lasagna.
Okay. Well, what if it was lasagna?
What if half of the lasagna was like veggie lasagna
and half was like a meat-based lasagna.
It was cut in half. It was like a giant pizza.
Would you eat it then?
Split the screen.
But I can't play it like that.
People are leaving because you keep making the lasagna.
Well, that's a very, very strong reference, I think.
All right. Well, stop learning it.
So we have- look, are you going to stay now?
I'm about to throw a briefcase at somebody.
Isn't that extraordinarily hilarious?
I'm leaving.
Sorry.
But why am I sorry?
All right.
So we got mission stories.
A perfect machine.
Intravenous.
We did this one.
The munchies.
The new army.
The triumph with turbocharged.
I mean, this one is so strange.
I need to- I kind of want to know what it is.
The new army.
So that's pretty far away.
Can I get in the boat?
Can I drive the boat?
I don't think I can.
That'd be amazing.
Turn off the sound.
What, you want the quiet man experience?
All right, here we go.
I'm not going to turn off the sound.
People are probably going to come here and be like,
oh, Hitman 2, okay.
Loud man.
No, and I'm not doing a cheese grater to my feet.
I'm not turning the sound off.
I'm not putting a cheese grater on my feet.
And I'm not going to turn the sound as loud as I-
I'm going to do the Hitman mission.
That is Ted Mendez.
One of the country's most influential military grade moneymen.
This must be connected to Kronstadt.
Okay.
Let's see if we can listen to what this guy said.
Look, dolphins.
Ted here.
Just returning your call before heading over to the expo building
to meet Knox with a new-
Combat Android presentation.
Okay.
Yeah, the stutter is kind of crazy.
Why?
It's because there's water.
I don't have a 780.
I have a 1080.
I mean, my drivers might be from like 2016,
but it's still a 1080, god damn it.
I'm kidding.
That's a joke.
I have the drivers.
Ted Mendez.
A defense funding consultant with the U.S. military
is scheduled for a private demonstration
of a new Kronstadt robotics project.
Okay.
Sounds like a way to get up close and personal with what-
Update drivers.
Disguise yourself as Ted Mendez.
You got it.
Hey.
My 10- my 970 runs again.
Do I need to get drivers?
Maybe I should update my drivers on stream.
Is this guy gonna see this?
I can't get him now.
There's a guy behind me.
Why is this running so-
This wasn't running like this before.
I have to get the fucking new drivers.
I have to make these guys run the other direction.
I did not turn the settings down?
Yeah, I don't know why.
I think it's definitely a driver problem.
Quick dump in the water.
Water, water, water, water, water.
Oh, fuck.
Turn the water off.
I dislike this stream.
It's not quiet, man.
Okay.
Save it and get indoors before my computer breaks.
Hitman.
It's time.
I have nothing.
I don't know what to say.
Approach to reception.
Here we go.
We're gonna do this fun mission.
Mr. Mendez.
Good to see you, sir.
The demonstration is scheduled to take place on the upper floors.
Look at the executive floor.
Please feel free to use the stairs right over there.
He finally ran out of jokes.
Excuse me.
Oh, I got so many.
Can you tell me where to go, please?
It's just up these stairs.
It's just some of the-
I run a joke library up there,
and a lot of the books are overdue,
so I'm just kind of waiting for them to be returned.
This is running like dog shit.
It wasn't doing this before.
Hold on.
Let me just go get the driver.
I'm gonna open Quiet Man up in the background
while we get the driver.
I don't know why it's doing this.
It's like unplayable, actually.
I don't know why it's doing it now.
Oh, I'll get it quick.
I have 10,000 down.
Oh, fuck.
Wait, will this turn off the stream?
It shouldn't, right?
No, is this gonna turn off the stream?
All right, I'll be right back if it does.
This one just came out.
Optimize for Hitman.
It actually is.
This one that came out like a week ago.
All right, let's get it.
Oh, hopefully it's the right one.
Turn the face cam on.
I don't have a webcam.
I don't have a webcam plugged in.
That's all right.
It's already done downloading.
I'm ready.
That's okay.
I have 10,000 to plug in a webcam.
Lies.
All right, I hope this doesn't turn off OBS.
If not, I'm gonna press the button and come right back.
But I cannot play like that.
It's just, it's not gonna happen.
Here we go.
Yes, I'd like to install the drivers.
Hey, let's put this up.
There we go.
Look, I'll be right back.
That was a virus noise?
No, it wasn't.
That was a weird installing noise.
Don't install the GeForce Experience.
I don't.
I just get the driver and I say, no, thank you.
All right, 55%.
75%.
Guys, I mean, this just proves that everyone says,
upgrade your PC, upgrade your PC.
I mean, I have a dual core Celeron processor from like 2008 or 2007.
So it's still good and it still works perfectly fine.
Checking system compatibility.
I said it's compatible.
Just get it so I don't have to deal with the Hitman issue.
Come on.
I got hungry people here.
I got hungry customers here.
I just went in the back and I'm out of pizza.
There's no more pizza dough ready.
And there's like a line of people waiting for the pizza.
And I'm the guy, I'm the manager, running in the fucking back going like,
where are the fucking pizzas?
Hurry.
I'm still testing my system compatibility.
Roll the dough out, get it in the oven, and fucking put toppings on it now.
Got it.
All right, here it comes.
I'll be right back.
If this stream turns off, I'll be back in two seconds.
49% of the restaurants want pasta.
Well, that's all right.
We'll just, we'll just, there'll be a station to the left of the pizzas
where you can put the fucking pizza into a blender and then it pisses out pasta.
I don't know, guys.
I'm trying to install a driver.
I'm trying to.
I don't know.
My stream's gonna like turn off.
Fucking quiet, man.
The pizza shop is currently on fire.
No, we're good.
Then we're gonna, we're gonna get back into it.
We're gonna be just fine.
But correct me if I'm wrong, but the last Hitman stream I did,
it was not like that, right?
It happened every so often, but it wasn't a constant issue.
All right, we're going.
We're going.
It's going.
How do I like, I need to like turn on a webcam.
Do I have any webcams up here that I just plug in?
How do I, I dare, I, hold on.
All right, here's a shitty webcam that I'm gonna plug in.
Is this gonna, am I live?
My whole computer is flashing.
I think we're live still, are we?
But my display just got darker.
Are we, we're not live anymore?
Why can I not, my other monitors are off.
Oh god, curse of the quiet, man.
All right, it's done.
It's pretty much, it's just finishing up.
Even your PC wants to play quiet, man.
All right, to complete installation, restart the computer.
No, restart later.
I don't have time for this shit.
All right, display.
Where's, what the fuck?
Don't, I don't, it doesn't detect any other displays.
Oh, you gotta be fucking kidding me.
Well, encoding overload.
Consider turning down the video settings is what OBS just said.
I'm at a 90% CPU right now.
I gotta get out of here.
I'll be right back.
I gotta go.
I actually have to go.
I'm at 90% CPU.
I'll be right back.
All right, let's try it.
Let's see what happens.
This reminds me of my favorite game, The Quiet Man.
If I just stayed in The Quiet Man, none of this would have happened.
I'm back, I'm back.
I'm coming back.
Can't argue with that.
Here we go.
Count backwards.
All right, get that off the screen.
Let's see if it fixed it.
I can see chat.
I've restarted.
I got my, I got all my shit ready.
I'm ready to go.
Let's just load where we just were.
And hopefully I don't, I don't run it like nine frames per second.
Why, The Quiet Man's currently trying to get captured.
Hey, hi guy.
What the fuck are you doing?
Jesus Christ.
Oh, hey, hey, hey everybody.
How are you?
Hey, how do I get that load game?
Quit game, load game.
We've pushed him too hard.
No, I just want a better menu than Xbox One.
Like I just want to load my game.
I don't have to buy my, okay, whatever.
I'm just going to load this.
It's under featured.
The one tab, it should be on the fucking first page.
It's like in Windows 8.
It is the first page.
But it should be on the second page too.
Load.
Okay, God.
Go, start it.
Hey, welcome to the stream everybody.
I was playing The Quiet Man.
We were making lasagna references.
And now I'm angry playing Hitman 2.
What the fuck is going on?
The race is entering its final lap, 47.
47, the race is over.
Sierra will be coming off the track anytime now.
It fixed it.
It actually fixed it.
We're good.
Game is fixed.
All right.
Let's settle down.
Everyone just relax.
Okay.
By the way, the mission was on a timer.
It's not on a timer.
We're fine.
Everything's fine.
Everything's good to go.
Let's play Hitman 2.
Am I allowed up here?
Okay, go to the executive floor.
I'm lagging though.
I shouldn't be.
I shouldn't be lagging.
Not fixed.
Turn off this.
Are we witnessing like the death of my graphics card live?
Did playing The Quiet Man like break my computer actually?
Check OBS.
OBS looks okay right now.
Go back to quiet.
Live exercise in progress.
All right.
I'm gonna be careful.
Let's save it.
I am getting like OBS.
I streamed this in taught.
This is what annoys me the most.
I streamed this entire game.
The whole thing.
Every mission.
Without any like encoding issues.
And I didn't change any settings.
So what the fuck is going on?
Save scum.
You have to finish Quiet Man.
I'm gonna say something provocative now, Ted.
War is going out of fashion.
It's dirty.
It's just plain bad PR.
Nobody wants to exchange their children and loved ones for flags and medals anymore.
The glory is cursed, Ted.
But luckily, Kronstadt has a solution for that.
Imagine this.
Android infiltrators operating in the field.
Disguised, fully embedded, ready to strike at a moment's notice.
Indestructible robotic operators who can infiltrate the deepest sanctuary of any adversary.
Quiet Man's not still running in the background.
A surgical tool.
An army of them.
Fully equipped Android medics.
Seeking out wounded servicemen and injured civilians.
Bringing them to safety.
Or patching them up dead in there.
Android pilots delivering payloads deep inside enemy territory.
So picture of target dummy.
And minimal collateral damage.
All right, Mendez.
It's very straightforward.
Let me show you.
So I have to sabotage this thing.
Any of the pictures on the desk.
Then I use the scanner to upload the biometric data.
And Pallas will do the rest.
Target acquired.
WB.
So this thing is shooting.
Okay.
So how am I going to turn this thing around and have it shoot everybody?
Annually feeding it biometric data.
This is still a prototype.
This is a pivotal moment.
No, there's no way it's still running.
I restarted my computer.
I had to turn the stream on.
Pallas is entirely full crew.
There ain't anything else running.
Is the pic a photo?
What's the holdup, Mendez?
Picture of target dummy.
Picture of target.
I need a picture.
I need a picture of you.
So I need to get a picture of him first.
I may have missed my opportunity here.
All right.
Target dummy C.
Let's do them all at the same time.
There's no way it's running in the background.
I know.
I just think how much more we can accomplish together.
My brain's your money.
The sky's the limit here, my friend.
I don't know.
Maybe I'm old fashioned.
I still prefer the human touch.
You're part of an old institution.
If this is running in the background, there's no fucking way.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait.
Five?
No, no, no, no.
I've restarted the computer.
No, there's no way.
No.
And you prefer the traditional approach.
I respect that.
It is like running like shit.
What happened to my computer?
This is the future you're looking at.
Autonomous synthetic systems will entirely remove human agents.
What does five mean?
I guarantee this thing will absolutely murder anything you put it up against.
Sounds promising.
So, Mr. Mendez, impressive so far?
It is pretty impressive.
So let me find a picture of you and shoot you.
Let me show you our on-site robotics lab.
It's small, but state of the art.
And it's fully mobile.
Don't hit a new PC in the meeting room.
Check HW.
No, I can see my CPU.
I have no idea.
So as part of the deal, Cronstadt will throw in one deployment cell per five.
I haven't been able to lock in and pay attention.
I really should just go back and play quiet, man.
Are you, sir?
Yeah, my computer is fucked up.
My CPU is being overloaded right now.
I have no answer for this.
My CPU is being overloaded now.
I need a computer doctor.
Check OBS to see if it's using CPU or GPU encoding.
The driver update probably caused it to get switched.
I was just playing.
The quiet fan.
No, no, everything's fine.
No, it looks fine.
Maybe something to be...
No, I played in this exact mission.
I was in the same exact spot not even a week ago.
And this wasn't happening.
It's unfortunate that this is kind of taking over the stream right now.
This is bad.
This is real bad.
Fuck.
Yeah, it's on H.264.
I just looked.
It is...
I can't...
Oh, no, I'm just sad.
The stream is a mess leaving.
I'm sorry.
I did not expect my CPU to overload and overheat and get all fucked up.
It was kind of funny at first.
No, I'm actually just kind of sad about it.
I'm going to reload here.
I'm going to change this.
Clean out the dust.
The inside is pristine.
There's no dust in there at all.
I'm not going to go back a little further.
Oh, I'm so defeated right now.
Because Italics just had major computer problems.
Italics's computer was smoking and almost lit on fire.
And now my CPU is fucking going crazy.
Huh?
Why?
Why are we cursed?
No, I'm going to go back here.
I'm going to go to...
Because I'm sorry I wasn't able to completely engross myself and pay attention to that.
My mind's been somewhere else, as you are very well aware.
So let's...
I'm going to do like this one.
I need to get like a picture of him, but I just didn't do it, unfortunately.
Hold on.
I'm going to find a photo.
Yeah, I'm sorry, everybody.
I'm sorry that technical problems have taken the stream over once again.
Picture of him in here?
Is there a photo of him in here?
Okay, I can do it.
Now I have to go back to quiet.
All right, where's that demonstration?
Right here.
All right, I'm back.
And I have something for you.
Go stand over there, buddy.
All right, here we go.
I'm going to get him.
This isn't less lagging than it was last time?
Yeah, but last time I was not getting encoding errors,
because I can look at my CPU right now.
It's going way harder than it was last time.
Yeah, this is all turned off and down and everything.
It's not this.
Yeah, task manager is there's nothing there.
Turn V-Sync off.
It was already.
Was it off before?
That like made it worse.
Bet three.
Thanks for the five community subs.
Switch to the other controller.
Well, I have to turn the stream off again.
I really don't want to like troubleshoot live here
and like, oh, I'm going to turn the stream off back on streams off back on.
I'll just deal with it for now.
It's very straightforward.
Let me show you.
I just pick any of the pictures on the desk.
I think we're going to scan it to upload the biometric data
and Palace will be the rest.
Obviously, the final system won't rely on you manually feeding it.
Unplug my webcam.
No, it's not that still a prototype.
This is a pivotal moment in modern.
Yeah, Palace is entirely.
All you need is to pick a photo.
But what's the hold up?
Mendez just scan one of the pictures.
All right, let's do it.
Hey, look, I have a picture here.
I wonder whose picture this is photo of Robert Knox.
Knox down now for the it's that easy.
I mean, I press the button.
Wouldn't they come over to me and be like, hey,
what the hell did you just do anything to do with this?
Yeah, you, Mr.
Oh, come on.
He's not hold on.
Wait, I stayed here for too long.
Really?
Okay.
Did I actually just get caught?
I was thinking that guy's going to get shot in the back of the head.
There's new settings in the game.
Really?
I mean, I don't see anything that's different from last time.
I don't see anything different.
It's running better now.
We'll see.
We'll deal with it.
We.
It was doing that before, but not as hard as that.
A new option that I can't change.
All right, let's do let's get rid of the do another mission.
So this is I can't do this one now, but maybe I can do this one intravenous.
Do the quiet man mission.
Failing hard drive.
I don't know.
I do.
I brought a fish.
I didn't even bring my actual tools.
I hope German doesn't get upset from streams like these.
I do.
But not at like anyone in particular, right?
It's not like I'm angry with you guys or anything.
Like I can't believe this.
How do I get that?
Just that kind of sucks.
You know, Hey, what's up?
It's having fun.
And now I have to like live troubleshoot computer problem.
Why is there like a dinosaur over here?
No, I'm good.
I'm good.
Where's the T Rex?
Is this lady?
Holy shit.
You weigh like 5000 pounds.
The record I voted for quiet, man.
Yeah, but I would have run into it eventually.
So better now than ever, you know what I mean?
Better now than never.
Hey, how'd you know I'm bald?
Can I go through here?
I'm allowed to go through this way, but let's see.
I probably should put his outfit on.
Can you be around better off than on?
No, you have a key.
Wait, you got a key on you.
You have a gun, but you don't.
I'm gonna give a key.
All right, come with me.
That should at least give me access to this next part.
Better quiet than hit, man.
Yay.
Ghost mode has more optimization.
You know, and I'm sure it does.
I should have a broken neck counter.
Ooh, I'm going to bring him over here.
I can't.
He's fine.
No one's going to give a shit.
Why can I not?
Why was I grayed out?
All right, open this from the inside so I can run out there if I need to.
Hornets are back.
I've been great.
Can I get in front of the camera?
That's a nice camera.
Sir, can you please get out of there?
Body found?
Who found that body?
I'm trespassing.
I'm trespassing here.
I'm supposed to be security.
What, mall security is not allowed back here?
We might have a situation.
Someone just got an ad.
All right, let's fish this guy.
How are you?
What?
I just beat the shit out of this guy.
And he got right back up.
All right, I need a place to dump him.
This way.
Come with me.
Quiet Man versus Sneak Man.
Quiet Man doesn't kill.
What, you're assuming I didn't kill all those guys?
All right, so I need to go that way.
In there.
All right, bye.
All right, here we go.
Medical tent.
Story revealing itself.
Let's just say she's got a bad case of intermittent explosive disorder.
She's got intermittent explosive diarrhea.
Now he has to deal with this guy suffering from urinary retention.
Not his day.
Let's just hope he doesn't somehow screw up the revitalization procedure on Ms. Knox.
No, it's just a simple injection.
But given his track record these past few days.
Well, at least we know who's buying us beer tonight.
Think that's the truth.
Okay, so.
So, it seems Sierra Knox has jumped on the revitalization bandwagon
and is scheduled for an injection of some sort.
The doctor who is supposed to help her with the procedure.
Okay, so I gotta get in here.
There's a doctor.
I'm gonna turn into this doctor and I'm gonna poison.
Can I sprint through?
If I sprint as fast as I fucking can, can I get through?
I heard him arguing with that Kronstadt lawyer earlier.
No, didn't have any luck.
Once he's done with that other driver, he'll just have to use the-
Oh, I'm allowed back here.
Nevermind.
I thought they were gonna be like,
Sir, you can't go back there.
You're not allowed.
Mr. Durant, I'll ask you to get a move on.
Sierra Knox coming next for a post race.
I don't want to keep her waiting.
Surely you must be able to-
That's it.
I can throw him in there.
Mr. Durant, you've inhaled around a gallon of water by now.
All right, how do I imitate his voice?
Hey, don't go in the closet.
How are we doing?
Yeah, yeah, relax, Tuck.
I know you've got Sierra Knox coming in for that fancy-
That was yest in time.
I'm doing my best here.
Oh shit, I need poison.
I need poison.
I don't have any poison.
Uh-oh.
Where can I get some poison?
Poison?
No, that's a sink.
Poisonous sink?
Medical staff only, I'm allowed in here.
Here we go, we got poison.
Lethal poison jar.
Ugh.
Okay, find a key or a crowbar?
Why don't I find a key or a crowbar?
Call Sierra to emergency.
I'm so happy to see you.
I'm guessing you're here to replace Dr. Sorensen.
I forget your name, sorry.
Dr. Reaper.
Ah, yeah, of course.
All the medics look alike.
Find a key or a crowbar?
Why do I need to find a key?
I'll prepare for her arrival.
Dr. Reaper.
All right, well, there's a key over here.
Okay.
Fucking frames.
So...
Where is this, uh...
There's a medical cabinet here, but...
Oh, there it is.
Open!
It's a wrench.
Get rid of the current patient.
Can I stab him in the neck?
How am I gonna get rid of this guy?
Illegal?
I don't have anything to throw at him.
It'll be all right.
Okay.
Call Sierra from...
No, wait, wait, wait.
Hold on.
Do I need to poison the drip?
Let me save it here.
There's already a...
Yeah, that's the doctor.
Blood is suspect.
Sierra Knox should be on her way to the emergency area.
Come on down.
So, poison the drip?
Right now?
I'm gonna do it right now.
Is there anything...
What's in here?
Okay, put it in the line.
So it's in the line now.
Come on in.
Dr. President Sleeper.
Oh, am I gonna give her a haircut too?
Stop killing people.
I didn't...
I just had to...
Well, yeah, I'm sorry.
I have nothing there.
I have nothing to combat that.
That's a pretty good excuse though.
Does nobody find it weird that the back of your head is branded?
Well, I mean, you could always just talk about how
the tattoo you got when you were younger
because you're such a fan of the Hitman games.
Dr. Lasagna.
Everybody makes that joke because it's a funny joke.
Can I tell her to come in?
Get in here.
I'm ready.
You.
Right there.
Let's go.
Ms. Knox, I'm ready for you.
God, I hope I don't break a leg or something.
Okay.
Thanks for the input, lady.
Really great GTA pedestrian thing to say.
Ms. Knox, come on in.
Have a seat and relax.
So, what's on the menu?
Oh, can you just get out of the way for me?
Have you ever heard of personal space?
I promise.
Shut up.
Once I'm done, you won't feel a thing.
All right.
Sit in that chair.
So, what's on the menu anyway, doc?
Mostly floral, extracts, hemlock, belladonna, aconite.
It's designed to be fast and efficient.
Fast and efficient.
Changed disguises.
Wait, belladonna?
Isn't that poisonous?
Yes.
Should I beat this round?
I'm not.
Just relax.
It'll be over soon.
Hey, doc.
Hope we don't need you today, huh?
How is she going to die?
Choke?
Puke?
Or just roll over in the chair?
What do you think?
Hey, you know what?
I do feel refreshed.
Thanks, doc.
My pleasure, Ms. Knox.
Is she going to puke?
Oh, god.
I got to call my dermatologist back.
Don't worry.
It'll be over soon, Ms. Knox.
Both targets down.
Well done, 47.
Head for an exit and we'll speak again soon.
Clean.
Oh, there's an exit right here.
Excellent.
Spotless.
Okay, now it's time to just go on an absolute insanity run.
Okay, so let's replay the mission.
Actually, let's do next and see what we unlocked.
Stands, toilet, sniper rifle, stands.
Okay, cool.
All right, so now let's go back to the menu.
Challenges, a man in the sea,
assassin with a fish trophy.
Sands.
All right, let's go back.
I want to replay the mission.
Re-plan mission for a second.
I want to bring in to the toilets.
Okay, let's start at the...
I start with this costume on.
Dolphin fountain.
I guess I'll start in the stands.
Start at the public toilet.
I want to see how fast I can eliminate both targets and get up.
Don't forget, the secret of endurance racing is to keep that car going until the end.
He's getting into character here.
All right, hold on.
Wait a minute.
Can I...
Let me see if I can do this.
What?
Oh, I got him.
Holy shit.
Nobody...
No, nobody...
What about the ones that are driving in now?
They're gonna smash into it?
No, I don't think they can hit it.
Wait a minute.
That was a pretty quiet grenade.
Do the Sean B mission?
Yeah, I'll go do that.
That sounds like fun.
That's the patient zero, right?
Don't forget, the secret of endurance racing is to keep that car going until the end.
This race is not over until the clock ticks again.
Wait, let's wait.
How much time remaining?
Don't worry, folks.
Anything can still happen.
Fuck.
That guy died?
I'm trying to punch this guy.
Why can't I punch this guy?
All right, let's do the other mission.
Wait, hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Hold on.
Bird.
For newcomers to endurance races, let me remind you that this is difficult,
and it's all about which team should seize it reliably.
How did I...
Two hours later.
No, no, no, no, no.
I was trying to throw it over.
Okay, elusive target.
47.
Good morning.
Your target is Mark Faber, also known as the Undying.
A disgraced former MI5 operative currently working as a freelance assassin,
Faber has been confirmed killed by ICA agents more than a dozen times.
On every occasion, he has managed to come back from the dead.
We have confirmation that Faber has a meeting in the Miami Bayside Center
to review details on a new target.
Illusions.
An informant at the site has provided us with reliable intel on Faber's expected movement.
Hmm, he's already taken a helicopter?
This information has revealed several viable approaches.
As you know, our inside man is meeting with the target.
Acquire the right disguise, and he'll get you inside the heart of the building.
Up close and personal is risky, but favors the clean kill.
Alternatively, smuggle in a sniper rifle via briefcase.
I like that idea.
The race tower is a perfect vantage point.
That's what I'm doing.
Access is restricted.
Race security is high.
Get through the locked door, and time your shot perfectly.
I'll get it.
Or infiltrate through the staff entrance at the back of the building.
Access the second floor using the elevator shaft.
Move unseen inside the weapons demo room, and infiltrate as you see fit.
Act once an opportunity presents itself, or rig the room to your advantage.
Leave unseen.
Be mindful, however.
The repercussions of being exposed here would be severe.
I'm gonna be very careful.
I'm confident even more opportunities will reveal themselves once you arrive on site.
I'm going for the sniper nest.
To be entirely honest, this one's a bit of an embarrassment.
Please, make sure he doesn't come back again.
I should act it.
Good luck.
I'm so ready for this.
One chance.
You cannot replay a target.
You only get one chance.
If you die, it's a game over.
You only have one time, one window, one death.
That's it.
Okay.
I can't fuck this up.
All right.
Planning.
I...
Okay.
Oh, that makes me so nervous.
Okay, briefcase.
How do I...
I want to put in the briefcase...
The shot...
Shotgun.
No, no, don't be an idiot.
This thing.
A mace.
I'm gonna kill him with a mace.
No.
What do I have for...
I don't have any other costumes.
All right.
I got it in the briefcase.
I got...
I'm gonna take coin.
I'm gonna lockpick.
Okay.
That's in the briefcase.
Smuggle of fish.
Not a bad idea.
I can't.
Unless he's...
I'm gonna duck.
All right.
One chance.
That's it.
Oh, my God.
I'm ready.
This contract is an elusive target.
In playing an elusive target, the following rules apply.
You must begin the contract before the countdown expires.
If you die, you may not retry.
Once you've completed the contract and successfully exited,
you may not retry the contract.
You may no longer restart the contract.
You cannot save your game.
Shit.
He already failed?
I don't say that yet.
It hasn't happened yet.
Good afternoon, 47.
Your target is already inside the Miami Bayside Center.
Faber has a full day of meetings planned
and we do not want to risk losing him.
Take your time with this one.
Eliminate Mark Faber.
He's already inside.
And there's Jerma.
Dave Ready, our informant,
is waiting for you in the reception area.
If you like, he can lead you to a meeting
where Faber will be in attendance.
What you do from then on is up to you.
Be mindful.
Talk to Dave.
He will not wait around for long.
Oh, fuck.
All right.
Well, hold on.
Where?
Can I go in here?
Dave's ready.
Are you?
Not yet, but I'm going to have to try.
Hey, what's going on, Dave?
Dave is ready.
Ah, yes.
You're the one I've been expecting.
The special guest.
I am.
Okay.
So like I told your superiors,
I can get you inside the meeting, but that's it.
What you do from there is up to you.
Just how I like it.
All right.
You can't go in dressed like that.
I thought I was going to be a sniper.
I'll work something out.
Good.
I'll wait when you hear.
The ICA has struck a deal with Dave ready.
Okay.
Hold on.
Mission stories.
They're expecting us upstairs in the conference room.
Okay.
I need to be an engineer.
Got it.
Briefcase and key card.
All right, Dave.
I'm ready.
How's this?
Where'd you find that?
Never mind.
I don't want to know.
Let's go.
Dave is already expecting us up there.
He's expecting us.
Oh, God.
But hold on.
Where are my exits?
I have a sniper rifle in this briefcase.
Are they going to search me?
This guy's with me.
What you do, I don't understand it.
This deal is closed when we enter the room.
All right.
I get you in.
That's all.
And then your people take care of my problem.
Don't worry.
We'll fulfill our end of the bargain.
Is there a place I can snipe from here?
All the people like them are stupid.
I thought I could make some quick cash, you know?
Buy that yacht, sail a couple of...
Hold on.
This guy can see right through me.
...for the summer.
Oh, my God, computer.
Why are you doing this?
...somethin' hemisphere.
You don't try to cheat those kind of people.
I wish I'd met you a little earlier, buddy.
Could've used that advice six months ago, you know?
Anyway, we're almost there.
So let's put on our game faces.
Oh, fuck.
Okay.
I got to get this right.
Hey, how you doing?
He's...
Is that him?
So...
Holy fuck, that's him.
...you finally meet.
That's him, that's him.
You don't quite...
I expected.
Oh, God.
I'm Faber.
Mr. Faber!
What an absolute pleasure to meet you.
I'm Dave Reddy, special acquisition gatekeeper working with you on this job.
I'd show you my breakbook when I'm sure you've already heard about me.
Can't say that I haven't.
Oh, I see.
I've prepped an extensive briefing to help with...
Please help!
Help me!
I did it.
I got to get out of here, though.
Get out.
Oh, my God.
I'm going to burn this computer.
Explosive penmanship.
They hit the aquarium and a clean headshot.
One.
Better than zero.
Boat rental hut.
HWK 21 MK2.
Explosive pen.
Florida fit with gloves.
You're supposed to kill him creatively?
I'm not good enough for that, man.
See?
I just need...
That's all I want is the checkbox.
I just want to get the diploma.
All right, let's go to...
Let's go to this neighborhood place.
So let's start.
I want to start in the construction area.
Okay.
I do have this now, but that's not silenced.
Not like it matters.
I can't believe you shot that guy and looked cool doing it.
All right, briefcase.
I can't take that with the current disguise?
No, I guess not.
A fish is okay.
That's not suspicious.
Apparently, there's a grenade.
All right, we'll take the pen.
All right.
So let's see what we got for mission stories here.
Pest control.
House for sale.
Whack-a-mole, we did that one.
No smoking area.
What about pest control?
Or house for sale?
Yeah, let's do house for sale.
Oh my god.
What?
All right, let's go.
You show him rooms and how...
We'll find out.
Did I put it on casual?
No, I didn't, did I?
So I'm pretending...
Don't I have to get like an application to work here?
Why is 47 just a construction worker?
All right, so we got radio.
No, no, no, I want to do the house for sale.
I think I can see through me.
Why would I even be here?
No, don't throw things at people.
Just do it.
Don't throw wrenches.
I always said bricks.
Jerma loves role play stuff.
It's kind of fun.
All right, here we go.
This is the open house.
I mean, I can just take as many as I want.
I want them all.
Give me all of them.
Proximity mine?
No.
I can say that I do.
Well, how do I make it explode?
You know, the one that police are down after the incident.
I'm not really from around here.
I don't know.
I just want to test it and see what it does.
Well, never mind.
You can wait a little.
Oh, I'm not sure I've seen you.
Anybody else feel that?
So it's a grenade, but it also can kill people on contact.
Okay.
Maybe you know him.
Mr. Nolan Cassidy.
All right.
So this is the guy.
This is the real estate guy.
Well, he's interested in the Schmidt house down the road.
You know, the one that police are down after the, well, incident.
I'm not really from around here.
47.
A real taste for the sweet things in life
is in Whittleton Creek to show a house to Nolan Cassidy.
It looks like he's stuck at a local muffin stand.
Don't be ashamed.
Keep Cassidy waiting.
This guy's a server.
Never mind.
You can wait a little longer.
I need to squeeze a couple more of these beauties down.
All right.
So there's a server somewhere else in one of these houses.
The question is, which house was he in?
Kill him with a muffin.
No, no, that's, that's too easy.
I want this guy going to break
because I know there's another muffin person somewhere.
Sir, get out of my way.
I'm leaving.
Just hold on.
What's my muffin of choice?
Chocolate, chocolate chip muffins or cornbread muffin.
I don't really, not a big muffin guy.
There's the party muffin in mailbox muffin delivery service.
Uh, I don't see the server here.
He's a server, but is he though?
He's kind of just a guy at the grill.
Maybe that guy goes on a break.
Do you go on a break?
What's the fucking door?
Oh, that was a stale.
Those are stale muffins.
Is there anybody else in the house?
Where can I put this guy?
Is there nowhere I can put you?
Did I bring a fish?
I did not bring a fish.
No, he'll be fine.
Just flush him down the toilet.
All right.
Obtain rat poison.
I wish there was a spit button.
All right, rat poison.
And then we're going to go become the realtor.
Put him in the dryer.
Knock, knock.
I'm looking for my secret ingredient.
Oh, what?
What?
Is this the guy that lost a pinwheel?
Yes.
Yes, it was.
It was incredibly embarrassing.
I couldn't believe it when it happened.
I cried on stream.
Tears were just streaming down my fucking face.
I kept on going like I can't do it.
I can't.
I can't fucking do it.
Everyone's just laughing.
Laughing, laughing, laughing, laughing.
Where's the poison?
I don't see any poison in here.
There we go.
All right.
Place the muffin on a serving plate.
I picked up a joint.
Apparently.
Well, that guy's not me.
How do I get rid of him?
If that guy can see right through me,
then how am I supposed to get around him?
Am I going to just pretend to be this guy behind him?
He's kind of distracted.
Disguise yourself as a real estate broker.
Just watch me do it.
You even have to watch it.
He's got a question mark.
Huh?
What?
I should try it.
And not just our height.
Eat the whole thing.
I feel sick.
Okay.
Say hello to your breakfast.
What was that?
That was weirdly Microsoft Sam in my ear.
So where does he go?
Wait, I can go in the sewer?
Oh, what?
I thought I was going to shoot at him.
That was so anticlimactic.
I thought I was going to spray straight in the line
and hit him right in the back.
Throw him down the sewer.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Where are you going?
I'm trying to think of like smoke weed.
Had to be this trash can.
Yeah, why this trash can?
Although here's the problem.
Okay, I got the key.
Um, I can stuff him in there.
That was so loud.
That's so loud.
That was louder than anything.
Put him in the trash can.
I don't think I can put him.
Okay.
Locate and approach Cassidy.
So where's Cassidy?
I think it's just on the phone.
It's the green icon.
I know where it is.
I'm just looking to see if there's anything else over here.
I'm seeing if there's anything else to do.
Throw the shovel at him.
I'm not going to throw a shovel at him.
I'm going to wait until we get in the house.
Aren't you the realtor?
Yes.
Mr. Cassidy, I'm sorry for the delay.
I'm ready to take you to the house.
About time.
Let's go.
Poke him with the fish.
All right, unlock the door.
Last one on the right.
All right, let's go.
Do I have to just run ahead?
Come on, let's go.
I was planting trees behind the property.
Pick up, what is it?
Pick up note for real estate company.
Unlock the door.
See?
It works.
Who's investigating a distraction?
Somebody in this house?
What are you doing in here?
All right, let's convince him to buy the house.
Thank you.
Goodbye.
All right, the tour.
So we have a television over here.
There's a piano.
TV.
Take a look.
Nice TV.
This is the downstairs living room.
It is most commonly used for watching television
and other recreational purposes.
Yeah, would you like a fish start?
A large room.
It's too easy to get to exits.
Dark floors hide stains easily.
A room with lots of potential.
What about storage possibilities?
Anything of that nature.
Well, that's why the shovel exists.
This guy likes sushi.
All right, come up here.
Follow me.
Here's the bathroom.
There's a lot of storage in the bathroom.
Oh, hey, how are you?
Okay, let's take a look at the upstairs.
Look, there's a TV up here.
What?
I turned on the TV.
Come up here and take a look at the attic.
What?
What are you doing?
Hold on, I'm trying to show him the house.
A spare bedroom, in case you have a lot of house guests.
It could also be used as an upstairs office
or a storage space with easy access to the attic above.
Yeah, you want to see it?
I don't know.
Got anything more interesting to show me?
It's all very interesting.
Yeah, come on, come on.
This way, this way.
Well, I don't.
Well, I can't even open this door.
This room is small.
I need to wow him.
I really need to wow him with something.
Hey.
What's this?
You can't go around throwing stuff like that.
What's the matter with you?
Oh, no.
Norman Cassidy is down.
Good work.
Janus awaits your attention.
All right, let's do...
No, wait.
Yeah, I'm good right here.
1808.
In case you have a lot of house guests.
Let me see.
Uh, Intel.
I cleaned the place as requested.
I was told the real estate agent would pick up the keys,
so I put it in the flower pot next to the door.
It could also be used as an upstairs office.
Flower pot next to the door.
Or a storage space with easy access to the attic.
This is like the president guy.
Oh, I was like, where the fuck did he go?
Okay, so we can go down here.
Follow me.
We'll show you something interesting.
Ding dong ditch your own house.
Here you go.
So I see the basement has a ample room.
And here's the basement.
The usual boiler elements are to be found down here.
And it seems a room with a safe of some sort.
Now that's more like it.
It's like a vault.
Let's unlock the vault door.
It's like a vault door to open.
Okay.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Nice work, 47.
Let's hope he doesn't set off the alarm somehow.
Wait, what?
Very nice.
I don't understand.
Wait, he's-
All right, let me have a look at this thing.
Is he able to get murdered?
The very strong-standing Matrix laser home security system.
We used to break these open for training at the academy.
The thing about these systems is most homeowners are lazy.
Seriously?
They don't reset the back resets and enter their own codes.
Push him in?
Let's just try the standard admin code.
Just for fun.
What if I go in?
Looks like Schmidt was a bigger amateur than I imagined.
Is he gonna go in?
Go outside and check the garden.
How visible this vault is from the outside.
Anything sticking out of the ground, weird, sloping things like that.
You got it, sir.
So you're looking to sell this for, uh, how-
What?
Just disable this.
I never did like these cron-stead systems.
Or that pompous-
So you're looking to sell this for-
What?
How much was it again?
1.1.
Sounds about right.
I suppose that's not-
No, don't turn it back on!
You know what?
Never mind.
What?
I don't think I want to buy this-
Turn it on.
Janus awaits your attention.
Wait, don't turn it back on.
You know what?
Ah, never mind.
I don't care.
I'm not gonna run.
I'm just gonna accept my fate.
No, computer!
Stop it!
Never mind.
I don't want to buy this place.
All right.
Let's go-
What else is there to do?
An apple a day.
The story mission did it.
No smoking.
We did-
We kind of started that one.
Let me try this one.
Do the dad living in the walls bit.
What happened with the elusive target?
Did it first try in less than two minutes.
Not a lie.
I didn't make that up.
Why does she hear that all the-
She would know you hear that all the way out here.
All right.
Cigarettes.
I'll take them.
They're back here.
I don't-
I can't get back there.
I have to climb over this.
Climb through here.
This is where the tree house is.
I'm gonna save it.
You can hear it through the whole house?
That's the point of a doorbell?
My doorbell is really silent.
Blend in as a gardener.
What is in here?
Hold on.
I'm just-
I'm just exploring a little.
I'm just curious.
All right.
We got a basement.
Wait.
Oh.
Right.
Okay.
Nothing over here that I need.
I need to try to sneak through here.
I can't unlock this shit from this way.
I can't even go over there.
I gotta go all the way around?
Goodness.
I'm sorry.
They had-
The guy was doing the T-pose.
I had to get around.
I had to do-
That guy was broken.
All right.
I'm gonna have a golf club, so...
What?
I want to use the golf club.
I can't do that apparently?
Wait.
That's not an ordinary resident of Wittleton Creek 47.
What?
This must be one of Cassidy's men working undercover.
I suggest you keep an eye out for more of them.
Okay.
Shovel.
Anything else?
All right.
Smoking kills.
Use the rake.
I can't grab the rake.
Where's there a rake?
Golf club.
Shovel.
Where's there a rake?
You can just let people walk into the rake.
Oh, yeah.
I've seen that.
I have seen it.
Well, I'm just gonna move out of here.
The rake.
All right.
I need smoking kills.
So I have the cigarettes.
I could give them weed too, couldn't I?
Give them some marijuana.
Game's gonna trap you until you find the rake.
So do I?
I need to like poison these, don't I?
Did I lose this opportunity?
I think I may have lost this opportunity.
No, there we go.
One of Janice's guards has apparently
tossed his cigarettes over the fence
and into the backyard.
Janice is using an oxygen apparatus
to help him breathe better
and the guard is trying to keep Janice alive.
Okay.
So I just go up there and let him smoke the cigarette?
So just go in the house and have him smoke.
Okay.
So where is that old man?
There he is.
These guys are gonna let me in, right?
Really?
Okay.
Well, fine.
I'm going through a fucking window.
Don't load the game.
Save the game.
All right.
Let's see.
Who's the closest person?
Should I like lie down?
Perform health check.
All right.
Where's that guy going?
I need to take that guy's disguise.
There he goes.
You coming in here?
Shit.
I gotta go around him.
Or you need to come in here.
Shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up.
Quickly, quickly.
Come on, come on, come on.
Excellent.
Pick up the Uzi.
Hide it.
Okay.
Time to give him his cigarettes.
You guys can all see through my disguise.
It's kind of annoying.
Say, Gunter.
Did you see my photograph?
The group photo from the first gathering?
Janice is looking for an old group photo.
It might be interesting to see who's always in his brief.
No, I need cigarettes.
Turn on the cigarettes.
How do I like put plant cigarettes over here so he smokes them?
Here we go.
Rig the oxygen tank.
All right.
And then hide in the closet.
Good work, 47.
All there is left to do now is wait.
I did it.
I just read the game FAQ?
No.
Yes.
I'm gonna be in here.
Look at how far away he is.
I'm gonna be here for a long time.
Uh, save?
I got an auto-save.
I'm good.
Can I hide under the bed or somewhere that I can see better?
All right, here he comes.
Let's get a save here.
I'm coming upstairs.
No, is he actually...
He's not gonna go out and look at the mole hills, right?
Do the grandpa voice.
Oh, okay.
This is fucking stupid.
I hate this place and I hate all of you idiots.
Taking away my cigarettes.
That's your last fucking straw.
He's doing it.
He's doing the voice.
So funny story.
I was at the grocery store and they got so many pastas there.
How are you supposed to pick up your favorite pasta?
I just fell backwards in my chair and like hurt myself.
That would have been pretty fucking crazy.
I would have caused damage.
Where's this old fucking man?
Might as well just get out and just hang out in here.
Sit in his chair.
I was gonna breathe in his oxygen.
You coming?
You old fucking man.
Hurry up and get up here.
Turn on the radio.
Pee in his bed.
I'm being patient.
I am being very patient.
I'm playing this correct.
We're just hanging out.
We're playing it right.
Bro, you are so fucked.
Am I though?
I don't think so.
You haven't lived until you peed in another man's bed.
How would they know it was me?
If I peed in...
Okay, here we go.
He'd probably think it was a cat or a dog or something.
This is it.
This is the climax.
I'm ready for it.
Fresh cigarettes.
Rigged up oxygen tank.
How's he doing?
Just sit in that chair.
Uh-huh.
Almost.
He's almost there.
That's a little closer.
Okay, he's there.
Ah, I think I have a pack of fresh cigarettes.
Whoa!
What?
That was quick.
That was really quick.
Hold on, wait.
Is that...
Is that camera up there going to be there?
I want to see something.
If that camera is up there, I want to try something.
Let's wait till it gets right here.
Joke incoming.
Um...
No, not really.
More like I want to see if the angle shows me do this.
Which would be funny.
Joke alert.
So we're going to see the picture in picture up there.
Come on, let's see it.
Picture in picture.
I want to see it.
Here we go.
I think you can see it.
The top left.
Peek through the window.
I... you can't.
That wasn't a...
I wasn't a joke.
I was just seeing what would happen.
I want to see if the picture in picture turned off.
I thought you could throw the baseball at him.
Oh, fuck.
You're right.
I'm going to get up and point blank throw it at his face.
Just point blank throw it as hard as you can.
Did that kill him?
No, I'm done.
First constant catch up with you.
That feels like an easy way out for a man like Janus.
I did that.
Still.
We are close now, gentlemen.
Both targets are dead.
All right, well, that was fun.
Anybody smiling in here?
What do you mean smiling?
Fuck the brownies.
Pop 100.
Oh, we're all the way back here.
Don't replay the whole mission.
He's checked out.
This guy is totally checked the fuck out right now.
Trying to throw them.
Throw it off screen.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait.
It's when he said as old, like right here.
Throw it at the camera.
I'm going to throw it at the camera.
That actually might be kind of funny because then it would bounce off the wall.
All right, let's go try that.
And then I'm going to load a different mission.
Don't give him any more ideas.
Shit.
Oh, I did it wrong.
I have to kill him.
Throw the joint.
Now, I got to kill both these guys while the camera is on.
I'm going to throw it into the camera.
Like right now.
Here we go.
Guard.
What's up?
What's this guy's problem?
Christ sakes.
That's enough.
Okay, here we go.
No.
It turned off.
Hold on.
This is the last time and I'm going to open up another mission
because we're just fucking around at this point.
The cameraman fucked it up.
I'm going to make this quick.
I didn't do it.
Last fucking time.
I promise this is the last time.
No, it wasn't even fucking worth it.
I almost just alt tab and deleted the game.
All right, go back.
Get back.
We're going out.
All right.
I think I broke everything.
Let's go here.
Alt tab.
Didn't even take the first step in doing that.
Let's go here.
Quiet mode.
It's taking syringe.
I thought quiet mode was only supposed to be three hours.
Yeah.
Yeah, it was.
Get in that dryer.
All right, what is it?
I want to start at the chapel.
It didn't last two hours.
You know, part of me thinks I'm going to go back.
I think I'm going to go back and play Quiet Man again after this.
I think I'm going to go back and beat it at the end.
What?
Oh, they didn't do anything.
They're all trying to get out.
They're all becoming one person.
That is the most single file.
Do these people just spawn in?
Did I put anything in the briefcase?
You need to try to put a mine there.
Oh, whoops.
Go put a trap at that exit.
Oh, god damn it.
Chat plays Hitman 2.
I wasn't allowed to be here, apparently.
Hey, you.
Excuse me.
Oh, that's a briefcase.
I got caught.
That just backfired completely.
I can't really go down from here.
I have to like sneak over there.
Let me try this one more time.
I got one person.
Wait, what?
What?
That took so long to get there.
Oh, this game is fucking ridiculous.
I didn't know I could throw it from this far away.
Look, what happens if I just throw the suitcase from right here?
Can I like target somebody down there?
This is not going to reach, so it's not even.
Wait, hold on.
I can lock on to somebody over there.
Hold on a second.
Did you hear that?
That's weird.
Hold on a second.
Throw a coin.
I'm so happy he found this out.
Well, I mean, at this point, I'm just fucking dicking around.
So, so hold on.
I'm currently on locked on to somebody down there.
Can I go all the way across, like all the way that way?
Catching something.
Okay, hold on.
Holy shit.
That's insane.
I almost hold on a minute.
What if I scare everybody and then do it?
Is it possible that I could scare everybody, throw it?
Is it only the briefcase or can I do it with this?
Oh, man.
Okay, hold on.
Okay, here you go.
Are we going to run?
Not yet.
I need to scare everybody.
Come on.
Here we go.
Where did it go?
I got to get this group to run.
Now, it's just a random person ducking.
That guy was already on the ground.
Gone.
Got him.
No, one flyover.
Take them all you got.
I was hoping I could get like pushed off.
All right.
I think I'm going to go back here.
It's time.
I think it's time.
End of stream, voice.
Go back to Quiet Man.
Yeah, I'm sorry that the technical problems kind of
threw it under the bus when we moved to Hitman,
but Quiet Man didn't last long.
Well, it lasted long enough and then everybody voted for me to get off Quiet Man
and I went to Hitman and then my computer couldn't handle it for some reason.
Now, let me get out of here for a second.
No, I want to see the credits.
That was all we're going to do with Hitman.
Thanks for watching Hitman.
And one second.
You could have just finished a game people aren't playing much and it was.