How you doing, everybody? Hope you're doing good.
Wait, hold on, hold on. My microphone's not here.
Hold on, my microphone's... I cleaned up my office.
Like, you remember, my microphone's like in a different place. Wait.
I was wondering. I was like, I can see my voice over there, but it looks very low. It still does. I fucked it up.
Is that better? I think that's better. Alright, okay. Anyways.
Hi guys, welcome to the stream.
Yes, I know, I know. The only thing anybody can talk about right now is, dude, that half-life trailer.
I know. I haven't even seen it yet. I haven't watched it, and I'm not going to.
I'm kidding. Alright, alright. I haven't seen the trailer.
So I was thinking, you know, what if we like do a little bit of watch the video and watch it and react to it?
You know, like, that's what I'm gonna do.
We're gonna get a live, real reaction of not seeing the trailer.
The trailer's like a minute and fifteen seconds long, so it's not like we'll be here for a very long time.
And also, what we're doing today... I gotta take a step back.
Because think about the last week or so of streams. Dead Rising...
Or is this Stressful?
Dead Rising 2, super stressful, beat the game time limits and all that shit.
I have Sekiro, I think like a year ago. I'm still feeling that one.
I want to slow down a little.
Bombo was stressful. Exactly, that's what I'm saying.
So, we're gonna play Farmer's Dynasty.
I was gonna play Hand Simulator, but everybody made fun of me in the pre-stream chat.
It was like people were just making fun of me, so I was like, okay, I guess I'm not gonna play that one.
And yes, I am aware that this is not...
This is not like Farming Simulator 2019. This is Farmer's Dynasty.
It just released on Steam.
So, I don't know. I just...
I said it because I was being a dick.
And I was like, oh, I'm thinking about playing Hand Simulator.
Everyone's like, if you're Tuber, okay, Tuber, that's stupid, that game sucks meme.
And I was like, all right, fine, Farmer's Dynasty.
And all of a sudden, you know what happens.
Yeah, yeah, do that, yeah.
So, if you guys have not figured it out yet, pre-stream chat has a lot...
There's a lot of influence when I'm in that pre-stream chat.
There are like at least a couple hundred one-guy scenarios.
You want to be the one guy?
Go to the pre-stream chat when I'm just hanging out for 20, 30 minutes before the stream.
You get like a buff to your one-guy influence in the pre-stream chat.
But anyways, let's watch this trailer.
Well, that's not the trailer, but I'm going to put it over that.
Wait, are we going to be able to hear...
I'm going to turn the music down here.
No, there is no music. All right, that's fine.
Give me a second. All right, let's watch it. Let's see it.
I want to see it. I haven't seen it.
Put on face cam? I do not have a shirt on, so I'm not going to put on face cam.
It's not going to happen.
All right, I got the YouTube link.
This is the right one, right?
Okay, here's the problem. Whenever you have a game like this come out,
you know how many random potential Half-Life fan-made trailers there are?
Half-Life. Alex Vance.
Somebody could have made this as a machinima.
There's a lot of them.
Let me make sure I got the right one.
This is the right one, right?
I haven't fucking seen this.
I haven't seen this.
What the hell is that?
Who's breathing?
Is this part of the trailer?
No, no, no, no!
No, don't start it yet.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Fuck.
All right, hold on.
Everyone slow down.
Hold on.
Wait, everybody wait.
Oh, I blew it.
I actually did blow it.
Okay, here we go.
I haven't seen this.
Why is close captioning on?
Is this HD?
What's this?
360p.
1440p.
I can't do it.
My computer can't handle that.
All right, here we go.
I'm ready.
Three.
Two.
One.
Go.
I can turn the volume up.
Three.
Two.
One.
I'm here.
So what's the plan?
We can get this weapon.
What we're doing here could change things forever.
There's no straight shot to the vault.
Electricity.
Find a way out.
Oh, more electricity.
I'm with you every step of the way.
Old guy.
You're going to need a gun.
It's unloaded now.
Nope.
They know you're coming.
You need to get out of here now.
Nice.
That looks cool.
Oh, God.
They've got Dad.
They're going to find out what he knows, and then they're going to kill him.
Oh, this is my father.
I never told you.
I couldn't.
I'm so sorry, baby.
You will not save him.
Alex Bams alone cannot prevent his fate.
Open your eyes, Harry.
Electricity.
Sweat is pouring down my fucking underarms right now.
My underarms are crying.
Yeah, I know.
I can't believe it.
I can't believe they got the default skin from Garry's Mod.
Wow.
I can't wait to play this.
VR only?
What?
What the?
That looks...
I don't know.
There's a lot of electricity, a lot of electric moves, a lot of electric puzzles.
It looks good.
It looks like it could be good.
It looks like it could be funny and interesting.
And the weapons look really great.
The way that you load the guns and everything.
It's that new controller.
It's going to be the new Knuckles controller.
And like, I'm going to have to get them because of how would you not get them?
Well, see, apparently I've been told that this is a full video game.
This is not just like a three hour Knuckles tech demo, right?
So this is like a 12 to 15 hour game.
That's the first time that's ever happened.
I don't think there has been a VR game that's like a full VR experience.
That's been more than like four or five hours.
Resident Evil 7?
No, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I'm talking a only VR.
Only, only, only VR only.
Not Resident Evil 7.
You could play...
Resident Evil 7 was a game you could play on your PlayStation.
On your Xbox.
VR only.
Skyrim.
Did somebody just say Skyrim?
Yeah.
On the ninth time they released that game, you could play it in VR.
No, I'm talking ground up VR only.
You couldn't play Resident Evil 7 VR only.
In fact, you could only play it on PlayStation VR for the first like six months.
Everybody on PC played that with keyboard and mouse.
Rick and Morty.
Fucking Rick and Morty.
Rick and Morty is like a four hour game.
It'll be nice to see that though.
I'm looking forward to it.
Alright, so let's see.
What's the internet have to say about this?
What does the internet think?
We got 155,000 likes and 4.2 thousand dislikes.
So 4200 dislikes.
155,000 likes.
Seems like people are taking it pretty well.
The internet thinks you should play Farmer's Dynasty.
Are you sure?
If I had a like and dislike ratio on this stream,
the second that this trailer comes down,
would probably be like 30 to 70 percent like to dislike.
So I don't know if you're correct on that.
I think you're actually incorrect.
Just wait.
You guys are going to just wait.
I think I picked a good one.
Alright, let's go.
That was cool.
I'm sure it'll be fun.
They wouldn't have waited this long and put this much time into it
if it wasn't going to be at least a fun game.
We'll find out when I play it on day one.
That's right.
I've got an announcement of my own.
On day one of the launch of Half-Life VR,
I'm going to play it on this channel.
What an announcement that I have for you, right?
The thing that somebody put tons of awesome time into,
I'm going to play it.
What a fucking announcement.
Shit, this is loud.
Upgrade my PC.
By then, I'll have at least another fucking 780.
You guys ready?
Can we go now?
Day one first minute?
No, there's no way I'm going to be the first person that plays that game.
Somebody from like fucking Russia will have like a leaked copy
two, three weeks before it.
It'll stream it for like 40 minutes before they get removed.
So I won't be the first person that plays it.
When I'm allowed to, I will.
You guys ready?
Move to Russia.
Some random person from like, I don't know, like Australia or something
will end up having like a copy from some Australian GameStop.
New quest.
Talk to Oliver.
Since your grandfather passed away, he has kept an eye on your farm.
He'll show you around.
That's a bomb you're dropping on me.
You're losing food from the pantry.
A cat should keep mice at bay.
First, my grandfather dies and now my cat's...
What's going on?
Hold on.
This is the sensitivity is too high.
That's controller sensitivity.
Wait, is there a controls?
Keyboard.
Change the currency.
I already did.
All right.
We got...
I might have to...
I'm your neighbor.
My name's Oliver.
I've been looking after this farm since your grandfather passed away.
Nice to meet you, Oliver.
I appreciate your help.
Oh, damn it.
This is my heritage.
Game already sucks.
Not a silent protagonist.
Why am I dressed like this then?
Why does he not have the belt?
Why do we keep doing the T-pose stretch?
I'll show you around.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
That's a little better.
I can feel the view.
Best quality.
Let's go.
Okay.
Follow Oliver.
All right.
Where's the punch?
He'll talk later.
How do you...
I want to walk.
No, that's sprint.
I think I might actually use a controller for this.
It's kind of...
It's a little painful.
Is VSync on?
No.
No, I got to turn it on.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I don't want it in a different language.
Holy shit, you've got it.
This has been localized in a shitload of places.
As you can see, the farm is quite in a poor shape.
Few repairs have been done here.
What the hell have you been doing?
I thought you were looking after this place.
Does that include eating Cheetos on the couch while the place rots?
But you can have some sleep here or even store some food.
You will have to bring this farm to a good shape yourself.
Soon you'll see how to do that.
This place sucks.
What did you...
Like, what did you...
Has this guy been living here?
So he inherited this farm.
Why didn't I get this farm?
It's empty now, but I'm sure you'll need it pretty soon.
Well, I'll take a full letter, Greed.
But if you can afford building materials, then you can fix the construction yourself.
Okay.
His farm, your problem.
Yeah, that's ridiculous.
That's the guy from How It's Made.
It really is.
I hope he tells me.
Imagine if he stands behind you while you work.
And he, like, just narrates what you're doing.
The farmer screws the nails into the board.
Oh, I hope that happens.
It's like, Oliver, will you fuck off?
The cowshed is old and needs some work, but it's still solid.
You can do the fixes and upgrades yourself.
Try fixing those holes first.
The cowshed?
So your animals stay healthy.
What holes?
I see you've come prepared and have your own tools.
Good.
Try to fix these doors since it's stuck and won't open.
Okay, hold on.
This game is like, I need v-sync turned on.
Because it's like, it's killing me.
I have to, I think I have to restart the game.
We'll get to a save point first.
All right.
Equip the repair tool from the work mode menu.
Check the barn for sections.
Okay, the work mode menu.
This is an open world game?
Why do I have a Grand Theft Auto map?
Are you serious?
Okay, I need a barn.
Your animals live here.
Keep this building in good shape
so that your animals grow healthy.
Oh, okay.
Engineer site.
Open, activate.
Repair old planks.
All right.
It should open now.
I already opened it.
The door, oh, I opened it already.
Why did I have to do that?
Wow, look at this.
Don't tell me what vegetable it is.
That's wheat.
Got it.
Build a scaffold to climb up there and check the roof.
Build a scaffold to from the work mode menu.
This?
Build a scaffolding.
Holy shit, that took no time at all.
That was instantaneous.
I'm carrying this?
All right, I'm up.
Is this Fortnite?
Real life Fortnite.
Should I just make a shitload of them?
No, if it was real life Fortnite, guys,
it would be like this.
Fuck, what are you saying?
Fuck me.
I always got hit by that.
All right.
If it was real life Fortnite, it would be this.
I can only have two out at one time.
Never mind.
How do I remove this?
Whatever, we can have two.
All right, what do you want me to do?
You can store harvested grains in the silo.
Fuck me.
So use these later or sell them if you want.
I'm sorry.
Before you use the silo, remember to fix it first.
Okay.
Repair rusty metal.
Do I need more pieces?
I think I did it.
Oh.
What is going on here?
Take a look at the greenhouse.
You can grow some veggies here fast to earn some quick money.
I shaved the back of his head.
Still, you'll have to fix these holes
so your plants can grow to a best effect.
Okay, fix these holes.
I see your grandfather bought some materials to fix it already.
There's a car over there.
You can use it to rebuild the greenhouse as good as you can.
Okay.
Pick up metal?
Steel sheets to fix it.
It was already gone.
Did somebody read that?
Rebuild rusty metal with metal.
Where am I going to do the door?
Okay, I'm done.
You were pretty good at this.
I'm sure you'll do well on this farm.
Actually, I might have a job for you myself.
What is it?
Why don't you come to my place and do some fixes to my barn?
It's mostly roof that needs work,
but some walls need attention too.
I don't have much money,
but I'll give you my old tractor as a reward.
I'm sure you can use it.
Stop.
Wait, this dialogue options?
All right, sounds good.
I'll take care of that.
Thanks.
Should I go to his place?
Yeah.
Sounds good.
I'll take care of this.
I love this game already.
All right.
I'm going back home now.
Good luck and see you around.
What the fuck do I do now?
You received a thousand social points.
All right.
I'm kind of lost.
I've got a really important job for you.
Why don't you come to my place?
The way that I'm like dressed too.
I'm dressed in like a Halloween costume repairman costume.
What's in here?
This is my house, right?
What the fuck is all this stuff?
Enter the pantry.
Oh, Italian tomato soup cooked or condensed food tasty.
And do I have to eat?
This isn't even doing anything.
Holy shit.
Imagine playing the game.
What is this FOV slider?
Let's go right in the middle where it starts.
Oh my God.
What?
What's going on?
He doesn't know.
He didn't know.
What's wrong?
Why even have an FOV option that goes down this far?
Who plays a game like this?
Why wouldn't you have the option to go up rather than down this far?
All right.
Well, at max FOV, this is definitely like 60.
Is this 90?
I don't think it is.
Whatever.
All right.
What's wrong?
I got to go to the guy's house.
Right?
Home sweet home.
Complete repairs on your farm.
Help Oliver.
Go to Oliver's farm and fix his barn.
Use engineer's site to see which sections of the barn need repairs.
Let's go there.
Is that my truck?
Police?
That's not what I was trying to do.
Oh, I see.
What's your trade?
A bit of everything.
Nails.
Soap.
Some food.
You know, I will also buy fresh food from you if you can spare.
Nothing big, but I could use some fish.
What about hamburgers?
Mushrooms, perhaps.
You know.
Well, that's really good to know.
I'll see you around.
All right.
Not going anywhere.
You know.
Where am I?
Oh, OK.
You notice a stranger by the road.
He clearly wants something.
Wait, what?
Wait, I want to sell you stuff.
Come here.
Good to see you.
Can I help you?
Uh, care to trade.
Care to trade?
Sure.
What do you need?
Here, I've got a hamburger.
Delicious food of great nutritional value.
Twenty-six dollars.
Canned food.
Oh, here.
Take that.
Here, take all these soups.
How much money do I got?
Five hundred and fifty dollars.
All right.
Here, take this spicy pumpkin soup.
Uh, I'm keeping the apple and the tomatoes.
You can have everything else.
Hold on.
Why are there drones?
A wedding ring?
Wait.
Perfect.
Expensive item.
Perfect gift.
Is there a chainsaw?
How do I equip the chainsaw?
OK.
Put it away.
Let's go.
I need to do my quest.
I haven't even started playing the game yet.
I have to play the game.
What is that?
Is that an animal?
Buy a ring from him and then propose to him.
Can you pet?
Can I feed the dog?
I don't think so.
All right.
Let's go.
Get in the fucking truck and just drive the damn thing for Christ's sake.
OK.
Where is Oliver's house?
Can I put a waypoint?
Go to Oliver's farm and fix his barn.
All right.
I have a waypoint there.
I think.
There we go.
Somebody else's farm.
I'm just driving over all this stuff.
God damn it.
Change camera.
Can I go?
Oh, I can go inside.
Destroy the competition.
Yeah.
There can only be one farmer in this town.
You're destroying strangers' crops.
It's bad for your social status.
Oh, are you?
Is this Oliver's house?
Wait.
This is Oliver's barn.
Fuck Oliver.
You let my grandfather's place go to shit.
You think I care?
All right.
What do I need to fix?
I'm coming over here with like a huge tractor and I'm going to just dig up all of his stuff
and steal it.
Have I already gone full blown psycho?
Where's his barn?
Oliver, where the fuck are you?
Is this where he lives?
Just like the sicko cutting his shit down.
Just block the road.
Well, he'll figure it out.
All right.
Where is Oliver?
You notice a lady by her farm.
Perhaps it would be nice to say hello.
This lady?
I don't understand what this game wants me to do.
I'm trying to find...
So good to see you, sweetheart.
Can you help me?
What can I do for you, ma'am?
My brother is working abroad.
He should have been back home a week ago, but he's still busy working.
I need one of my fields plowed and cultivated.
Will you do it for me, please?
Use that old plow over there by the barn.
You can keep it when you're done.
All right.
I'll do it.
My brother plans on buying a new one anyway.
I can keep this.
Okay.
I'm going to keep this.
I get a new thing.
No promises, but I'll see what I can do.
All right.
The quest is being fought.
I need to work on Clara's field.
It's here, but...
Okay.
Let's mark it.
It's already being marked.
Do I need my truck for this?
I think I need to back my truck into that.
Yeah.
I got to back up my truck into that.
I got to get my truck.
These wheels are off the ground.
Sorry about that.
Okay.
Back the truck up into this.
Somehow.
Other way?
You can't do this with a truck?
Attach.
Didn't I try to go in here?
Oh, shit.
There's no tractor in here, you guys.
There's nothing in here.
Where's your tractor?
In my barn?
You fix this and then they give you a tractor.
Wait, I have to just plug the holes?
All right.
I did it.
I can use my farm revision.
Farming is really easy.
Attach the old plow to work.
The quest is being fought.
Complete repairs.
Am I just dumb or do I not have a tractor?
Do I have to get a tractor?
Do I have to fix up the rest of this barn?
Yes.
But you do need a tractor.
Okay.
So you get it from...
All right.
We're going to come back here later.
Oliver first.
I need to repair my own place first.
Is there a horn?
If there's not a horn, it's the worst game.
See you later.
Oh, you both don't like me.
Bye.
All right.
So I need to go...
I need to like save the game first and then like restart with VSync on.
Yeah.
Okay.
There we go.
Saving the game.
Am I good?
All right.
Yeah.
Let me just...
VSync has to be turned on.
This is like killing me.
My credit sucks.
It'll improve very shortly.
No, it's not on.
I have to restart the game.
It'll be turned on.
Here we go.
One, two, three.
You want to leave?
Yes.
Is this like actually an iPad game ad where I accidentally click on yes and take me to
this person's Discord?
That's kind of...
All right.
Whatever.
Let's reopen it and then we can go.
I have to turn on VSync, otherwise the game's going to keep hurting my eyes.
All right.
Load game.
Wait, what's going on here?
Why is this so tiny?
VSync on 1920 by 1080.
What the fuck is this?
Why is this in such a tiny window?
What is going on here?
Why does it look normal for you but look awful for me?
I mean, I'd definitely play it, but why is it in such a tiny...
It's in a small window.
VSync...
What do you mean VSync off?
No.
VSync on 1920 by 1080.
What are you doing?
Windowed off, 1920 by 1080.
Let's go.
Come on.
It's in like a 1200 by...
It's like a 720 window on my desktop.
What the fuck is this?
Okay.
Is it doing this shit again?
Why is it in a window?
I have no idea what's going on.
Save the settings.
What do you mean save the settings?
Alt-Enter.
All right, we're good.
All right, let's go.
No family, pretty good condition.
I'm ready to go.
That was fucked up.
There's no save settings.
Guys, there's no save settings.
You have to restart the game to have your settings take place.
Did that help?
Yeah, it did.
All right, let's go back to...
Where are we going?
We're trying to go to Oliver.
Fix Oliver's barn.
All right, that's how you mark it.
I get it.
Let's go.
Am I running out of gas?
Why am I going so slow?
That's a huge bird.
That bird was like 10 feet tall.
All right, Oliver, what do you need?
I'm here to fix your barn.
Yuck.
Did use a lot of work, Oliver.
All right, Oliver, I'm here.
I don't know what's going on this way, but can I pick that up?
All right, we've got it.
Oof, broken.
I'll fix it.
That's that.
Up there, too.
Can I reach?
Of course I can.
What's that Minecraft hack that just builds in like 10, 15 blocks ahead of you?
How do I...
I've got to get on the roof and fix this roof.
Oh, Oliver.
All right, we've got to get on the roof.
Scaffolding time.
Okay, let's repair this.
Dude, pog, let's go.
Do I get social credit with this?
I wonder what that means.
Steel tractor.
I'm probably going to get one for this.
This is going to take a long fucking time.
Imagine redoing somebody's entire barn, building it back, repairing everything for 50 likes on an Instagram post.
I'm not so sure that's worth it.
Okay, well, that's almost the other side.
Actually, it kind of feels nice to do this.
Is there a third-person mode?
No, of course there isn't.
I'm not even doing my own house.
I drank coffee so I wouldn't fall asleep today.
Well, you've got two factors fighting back and forth.
You've got farming dynasty stream and a bunch of coffee.
You're being pulled in two different directions.
I did it.
Barn fix, talk to Oliver and ask for your reward.
Is it fall damage?
Ooh, I'm going to get that.
That's mine.
Oliver, I fixed the barn.
Looking good and solid.
Thank you.
Now, I don't have much money, but as promised, that John Deere over there is all yours.
It should do well until you can afford a real neutral.
You said the copyrighted name.
I can totally start fieldwork now.
You were supposed to not say the copyright name.
The copyright names are kind of short, but I think I'll need more farming machines.
You should talk to people.
I'm sure a lot of them will have some work for you too.
You'll need a plow, a cedar perhaps, and I've seen a cultivator already on your farm.
Good luck with farming.
I will look around.
Thank you.
I just stole an apple.
Okay, so drive your new Jack Bear tractor.
Cool.
Have you finished your task?
I did.
All right, thanks for the tractor.
Where are you going?
Who is this person, and why are they sprinting?
Not now, sorry.
I'm curious.
I need to know what you're doing.
What?
Where'd he go?
Wait, did he go into the corn?
Oh, shit, he went into the corn.
Uh-oh.
Wait, I probably shouldn't have done this.
There we go.
Thank God I have a map.
Well, that was weird.
All right, give me my tractor.
I can purchase your field.
So I'm just going to end up as a monopoly farm and own everything?
Okay.
You received Jack Bear C and 100 social points.
Cool.
All right, now I can do Clara's job.
That's the one we're going to do now.
Okay, I don't really want to drive this.
This is like driving around a giant unicycle or a giant tricycle.
I don't want to lose social points.
It has four wheels.
That don't matter.
The two in the front maze will be one.
99.
I have to get gas too.
Look at how big this bird is.
Birds aren't that big.
That would think it was like a fucking bald eagle.
All right.
How do I, let me, I got to attach this.
How does it attach?
I've never, I don't know what this thing is.
He's a fucking city slicker.
I don't know what the, I don't know how to do this.
I don't know how, what this thing is.
I know it's like a plow and his blades on it and shit,
but I don't know how that would do.
Why can I not attach this?
Did I have it before?
Oh, okay.
Got it.
Plow Clara's field.
This one here.
How do I use the plow?
Yeah.
You got nothing here, Clara.
When you plow your field, drive over your sand.
What is here?
Am I doing this right?
Oh, wait, wait, lower the machine, lower the machine.
Oh man.
Okay.
Lift the machine.
Wait, I got to do this whole thing.
Oh boy.
Oh shit, I'm tearing up the whole world.
All right.
Let's do this quick.
What do you mean?
There is no quick?
All right.
I almost did one pass.
Now he's going to, I'm going to just like mow in a lawn.
Holy shit.
This is going to take like two hours.
This is going to take so long.
This is going to take like an hour.
This is absolutely nothing.
This is how I mow lawns.
I don't know.
Everybody thinks I'm fucking crazy, but my father used to tell me, son, I want you to
get out there and I want you to mow the lawn.
I'd be like, all right, fine.
And I would just do it like this.
So I would never have to stop moving.
You don't have to stop reverse, go back, stop.
No, I would just go in a circle in a spiral until I got to the very end.
Wait, slow down.
Am I going too fast?
I am going too fast.
Fuck.
Hold on.
Don't go slower.
There we go.
Okay.
What about what?
It's cruise control.
Oh, it just drives it for you.
Good.
I'll do that.
I want to change the camera too.
Let's like relax.
That's way better.
All right.
Now I can actually see what the fuck I'm doing.
Right now, they're all in the house preparing dinner, looking out the window at this.
And they're just like, no, no, just let him do it.
Let him do it that way.
I mean, don't go out there and like correct him.
He's kind of a weirdo.
Just let him do his thing.
What's going on over there every time?
Why can I not do that turn?
What's wrong with me?
I got plenty of gas.
I have 95%.
What's the issue here?
What do I keep doing?
Shit.
All right.
I'll get it.
I'm just going backwards.
Can you go backwards in a plot like this?
No.
Yeah.
But this is, this really is a scenario where somebody would just burst out their fucking
back door and be like, Jeremy, Jeremy, Jeremy, Jeremy, stop, stop, stop it.
Stop, stop, stop, stop.
And it's like, what?
What?
Stop.
Get off.
Get off the fucking tractor.
I'd be like, what's going on?
What's the matter?
I'd be really kind of nervous and like kind of sad.
Like what?
What's what's what's happening?
Get off.
Just go home.
Thank you.
I appreciate the help.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
But just get off.
I can't do it.
Yes, I can.
Back left wheel.
All right.
I'm going to just, here we go.
I have a new plan.
I can't use my old lawn mowing technique.
Does it matter if you just like go over, you are getting hungry.
Okay.
I have to eat.
Just go over there and eat.
Can I just like walk over there?
Does it?
All right.
I'm hungry.
Lunch break.
Exit.
Do I have any food?
Oh, an apple.
Here we go.
Your condition.
Food.
Your condition depends on both eating and sleeping.
I don't know how to feel and work better.
Food, 44, sleep, 63.
What do you mean sleep?
All right.
Unhitched it.
Oops.
They're looking out the window again.
Yeah.
He unhitched it.
I just, I mean, that thing was expensive.
I just don't want him to break it.
I'm going to go out there.
I know I shouldn't go out there, but I'm going to go out there.
I think he, oh, he got it.
He got it.
Okay.
I just don't want him to break it.
Honey, I don't want him to break it.
Right.
There's an argument going on in that, in like the living room over here.
It's all my fault.
Let me get this little section.
Why is it so hard for me to do this?
Because this thing turns.
This thing, it's hard to control.
It's not, it's, it's hard.
It's like, it's hard to turn on a dime.
Look, it takes me a full, whatever.
I don't care.
Wait, press R so I can turn better.
Dragon the whole time.
All right.
They're not going to be able to grow shit in this.
Look at this.
Look at how bad that looks.
Oh, this does not look good.
This is a coloring book that you gave a four year old.
At least I'm staying inside the lines, but inside the lines is a joke.
Strokes go in two or three different ways.
I'm almost done.
Look at how bumpy it is.
It's so bumpy over there.
It's not smooth at all.
I've made dunes.
Oh, this is very, very bad.
Do I get in trouble if it's a bad job?
Or is this a game not smart enough to tell me that I did a bad job?
I can't get this last trip.
Wait, quest updated.
To cultivate field, go for your own harrow.
You'll find it by your barn.
What do you mean cultivate?
This is not cultivating.
What is this doing?
This is plowing.
All right.
No, I got to get that last piece.
I have to.
It's going to kill me.
I'm sorry, guys.
But yes, city boy, city boy, lol, omega lol.
Sure.
You can do your omega lols.
If I grabbed my fucking 80-year-old grandfather and I said, hey, grandpa, have you ever played
a video game before in your life?
No, not at all.
Hey, beat Dark Souls right now in front of me.
He'd be like, I don't even understand what this is.
What?
I'm not city boy.
I've never driven a plow before in my life.
I don't even know what this thing is.
Let's grind up the pavement.
No, no, not the sunflowers.
Those are expensive.
What does it want me to do?
What the fuck am I supposed to do with this?
These are medieval torture devices.
Honestly, if you had lined these up, right?
Let's just say, for instance, that I had you blindfold, you take me to a space, you go
to a warehouse and you show me that on the ground.
I'm going to think, oh, what is that?
I'm going to say, oh, that's they put people on that in the medieval times and they like
stretched them out and like stabbed them and shit.
I wouldn't know what the hell this was.
All right.
I need to attach that.
You have fixed.
You have fixed your garage.
Congratulations.
Your neighbors appreciate your work.
You received 5000 points.
Somebody fixed my garage for me and they didn't have the heart to tell me.
All right.
I'm fucking up all my weed.
How do I drop this thing?
Drop it.
Is this mine?
Why would they put it here?
People are just doing chores for me.
I think people feel bad for me.
All right.
Now bring it back.
Go back to Clara and cultivate her field.
Cultivate the pavement.
I'm going.
Can I break these things?
Oh, the noise this would make.
Go around me.
An idiot.
I would put like a little sound board up here and have like choo-choo sounds.
That was a pogchamp moment.
I would not have made it through that.
Do you see how narrow that was?
All right.
Cultivate the field.
I have a new strategy.
It's called go horizontal.
You ready?
Wait, wait.
What the hell am I doing right now?
Am I just redoing the thing?
Is this going back to what I am?
Am I just making it go back the way it was?
Why did you make me do all this?
You're stealing your neighbor's crops.
It's really bad for your socials.
What do you mean cultivating?
This was the exact same way it looked before.
This is the idiot test.
You know that funny business card that somebody pulls out where it says,
this is the idiot test.
Turn around to find the answer.
And then on the other side, this is the idiot test.
And I turn it around five, 10 times.
I idiot.
That's what I'm doing right now.
This is the idiot test business card joke.
I should just go steal all their crops.
Do I care about my social score?
Do I care if I have a bunch of haters?
That's all that means, right?
This is not going as bad.
Do you care about getting arrested?
Okay, the only warning that popped up on my screen was,
hey, some people on social media aren't going to like you anymore.
But here's $700,000 worth of crops.
Oh, you're going to lose like 12 Facebook friends.
But gain a million dollars.
He's fucking calling me.
Is money all that you care about?
No.
It's one of the only things I get.
People won't buy these crops.
Well, then I'll just store them in my silo for when fucking Armageddon happens.
What is this pattern?
I call this pattern late game space invaders.
This pattern is called.
I'm supposed to use this machine on the Wii.
Now, that would be really, really funny if I believed you,
because then I would just drive over it and go,
oh, I'm supposed to be here doing like tilling her wheat.
Right. Okay.
But you're a little late.
I accidentally already drove over a portion of it and it told me stop.
Yeah, this this outfit isn't looks intentional.
Like I'm dressed up to be on this tractor.
Almost done.
Dressed to catch Pokemon.
Lower it. Your character is honestly shit.
Can I join your server to kick your ass?
All right. I better get something good for this because this was like two.
This is two.
Clara seems to be really fond of you.
Got it.
Work done.
You may keep the plow, but you can still talk to Clara.
See if she can teach you something.
Nice.
I don't even need to do the rest.
Who cares?
You received the plow and five hundred social points.
Good.
All right. Let's go to let's go talk to Clara.
Oh, wait, I have to do my have to fix my house.
Where was Clara?
She's over here, right?
This is her farm right here, right?
Oh, lift this up.
All right.
Clara.
What can you teach me?
Getting stuck.
Hey.
Okay.
I thought that was this guy's hair.
For a second, it looked like he had like a weird clown hair.
Okay.
Can I help you, sweetheart?
Sure.
I'm kind of green.
Can you tell me a bit about field work?
Sure.
What do you need to know?
What about seeds?
How do I prepare fields?
How do I gather crops?
Anything more?
What about seeds?
It's best to buy these in the agro store.
You'll get most crops using prepared seeds.
Oh, cool.
Okay.
And fertilizing.
You can buy good fertilizers in the store and spray them on your fields.
Okay.
Let me get this.
But if you have animals, use manure to fertilize fields, too.
Oh, I can get animals?
If you combine these.
I got to go.
No more quests.
I got to go fix my shit.
Use different machines for these, of course.
Thanks.
I'll see you around.
All right.
I have to do the main storyline quest.
No, I'll lose points.
I was going to just take out the whole thing.
I was going to do every single flower.
It was going to be gone.
I can't fucking leave this way.
I want to just ditch it.
I just can't do this GTA style.
When you get stuck, you just run.
Okay.
I'm almost out.
Where's the exit?
Jump it.
I can't jump with this thing.
I have to go all the way out.
Can I take all the...
No.
All right.
Day one is almost done.
I still have to sleep.
Okay.
I almost got it.
That was close.
All right.
Back to home.
You can have animals.
Can I just have an animal farm?
What if I don't want to do crops?
Where's my truck?
I have no idea.
I'm going too fast.
I just have thousands of ducks.
Okay.
That actually sounds like pretty fun.
I'm not sure which garage is the garage I'm supposed to use to park anything.
All right.
Here I am.
I need to repair this barn.
Your animals live here.
Keep this building in good shape so your animals grow healthy.
Are there animals even in here already?
There's no animals even in here.
If they are, this is horrible.
All right.
Let me fix this stuff.
I'm not even going to scrape the extra bits off.
Okay.
Repair the bricks.
Go down here.
Is it supposed to look like that?
Okay.
The door.
What else is he fixing up there?
Can I get it?
I can reach from here.
Good.
The ceiling is fucked.
It still looks like shit.
Can I replace all the brick eventually?
This looks horrible.
I can't even paint it.
There's still a hole here.
Something wrong with the tub?
What's the first animal you guys want?
Duck?
These ducks are going to give you a bad Yelp review.
What is this?
An Airbnb?
Okay.
Is this still fucked up?
Witcher senses.
What is this?
It's more like Hitman, actually.
All right.
I don't even want to get on the roof.
Why use the scaffolding when you can just look up?
That's a lot of info up on that HUD.
Too much info.
Only if it were this easy in real life.
If only.
All right.
How are we doing?
Outside look all right?
I have to get up there with a scaffold.
Where's my scaffold?
How do I remove the scaffolds?
The whole place is going to be covered in scaffolding.
It's going to look terrible.
Can I remove all this rotted wood?
This is the aesthetic.
That's not a good aesthetic.
There's so much work to do here.
I'm not even close.
Is there a watch?
You be a real farmer.
Use the sun.
I mean, it's about to go down.
What happens at night?
Is there any downside to being out here at night?
It doesn't even matter.
Zombies.
You have to kill stuff with a nail gun.
I mean, I'll tell you one thing about this game.
You can say whatever you want.
It doesn't matter what you say.
You could say, oh, this is stupid.
This is great.
Sound is that nail gun sound is fantastic.
It sounds great.
All right.
So this is almost as this dollar done.
Let me use my spider sense.
Slurry tank.
When your animals produce slurry, it's deposed from here to be used as fertilizer.
You need a dedicated spreader for this task.
Wait.
What do you mean?
When my animals produce slurry.
Why do you have to call it slurry?
Just think good to go.
That sounds gross as fuck.
It does because it is.
Oh, man.
This is all rundown.
How many times do I have to do?
OK, not that much more.
And then we get our first animal.
Are they expensive?
I mean, how do you get money?
I have to sell crops and shit.
I don't have any crops.
Get an animal.
All right.
I'm going to buy an animal.
How much is it?
How much is a duck?
Less than 100 bucks.
All right.
This shit is done.
It has to be.
I don't see anything else.
Cows owned.
The whole thing's repaired, right?
Oh, come on.
I think this is cows only.
You fixed your cow shed.
Your neighbors appreciate your work.
You receive 5,000 social points.
Cool.
How do I get a cow?
Do they live here?
Social points.
How do I get a cow?
Hen house.
Your poultry lives here.
Keep this building in good shape.
All right.
I get it.
Hen house.
Your poultry lives here.
Keep this building in good shape.
All right.
I guess I just have to repair everything.
This doesn't have as much damage as the other one.
It's getting dark out.
Yeah.
I don't think it matters.
I truly don't think there are any consequences for not eating and not sleeping.
Almost done with this.
You will die.
You don't die in this game.
They did not program in dying, except in the very beginning when your grandfather died.
That's the only death that's programmed into the game.
So get a roof.
How do we...
Can I put lights in here?
If you don't eat, you're going to lose social points.
That would be actually pretty funny.
What's left?
One more.
One more section and then we can get...
I'm going to go to the store.
I'm going to steal a bunch of crops, sell the crops and then buy some hens.
I think that's the plan here.
What else?
Anything else broken?
Didn't tell me I did it.
Hey, congratulations.
You completed the hen house.
Why?
Oh, because of this.
To sleep in the hen house.
I would if I could.
I probably can.
What is this?
Is that where I can place the hen houses?
I have to buy a hen house then.
All right.
Here we go.
Actual fucking...
Actual thing going to happen on stream.
Can you believe it?
We're going to get a hen tomorrow.
Hen house is almost done and that's it.
Neighbors appreciate it.
Three thousand social points.
What time is it?
What is all this?
Field owner you.
Canola ready for harvest.
Shift plus left click to sell this field.
How much do I get if I sell it?
What am I going to sell on it?
All right.
Complete.
I get to finish the repairs on the house.
How tired am I?
Your condition depends.
So what does this even mean?
Humidity dry.
Animals.
Dogs?
Cats?
Cows?
Hens?
Ducks?
Geese?
Pigeons?
Eggs?
I can get geese?
That's cool.
All right.
I'm just going to go to bed.
I want light.
Where is my bed?
One of these is my house.
Here it is.
Right?
Do I have a bed?
Why do I have two twin beds?
Okay.
Hold on.
Did I just sleep for a week?
Sleep on bed.
Rest for a week.
Am I okay?
I haven't eaten in a week.
Good thing I have a tomato in my inventory.
Start the music again.
All right.
That's my pantry.
Why would you have a pantry in the basement?
I have no idea what that function is for.
Why does that exist?
Why would you have sleep for a week be an option?
What does it do if you get injured?
And by the way, speaking of something, there's like four or five bedrooms in this house.
Can I actually get a family in here?
Look at all these rooms.
There's a seesaw.
I'll fix that seesaw.
I'm getting married too.
Oh, you thought we were going to play this game for like 10 minutes.
Wow.
You were so wrong.
That couldn't have been more incorrect.
All right.
Is the roof all right?
Do not misunderstand me.
We will never play this game ever again after probably the next day or so, but I ain't playing
this for 10 minutes.
All right.
What about the outside?
Oh, it's in fucking shambles.
Go harvest your crops.
I don't have any crops.
This is the game wants me to, I don't have any children with multiple slides.
Rusty metal.
I'm just shaving down the rusty metal.
Just buy a new one.
How much are these?
How much is a seesaw?
Like it can't be more than like 30 bucks, 40 bucks.
Repair of the old wood.
Oh, this is like dangerous.
Just get a new one.
Replace the sand in here.
This is fucking gross.
There's like shards of glass in here.
Make sure you repair the rotten wood.
Can you, can I push somebody on the slide eventually?
Wow.
That would be so cool.
This is my farm.
This is my house.
Ain't nobody going to take this from me until the storyline dictates when it should happen.
But for now, it's mine.
Wait till we have an Oliver, Oliver's going to turn on me.
Highly doubt it.
Air bricks.
Can't reach it.
Better get a scaffolding.
But let's check the outside bed.
Sleeping regularly helps you maintain good health and energy for work.
Combine sleep with good food.
You might miss job opportunities when hungry and tired.
Or for sleeping for a full week.
I think that's the easiest way to miss an opportunity.
I don't think that has to do with if I'm hungry today.
You can use it to turn basic foods into canned ones.
A wife can cook delicious treats.
I don't have a wife.
You're losing food from the pantry.
Who's this imaginary wife that I have?
Do I need to get married?
I just got here.
I don't know any of these fucking people.
All right.
We're almost at the, I have to go all the way up really.
That looks worse than like it did before.
How's the outside?
All right.
Time to go up to the second floor.
That's a gigantic chimney.
You can cut that in half.
It would still be fine.
It's a Minecraft house chimney.
That's too big.
Let's get up.
Hey.
Do I have a well?
Can I get water out of the well?
Look at all this other shit I have to repair.
Can I not go up?
Shit.
I gotta go this way.
Delete the scaffolding.
All right.
Let's get up there.
Repair and another scaffolding.
God damn it.
Am I going to play Half-Life Alex on stream?
Probably not.
I mean, no, I don't think so.
No, I don't.
I mean, no, it's just probably one of the largest technological VR jumps in technology
and gaming and the history of virtual reality headsets.
I probably will play a free to play horror game that somebody made in three days next
time or a unity farmer game.
You don't know this is made in unity.
How do you know that?
How do you know this is made in unity?
You don't know.
How do you know?
It's not unity.
This is a proprietary engine that was crafted in-house.
For all you guys know, this could be better than the frostbite engine.
This runs better than frostbite engine.
So yeah.
All right.
We got I got to get in there.
The second floor is having problems.
Oh, my shins.
Don't worry.
Dad's okay.
Dad will be fine.
Upstairs.
What do you mean dad?
Question mark.
Who the fuck do you think I am in this scenario?
How would I not be dad?
I'm the only one here.
It's me, dad.
This one piece that's just broken somewhere and I'm never going to find it.
There it is.
Oh, fuck off with this.
Where is it?
It's the door.
Where is the problem?
What's the issue here?
What happens if I just sleep for a week?
Like a hundred times in a row?
Do we just teleport like 10 years in the future?
It's sleep.
Should I sleep for like 200 years and see what happens?
There's a chest.
Fish.
I thought it was a chainsaw.
Fish in aroma oil.
I don't think this is something you would take out of this chest.
You would throw this away, but I'm going to eat it.
But before I eat it, I need to like make a, I have to turn on my YouTube channel video.
I have to, yeah, I have to like videotape me doing this.
All right.
That's it.
Right?
What else is left to repair in the house?
There's nothing else here to fix.
Help me out here.
The fences outside.
Does that count as the house?
Did I miss a room?
I did.
Yeah.
All right.
This thing that I don't understand though, is this, all this stuff is like shitty.
Even if I, I want this different wallpaper.
Use the kitchen.
Applesauce.
Cookbook recipes.
What about honey based recipes?
Eggs.
Hot sauce.
Unknown.
Egg based.
I don't know any of these.
There's food here though, somehow.
I have to, it's the fence outside that's doing it.
Are you sure?
You might be right.
I kind of want to save the game and then sleep like fucking a hundred times and just skip
every cut scene and see if we can like teleport 10 years in the future.
See if the world changes at all.
Get a family first.
Yeah.
Let's get a family.
Let's have a wife, have a kid and then sleep for 30 years and see if the kid grows up.
That's not a bad play.
I like that play.
There is nothing else to fix over here.
Why have I not gotten any social points for this?
I'm going to piss my pants.
I'll be right back.
Pretty good condition.
No families.
11,000 points.
All right.
I'll be right back.
I'm going to pee my pants if I don't get the fuck out of here.
Right back.
I'm back.
I'm going to do this thing now where when I come back, I don't just go like this because
it means I'm gone for three minutes straight.
Hey, I'm back.
It's like, Jesus.
So I'm going to slowly be like, Hey, I'm back.
Okay, let's go.
All right.
The goal here is find a family and then try to artificially age them all by like 10 years.
Well, that's going to be such a waste of time.
You know how long that's going to take.
Game sucks.
Play Half-Life Alex.
Yeah.
So I'm just going to play this until Half-Life Alex comes out.
That's what you're saying, right?
Like, yeah, game sucks.
Like you should transition over to Half-Life Alex.
Yeah.
So in four months or five months, I'll just do this for five months.
That's what you want.
All right.
Game save.
Let's go.
Just got to fix some more stuff.
I'm into it right now.
I'm into this.
I need to see this through.
Harvest the wheat.
Get mad bucks.
I need to find out why this is not done.
Is there something on the roof I missed?
You've earned no money.
It's not all about the money.
Okay.
It's not about the money.
Sometimes it's about just having fun and relaxing and making a farm.
It's always about money with you guys.
Money, money, money.
You should make more money.
I'm always about how I want to just do something because I want to.
It's the basement.
Is it the basement?
That's such a huge fall and it's funny that it didn't happen.
No, there's nothing in here that's broken.
Nothing in here.
Damn it.
What is the one little thing that's wrong?
The well?
There's one tiny thing wrong with this house that I can't figure it out.
Hold on.
Is there no bathroom in this house?
We don't have a bathroom.
Why is there not a bathroom in the house?
It's a huge, huge issue if this is going the outhouse.
There is no outhouse.
Are we just supposed to shit into the well?
All right.
Well, I don't know what's wrong with it.
Is the gazebo broken?
No, this is normal.
It's ugly, but it's normal.
Grain storage.
Okay.
I have to make some money.
Dog house.
How do I get a dog?
I still don't understand what...
Wait, there it is.
I see it.
No, I don't.
What's the problem?
I've got to get up there before I delete this because there's a scaffolding all over the
damn house.
All right.
Delete it.
I don't want scaffolding on my house.
Follow the arrow.
What do I have for a mission?
Complete repairs on your farm.
I have this fucking dumb place.
God, this is going to be great.
Great.
Is it a balcony window?
I'll check it out in a minute.
We're not going to get a family unless I make this place a home.
I'm not going to impress anybody that comes over here if it's the exact same thing as
if to take somebody to like an old abandoned hospital.
Yeah.
You want to see where I live?
Let's go to you.
Let's go to your house.
Yeah.
Sure.
Come on over here.
Cool.
Yeah.
We're pulling up now.
What do you think?
What do you think about my old fucking haunted house YouTube channel?
Abandoned hospital.
Let's walk through it.
It has to look at least okay.
What is this?
Grain storage?
All right.
There's a lot of stuff I need to know.
What is all this?
Okay.
Stop.
Stop getting distracted.
That's the only thing only.
That's the only thing I need to do right now.
That's it.
Nothing else.
Repair only.
Make sure I save the game there too.
That would be such a painful disaster if this is like my I have my own gas station.
You have your own gas station on a farm.
I pull shit in there to pump my own tank.
That's kind of cool.
I got to get up.
Get up top.
I got to get all the way up though.
Yeah.
There we go.
Sit.
Shit all right.
He says sit.
Sit.
It's not so bad getting up top in the middle.
Now, I don't want you to put me up top either, I don't want you out the bat.
All right, I'll mark this, I'll mark this.
I'm going to go on top of it.
I'm going to go on top of the camera man.
I'm going to try to make that count for a while or whatever.
I lost until m we're gonna get close to the wall which is the goal.
That was great.
Let's go.
Go.
real estate video game where you like buy build dress and sell a house don't
that's my idea that's my idea let it be known here at first the no not like a
tycoon game where you just put down monopoly buildings no I'm talking about
like you build with wood you build the houses and you do it the way you want oh
this one's gonna have a basement this one's gonna have an attic this one's
gonna have look at this big open concept in the living room you and you
did you design it you decorate it you put the furniture in and you sell it so
yeah minecraft but not blocks but real and you can't sell real estate in
Minecraft that's not minecraft what are you talking about so real life yes guys
like real life I'm gonna spend three four five hundred thousand dollars on a
built building no I want to be able to do it in fake life so I don't have to
spend any money what else needs to be repaired that but all right do I got
everything on the roof I think so which builds a house there's no way that would
work you know I thought of a stream a while back there actually this is during
the house flipper streams I was thinking about it would it be funny if I were to
try to actually like redecorate it like a house in real life just an open floor
with paint and stuff just put up like put up make build like three or four
artificial rooms and then decorate them and take you through it okay that's do
I think that's done oh fuck hello there's so many repairs to do they would
take too much effort ah it would take a lot of prep but I don't think it would
be too big all I would need to do is just put up like a wood and then just
have like some drywall just just make like a fake room in like a studio be at
beyond studio and have like three small rooms made that can have like couches
and furniture and stuff in them like a TV show set yeah that's I'm saying it
wouldn't be like a full house it would be like the Seinfeld set but I would
just have to decorate it and paint it dollhouse the German dollhouse have
multiple floors and what's just weird the camera zooms out I like walk up the
stairs I get into the bed oh this is comfy that would be real-life sims
god damn do I have to actually write this one down imagine if I made a
fucking dollhouse cut in half sort of like set and you guys just played the
sims but it was just me in a house that would be really really creepy that would
be scary in a way because I would be acting like a sim I wouldn't be
speaking English or anything I'd be talking like sim and you guys have to
tell me what to do I would be speaking simlish and waving at you guys and
stuff doing the thing we're like I'm gonna fucking shit my pants and like you
got I go I won't go I just pee on the floor and stuff that oh my god I have I
think we might have to do this you'll have bars underneath I'll have to go get
a job I wonder if you guys can handle that and if I leave the house or lie
down to go to bed we just do like a fake it's going times 10 speed so we'll just
go to the next day and I'll like shake around like it's going fucking 10 times
speed in the bed I gotta be careful I don't tell you every joke that I'm gonna
do oops all right we're good how are you gonna deal with the fires
set is burning down and I'm just jumping up and down going ah so so oh yeah
that's also ah I'm getting like burnt install mods no cooking I would have
skills that would be the only time where I would even remotely know that I
couldn't even do it though I couldn't do it what is that you found a string
trimmer now you can cut grass oh nice no breaks like 24-hour stream type shit
but I can't do it I couldn't do it I can't do it 24 hours I just can't do it
I physically can't plus I ain't going to the bathroom like in that dollhouse
no no way maybe I would artificially go to the bathroom all right honest to God
what else is broken I see something in there yeah and my job would I mean I
would make money and we could you could purchase stuff oh man I'll just have a
bunch of like random fucking furniture that you guys can buy and just moved
into the house you've got yeah you can do buy mode and just put stuff in the
house can I reach it nope all right put a lid on this put a lid on this okay we
never talked about this did it all right the barn is fixed what else do I have to
do now fleet repairs on your home is it really more shit to do am I sure I can
handle a real job I handled students okay I was I was a goddamn teacher you
don't think I can handle that if I can handle all the kids like screaming and
oh I can handle what is the last thing I need to fix in this fucking stupid town
this is a town this is not even a this is a town what am I missing this music
is way too epic this I don't like this it needs to be slower and music to pump
in like Sims music I'm going to be a moron on this stream too like I know you
like that anyways no I'm talking like sim I'm only gonna go where you tell me
to go it's not the basement I just was down there what's wrong with this house
what did I miss what are the repairs door there's no bathroom in this house
you can't tell me I missed the bathroom something happened to me and I can't
explain what it was it just sucks ah life sucks right this second I found it
there is a bathroom in this house no that's not there's just a bathtub where's
the how do you go to the bathroom what is this is this a urinal do you just poo
down the drain this is still something to repair okay the house is what do else
do I need to repair all right I gotta turn this music down it's giving me
fucking anxiety I'm scanning everything I already did all that the grain place
now damn it this stupid thing this whole thing needs to be fixed very clearly I'm
just repainting this honestly the inside of this looks like a silent hill good
this town is making him stupid um are you sure it's not all the rust I'm
breathing in I don't want to get on scaffolding I have to get on the damn
scaffolding don't I fine get on it let's go
farmer's destiny sure did turn into be farmer repairs a whole town this is your
farm I'm not I'm not farming anything I'm scraping rust off of metal what do I
get to have corn in my inventory look at how fucked up this whole thing is this
is so labor-intensive just get a helicopter and like airlift it off my
property remember this is gonna be a mayonnaise stream if I can make mayonnaise
it definitely will happen he's just snorting rust I can't help it look I'm
going as fast as I can there is no tool upgrade for me right now they might they
might be tools at the store that are better than this I doubt it though lying
about mayonnaise if it's positive I don't know what I can make I'm just
trying to get the next request all right that's good just but I need to get that
okay everything on top done yes now gotta go inside whoo this see that's
where they store the seeds okay pick up metal oh metal what this that takes
longer than shaving it do I have to do this to every single one please go farm
I I can't until I do this I have to do this first next iPad game no I'm staying
here I want to see what happened we just have to deal with the paint your whole
entire town again once it's done it's done and then we can move on it trust me
it's gonna be worth it we're gonna make corn wheat I'm gonna get beans quick
refunded it's like I've been playing for two hours it's not gonna happen it's
over I'm not gonna why would I do that anyways no I want to be rewarded for my
labor because it's you don't know that it sucks yet we haven't gotten that far
yet I'm almost just just bear with me for a
minute you're on the tutorial yes I am just wait till I get my own seeds that's
not exciting what I'm gonna pretend it is there are yeah there are seeds in
here this is the first strand type game what are you talking about this is the
best way you to pretend to work how's it going out there that's going good I'm
just uh shooting compressed air into a board of sheet metal if there was like
60 people on this job I could blend in pretty quickly all right see that didn't
take as long as you thought it was going to done almost you're a movie extra
yeah why is everything to be the same color why is everything great the okay
though everything's just metal what what does that do oh I'm just shooting water
all over me I probably shouldn't have electricity in here well I'm hungry on
our now it's gonna get all rusty again no it won't we'll be fine let me just
replace all of these Silent Hill hospital beds will be good and then I
can finally start to make my farm I am making my farm reusing jokes I said
that I told that joke like nine minutes ago it's still relevant I can still what
re-use it's not like been six days it's been like four minutes I haven't even
got off the stage yet you fix your greenhouse congratulations thank you all
right seeds what we got use tomato seeds use tomato seedlings store all right
tomato seeds how many do I have ooh okay now what do I do how do I keep them
alive need water okay hold on but how much water does a tomato need why would
you stand inside why wouldn't you put this on the outside this seems like the
dumbest mistake ever too much tomatoes and 90% water I'm gonna keep it at
comfort instead of wet all right that's good how long did they take to grow okay
cool nice I got seeds in there now don't say I'm not doing anything you're wrong
this is still something to repair okay I didn't repair everything in here did I
the silo thank you thank you get it it's not it there's more which roof this
roof I need to get up and see all roofs okay I can see all the roofs from here
nothing's glowing I thought that was it but it's not where is this where's this
last thing to repair all right can I make the jump nice okay fucking break
inside the building with the fuel nothing over here right all right
inside the fuel building yeah the greenhouse is done what about in here
fuel tanks the greenhouse roof no greenhouse is done I already got the
reward for it grain duster what is it all right where is this oh god damn it
it's right here 20,000 social points I did it it's all done finally no more
quests now now what do I do drone race new quest new quest fix one of the
buildings new quest transport I'm gonna go to my fields anyway I don't know I'm
gonna go to the store where's the store general store right where's my truck is
that my truck now my truck is over here all right we're gonna go gent truck
general store and we're gonna find ourselves a wife steal your neighbor's
crops yeah I feel like that was like three days ago this mine wait this is
already done this is mine how do I harvest it will this harvest it no no
don't don't don't stop don't don't don't are you sure this doesn't harvest it
which what harvest it do I even have the thing to harvest it is that a harvester
like will this work this is no this is like a tiller use a fire I need it it's
a different tool all right well fuck it we're gonna go get it it's a different
vehicle so I just got like thousands of dollars worth of stuff that I can't sell
because I can't get it I need to hire a worker we'll go to town and find a
worker I need money though I don't have any money so here's the problem I I can't
go get my truck because if I get my truck then I'm gonna leave my John Deere
if I leave my John Deere I can't get the harvester I can't get the harvester I
have to transfer back and forth running is probably faster than this it's not as
stylish though yeah but it's really slow I wish there was a wave button Ram we
already tried it you just stopped like two dead bricks yeah run this guy runs
guy I've already tried to run this guy over so I'm sorry good to see you John
yes I'd like to trade care to trade sure what do you need I need perfume I don't
have how do I have zero dollars zero string trimmer mow grass a shovel I'm
gonna drone a headlamp look at what's with all these chocolates get a fishing
pole I'm gonna keep the string trimmer no I don't want to sell anything I just
take food from behind the counter oh well now what do I do goodbye ready for
harvest click to hire worker hire the world wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait I don't have any money plow the field and cultivate sow wheat I don't
have enough money to do this I'm selling okay here take the chainsaw back good to
see you can I hear I only used it once sure what do you need take it okay let's
get a worker can what about this dog can they can I keep the dog somehow all
right hire worker to which one harvest and sell right you have just hired
worker to harvest your field and sell the crops he's driving to the field and
we'll start working shortly all right cool is he on my map there he is let's
go I want to go see what he does make sure he actually works and I take his
vehicle what you guys don't understand is why'd you just hire that worker well
I paid $490 for a brand new truck holy shit here he comes there he goes how do
I get one of these look at the money whoa 300 $400 $500 look inside that's
one row I'm gonna have tons of money now and watch this ready whoa wait where's
my other where's the other one don't hit me what's on this other one nothing all
right harvest and sell this shit too now I got two workers have fun all right
now I'm just gonna have money generated forever it's gonna take that guy like
three hours to do all this plant more wheat in its place I will I will let me
check on my tomatoes it's been like not even a half a day how they're doing what
the fuck hurry up they're not dead they're fine all right should I use the
beard trimmer on these this looks like shit all right I'm gonna do this
grind it done grind it done looks much better this shit's overgrown guys what
about the flood that kid I'll get new floors don't worry wait why don't you
just run this over with the tractor with the grinder on it will that do the same
thing turn with the water the water what about what do you mean the water what's
wrong with the water cleaner the tomatoes are gonna die fine you're
flooding the greenhouse I'm not flooding the greenhouse what check it check it
check and I'm going what's wrong what what's the matter with you guys like a
five grand is it effective if I just walk not really go buy a drone no that
would be such a waste of money I want to buy a new field and plant crops not go
the first paycheck I get go buy a drone holy shit I want to know he was right
there you didn't get it all two workers nice job guys let's test your reflexes
not bad so wait do somebody said do I want do I want Chinese food yeah well
that sounds good gotta be real hungry after a whole day working in the farm
they're out of place though I have to get rid of these no I could definitely
like hot can I hire somebody to pull the lawn all right tomatoes are fine I mean
it looks like shit but what am I gonna do I need a better tool all right back
to the all right now I can go get the drone all right drone time so why am I
doing this guy's yard work for this is not even my this is like public property
why am I doing this all right I've got money whatever what do you got good to
see you can I help you where can I buy a vehicle where can I buy vehicles you
can buy new ones in the vehicle store but these are very expensive you can
also talk to people you know lots of them have some old equipment that's like
eight-year-old logic they will share for some work or food where can I buy
vehicles at the vehicle store oh that makes sense I mean it is a store that
sells vehicles what do you have here to trade sure what do you need just give me
everything you have who cares I'll take your whole without proper watering your
flowers may die get it rake you're destroying the economy wait seeds two
lips Zinnia gourmet eggs gourmet recipe one egg what a recipe that is seeds
flowers okay tomato flower fish seeds pumpkin seeds fucking up the whole
economy this guy's got nothing left you're gonna have to close the store
there's nothing there thanks for everything goodbye okay now I want to
see a drone let's use it how do I go up shift this is a powerful fucking drone I
could move trucks with it oh Jesus I went under the car wait go annoy the
workers yeah I want to hold on we have was a science here I'm gonna get this
fucking thing I'm gonna get this motherfucker I'm taking him up to the
stratosphere when I get him it's actually a hard to control this it
floats around I'll get it bigger car this one I gotta use two hands on the
keyboard for this not the mouse I swear I'm trying to get it you get on your
phone and call the police I'm trying kids hard to get under him oh he's
freaking out perfect opportunity all right good perfect he's slightly raised
ready we have to go up then we have to go down and then under got it almost
almost almost slow down slow down slow down it's so it's so hard to do this
but I have to get it let's come in from the front I gotta go under I gotta
balance it too that's the other thing lift it or no I'm trying there's a lot
of momentum with it that I got see right I'm not pressing any it's kind of it's
very very floaty I'm doing my best oh it's close it's close here we go we got
liftoff I got him he's too heavy he's too heavy it's too heavy it's too heavy
drop it on my head oh no let me drop it on my head first
just he's looking out the window all right all right slow down oh shit can
it look people with it hold on I'll try that in a second this is a perfect
opportunity damn it all right last attempt put it on the roof after I am
oh almost see the issue is so right now this is where I have to be when I hold
shift see I'm holding shift right now you bounce right back up see I'm not
pressing any buttons it's just doing it let's see if I see what I mean it's like
I even if you hold shift an attack of the giant bee I can't believe I got it
that one time it's so close again well this guy's never okay I'm gonna
teleport like 10 years in the future and see if he's still here fuck I have to
get it one more time I don't care how long it takes you know it's dark too so
no he got out he got away wait is that an animal what is this thing this is a
big it's a wild hog new project a new project get wild hog he's so fast is
you know did I get him where is he is he on top of me no he's not is he I killed
them all right I have my fun no you can't I need the faster drum I'm so
addicted to like trying to grab people with this thing this dude turns his
lights on at least all right there's a big truck last attempt last try no fuck
okay stand over here it's a bugle very driving the car I might need the racing
drone for this all right racing drone how much money do I have I'm busy I did
this all day wait what what I just do Rex is fond of you what did I do what I
give him that does get a dog what I feed him a sausage where's he going now wait
don't I have a lamp be careful crossing the street careful crossing the street
dog Rex no Rex run let's go go on yeah I got a new dog you have a dog house too
over here right let's go come on what does the dog do do you know what the
dog house is because I don't know what's he doing he smells something I have to
go to bed shut the gate oh right can I not sprint with the helmet on why all
right we're safe now ready to go dog dog I thought that was a lion well he'll be
all right the hell was that I'm gonna eat I get to eat I'll eat a sausage I'll
eat two grilled sausages and then apples this is a unity flashlight I don't think
okay turn off the helmet what else did I get a rake cool all right it's a new day
I'm gonna go plant all those seeds I'm gonna check on my tomatoes the dog is
actually gone that's sad I closed the gate and everything so how the tomatoes
doing we're good comfortable you take forever okay use still I don't have any
where my seeds seeds of a lovely Dahlia flower prepared garden soil planted in
the garden in a garden okay I got sixty two hundred bucks I'm gonna sell this
drone and then get the faster one I need my truck just go get it it's down here
oh my fields have all been okay now I want you to I want with my workers I
want you to I want you to do everything for me so what do I want to do what
should I do here peas soy grass fertilize plow and cultivate right you
plow this out plow that field and then I want you to plow this field what's
wrong I can't why can I not hire a worker here because you fucking left
something didn't you look at this what am I what am I paying you for is this
just to be a dick to me I'm not collecting these oh cool all right go
plow my field and I'll see you later how you gonna plow my field with that okay
he's wish was was my command he's got a retractable okay let's let's tell one
thing technique quick everybody laughs cuz he can't make the turn everybody
laughs ah he didn't do it he can't make it he sucks at the game what was that
turn he sucks see oh shitty turn he's terrible it's not that easy where am I
going over here on my truck okay that's a lot of social points to lose I just
lost a lot why was that costing me money wait wait wait wait wait what do you
mean where's my money where's my money like the HUD all right back to the store
I'm living in such a small world right now look at how much there is I'm just
staying here I won't leave the tutorial zone there's so many things going on
Janet okay I'm gonna talk to Janet after this that's the next step okay he got it
he got it he got it now if he missed any I was gonna say well now they do it do
you gonna make fun of that guy he's programmed to do it correct you know
guys I'm not even driving the car I'm moving the chassis I'm not turning the
wheel the chassis of the car is moving it's not anything to both has nothing to
do with the wheels hey I gotta talk to you yes you can help me I would love to
trade how's your stock looking sure what do you need damn this guy filled
up quick again okay super drone 4400 what do you what will you take for one
of these drones what about how much is it 7400 what about a trimmer will you
take one of these about a what do I need 1400 silver rings 64 I'm not even close
give me those back fuck sorry I have the gold ones I okay I'm gonna start
stealing crops how do you steal crops you lose money if you steal crops what
kind of what does that even mean how all right Janet what do you want
Jenny you have a harvester I'm avoiding them look steal money not plants all
right where's Janet everybody okay hi Janet but first let me go into your
house first no I can't it's fake hi mr. I'm Janet have we met not yet I'm your
neighbor I live just across that lake moved in not long ago hey we just moved
in to bought this farm and greenhouses to start a tomato business tomatoes I
love tomatoes I feel cheated the greenhouses are a ruin I guess I can
help you restore these can you know that would be so great but I don't have
much money to pay you what about that harvester over there I think it's worth
the effort I can take it for an exchange this sounds great we have no use for it
anyway we wish to plant tomatoes don't own any fields but the one I just drove
over in this case I'm on it I will fix your greenhouses in exchange for that
harvester what about the barn over there can you fix it too I'll add the
headers to sweeten the deal sure I could definitely that's a lot of work that's
too much I'll do a lot of work but it's worth it have you finished your task
not this again I have to do this again no all right just I'm gonna do it as
fast I can no this sucks I don't want to do this I want to plant I am actually
having fun but I don't want to do this scrape the metal again I just got over
this this is actually much faster all right I'm gonna do this and I'm gonna
instantly propose and we'll see if it works I need to have a child I need a
kid my claw the clock is ticking what do you mean the clock is ticking just buy a
cow right I need to get animals okay I'll do this later I'll finish this
another day I need to buy animals but I'm doing minimal amount of work by the
way I don't care if I don't oh what about that little spot no don't care
okay just the roof stand up on these boomer vision how's that boomer vision
like cuz he's holding a tool in his hand good all right I should have just said
fuck that is too much work boomer C and sepia tone that it okay now what you
want this yeah what I'm done have you finished your task fix the barn fuck I
forgot I said I agreed to do this was that a cell phone tower wait there's a
cell phone tower in her backyard you got 5g there's a 5g tower here I'm gonna
start hallucinating I can't reach that is this the harvester this thing's a
piece of shit it's broken why do I feel like if I look at this tower in real
life if I was standing right here and I went like this it would go I'm afraid of
those things as it is it weird that I think that I feel like those things give
you bad dreams it's just like mmm humming like next to your house it's
probably gonna give you fucking nightmares you're gonna wake up with
like a metal taste in your mouth are you also suspicious of chemicals like that
chemtrails wait what happens we get to 6g we're gonna be careful we'll get to
6g you'll sneeze and your brain will end up like shaking back and forth and like
knocking yourself out from the microfibrations you just need to do the
but wait am I if I just fucking not paying attention and fixing up there a
whole entire townhouse thing here I'm fixing everything I'm not supposed to
be doing this okay just the alright you're gonna get a nosebleed I have to
this is not even high enough I'm gonna leave the scaffoldings because I don't
care you can take those down well those carrots wait you can plant carrots in
this game and I haven't I haven't even started doing it yet I'm just fixing
people's roofs and shit like I want to build I want to put carrots in the
ground what you're destroying crops that grow harvest the crops before you grow
what are they talking about I got a good view of my farm at the
time of my farm what's my worker doing what's he doing over here why is he all
the way over here are there binoculars can you climb the tower let's find out
use the drone all right that's sick I sold the drum I don't have it anymore
almost done we've got one more panel to put on and then maybe Joseph will throw
a carrot to us what else is left here oh come on all right quest done sorry can I
have one what the hell are those all right let's go back and talk to Janet
Janet hi I did what you asked did I agree to this plant tomatoes in the
hen house I know seriously what the hell was this even for I'm not gonna use this
shit this should be mine I want this it's mine now okay all right now will you
marry me all right I just got to fix the ceiling and then not tights time to
propose got it after this you and I where I'm gonna propose to you and we're
gonna be we're gonna have a nice happy family clean my gutters while you're at
it oh and by the way can you also go I'm gonna post mates McDonald's but can you
just go get it for me yeah sure sure so after this and then what she's she's a
real one if she orders McChicken I can't disagree with that all right let's keep
this up this would take so this would take months to do for your broken
tractor in the backyard this is this is two or three months of work all right
close we can do a shit job who cares fast and I'm stealing all the seeds that
she has whatever they are you know any seeds what about what happened to I'm
weird tomatoes I do tomatoes for the love of God I really hope I don't have to do
anything after this just give me the thing so I could do my own shit the
art the best part about this is the fact that this is this right here is by far
like the most tedious thing in the game and I just did I just did this to my own
house it took like an hour and a half to do this and now it's hey let's do a
quest all right let's go talk to Janet do that again but do it to my house
there's anybody gonna put me on a mission to like hey I would like 20
carrots no shave my metal house that it's no not it all right this is gonna
be it the next person that wants me to fix their whole entire living space I'm
gonna say no and I don't care I will buy the vehicle finally there you go Janet I
did everything Janet she's got the fuck out of me that's fantastic the
harvester and header are all yours I can also sell you the seedlings cheaper if
you want tomato vendor yep all right and now let's get married we'll talk later
we'll talk later you've received harvester in this thing is a piece of
junk get this isn't even drive move discharge pipe wait what do you mean
where does this go does this work like a vacuum cleaner I just to put on
different attachments which one is correct oh shit I just made a battle bot
is this going back go destroy the 5g tower how do I how do I use it save your
town Z he's not doing anything Z oh I'm good so how do I take the other thing
because this too is this the only thing I can use because there's another like
attachment back here I don't want this one this one's stupid I don't want the
claw where's that 5g tower okay move this down I don't want I want the
harvester I want this thing how fucking perfect do I have to do I just want to
put I don't want I don't have corn I have wheat oh my fucking god is there
church over there did the 5g tower doesn't even there it is fucking
whatever it's gonna stay right can I climb it I can't no I can't climb it
damn it use the drone I don't have a drone anymore I sold it back to the guy
I got scammed because I wanted a cooler drone all right well I want what about
I'm gonna go check out the church no I just put the harvester on it I have to
get that attachment seriously and I'm gonna go to the church I have to line
this up so it's perfect what is wrong okay I hitched it no I didn't hitch it
okay now drop it this is the one that I want not the corn one this is worse
than parallel parking pog champ pog champ let's go to the church time to
steal some wheat you're moving too fast you'll be losing some crops what are you
talking about save the game that's a good idea
holy shit it's been so long okay what's the money doing what is the
money doing the money went up at first and then it went down you're paying for
their damages what fucking horse shit I understand losing social but I lose
money too so I lose so I steal from them and I lose money from stealing money
and fame why is this disconnected paying damages no I didn't get caught
where's the police was the investigation where's the due process huh I don't see
any courtrooms that I do it yes but where it's a video game whatever all
right let's go to church and it's like a little market over here to drive car
into the church like in the front doors you got caught on the drone footage you
actually pray in here there's a carnival over there too look there's like church
there's a carnival going to church is a good idea all right you receive a
thousand so sure because I just walked around in the okay I I'm trespassing on
the church I'm not going into the church there's a horse there how do I get a
horse all right I'm gonna sneak up on the horse and feed it what do I have
come here I want to feed you I'm gonna feed you like a cake come here what's
this why is it slow-motion sound effect it's just running through all right what was
at the market but there's a little carnival market thing over here and we
selling anything who okay there's a person here what's this called coffee
shop Google hi hello I'd like to I'd like to buy some coffee care to treat
this is a nice place to live you don't look so well are you all right you don't
look so well are you all right I am perfectly fine thank you why would you
ask that this is a really nice place to live yes I love the countryside okay
welcome welcome to welcome to Starbucks you don't look so well oh thanks care to
trade absolutely okay so what if I can I give you the ring is selling the ring
here no you just bought the ring off of me I was trying how do I give you a ring
how do we talk about hi there good afternoon you don't look so well are you
all right I am perfectly fine thank you thanks what was that is this your house
I don't know how do I like even start a conversation to go on a date with
somebody I'm gonna take the fucking bus so let's just take a this is the bus
right Mary waters local sports event mmm okay building materials for free by a
shingle you just bought shingle place on the unloading ramp what unloading
right wait this is where I this is where I can buy stuff for my house by
scratch coat by wood glaze oh man by roof tiles by bricks pick up shingle pick
up shingle hundred pieces how many do I buy new ceramic roof by bricks yeah do
I I don't understand how this works do I only carry around one brick I need a
car go to the vehicle shop I got a truck right here right click no I got my truck
is right here he's crazy what does this have to do with farming it's called
listen the name of this game is not called farming today or it's a farmer's
job this is called farmers destiny it's with an apostrophe where's my fucking
truck farmers dynasty that's right so this is not farming simulator this is
farmers apostrophe dynasty there's much more to do in your dynasty than just
plant all right let's go pick up my shit I'm an ugly van all right so I got a car
let's go in and pick up my stuff so you're saying what just back it over
here back it up do I have to actually drive brick by brick no I don't what
that just say just said something they were four options what did you say wait
furniture store kid buy new home furniture for the for the bath you kids
of your kids room you've bought new furniture for your first kids room why
am I already planning for children kids and shit when I don't even have a I
don't even have a girlfriend air bricks those cool all right uh here's a train
station place to meet people trader ask for work yeah sell the bricks they might
just stay there I think they're just gonna stay there for me to take
whenever I want they didn't despawn why am I going up to try I'm grinding the
fuck out of this tree all right train station too I can meet people at the
train station okay do I still have a ring right I better there's nobody here
there's nobody even here can I re brick your building there's a treasure chest
where oh fuck there is a treasure chest I'll take it I thought I could meet
people here boring town fuck ooh jump this is fucking
chest dress right there oh fuck there's a beer two beers am I hungry oh fuck I'm
gonna die I love us it's probably not alcoholic why does it have to be
probably not alcoholic it is or it isn't all right how much is this stuff buy a
boxer what's a boxer do you can pay full retail price or you can use social
points for a discount you have to spend the points but a little buggy how much
is this thing this is $90,000 I don't have how much is this a hundred and
$30,000 okay well I'll never have that new quest available place to relax just
chill and relax let's go to town square here I need to find a friend or like a
wife or something what do you want gas because I'm gonna be out yeah I haven't
talked to Oliver in a long time either that's true all right let's get in here
looking for people all right town square the towns where let's go
doesn't matter if my character what's going on oh I'm inside the building okay
I can fix that town square friends did anybody live here this person person
person one person let's go hi there hello there oh it's you again looks so
pretty today what is wrong with you do you always talk like that I just felt
this all over me you look so good it almost makes me speechless it is so nice
to hear thank you hi we're gonna go again no flowers as beautiful as you
flower is as beautiful as you are so nice to hear that okay hello there I can
now I want to give you a ring where's the ring how do I give you a ring
is there something I can help you with no not at the moment okay did you hear
the latest news I don't even watch TV anymore oh okay we can't we gotta that's
all thanks okay how do I do this hi good afternoon did it hurt when you were
falling from the sky you're a real charmer aren't you hi there good
afternoon you look so pretty I need to like leave this person alone that's so
sweet how do I do this there's no other is there any other way to do this hello
there good af would you have any farming advice for me keep talking driving on a
sold field destroys your crops so just don't all right thank you for the advice
you really look beautiful today you're a real charmer aren't you how do I take
the ring out I can't equip ring what about chocolate how do you give a gift
to somebody I can't just give this to you you need 50,000 points and there is a
timer we mean is a timer remember where this is I just saw a paragraph of how to
do this somebody somebody relay that to me you need to raise her likeness to
above 90% so no no no no no I'm guys that like to like last time one sentence
I can't when it's when the paragraphs are being spammed I can't read it one
sentence just like five words she doesn't love you yet she must love you
first okay now in another one sentence how do I make her like me how do I like
get her to like me how do I get the game to make people like me Calvin Calvin can
I get you to like me care to talk good afternoon all right how do I make you
like me why does nobody like me all I do is talk shit you don't look so well are
you all right I am perfectly fine thank you nice weather ain't it it sure is
that came off as a kind of abrasive nice weather ain't it nice weather ain't it
it sure is I am looking for work there is something I need indeed care to bring
the package to me my friend has it now sounds good pick up the parcel Calvin are
you fucking kidding me that's so much time I haven't even planted a single
seed not one seed has been planted how is this possible I'm buying an animal
who cares I'm gonna have a whole house full of animals that's 2.7 million away
where's what do I buy animals have some rest with a cup of rum and no that's
coffee shop church bus greenhouse for sale vehicle store where that I wear
animals deliver a tomato Becky Lydia Frank I don't see it like an
animal store anywhere Steve the old mill buy seeds and agricultural equipment a
coffee shop church gas station what do you get animals am I insane have you
hired any workers I lost my points so no and I lost all my I mean okay I'm gonna
transport this to Calvin because I need the points it's cuz I bought a drone the
agricultural stores have animals am I gonna pass one on the way there okay
there's an agricultural store here no that's not an agricultural store
field info owner no place to relax whatever let's go just place stardew I
already did stardew though do this I'm not gonna read it you know you are the
only one it says it sucks a lot I think it's charming in a way I
need to see at least some of it through peaked at the drone I need the other
drone I need to like at least plant something anything I don't have enough
social points to have like a farm and why would I do that when I just pay
somebody 480 dollars to do the whole game for me no don't I'm working on my
social credit right now I'm about to deliver a package of this guy he cares
about money I've just been running errands for people where even is this
package up on a hill IRL you are just a massive pushover in this game yeah I
mean new spot though seriously get out of the fucking way but there is a car
that's a drivable car that has to mean something hey I'm ever a package
delivery I'm here for the package sure here it is hi good afternoon I am
looking for work got anything for me no not at the moment these sunflowers are
huge thanks care to talk hello I am looking for work got anything no them
politicians what are they thinking don't even start bothering me no I thought it
was gonna go off I thought we were gonna get are we gonna get like a rant that's
angry person person hello good afternoon why can you do this with lady you look
as beautiful as a sunny morning save it I don't know you hello there good
afternoon I would have arrived earlier if I knew I'd meet a beauty like you
that's so sweet you are really nice
hi good afternoon does this keep going like this I need a quest well thank you
is there a telephone in this game or anything how do I get a phone number
hello good afternoon is there something I can help you with no not at the moment
goddammit good luck I'm moving I'm gonna move the car I know 2568 million my
truck is smoking yeah I guess it is that's a little weird oh fuck fuck I
just flanked I just was planking out no I just lost the points that I just got
that's kind of funny but I'm okay there's the 5g I got too close to the
5g tower easy turn do joke again no I gotta focus I need to get to 50,000 I
need another drone I need to have a wife I want to have kids the whole reason
why I'm doing this still guys is because I want to have a child and then I want
to teleport five ten years in the future that's the only reason I'm still in the
game it shows the sex it does not show the sex I will put down 50 trillion
dollars that says it does not show how you having sex on camera in fact I'm
gonna go sleep for a week after this yep because then they'll be I'll be to
come back a compliment I'm gonna go to Nellie compliment her sleep for a week
come back compliment her what's happening over here there's people a
gathering friends care to talk hello beauty so nice to see you well take it
somewhere else we barely met I pulled over I was driving and I pulled over on
the side of the road to do this good afternoon no flower is as beautiful as
you are it is so nice to hear care to talk good afternoon you look so good it
almost makes me speechless well take it somewhere else hi there good did it hurt
when that's so sweet you are really nice hello good afternoon did it hurt when
you were falling from I just use that one what is wrong with you do you always
talk like that what was that hello there good afternoon yes I do always talk like
that lady you look as beautiful as a sunny morning so nice to hear that
thanks hello there well hello looks so pretty today
look so pretty today save it I don't know you hi well hello there
stupid this is you look like the princess I've been looking for my entire
life you are a real charmer aren't you okay cool so it's Kennedy what about
what about you talk hmm them politicians what are they thinking they only care
for themselves oh that's what they all do okay see you around thanks care to
talk good afternoon wait hold on I get is there something I can help you with
no not somebody give me a task so I can have a friend it sure is thanks nobody
have anything for me to do hello nobody has anything for me to do is there
something I can help you with no not at the moment that's all how do I use this
Lydia put down I ask you something oh care to talk good afternoon you look so
good it almost makes me speechless what's with that sweet talk I don't even
know you hi good afternoon you look so good it is so nice to hear hello there
good afternoon hello beauty well thank you hi there oh is there something I
can help you with no not that's all I ever I these people persistent but what
are they not persistent what do they leave do they just get auto-generated or
these people actually in the town I'm just trying to go around okay Jesus this
is harder to control than the drone is there what's the train sound all right
here's your fucking package I'm in the building again god damn it okay I don't
I don't I will actually fucking softlock myself this is not good there we go
care to talk epic rider care to trade absolutely what you got oh you have a
lot of shit I don't know can I sell you something for way overpriced bullshit
you know what about a beer no I need a ring I need the perfume I need all this
stuff get 15 pumpkins I don't care oh shit and another congregation of people
here's the package you requested thank you why am I something for you 12 feet
tall would it give me a thousand social points I'm almost there
hello there it's me good evening you look like the princess I've been
looking for my entire life well thank you care to talk hello is there
something I can help you with no did it hurt when you were falling from the sky
so nice to hear that okay I need 50,000 social points right how much what am I
how close are we so I got somebody somebody wants something right around
here anybody need anything right here okay deliver tomatoes sure let's go
right here let's do it why would it hurt if you fell from the sky because you're
falling 5,000 miles down what are you talking about hello hi hmm I am looking
for work no not nobody has any work that's all there are shitload of people
in this town seriously there's so many people here to talk good evening
good luck what do you hi there Salma oh it's you again it's me again that's
right I would have arrived earlier if I knew I'd meet a beauty like you save it
I mean it does look like BF Bugleberry you're right hello there oh it's you
again people seem to pretend to know me but not know me looks so pretty today
what's with that sweet talk hello hello is there something I can help you with
quest yes I need some tomatoes but can't go to the shop now will you bring me
these absolutely sounds good I'll take care of this yep deliver 20 tomatoes
I'll be right back stay right there where's my car where's my car wait I have
to actually go get tomatoes I just need 20 tomatoes wait I have tomatoes grown
in my garden all right we're gonna go sleep for a week and then come back to
go back home let's work on those tomatoes won't you
tomatoes die if they're not watered they should be okay but I don't care did
the tomatoes a tomato in this game they could be rotten for all that she cares
as long as there's 20 of them who cares we'll go to sleep and see if we have any
tomatoes to harvest all right home sweet home here we are wait a minute look
at this shit I didn't I'm gonna yeah remember when I planted these yeah I
remember I planted these they're actually here that's cool we get the
first harvest of apples cool all that hard work paid off tomato tree I can
sell these too anybody need an apple or one an apple I get the rest later let's
check on tomatoes it's comfortable in here how long does this shit take to
grow okay good night nice all right looks a lot better plus I just want to
get rid of these you know what I kind of always wanted to try something about it
it's the way that like this the slosh like goes on the you slurp the fucking
you spread the slosh on the all right let me try to let me slow down for a
second here let me pause it cuz it's hard for me to even get this up when you
lay bricks and you get the little scooper and you like you slosh like that
paste the cement down you stick it on there I feel like that would be I want
to try it you get that bucket of just you get the little scooper you just and
then you glue them together being like a brick mason I think I mean it's it's a
it's a hard job but I kind of want I want to like just do it once I want to
look like let me put this way I want to do to be a brick mason for as long as
it takes to go from here to here and then be like that was fun I'm done
cool all right let's go look I got ooh hold on nobody just do it let me just do
it I actually can replace all of my shitty stuff okay I'm glad you can do
that how many bricks do I even have left no that's how many I have all right
bedtime okay check on tomatoes if the tomatoes aren't ready I'm gonna sleep
for a week why does my wallpaper look like that all right it's not a good a bit for a week
how long this is gonna take a million years can I just buy tomatoes I'm just
gonna go buy them all right I'm gonna go buy tomatoes who sells tomatoes I need
a market general store no he didn't sell tomatoes vehicle store is there only one
general store agriculture all right we're going here for the sole reason that I
want to see if I can buy any animals the 5g tower lady sells to me that's right
you're right you're right you're right 5g tower lady does sell tomatoes where's
her farm which one I don't even remember where the fuck it was where's the 5g
tower let us click by lakeside is it down here like this way what's going on
what just happened where am I okay that was weird is it over here where's that
5g tower it's where I left my corn header over here I need my truck why am I
over what happened to me this fast travel in this game and I didn't even
know about it so why don't I just park this across the whole world this
seriously can't be the place that I get stuck into the fucking river just do it
it's not that hard all right we're gonna find the 5g tower and we find it yeah
what's the point of being I'm gonna just put my tractor on one side and put the
car on the other side they're fine don't worry death stranding looks weird on PC
yeah yep all right 5g tower where's the 5g tower it's over here somewhere where's
the 5g tower still on tutorial island where is this place there's no fucking
idea I have no idea that's it writer you know how I know because everything is
done completely built up and looks nice except for this one because that's what
I didn't do right isn't it right here no nevermind it's not fuck where is this
person that sells the tomatoes ah god damn it it's over here somewhere more
over here over here it wasn't up here I cannot see the tower from here wasn't
it right next to the first farm wait what do you mean right next to the first
farm like over here I should have kept a damn drone so I could have been able to
see where I was going does the gas station explode not even a good game and
actually I think yeah I think you're right I think it was the one right next
to my house was it though I don't remember I don't see any there it is
tomato time farmers dynasty haven't done a single fucking thing to have nothing
to do with farming to have done absolute zero to do with anything to do with
being a farmer in four and a half hours I I plowed a field once that's it god
give me a break I'm just gonna go all the way back and then turn it go this
way everything just has so much just fucking walk whatever I'll buy a new one
was the tower all I care about is that tower it's this way right where was it
why is it not spawned in all right hey excuse me I'm here for the tomato this
is my house those 5g signals are melting his brain oh okay but let me be let me be
fair though I planted tomatoes right how long ago is that in do I just have to
actually go to bed for like 10 straight days for them to grow hey hey hey hey
excuse me I'm busy not now hi there so nice to see you are so beautiful I wish
I dream about you tonight it is so nice to him wait a minute what really hi so
nice to see you like did it work care to trade absolutely Janet how do you not
have any tomatoes you are apples and pumpkins and zucchinis I thought you
were a tomato farmer aren't you growing tomatoes what are you doing do you have
a talk good morning good morning do you have any them politicians fuel prices
are outrageous that's all I came all the way down here with tomatoes good morning
I was let us stray is there something I can help you with no not at the moment
no flower is as beautiful as you are it is so nice to him she but she really
likes me how do I like go on a date or something do you seriously not have any
fucking tomatoes in your whole house what am I doing here then you just have
apples what am I doing here I need 20 tomatoes that's the general store sell
them they might I think it's apples just go to sleep and go back tomorrow if I
sleep for a week I might lose the I might lose the job hold on do you have
tomatoes good to see you do you have 20 of them care to trade sure no this guy
doesn't have any tomatoes he is the super drone and he no no tomatoes I'm
going to sleep for a week okay sell you wheat every day
unfortunately I can't hire a worker to do it because I'm not cool enough to
hire people what a nice rest weather effects no way let's see this house
sucks so bad I can't even leave it imagine if your entire fucking house
your entire house was wallpapered like this you'd get lost in every room every
single part of the house is this weird grandma flower paper tomatoes check them
was this a beehive place for birds what is this what is it I don't know that's
for back to bed back to bed go back to sleep I'm sleeping I'm gonna save it I'm
gonna sleep for two weeks who gives a shit nobody cares about me in this town
anyways all right let's go let's harvest the tomatoes how are these not ready
water them they're already watered they're in a comfortable wet position
years even watered them for weeks it's a greenhouse you're not gonna go here
like a spray bottle oh it's a greenhouse look tomatoes let's go how
many twelve tomatoes oh fuck yeah hundred and fourteen tomatoes I'm gonna
be a quadrillionaire let's just hope that I don't know her name let me avoid
the war I'm damaging my vehicle you're getting hungry well good thing I got a
hundred and fourteen tomatoes it actually is truly stuck I'm thinking
maybe turn the wheel all the way this way because what is I'm hitting the tree
hold on all right I'm hitting the base of the tree and it's fucking it all up
this is over I can't get this up I need to drone it but I don't have a drone
anymore god damn it I don't have a drone I'm gonna sell a bunch of tomatoes to
the guy and all right I'm gonna drum that out you're right good idea I'm gonna
sell this guy like 70 tomatoes good to see you can I help you care to trade
sure what do you need all right how many price per you that's terrible that's it
not even worth selling it's like a hundred bucks they're just tomatoes
they're the best tomatoes they're the finest tomatoes you can buy oh this is
expensive um what do I need 17 I'm just gonna buy that who cares just give me
the fucking little baby drone I'm done I'll come back later all right let's go
get this thing out I'm gonna go from the other side this moves cars so radically
on the road you want to see my thought process watch this those of you that
weren't here those of you that weren't here like an hour ago that's my thought
process all right I thought this car didn't even exist one more idea push it
with the tractor I have to go get the tractor hold on that's what I mean right
there off of the low fuck God just give me the damn tractor and just come back
where's my tractor this is this possibly the stupidest stream on twitch right now
I'm trying to get my fucking car back what you think I'm trying to do full
speed who would have guessed actually not me because these wheels are fucking
enormous the wheels are huge where's my harvester that thing is huge that's
really big where's the harvester that's so far away is this water okay get out
of the water out of the water like this guy sucks I wouldn't want to know this
guy either imagine you ran a business you had a general store and somebody was
flying their drone trying to like flip cars in front of your business and got
two vehicles stuck in a river in front of your business and then you find out
and you hear through you know through gossip that he's on his way back right
now with a giant tractor and he's gonna try to get both of his cars out what are
you gonna do what do you do you call police harvest the grass you just
record it yeah that's true you would just record it you would make an entire
YouTube channel around this person and they wouldn't even know you know you'd
be able to get permission from this person real really really easy you'd be
like hey dude hey what's up hey do you care if I like upload like the shit that
you're doing to YouTube yeah fucking that's fucking awesome dude yeah go for
it okay and like record yourself doing that it'd be very easy I don't give a
shit thank you and like what's a month when you get like paid out from YouTube
and you take and you take your like you're like eighty nine hundred dollars
a month you're gonna make from this guy just like be like hey hey what is hey
man um you want like a hundred bucks what the fuck oh yeah that sounds good
to me I'll take a hundred dollars right now keep doing your thing oh I will
thank you sir because I mean there's another point though this puppet guy
this guy probably has a lot of money you don't lose a truck and then a tractor
in a moat and then come back with like a four hundred thousand dollar piece of
machinery to get remove it this guy has a lot of money I'm going the wrong way
what no he doesn't have any money he just has like a bunch of loans no that's
not that wait what do you mean star is wrong no it's not this is where all my shit is he'd
see you with the money he's like you have a briefcase you don't know he
doesn't know I need to go ramming speed I don't have any crops yeah because I'm
not cool enough to have them planted by anybody I have to I need I just want
look I'm just trying to get tomatoes here all right let me line this up put it
down I don't think you can get them out it's this guy's this one's too big to
get stuck I think so they can't be moved they actually can't be moved the two
they're like cemented to the ground yep no they're here forever no I can't get
them oh well let's turn this back up let's get out here ram into the truck
from the tree side no it's it's got solid collision I can't I will give it
one attempt and we're gonna we're gonna detach this so it's just a ram stop
spinning this thing drop it all right now it's just an actual ram go get the
tow truck get the tow truck all right I gotta line it up how do you soft lock
yourself in farmers destiny you try to drive over a moat that has a tree in it
hold on can I cut this tree down with the chainsaw oh fuck man I think I can
cut the tree down with the chainsaw well this is our car now wait I can dig
myself out I'm gonna dig myself up I think it's gonna work it's just like
snow you got to get your back tire free okay let's try that other side right
there okay let's try telling me my ideas are wrong this is gonna work oh you
motherfucker turn sharp left when going forward I can't I might be able to I'm
gonna brute force out come on it's going please drone drone can fit under there
don't do it do it do it do it fuck off well call the tow truck in the tab menu
we're talking about this person still want their tomatoes I hope so dig in
front of the truck I can't dig in front of the truck because it's uh it's not
grass don't count see it said tow truck in the menu where are you seeing tow
truck what are you talking about there's no tow truck in the menu please get me
out of this I need these things I need these things I have to holy shit is a
tow truck there is a tow truck my god are you serious no it is not no way you
gotta be fucking kidding me Wow unbelievable un fucking believable why
this wasted like 40 minutes let's go hello there good morning nice weather
ain't it it sure is ain't it is there something I can help you with no not at
the moment plus 80 social points I'm almost there I would have arrived earlier
if I knew I'd meet a beauty well take it somewhere else what's going on I'm gonna
need that tow truck again tomato delivery incoming fucking playing daisy
well like PUBG or something not great music choice but you know same car
mechanics I think it's got some air I'm here I'm here I made it she's running
away from she being chased I'm coming I'm coming so there's somebody like
chasing behind her somebody's chasing her was it me the whole time wait was it me
there was somebody else it's just been me hello there no there he is good wait
is that me more than same clothes no flower is as beautiful as you are so nice
to hear that thanks still don't even care to talk let's deliver tomatoes to
you like me at all is there something I can help you with no thanks now what the
fuck am I supposed to do I need 50 I need more social points who's this Frank
50 social points that I don't know about them I can work by time 50 that's
it new quest available spicy pumpkin soup I don't have that that's not
available to me I'll do a transport quest there was a ghost behind me what
was that buy new property and fix it up for social points I don't have enough
money to buy any property I have to I gotta go do it on my own I'm gonna go
put what no who cares but I don't want Frank I have to go bring my tractor back
and harvest and plant some seeds am I going can I fit through that can I fit
through this can I fit through this can I fit through this yes yeah I gotta get
it's a nice little garden okay where's this person what do you need to get wait
what if I just fix this person's house I'm pretty good at doing that all right
hold on I have an idea but hey I'm gonna fix your house okay hey I'm gonna redo
your whole house please give me a thousand points hi there oh it's you
again I am looking for work got anything for me there is something I need indeed
care to bring the package to me sounds good you know I'm not gonna get anything
to this that's a thousand social points all right what's the thing I'm doing now
this all right let's go pick it up do I have anything closer I do the no mailman
in this game apparently not yeah this thing doesn't go fast at all I can run
faster than this shit okay I'm starting to hit this really really hard
realization right now fuck all these people I'm gonna go far that what am I
doing this for a new party member Oh right cuz I was trying to find a wife
now I remember can I run faster than 25 miles per hour let's find out yes I have
to it's so slow I have to go this way hot air balloon can I go in there oh no
it's just a dumb sign I could take the bus yeah I'll take the bus I'll take the
bus there and I'm gonna take the bus back to this bus station this is so
stupid I'm gonna take the bus from here to there pick up the package take the
bus back and then get in my car and drive it to him what are you doing what's
it doing that is blackout how tired no I'm good this is closer you just ate a
pumpkin what the fuck are you a porcupine is there another bus stop
that's closer imagine bus hopping this much wait coffee shop care to talk good
morning why can I not this is a really nice place to live yes I love it here
care to trade absolutely you want a drone here have some tomatoes 12 of them
okay this is what's the point of this imagine walking up to a barista and
saying care to trade yeah like it's the 1300s I finally have 50,000 which then I
somebody said after 50,000 I can start to actually get like a wife I get it
holy shit that was an accident that's actually was scary wait wait wait wait
stay there let me fix this no no no don't move don't move I'm gonna go up
and then down and then we got it boys and girls no I don't had it whoa it's
got to be perfect I had it that one time damn it let's go sayonara up don't
exit the drone this guy ain't going anywhere for a long time the roads made
out of putty try stuff them into the ground stack the vans that's gonna be
fucking hard to do who's behind everything poetry over here flip them
this way no stop escaping he's in he's in he's stuck they ain't no fucking
turning around from that one got you you're right in there what was the goal
what was I doing here stacking vans right right hold on I think I can get it
I gotta go through the middle all right I got his front up play there here it
comes fuck fuck German the crops I'm not destroying him he is you're in trouble
you're in trouble that's disturbing when does he say that I was fucking
disturbing yeah that's suck doesn't it I can't move this guy anymore I forgot I
was screaming okay well hold on I'd like forgot this is a live stream look at
that sicko where are you going now minus 10,000 but 50,000 social points yeah fuck
you your social points are destroyed that's what it feels like to be the
fucking guy in town I know what he talks to wait how did he get away he didn't
get away I think I have to stop playing a game I can't stop I have to be ready
for him all right perfect opportunity on the fucking roof let's go boys and
girls oh he slipped off I can get it hold on he's gonna just drive in circles
again okay okay all right I think I had fun oh he's so stupid okay let me try
damn it that's so tricky to get right underneath like that like that like that
slow it fuck it's so slippery it's so hard to get it get him on the roof of
riot trying my best now he's stuck forever it's gonna be up a little bit
you couldn't have made this any better for me could you I just turtled him
again I need to get him on the roof but I can't I have to stop what if I turn the
volume down is that gonna go I had him it's so hard to keep it steady because
it just rips around in so many directions all right I thought I'm gonna
play the game I have to play the game now I have to stop I will sit here for
like three days and do this my brain is so fucked up I will be here all day last
chance here we go this is the last opportunity no the roof it's gonna kill
me it's gonna kill me he's right here oh it's no it's too hard to control it
really is it's so difficult hold on quiet ah oh my god I'm gonna lose my mind I
have to do this I'm gonna lose my fucking mind I did it twice oh it's so
difficult this is the heart it's a harder than the last boss in secure no
no it's got you it's got to be in one fucking swoop it has to be perfect
he'll turn around go slower I can't trust me trust me look trust the guy
that's been doing this for two hours I trust me no not it wasn't perfect
because to be able to get under in the first place you have to go fast enough
for the game to why are you even explaining this even describing what I
have to can I use a controller I'd be probably harder what is the joke here
there is none I just want to pick him up and put him on the roof this is not a
joke I just like how my brain is just fucking fried and I have to do this I'm
like leaning back in my chair and shit my hands are sweating you see how I'm
like I have to glitch into the ground all right this is not a terrible
opportunity here and you got to get near the back wheels directly right in the
middle of the car I fucked it up no no you have to go up and then like scream
down so you get into the ground and then you're already going fast fuck roof fan
he's got it he's got it no he doesn't no shit it's too hard is too impossible I'm
here for the package sure here it is first track all right I never get him on
the roof from here I just fly him let's see if I can fly him carefully I don't
think I can fly him carefully no no you can't you can't do it you can't move
them at all you can't move them at all I have to fling them where's the package
with my car in my car I have the package let's back to my car I don't know how
long I did that for but I had to I had to try I had to try to get it on the
roof I wanted on the roof so bad because he would have probably disappointed
right now there's no payoff oh I'm unfulfilled I need to fulfill myself how
do I do that I'm completely unfulfilled oh that's the kind of shit that you have
nightmares over here's the package you requested thank you here's something
for you we can't let him get away with this all right 50,000 points time for a
girlfriend time to go socialize with 50,000 points now check this out let's
do it higher I want to what if we should do corn I plowed it cultivate it and then
corn should I do corn or do I need to cultivate it fertilize and then corn do
I need to do that for do I need to fertilize our cult is it gonna just do
it do I have to just gonna just click on make corn please cultivate all right
good now let's go make a friend care to talk hello you are so beautiful I wish I
dream about you tonight what's with that sweet talk hi good afternoon hello
beauty so nice to see you that's so sweet I need a quest or something does
anybody actually like me yet yeah that was like a synchronized tee good
afternoon this is a really nice place to live yes it is nice and all good folk
you really look beautiful today I'm out of gas I need I just did the same thing
you did why did I do the same thing you did what was I doing that for any
quests any people any friends any family search for mushrooms drone race
let's go the tomato lady wait where am I there's a bus right there I know who
cares it's driving I don't have a racing drone never mind all right we're going
to well writer see because tomato lady it had a smiley face on us okay I don't
know how that happened the game just ripped me that way the my front alignment
is okay I'm seriously my front alignments fucked up the tomato girl
thinks I'm cool yeah let's go back there you are seriously hungry
imagine eating seven tomatoes just raw how fucked up is this person he's
driving around not even on the roads eating raw tomatoes losing his cars
flipping people off with drones just this guy's a menace there's no sound
effects there's no that's my dog what do you do with my dog this is my house
no it's not what are you doing with my dog this is my dog where are you wrong
house that's my dog plow the field area new
quest I'll take it I'm right here excuse me watch out I don't want to hit the dog
all right this shit is right here a fucking monster oh good day wait can I
help you sweetheart oh it's kind of green can you tell me a bit about field
work sure what thanks all right plow which field this one here this one here
all right let's do some farm work who has the quest you you which one of you
guys actually has this quest hello good afternoon I would have arrived earlier
if I knew I'd meet a beauty like you well take it some new quest plow the
field area but who is giving this to me I don't understand there's nobody here
to give this to me hey rune let's hide there hmm you have work is yours for
work got anything no thanks bye this is yours who's is this hello there good
after is there something I can help you with there's a field nearby that needs
plowing will you do it unbelievable yeah I'll do it sounds good plow the
field this one right here shit I need if I need a plow where's my equipment no
so here old machine grass mower Wow there it is let's get the plow let's do
some actual work for God's sake term I feel like this stream is gonna kill me
hang in there I know what that's like man let me help you out here all right
you're good saved I saved your life give me five hundred dollars now I plow that
field where are my plow stuff over here right that's a plow right this is a
plow this is a plow isn't it holy shit I somebody harvest this shit this is mine
somebody harvest this what the hell are you doing over there drone these guys
no don't fuck me up somebody come somebody I'll do it all right
now I'm doing my job I'm doing my goddamn job I don't remember where it
was I wish I could float I can't just press it go go gadget inspector gadget
button and float over that and just drive over this it's not even worth doing
this is the second farm thing you've done in almost eight hours little six
but yeah six hours ago yes I did plow stuff and then after some time went by I
you can't throw something like that at me and not have me look and not have me
do something about it the person's just out walking that their car oh we almost
hit the pole all the van I AI is what am I how am I getting money I've got like
$25 all the van AI is fucking destroyed they all just driving circles every van
now does this all right fuck it we're going this way I'm not taking the road I
don't care I'll lose oh no you ran over somebody's
bush minus 500 points actually it's not that bad yeah I can drive over this I'm
not grinding it I have to get the super drum before the stream turns off this
is the field right here right that's the one no it's the one after that
actually not doing shit why did I only get like $20 wasn't there a whole thing
of wheat 99% Oh ready for harvest there was like point two percent ready to eat
all right here we go let's do I get money for this I hope so this is the
field right just make sure I'm not messing this up it's this one which one
is it is it this one is this trade ahead of me wait hold this up it's how
it's this one wow the field Sally you don't have anything you don't own shit
Sally what do you mean Wow wait like it's this thing oh this sucks this is the
only farming content that's been on the whole stream is scraping the dirt
sometimes this is so much bigger too this is five times larger how much it
what's your field is isn't this that doesn't count as your field right no
don't touch it don't touch it don't touch it get off get off get off get off
that was close no this is not even close it's just this how much I have to do
this is too much I got to do in chunks this is what you do when you farm so
farming is not driving around looking for tomatoes and desperately trying to
find a wife and flying a drone around this is what you do all right if I give
up right now can I just knock on her door and be like hey I'm done I don't
want to do anymore just can you pay me like 8% like 4% of what I was gonna get
I don't feel like doing this and I just have like if it was gonna cost like 500
bucks to do this can you just give me like $12 also also you want to get
married let's have a bunch of children too so please marry me
marry me you're giving us city folk a bad name why would anybody that lives in
the city know how to do this that's okay why would you expect somebody that has
lived in this city their whole life to be able to know how to plow a field is
it disappearing on me like I did this already like four times okay why don't I
just hire like 25 people to all bring their tractor and then we all start
side by side by side by side by side all start at the same time and just drive
forward once how much more work could we get done instead of taking 12 hours to
do this just do it in 12 minutes and then drive to the next one and in one
day we could do every single field in the whole county that's a utopian
utopian streamer he's a giant tractor that's another one too why not just
build a tractor that's just like this looks exactly the same except it's 100
times larger the seat could be the same size it's it's just as big as four or
five houses put together so you're just driving this huge-ass mothership across
the plane and doing it one just drive forward once you ever mowed a lawn
yes and if the lawnmower was as big as my house I could just sit it in the
backyard turn on the blades and then turn them off and the yard would be cut
now granted that would be a catastrophic death machine it would be
immensely dangerous but then you then you have a lawnmower instead of a yard
that the grass just grows up to the blades and then you turn on the giant
blades and then turn it off you don't even get a you don't have to get to
have a backyard no it would be on a mechanism that the blade was up like 60
feet like a hundred feet or something hovering over the yard you could play
out there you can have fun you can hang out back there and then you would lower
it down to cut the grass just don't have grass that's another one too just have
like just paved your backyard you know how much coolest shit you can have in
your backyard with a paved backyard you can have a basketball court you have
tennis courts what is all the rain go to the drain that you have built in the
middle of the backyard a huge drain you didn't think I thought about that a
giant drain that's connected to the sewer system and it just there you go you
can put a shower back there you could have like a bunch of showers in your
backyard draw a penis already all right well I'm gonna try to spell something
and I'll look at it with the drone I don't even care if I fuck up somebody's
I'll be done with this game in like 20 minutes anyway but does it have to be
this slow why can't you attach this to a go-kart those things go 20 no power to
pull time is it I'm like very tired and very hungry and it's like okay I guess
we're gonna just keep doing it it's almost done anyways I can't quit before
I have children all right but you know how long I'm
gonna have to play this game before I'm allowed to have children I know I wanted
to go into a coma for 20 years but I gotta get I have to get married just
don't fuck around with drones yes I can see what I've done it's bad it's really
bad I don't know that I just gonna stay with stick with what I was doing before
I'm not even close has it been 24 hours the Sun's about to come up you know bad
this job is how overtired is this guy he's so sleep-deprived he just fucking
the whole thing up this line right here I've been trying to sleep to this shit
you would not be able to sleep it's like this for 12 hours outside from 5 p.m.
forward who the hell what am I who am I kidding I guarantee you with complete
certainty that there is a relaxing sleep sounds music video on YouTube that
is tractor sounds guaranteed yeah it's already there of course it is let's play
a game well I finished this name a thing that makes noise and is it a YouTube
video that's four hours long of sound effects for you to sleep to fish yep
fish is gonna be like oh inside of an aquarium industrial brick laying apps I
guarantee you type in brick laying sleep video farting guaranteed it's
gonna be like sleep to farting I swear to God it's I had has to be you guys know
that that like oh rule 34 if they exist is porn for it right this is what I
would make a new rule if it exists there's a sleep soundtrack for it
sleep soundtrack in fact there's probably more sleep sound effects
soundtrack you're very tired your arms are sore physical pain I'm almost done
my arms are killing me all this sitting and doing the equivalent of holding a
book I did it did I what do I get for a present why is the bed lit up Sally
Sally Sally I did what you asked I want that money Sally I'll take care of this
for you Sally don't worry Sally I got it how could you have this messed up brick
back here Sally I'll handle it Sally can't have cracks in her walls
Sally needs to have her front steps re-concrete paved I got it I'll take
care of it Sally needs new furniture I'll go get furniture and bring it to
Sally I miss my bed I have to go I'm running to bed what are you still doing
out here Sally hello good evening care to trade absolutely back to work holy
fuck you go five look at how fast I'm going this is bed um why is there a bed
symbol whose bed am I gonna sleep in let me help you out here he just buried
the he buried his rake in the ground what a fucking weirdo what a weirdo why
did you do that what I have to go to bed Sally I can't even turn the I gotta go
back this way I'm home what is going on here what is the money for to buy an
expensive drone that's the only thing I can use it for right at the front door
let's go good okay now I should be able to go back and actually get my reward
where's my plow where's my plow what the hell's going on just take the bus and
take the goddamn bus I all right I'm gonna take the stupid bus this uh why
are you not driving in circles he is all right I need to go to down here take my
reward and then okay here we are I'm back social points I got it and I got
$600 that was a waste of time care to talk good morning you look so good it
almost makes me speechless you're a real charmer how do you give is there
something I can help you with no you really look beautiful today it is so
nice to hear go to the tomato girl I'm gonna try to go to the tomato girls
house open my rusted-ass door yes the green smiley face you'll not you will
not be able to gift anything to the lady yet there's another state where the
smiley has red hearts for the eyes at this stage you can start trading with
the ladies there is also another state where the lady has a red heart of our
head that was the state that was given the option to ask you to marry me okay
so how do we get to that stage was red eyes how do we get a lady to have red
eyes might be in the right place oh can I help you I'm kind of green sure no
thanks where is it I forget every fucking time is it this one here you
have to trade her the ring I did that before and it was a disaster it's
isn't this one down here it's not this one either where's tomato house was the
tomato house I don't know I don't remember it's like I don't have any
idea what I just do I'm looking I made it all right tomato where's the tomato
family that's tomato Frank where's tomato Sally this place looks different
this is not even the right the new people move in oh it's this one over here
do you know what I could go for right now like an insanely greasy large cheese
pizza you know the one time that one I'm talking about where you pull a slice
off and you lift it up and it just falls down and it's so weighed heavy down by
the oil and the queries you get it it's like everything comes off of it you have
to eat it with a fork and knife I don't even like that kind of pizza but that
that's kind that's what I want right now they'd be home Janet who's this person
that's always here is it is this like a is this like a friend or is this a
husband hello great to see you again you look so good it almost makes me
speechless so nice to hear that thanks hello there hello come come closer come
closer she's just to come closer you really look beautiful today so nice to
hear that thanks I have a plan are you guys are gonna are you guys ready here
the plan hello there hello is there something I can help you with no care to
trade absolutely okay I here's the plan I'm gonna bring my truck here I'm gonna
park it right here I'm gonna bring my tractor right in front of my bedroom to
my house I'm going to go back go sleep for a week teleport to the truck say
hello teleport to the tractor sleep for a week teleport to the truck say hello
teleport the tractor sleep for a week until it's oh until I marry this person
here have a flower hello there good morning you really that's so sweet okay
all right give me my truck mark it right here if this doesn't work I'm out of
here where is my where is my tractor okay there's there's this one well this
one's close enough we'll park it over here by the way if you wonder what we're
doing tomorrow I want to play that game sniper contracts the new sniper game I
feel like it could be pretty fun we're gonna do that tomorrow it sounds like a
mobile game it might be yeah it's like a it's by like the sniper elite or sniper
which would it's one of the game studio that makes only sniper games there's
like two of them all right let me get this in a good spot there we go
park it here teleport to the truck truck is gonna be parked right outside my
front door in my bedroom here comes a strategy that's not even possible it's
seriously not impossible to have that happen it really isn't and then the plan
is that next week we're gonna do outer worlds I'm going to do at least a couple
streams on outer worlds over the next few days it's doing whatever what is
that game about that's the fallout new vegas devs made fallout new vegas but
it's in space this time heard it's pretty good okay now this has to be
right in front of my bedroom all right my bedroom is right here there we go
perfect placement save the game this is my last attempt at farming drive it up
the stairs if you could get a motorcycle I would do it all right sleep for a
fucking week all right I'm back hello there all right good morning friend good
morning how are you good to see you again no flower is as beautiful as you
are you are a real charmer aren't you mm-hmm hey thank you hi good morning
lady you look as beautiful well thank you lady whose bed is this this is this
I don't know why there's two twins what if I have a wife we're gonna sleep in
separate twin beds and also all alcohol is not alcohol it's an interesting game
all right it's been two weeks I'm back how do I make you look bad them
politicians no don't even thanks I'll care to talk good morning friend hello
beauty so nice to see you that's so sweet you are really nice hello there
good morning is there something I can help you with no no I would have
it is so nice hi there good morning did you hear the latest news I heard they
opened the old mill again interesting you are so beautiful well thank you
we're not progressing this is week three coming up stop sleeping for a week you
only just leave for a day hey me again just back to what you know tell you how
much I like you in front of your husband hi there good morning you look
so good it almost makes me speechless so nice to hear that thanks care to talk
good morning is there something I can help you with no that's all right what
if I get her give her a bunch of money you know I mean if I trade care to talk
what if I trade what if I give her like a bunch of here to trade absolutely okay
what if what if I make you like very wealthy and like look at how much better
I am look at how much cooler I am I got fish in aroma oil I have beer no this is
me no no this is her I know other way around this is me taking money from her
she's paying me how do I just give gifts I'm making her broke I'm not making her
wealthy all right as I don't think this is gonna work I think it might be timed
or you guys are always doing the same shit I'm gonna sleep for like three
months care to talk good morning friend you look like the princess I've been
looking for my entire life it is so nice to hear thank you hi good morning is
there something I can help you with no good luck at some point I just have like
a memory problem and I just keep coming back here thinking it's the first time
I've ever been there okay it's been a month and right now she's thinking I
haven't seen that weird motherfucker lately that strange guy that kept
coming over to our house where has he been don't worry I'm coming I'm back
hello so nice to see you I see you too you are so beautiful I wish I dream
about you tonight you are a real charmer aren't you hello hello is there
something I can help you with no thanks we have to go deeper I've
sleep for a year it's been a month okay what what what season is it doesn't snow
in this game all right it's too you think two months is enough no you slept
too long she died I go back to where is she where is she oh how many was it
July okay July okay almost June July almost August you miss the rapture how
many months has been for okay I think it's time to go take a look around to
see what's happening in the world okay somebody said that you're still your
tired meter was low I was like no fucking way is the food okay I need to
fucking relax that's just leaving for six months wake it up and be like god
damn I'm exhausted I think I should do that again all right it's it's been like
five months I think it's time to eat a couple of apples oh that fucking did it
to me it did oh it's starting to take longer I started like fucking like
crying it was just like instantly oh my god I thought it was through like no way
would I be tired April what do you mean I have to pee so bad this whole bed
would be pissing shit by this point this would be a wet bed it would be a soggy
bed all right how long is it what how much what would where do we start this
what month was it when I started whose may wait it was it may it's been 29
months what's that sound are they like bulldozing my house because they don't
think anyone's here all right how long has it been it's been 29 weeks okay it's
been 30 weeks should go for a run Julie Julie it's me your name is Janet I
forgot your name was Janet Janet hello hello nice to see you again it's been a
long time I would have arrived earlier if I knew I'd meet a beauty like you so
nice to hear that thanks hi there hello is there something I can help you with
no did it hurt when you were falling from the sky that's so care to good you
really it is hi there so not lady it is so nice hello there good morning you
look so pretty today that's so sweet she didn't even miss you I think somebody's
like cleaning my house this is bullshit and I'll tell you why I don't think
anybody's played this game for more than 20 weeks we're seeing this there's no
way no one has skipped this far ahead the game came out today the guide wait
is a guide what's this guide for how to get a wife I have no clue about this
post you but here it goes help and tricks and how to get a wife make sure you
have at least 50,000 social points okay the step-by-step was done when I was
between 50,000 and 90,000 points if you're lower than 50,000 you might have
to talk to the ladies more often okay talk to ladies everywhere on the map I
talked to most of them got 50 social points per conversation complimenting
them you can right-click to skip the dialogue you don't have to listen to the
whole conversation I talked to the women about once every two days to make sure
the timer actually resets well I've been sleeping months in weeks since one game
hour is about five minutes that means 12 hours in game you can talk to the
ladies wait what you can only compliment them once per real hour since one game
hour is five minutes it means 12 hours in game to talk to them but I'm sleeping
for months I'm sleeping for months the clock on the PC put your computer clock
forward does that work hold on if I make my computer clock an hour ahead will it
work okay let's try that okay save game save games it's not gonna work why would
it work yeah I guys why would that work this is not like a this is not a DS
just try it okay it's I'm making it I'm making it I'm gonna make it nine I'm
gonna make it ten o'clock what you're already doing is gonna work
adjust date and time okay set time to change date and time let's make it like
I don't know fucking ten like 10 p.m. 1041 p.m. I have to come back I have to
come back I don't know why that fucked up the stream I think the time
synchronization there it may I guess it's like that the twitch doesn't like
that so I don't know I'm not gonna do that you literally traveled to through
time okay I can't do that because the streaming software into twitch does not
like that I'm pretending it's 1040 p.m. for some reason it's counting how many
minutes you actually play great no I'm not gonna get a trainer you are not
going to watch me download a trainer and put it on this engine on stream and plus
the trainer doesn't even do anything the trainer gives you super speed and
unlimited money I can't change the time I can't change the time it's not good
that you can't change the time the stuff I was doing should work it doesn't care
how long I'm playing all right well hold on what if we do this is there a way I
can see a watch what if I just stand there for okay I was gonna have a
podcast it's six o'clock right now I'm just gonna stand here until eight not
now sorry not now sorry well I mean but holy shit and like in seven months you've
got a great garden now hello there hello did it hurt when you were falling from
the sky that's so sweet okay and what time is it six two hours
although it's take five minutes but I count to 300 out loud to pass the time
fly to the source of the 5g that's where I'm going it didn't work as racing drone
time I think it's time to sell everything and then just get the cool
drone and like who cares who needs a wife when you can have a super drone and
fly around I don't need a wife and kids I don't know why I need all white picket
friends I don't need that shit in my life I got me and my $10,000 super drone
that's all I need I am gonna try one more time I just need my $10,000 super
drone why does it say that I've played this game for 13 hours you've played
for 13 hours no I haven't going yeah but I only went for two hours the street's
been live for about seven hours I started playing this game for that when
that started why would it add six more hours on top of this I did not play this
at all before the stream absolutely not 13 hours playtime how I mean okay if I
had skipping forward was two hours so nine hours where's the other four hours
from you went forward to and then backwards to that comes out to four
that's not how that wait it counts reversing time almost we're getting
there one more another hour scaffoldings pog have I passed enough time yet it's
only been three minutes are these being deleted all right let's try now hi there
hello hello beauty so 12 in-game hours but is that all right am I no I'm out
I'm just gonna make I'm just gonna get the cool drone I'm done I'm selling
everything how did you even manage to do that hey I'm back good to see you can I
help you yes I'd like to trade with you but sure and I would like to give you
everything I want enough to buy the cool drone I don't care get rid of it all
don't even need a break fishing line cares I don't need that I don't need
these anymore super drum and give me some of those
fucking tomatoes back you don't deserve them all I need to eat stuff who needs
that who needs a family when I got this so much better than a wife I don't need
I don't need I'm gonna do a drone race just taking the bus all right so I was
trying to drag the map and I think an extra bus now great where is it up here
where is it drone race time there it is okay let's go on this it's that one I'm
going to destroy the competition right now and by the way this is the end of
the stream you're gonna make it no you are lined up in a perfect no how did you
do that it's actually harder to control this one because it's not first person
all right let's go drones what are we doing drone battle where's the drone
battle this is the drone competition yes need anything looking for a job
actually I could use that manure spreader over there interested manure
spreader know anything about construction repairs sure I'm good to
hear all right I'm in between travels sounds
fair where's the drone competition I walked into more work
who will challenge me who will challenge me no one it seems oh I have to have to
wait a day I slept a goddamn year and now I have to wait a day well wait I
didn't buy an animal I didn't do anything I'm busy hello there good
morning you look so pretty today it is so nice to hear hello good look it is
care to talk is there snow did you hear what thing goodbye bus station let's go
to the bus stop and let's go just let's go to the drone competition where's my
truck bus stop I mean yeah I mean life is a little hard right now but imagine
being that guy all he can do is drive around in a circle this is it I get to
show my there we go come join the local sports event drone race let's do it I'm
ready I'm gonna accomplish something in the game we're gonna laugh my ass off if
I win the drone competition and there's like a girl there that's flying drones
too and is impressed by my drone flying and then I can marry her I got the
fastest drone in the world what do we what do we take out our drones this is
what you are up against this right here is what you are gonna have to go against
wait Superman 64 when I gotta impress somebody slow down it's gonna be too
fast pull up pull up pull up pull up all right easy easy I won the race I won I
got a hundred dollars and twice the social points who cares hello there hmm
you really look beautiful today so nice to hear that wow I did it I won the
drone competition I'm the drone master whatever fuck all you hello well hello
this would be like the second quest I've done you care to talk hello is there I
need one of my fields called sounds good I'll take care of this so here is the
biggest field well nice work on that drone race you really just did so good
please cultivate my field for me this sad I'm running faster than this car oh
you know what this is what I'm good at do what you good at oh no you know what
you know what I have better idea well this is sad this is a culmination of the
last full year of this guy's life had to call a tow truck I can't even destroy
their crops anymore fine I'm gonna go away I'll make my own world down here in
player solitude I'm gonna go live on the beach wait how is this player solitude
when somebody lives here this is the first spot that I came to I actually got
off on this beach I rode up thought I could just throw myself into the world
of farming like people do Hollywood a lot harder than that I thought it could
have been easy this is the spot slept a lot but you know I was tired four years
ago when I arrived here the boat was parked on this beach it looks like
somebody stole that from me it looks like there's an invisible wall that you
can't cross you know just like in life how many invisible walls do we have set
up for ourselves the world is teaching me something right now I'm being shown
something very important that I need to try this with a truck it's time to
break down those barriers social points some how many likes you can get on
Twitter how many that doesn't matter to me and once it doesn't matter it stops
as you see every mountain is hard to climb it's about getting over those
mountains if the water seems too deep call on a friend oh no friends no hold on
when friends come in all shapes and sizes it broke it I broke the drone and
my other friends dead I have to run to a gas station now damn it it's sometimes a
stranger the kindness of a stranger it's all it takes but our furry
companions are the true friends what a boring fucking animal stop I need to get
that I need to get I need to I need to sell something I need to sell something
does any does anybody here sell do you sell anything I good morning I need to
trade good oh my god okay there's a coffee shop over here is there a store
in town no I have nothing to sell are you sure about that sometimes our
material things need to be let go oh well you fucking just get an AI oil
change for God's sake I have 17 tomatoes and a $10,000 drone I don't need the
same fucking ice cream truck stream snipers they're coming for me get them
hi care to talk good morning care to trade that's not enough I need to yeah
walking into Starbucks and asking the barista behind the counter if they'd
like to buy a $4,500 drunk I think you're gonna probably want to sleep on that
one all right tow truck where's my truck and sometimes you get a call on a
friend to pull you out no mountain news do I but that spot one spot that one
little spot I don't know I'm trying to get I'm trying to add sounds to the game
cuz there are no sounds that spot that my grandfather brought me to all those
years ago it's one of my favorite things when it used to be a kid and
sometimes you got a call on a friend more than once where's the beach where's
the beach guys this video they're dropping cars out of the sky why are
they doing this there are the dropping cars are coming from the sky in frame it
doesn't make any sense all right can I get in here now
hey holy shit it broke okay I made it that this old truck since I was 17 I
first got my permit when even that grandfather drove this over in our boat
it's a long paddle and sometimes you call on a friend sometimes you have to
try to glitch into the wall like you do on the houses sometimes you need to call
on a friend not this time this time we do it on our own
push sometimes you got to give up sometimes you got to give up sometimes
you want to go get a large greasy ass pizza so you don't want to do this
anymore I'm going to bed sometimes you got to go to bed although interesting
sometimes you have to stick around because there's an invisible wall next
to me and an invisible wall in front of me we're not leaving yet I can't leave I
can only go this way I think I did get out into the invisible wall because this
is blocked and this is blocked let's see what happens I'm going over this
waterfall can I I wonder what happens here can I actually make it over is it
moving I can't tell if it's getting closer or not no I found the true end
this is the true end yep that's it we're just stuck in the water forever but
sometimes alright see you guys tomorrow we're gonna play sniper contracts
tomorrow who knows if it's gonna be any good it could be terrible but I'm
willing to give it a try oh no everything is broken can I even change
scenes in OBS from the time traveling thing when I went for two hours it just
fucked everything up I think I can do it manually through here let me see can
I I can all right cool I don't think I can play the music though this is like
broken let me try to reopen this thanks for watching though guys that was a
farming destiny but whatever the damn thing is called farming whatever it's
got whatever farming simulator what's it called farming dynasty let's see can I
yes I can I can't even open a media file on my computer we're going musicless
apparently why did that happen why does that matter hold on I'm gonna like just
force quit it must I'm still library okay let's try this there we go all
right good although I can't see how loud this is because my my actual OBS is
completely broken I have no idea if this is too loud or I can't I can't tell am I
fixing it because I don't have an indicator how's that now it's too quiet
how's that I'll see the bits let's go over them from earlier thanks for
watching again everybody see you tomorrow probably for sniper contracts
let's teleport back to that was fun that was so I didn't do a goddamn thing but
that was a lot of fun let's go back thank you to uh no major no Neha AR
thank you for the 300 bits hey German thanks for the Vegas advice since
Danganronpa doesn't seem to be up your alley can I recommend force unleashed
it'd be a lot of fun to watch you throw Wookiees off bridges oh and to answer
your question I'm 24 all right um force unleashed should I play the force on
there's so many games that I just I have not played force unleashed is really
good there's two of them aren't there two is all right two is a second one
that's kind of sucks okay put it on the list guys I still have to play through
all the halo games so that's gonna be a while should be a lot of fun though and
half-life one no I'm not playing through I've already played through half-life one
a bunch of times hey Martin had a meme thanks for a thousand bits I say romance
dialogue options and experience points is this grass effect hey blue DK RF
thanks to the 500 bits and never make that noise again I make a lot of noises
on these streams so I'm sorry I don't know which one you're referring to I
was it was seven and a half hours ago whatever it was it was the really bad
one oh okay well that there that narrows it down for me thank you gnarly for the
250 here's another addition to the Jeremy was in my dream journal okay your
stream starting in an hour so I'd launched a steam game that was a souls
like set in Fallout New Vegas I got a steam alert that you just launched it to
I asked if you wanted to play with me and you agreed we played for like three
hours chat was fuming when you were two whole hours late to the stream we should
play again sometime hit me up dark souls like in New Vegas hit me up that sounds
like an interesting dream that sounds like a fun game too thanks to the 250
seriously thank you raddest raccoon for the 250 German play Chrono Trigger on
Steam on stream for me please I might do a remember when I played Mario RPG we
just did the whole thing that'd be another one of those scenarios where I
just play Chrono Trigger on stream I would not be experiencing anything new
it would just be me showing you how much I like this video game that's kind of
with Mario RPG I'm just showing you how much I liked this video game it's pretty
long too yeah it is it is pretty long you're right I don't know I did it once
maybe I'll do it again but thank you Raddest Raccoon thanks to the 250 for
Liddy we missed some subs I missed ten community subs from for Liddy thanks a
lot for Liddy for your ten sub drop appreciate it thank you pretend dear
thanks for the 250 today is yet another example of why we need germa psycho yeah
it'll be there eventually I tell you there's gonna be a stream dedicated to
just me just making emotes hey sad Vega thanks for the 250 this game is
unbearably fucking bad why am I laughing so hard at something so awful you spent
two hours trying to get $95 by growing tomatoes over the course of a month and
you did about $4,000 worth of damage to your vehicle in the process I didn't do
any farming I didn't know I did farming for other people right I did I did work
for other people I just dragged the thing on somebody's lawn I did plant
tomatoes though and they were succulent it was a fun game though vanilla grime
thanks for the 489 please help I can't I still can't stop using the bathroom well
I would go to a doctor have a doctor come see you thank you Jade sphere for
the thousand bits this is the my first time ever purchasing bits but I was
choking on my tears and had to find a way to give you some money well thank
you I appreciate it it was a lot of fun I had a good time I actually did laugh
pretty damn hard I would like I have tears are welling up in my eyes that was
fucking funny as hell hey stinky beaver thanks for the 250 turn on cam doesn't
work I have a turn on webcam blocker when I'm not wearing clothes which I am
not wearing any right now so it's not on thank you produce Sasan for the five
community subs thanks a lot produce or produces thank you and speaking of subs
hey why don't we just move over here take a take a walk with me take a walk
with me I'm just dropped my monitor holy shit that would have been bad and now
you're probably asking what the hell is he talking about I cannot I cannot
explain what I mean it's not possible for me to tell you what I'm talking
about I my monitor almost fell backwards just trust me on that one thank you for
all the subs welcome all the new subs all the community subs everybody that
sticks with this channel really appreciate it thanks for letting me do
what I'm doing cuz without you there is no me so thanks and don't you forget it
I guess not even sub ban him no you can express his opinion and I can express a
fart out of my ass anyways no thank you seriously I'm just kidding thank you
lab it or labette for the 400 bits this was the one of the funniest things I've
seen in a long time thank you you're welcome thank you for watching thank you
for experiencing with me I thought it was a fun game I just didn't know that
you had to actually spend like 12 hours in game to do anything it was it was
enjoyable a game doesn't have to be like nine out of ten on IGN to be an
enjoyable experience and you make your own fun sometimes that's more fun than
when you don't there's a good amount of water in here yeah he was about to say
good it has something for everyone farming simulator doesn't have drone
car flipping if you want your own car flipping in your game why is there a
drone in this game there's no camera on that drone you don't take pictures with
it why is it in the game just because that's just cool there's no farming
reason farmers use drones maybe they do red walrus thanks for the 346 hey tomato
pretty big fan of your YouTube content really happy that you're streaming now
if you consider playing any of the time splitters games on stream they'd be
pretty cool to watch if you and played with criken and what are you talking
about you know wrong stream haha funny joke but
seriously oh darn boy it'd be entertaining to see if you played oh
okay all right because tomato so I was saying tomato in a bunch of times there
were a lot of tomatoes in this stream also win back for the ps2 would be a
great stream pretty much the most influential third-person shooter ever
yeah uh I don't Joel came in here and was talking about doing doing a co-op
thing so is Joel streaming right now I gotta hit him up on discord
we were that way it was just like let's play a game and it's like all right
we're gonna play tribes and he was like yeah and I was like yeah and it was like
all right let's go then I went to sleep and it's been like a week or two I slept
for two weeks and what where are you Joel he's he's not on the same spot shit
what do you mean where is he where are you where is it where is he where is he
where am I I'm here I'm right here where is he he's not right is he here
right now where is he he's not here he's trying to sleep for months to
impress a girl no we we haven't even talked to each other about it but that's
a good you know after this free men's I'm gonna send a message and say hey
what are we gonna play hello master chief edition whatever we're gonna do
we'll do something me and Joel have been trying to play a game together for like
almost two years it just had never happened hey what do you want to do this
I'm kind of busy doing this oh I'm busy doing this I'm doing this I'm not gonna
be I'm gonna be gone for like two weeks so I'm gonna be gone for a week we've
been trying to play a video game for like a year and a half
sell him your drone he got busy and I got busy and then he got busy and I got
busy how do you hang out with friends these days it's impossible now we'll
play something it'll be fun it's been on the docket for like a year so well let
him up tonight see what he's doing you had over 4,000 people watching you try
to stack cars when you didn't say a word for five minutes it's crazy but I
failed I didn't do it that was the worst part I was trying and I failed I think
I've mentioned this a bunch of times before but if this was if this was
youtube.com slash German 985 from 2013 2014 I would have sat there every day
until I got that car on that roof even if it took 20 straight hours and it
would have been one clip in the video that would have been a total of about
eight seconds or nine seconds of time in the video but when you're on broadcast
and you're on a stream you got to move on sometimes you can't keep trying to
get the one thing you want yeah you know I'm willing to give it a shot so you're
saying is you don't care that much anymore no what I'm saying is if I turned
on my stream tomorrow and started moving a car with a drone with the same game
and that's what the stream was for seven straight hours and then I did that again
the next day I think I think people would be like I don't want to watch you
do this at all I don't want to see this and this is the you stream like three
sometimes four times a week this is what we're getting for the whole week and
then you're gonna take like a few days off okay well that was that was a cool
week of trying to get a car on a roof all right those aren't real fans it
sounds like a good stream to me they're almost it leaves there there are at
least two thousand insane fuckers here who would watch that I do realize that
um and those are hey and those are the fucking those are real ones yes the two
or three thousand of those there's 2200 people here right now you guys you guys
are the real ones the real ones no anybody that watches any portion of my
streams your thank you for doing that but if you're willing to watch me try to
flip a car with a drone for three days that's next level leavers I can't expect
anybody to like go sit there and watch that I'm just fucking around but thank
you for watching it don't worry it's fast forward to tomorrow when I try to
like snipe the same person for probably two straight hours and I mess it up
I can already see it happening don't worry I'll try to I'll try to flip a car
tomorrow okay I will flip it car if there's a flippable car tomorrow I
promise I will flip that car stream eat stream eating the deep dish pizza why
would you say I was gonna get a deep dish pizza I don't want I don't want
tomato paste in a pie tin did I just give a opinion on deep dish pizza you
sure did what's the last flavor of pie you've eaten banana cream pie and it is
the best it has absolutely no equal by the way let me give you a little bit
quick little like what fuck scenario why can't I find banana ice cream
anywhere I've tried everywhere I want banana ice cream not I the chunky monkey
is banana ice cream with a bunch of bullshit in it I don't want that I just
want banana ice cream no we have Ben and Jerry's has chunky monkey that's just
that's banana flavored ice cream with like walnuts and almonds and fucking
chocolate syrup and mm-hmm just banana ice cream it's hard to make it's
incredibly simple you just mash up bananas and blend it in with the ice
cream it's probably the easiest thing to possibly do then do it I don't have an
ice cream machine well I don't what I'm supposed to go buy an ice cream maker
then make my own banana ice cream that's actually a pretty good idea nice idea
good idea really good I'm gonna do that yeah cool I'm gonna get it I'm gonna get
an ice cream machine and I'm gonna make banana ice cream I'll make it better but
yeah banana cream pie is the best banana cream pie is better than chocolate
cream pie I think because chocolate cream pie is just fudge with whipped cream
on it let's be honest as banana creams way better it's just it's just mousse
it's just chocolate mousse with whipped cream all over it that's not I don't
think that's as special but German banana cream pie is just banana custard
with cream on it stop stop it don't get out of here get out of my room get out
of my room I'm just trying to get out of my fucking room all right Jesus some
people just come in and they just talk shit to me would you eat Dorito ice
cream no that's just I don't like to put bacon on my ice cream either people
look at put big look at a big bacon ice cream no I don't know that's too much
for me would you eat chocolate dough yes I would eat chocolate ice cream I love
chocolate ice cream cool rank ice cream flavors strawberry smooth without any
strawberry bits or pieces in it just strawberry flavored ice cream and I know
yeah oh he's a serial killer serial killer he's he's a serious killing he's
a serial killer no not sherbert just strawberry flavored ice cream plain plain
banana ice cream plain chocolate ice cream plain he sees case case killing
people and eating them he's eating he probably eats people I know I know what
you're saying I but I really do believe that straight-up just flavored strawberry
smooth ice cream is the best no no tearless no I know maybe tomorrow
well get it get me some good tearless maybe we'll do them tomorrow cuz sniper
contracts is gonna last like 38 minutes I'm gonna play it for like an hour and
I'm gonna be like this game's stupid and then we'll I already bought it so I'm
not gonna this is what we're doing I'm going in with low expectations so if the
game's actually good then we'll play the whole thing but let's finish up the bits
thank you stardust flair for the 300 bits thanks Jermis so many laughs tonight
and an amazing stream thank you glad you had a good time I did too
flug boy thanks for the 250 nearing the end of death stranding it's definitely my
game of the year it's not for everyone but it's a Kojima game for sure not
sure if you got your hands on it I have not I'm probably not going to play it
anytime soon because I heard it is it's something it's like a 50 hour game to
get to the end if you're like a 40 to 60 hour game that is that correct I don't
think I I'm not sure I'm ready to commit like 50 plus hours to a game at the
moment unless it was on stream because for the most part when I play video
games I play them on stream it's just kind of when I game at this point is I
do some stuff off stream and played God of War a little bit but 40 is standard
yeah it looks cool that's just something I don't think I would stream if it's a
game of the year that's good hey better late than never right we are almost at
the end of November game of the year but they say also that new Star Wars game
I'm hearing is very secure Oh like you should check it out you guys gotta help
me out on this one cuz I it's every time that new Star Wars game comes up
it's like don't play that shitty game it's boring and sucks and like the
middle five to ten hours of that game is dogshit and then another group of
people say it's so it's great it's so good you're gonna love it it's like fuck
this like it's like so split what I've been told is that it's fun like as a
complete package it's a fun game but there's like an unbearable like string
of five to six hours in the game that are just like this game's stupid you
played farmers dynasty but you can't compare you call on you cannot compare
the farmers dynasty stream to if I'm going to actually sit down and play Star
Wars the fallen order game that's like there's two different things going on
there I'm not going when I opened up farmers dynasty we would you know that's
the same mindset going and playing Star Wars on hard you played this for eight
hours yeah but I'm not gonna play this tomorrow for eight hours if I play Star
Wars tomorrow for eight hours I'm gonna play Star Wars again for eight hours the
next day we'll be flipping cars here yes you will you promised a roof car so I
can't I can't play Star Wars tomorrow then because there's a I can't put a car
on a roof how am I gonna put a car on a roof in a sniper game he's no I'm not
gonna play this again let me get some more opinions on the Star Wars game and
then I'll just probably just in a plane the damn thing there's you know what I'm
probably gonna play Outer Worlds I'm gonna play Star Wars game the reason why
I'm gonna say all this is because we're about to hit that point after holiday you
know from November into December there's gonna be like two or three months
straight with nothing releases so we'll get a bunch of good stuff now alright
we'll figure it out we'll figure it out we'll figure it out we'll figure it guys
we're gonna figure it out but disinterest thanks in 350 hey Jeremy I
cried with laughing multiple times during the stream just for you for your
information it was fun I can't believe he's gonna play real games what Dead
Rising and Dead Rising 2 aren't real games those are like some of the most
beloved third-person action video games ever those are like two of the most
beloved video games like ever everybody loves those games they're like those are
those aren't real games they're not they're shit whoa no one likes Dead
Rising 2 I thought it was okay a bump bumbo is not a real game that just came
out hold on I want to go look at my lap my past
dreams what have I been playing bubbles that's a real game oh let me see here
okay we had farmers dynasty all right I'll give you that one
kata kata Mari is not a real game the cut beautiful Katamari is not a real
what Planet Zoo is a real game well you guys don't like Katamari only triple-a
games count that's not fair what was the last triple-a game I played on this
stream I don't even play that I don't play triple-a games sometimes what was
the last triple-a game I played on this stream let's go back and find out I'm
gonna read every single video game I played in the last like six months okay
we got farmers dynasty bumbo Dead Rising 2 Dead Rising Katamari watching just
chatting videos okay right that was community night Planet Zoo that's that's
is that triple-a is Planet Zoo triple-a not really no it's not um Parappa the
Rapper is a triple-a game but does this have to be a triple-a game that came out
in the last five years that was like a first-party Sony PlayStation 1 huge
exclusive video game it was huge Darkwood fear Spooky's jump-scare
mansion numbers go up Hitman 2 there you go found one Hitman 2 and that was two
months ago so I'm every every couple months we'll play like a triple-a game
but I don't I mean they have to interest me that's hitman 2 DLC wait stop it
because it's DLC it doesn't count no it counts I played Hitman 2 it counts god I
love that game Hitman is just so this so fun Star Wars isn't all right well so
we got to pick one every couple months I play a triple-a game we got to find a
good one it's gonna be one that I really want to play we got outer worlds that's
not triple-a okay we have Star Wars triple-a that one's an option call of
duty I don't play no I'm not gonna play called it all the triple-a games of
Call of Duty games anyways what triple-a games have really okay triple-a games
you guys act like these triple-a games are like the grace of God let me see
triple-a games that have released this year are they battlefield and call of
duty okay here we go we've got Metro Exodus is not a
triple-a game Resident Evil 2 I played it it was great it is what I mean it is
Metro Exodus is a triple no it's not it's published by Deep Silver what do you
guys what okay what's a triple-a game to you guys
triple-a means high production value that's it it means it's $60 and it was
made by a bunch of people high budget okay all right so you got Metro Exodus
Kingdom Hearts 3 I'm not gonna play that game why would I Resident Evil 2 which
was fantastic okay apex legends not gonna why would I play that far cry new
dawn no anthem nope the division to absolutely not why would I play that
rage to nope any of these ringing a bell for his games that you desperately
want me to want to see me play so then if I don't if I don't haven't played
triple-a games this year then like what you want me to play you want me to play
the division to we need more division to on this stream devil may cry five fuck
that's one that's one that you got me you got me there yeah you got me that's
that that's one that I really would have played and I should have played but all
right so and then secure Oh and then Mortal Kombat 11 is on here too but I
mean Mortal Kombat is a really really cool thing but I it's a fighting game
I'm not I don't really invest time into them but as of all these ones on this
list I played the good ones Resident Evil 2 that's a good one
Sekiro that's one of the good ones devil may cry five is the only one on this
list I think that I haven't played that is like one of those single-player
experiences put it on the list we'll do it the Witcher 3 came out like four
years ago smash ultimate I played smash ultimate but I didn't stream it
triple-a pronounced and sometimes written triple-a is an informal
classification used for video games produced and distributed by a mid-sized
or a major publisher informal informal now I'm not against playing triple-a
games but I just I need to be into them that's crackdown 3 is technically a
triple-a game and I'm not gonna play that I to be completely and totally fair
though Metro Exodus and devil may cry are the other two that I have not played
this year but the reason why I didn't play Metro Exodus is cuz I had a melt
down during last light I played it for like 30 minutes and I died like ten
times on my hardest difficulty and I like had a fucking meltdown and I quit
the game forever so like I can't I can't just skip that game because I can't go
back to that game I've tried I thought about it I did the Metro 2033 and it was
really good it was awesome and then I played last night I had a head of full
on like I can't do this meltdown I just couldn't do I could not play the game I
don't know why it was something's going on I've put the difficulty in the wrong
place and I've rage quit it what about salmon max that's not triple-a you do
that a lot I do not do that a lot when was the last time I've rage quit a game
in 30 minutes and never played it again it was last light that was the last time
I did that you know how I know that because I remember it every damn day Neo
yes that did happen with Neo 2 but that was both way before last light hotline
Miami I beat hotline Miami and hotline Miami 2 we talked about tougher like
right when was the last time I rate I rate yeah I've raged in hotline Miami 2
but I stuck with it and beat the game he checks out that I know I know I do
even played rage shadow legends I don't even know what that is hey so Sretto
thanks for the four dollars and 20 cents hello beauty hello beauty lady
remember the stream that would would have been funny we were talking to the
pre stream chat or I think it was maybe even the recommended on discord
somebody said just to open up my iPad open up a like the first YouTube video
like I just open up as many YouTube videos as I can try to get ads and
click on every ad for every mobile game that's an advertisement and play them
download every ad game just go find them just open up any gaming website and just
go click on every one of those ads and download those stupid banner ads but
then I thought it's probably a really bad idea that's like a really easy way
to get just like on like a never-ending sucker list do it on a VM get an Emmy
letter specifically for virus streams just emulate windows for like the
specific virus mobile ad games we'll see it was a funny idea is there an update
on the Sultan stream not yet the fuck the king server stuff is still being
worked on which actually I can talk about this just a little bit before we
go this is going to be and I've seen a lot of questions about this this is
going to be because it has to and I really wish there was another way but I
really don't think there is this has to be sub only not only does it have to be
sub only but it might have to be multiple month sub only to join this
server for a few different reasons the unfortunate truth of the game like
Minecraft is somebody could just open up a script and just go in the server and
I have to be I have to lock it down where there's probably gonna be a
whitelisting phase before like a week or two before the stream and I'm probably
gonna have to do not just a one month concurrent sub because then what think
about that scenario oh okay well it's sub only I can get in that server all
right let me just I'll just pay five dollars and then jump in and fucking
destroy everybody so it's gonna have to be locked down we I've been trying to
talk back and forth with people that are working on it but we don't have a final
a final game plan I guess yet but it's absolutely gonna be sub only and
multi-month probably so and hopefully we can get enough of you in there tier
three subs only I'm not doing that I think as long as it's you've been subbed
for a full month like you're on your second month that's probably enough
because that means that people can't just sub now and in like two or three
four weeks when this is probably not gonna be happening for at least a few
weeks but I just don't want somebody to be able to sub like right now and we'll
have to find out it might be three I don't know we're also trying to get in
touch with some people that like code in Minecraft and some anti-cheat people and
I want to make this really work so I'm trying to put in I'm trying to put my
thumb in all the holes that are in the wall that's why I have kind of just said
hey I'm thinking about doing it and I want to do it and it's gonna happen but
I'm not talking about it in the last few days but there's an update on that I
know I've seen a lot of questions about is that specifically we'll see but we
have a two more bits to do thank you Malto for the 500 bits hey I'm
struggling with the acne can you recommend me a good dermatologist