Yo, what is up guys? It's Jerma again with a gameplay commentary.
This time I am on King of the Hill Viaduct.
There's actually gonna be two gameplays in this commentary.
There's gonna be one on Viaduct and then one on Turbine, Capture the Flag Turbine.
These gameplays were taken from my event that I had this afternoon,
where I made everybody flood an empty server.
I know that a lot of you guys had some bad ping and I'm really, really sorry about that,
but it will get better over time. I plan on getting my own server at some point here,
so let's get into the gameplay. This is an engineer, combat engineer,
using the Mini-Sentry, the Frontier Justice, and the Pistol, I believe.
Yep, the Pistol.
So my Mini-Sentry here gets three or four assists in a row,
and I get a couple kills with it, which allows me to switch over to the Frontier Justice
and get the Revenge crits. I destroy it, come over here,
this spy just destroys one of my teammates, but I get him right in the back.
This jumping Demoman goes down, too.
And then I get backstabbed by Larry, the combat spy,
who had it out for me the whole afternoon, and I was raging Cajun, man.
I'm telling you right now, I was raging Cajun.
So anyways, guys, if you haven't checked out the Borderlands let's play
that me and Leptor are doing right now, go check it out.
That's where I've been for the last couple days.
We've recorded a lot of footage, so I hope you guys check it out.
Go over to Leptor's channel and check that out.
Getting this teleporter up to level three,
which you never see people do this on a King of the Hill map,
which is very, very important because level three teleporters
make this insanely easy for your team just to get right to the front lines.
I somehow kill somebody. Who did I just kill right there?
Was that a disguised spy that I killed with that pistol?
I just had no idea. So I turn around, this guy's on fire.
He goes down with a couple of shots from the shotgun.
This Pyro, I knew he was going to come up here.
I'm trying to lure him up here with the Mini-Sentry.
I end up doing a great job of it. He gets killed.
Trying to get a little bit healthier. I thought the health was going to respawn,
but there's a dispenser.
There was like two other engineers that were on the team,
so it actually worked out pretty well.
So I go down by a Mini-Sentry from the other team.
Captain Defender had one place in a good spot.
And then Famous Amos, just being a real psycho,
comes over and tries to repair my Mini-Sentry.
And I'm not sure if he knows that or not,
but Famous Amos, dude, you're the man for trying anyways.
I appreciate it.
So let's respawn here.
Come out, get in my teleporter that I built to level three.
And this is where things get a little kooky
because there's just too much crap going on.
I come over here with the Mini-Sentry placed,
and there's an Uber charge.
I run out of the way because I'm not going to get myself killed
and wait for like a 25-second respawn.
Double engineers building up a dispenser to level three.
And then Larry, the combat spy, again gets me with a backstab.
So that's not good.
But what is good is the fact that my Mini-Sentry
has got a couple more assists before it goes down.
So we have less than a minute left.
They haven't even gotten onto the point yet,
which is good because we are probably going to win this round.
There's an engineer on the other team trying to build
a big Sentry up on the top right corner.
It does end up going up, which causes a little bit of problem,
but it's okay.
Our teammates are doing well enough where it's not a big deal.
I almost die from it, but I end up hiding in this corner,
and I'm not going to get myself killed by that.
My Mini-Sentry gets an assist, and I get the revenge crits
trying to get something happening, trying to get something going.
Build a little Mini-Sentry just to keep this point secure.
I thought I missed that engineer, but I guess I hit him
with the tail end of a pellet.
So now I try and do some sneaky spy bullshit,
and it doesn't work.
You'll see what I'm talking about.
I get behind everybody, and then watch this.
I'm going to get this guy. Ready?
One, two, three.
No, it didn't work.
And I just die.
But that would have been really funny if it worked.
I probably should have tried to taunt kill them or something,
but we end up winning the game with a flawless victory.
German number one, baby, even though it doesn't even matter who cares.
We're just playing for fun here.
And now we're going to move on to a medic gameplay.
Not really a medic gameplay.
I just want to kind of showcase the quick fix
and why I found a couple of good uses for it
and why I changed my mind on it a little, I guess.
So the loadout for this match is going to be the quick fix,
the ubersaw, and the overdose.
I find this to be a very, very interesting setup
because it allows you to be a combat medic, a real combat medic,
because you can run faster when you have uber charge on the overdose.
So it allows you to run around really fast and smash people like this.
Even though he's disguised and he was a dead ringer, it's okay.
I still made him have to use his cloak.
So let me show you now a good reason to use the quick fix.
This is a good example right here.
Three or four people in a row come over to me
and I heal them all to full health within five seconds,
which you would not be able to do with any of the other medic guns.
It's huge because now these three guys, these four guys now,
have full health, ready to run to the flag to get it.
And now I have an uber charge,
and this is where it really, really, really, really is cool
because you'll see what happens.
The guy with the flag really starts...
Oh, watch this, by the way.
Nice, like, fail.
Dude, let me, like, jump the fence.
Oh, no, I've got to walk over it.
So this is a great example right here.
I pop it.
These two people need health bad.
Boom, boom.
Full health automatically.
Amazing.
Really, really cool.
If I had the regular medic gun, I would be able to uber charge one person
and the rest of them would just die.
With the Kritzkrieg,
I would have had to just give somebody Kritz
and they could have just died instantly
from just somebody spamming with a rocket or something,
but not with the quick fix.
If you're using the quick fix, especially on a capture-the-flag map,
everybody's trying to protect this one person that has the flag.
And Turbine, Turbine is a pretty small quarters capture-the-flag map,
so everybody's kind of in that one middle area if somebody has the flag.
In a place like Two Fort, there's, like, five different places you can go.
The sewers, you can go around the top if you're a soldier,
you can go down the bottom.
But Turbine, you really need to protect your teammates,
especially the guy with the flag.
And that guy had, like, five health left.
And even if I uber charged him, the sniper that was next to him,
the other medic that was right there, probably could have just died.
And then by the time that the uber charge is done,
if you have the regular medic gun,
you're talking about it's you versus the world.
You and the soldier versus the world.
So it's great to have the quick fix and keep everybody on the same page.
That's why it's a fantastic new item.
Anyways, you'll notice that there was a cut.
And what I'm doing is I don't want to show a full gameplay
because I didn't really do that good in this particular gameplay.
I was getting kind of owned by a lot of people.
But this is a good example of why I underestimated the quick fix
and why I will not underestimate it anymore.
This spy goes down from Bacon.
And me and Bacon really, really rip shit up right here
because of the uber charge on this item.
I try to save this guy's life, but it doesn't work.
I uber charge Bacon and watch this.
He kills one, two, three, four, five, six, seven people
with the uber charge of the quick fix.
So Bacon, that was a pretty sick run.
And I will never, ever again pretend
like the uber charge on this item is not sufficient.
Come back over here with these two soldiers.
I get whipped, which makes this run really fast.
And we are going to cap this point, and we're going to win three to nothing.
I don't make it to the top of the charts, but that's okay.
These other guys did a fantastic job,
so I really appreciate them coming in.
This event was a lot of fun, guys.
I'll do a whole lot more of these.
And thank you for watching again so much.
I appreciate it.
And I promise you guys, sooner or later, I'll get my own damn server
so you don't have to deal with any of this bull crap anymore.
So thanks a lot, guys.
We filled the server. Let's do it again sometime soon.
Thanks a lot. Take care, guys.