Hello, how's everybody doing?
Yeah, we're very on time today.
That's what happens when you spend
two hours troubleshooting
mods, and you get it
to a point where, wait, oh,
he's talking, hold on. Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Three, two, one, what are you doing?
Hey, how's it going?
Hey, what are you doing?
People said they're shocked that we're
actually on time today. But what I was saying
is, we spent like
two hours getting this to work yesterday,
so it's gonna work now.
Yeah, it works now. We did it.
We double checked. We crossed our T's.
Everything's good.
Your guy needs some pants.
How'd you sleep?
Not enough.
No? Oh, that's right.
You got up and went to the gym, right?
I did. There was a bit of pumping
this morning. I actually got back like
an hour ago. Are you serious?
Yeah.
So you got energy
then? You're high energy then?
It's the opposite because it's like
a two hour session of like
now I have no energy.
I'm energized for some Elden Ring.
Okay. Well, so am I.
So you ready? Yeah.
What adventure lay forth
before a fun this eve?
I don't know, but should we
get a recap?
Sure. Okay. Yeah, because
I had imagined people on my stream weren't watching
until 2 a.m. last night in the like nine hour
ring session. That's really true.
So a lot of people that left. Here's a little bit of a recap.
Ah!
What the fuck?
I disconnected.
Oh, I'm back.
I'll re-invite you.
Okay. So that's pretty much
all that happened yesterday.
We did get
up to Ray of Lucaria.
But if you don't know, we're doing randomizer.
So nothing is
the way that it's supposed to be.
I don't know randomizer, but every item is randomized
and every enemy is randomized.
We got stuck with, I don't even
know the character's name, Placid
Deuce? Placid Deuce?
What's the... Placid Deucex
is the boss in Reina's...
Placid Deucex is the Queen of
the Moon. Yes.
He's the Queen and he still has two phases
and his second phase is Loretta.
But him teleporting through walls
was hard. We didn't beat it. So we got to
farm up. You have like
a deleted finger plus six weapon that I
can't give you. So we just need...
We're going to go around and do some catacombs or
like a little mini boss encounter
stuff. So we skipped... Honestly we skipped
a lot. We basically ran straight to
Lucaria. We have to... The wall right now
for us is... And we're not
going to reset. We're not going to reset. Do you want to know the wall
for me? Is that
your name is Mestrong and mine is
Mesmart because I am the spellcaster.
I have no spells.
I have not found a spell. You've been
casting spells though. It is
a weapon art but I don't actually have
a spell. But it still scales off of how
intelligent you are. You have to be really smart
to do it. I want you to be on my side that I
haven't got any spells. Like what if I had
Crystal Laser Beam Supreme? What if we
go into a catacomb and we get Crystal Supreme?
Yeah. But what's up with your title by the
way? Somebody? I didn't want to name
drop. I thought it would be better to just write
somebody. I wrote your name.
I wrote Sturr.
Oh you're going to name drop like that? Like oh you're
just going to get all the viewers because all he's playing with Sturr?
You know, I will
say, years ago
that was actually a great
idea. Those of you that don't know, back in
the TF2 days, Sturr was
big, big deal.
And if you put Sturr
in your title.
Alright, I'm playing with Derma.
If it was like oh dude, TF2
man, TF2 is like such a fun
game. Live commentary with
Sturr. I'll click this one.
A lot of the newer
viewers here maybe don't know. Sturr
was a TF2.
Yeah. If you don't know
you're getting the like way
washed up Sturr. You don't even know.
I don't think so. You don't know what you missed.
I think this Sturr
is pretty damn good.
He's a good guy.
All the Sturrs across the last
10 to 15 years have been good.
He doesn't afraid of anything.
No. I like each
Sturr. But anyways.
Anyways, onto adventure.
Did we kill the magmorm?
We did kill the magmorm at the urn tree. I know there's
down by the beach there's like a sewer
we can go down. Oh, by the way, I
played off stream and I know a lot of people are going to
yell at me. You fucking
piece of garbage. You human
garbage. But there's a very
hold on. I didn't do anything
though.
Get the fuck out of here!
It's one of these things.
Did I just hit him across the game?
Don't be afraid, man. Hey, hey, come on.
Hey, you and me. Hey, you and me. We're starting a new
arc right now. Here it is.
I'd rather fight a boss.
We ain't afraid. Look at that.
Alright, that arc is over. We can go on to
another one. That was like a pretty good one, I think.
Okay. Adventure 2.
I think we showed a lot of growth in that.
Why is there a golden sheep?
Is this rare? What is this? Oh, right.
Oh, a lightning sheep. That's right.
Okay. I thought there was like a randomizer
thing. I also never found where you get
that ability. I thought that
I thought there's gonna be runes or something.
Oh, anyway. Okay. So people ask
I may have
I just killed I killed the
same enemy like 10 times to get
some souls because I wanted to
get you. You have more levels than
me. But if you don't I wanted to buy
some smithing stones. What level are you right now?
I don't know. Why do you need to
I want to know what level you are. What level are you? And then I'll
tell you immediately after. I am 37.
You are as old as I am.
I'm 49.
Okay. We evened out.
That's like not bad. But anyways
I
wanted to get stones
because
a big boy.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah. I do
it all the time. And I think I'm pretty good at making
that joke. So I'm gonna do it whenever I get an opportunity
to. Let's help this boy.
Wait.
Could I could could I have duplicated
I could have duplicated shit, right?
Yeah. Oh my
God. All right. That's why we're saying
not to do that. I remember
it being well, I know this was a long time
ago, like a year ago when randomizers
burst out all of my
duplicating my ship with
super glitch. Do we have we have another one of those
like poison spitter teleporter
pieces of shit on me?
It's funny
that you said that. I know exactly what that meant.
And I'm poisoned.
Sorry, just poison is not that bad.
You just heal through it.
What's that character's name? Royal
what's the character's name?
The character? The thing that we just saw.
That enemy? I have no idea.
Royal Revenant.
Royal Revenant. That sounds like a League
of Legends item.
I think the I
think this is random. Is it random?
You get like an item in here too.
I can't remember. Who knows?
That felt like it lasted
a long time. All right. So what's in here?
Oh, look at you.
I still haven't found a remembrance.
I am so sorry about
this. I have to apologize immediately.
But I need to get
I need to be in a safe spot.
Because I
auto needs to go outside. Follow
me. So I can't really follow
you. We're going to the shack. We're going
straight up to the shack because there's a merchant here
and then you can
You can go off and care for your
doggy. I don't know where you're going.
Straight west.
Straight west. The game really does not
like sometimes when you get on your horse.
I think it's when we transition
areas. I don't know. Yeah. You kind
of desync for me too. I'll just follow
you. I got to let auto up.
Let's get to a spot where I can
not going to take me long. Maybe
less than five minutes.
Less than two minutes. Show auto.
Maybe. You're good.
All right. I'm just going to if I just sit here
while that screw anything up. No, you're good.
All right. Oh, also I got another
sacred tear accidentally. I
love that for you.
All right. I'll bear it back. I'm just literally
going to leave this open. My merchants selling
two different seed bed curses.
I'm not even going to mute my microphone.
I mean, I'll mute it over here. But I just
you know what? No, no, no, no. No, I'm going to mute you too.
I've
learned over the years.
Probably a good idea. I don't want to say
anything weird, but I'm going to feel pressured like I
have to. Any time that you are under
pressure to like talk,
you just talk and you
just you know what? I'm just going to say whatever the fuck
I'm going to say. Hey, guys, see
that. So I did. He's gone.
I got rid of him.
I'll be right back. I'm not going to put actually, you know
I'm going to put a BRB screen. People can be like, what the hell is going on?
Right back. Yeah.
Telster.
It's cringe. Yeah.
That's the first thing people hear.
It's cringe. All right. So
hold on.
Yeah. Sorry. I had to take Otto out.
He's good. He's relaxing in the other room.
Was he and is he
a good dog? Yes. Okay.
That's good to know. Of course he is.
What's the worst thing he's ever
done? I don't think
there really is anything. He's
a really good boy. He is.
He just, I remember he doesn't
like do anything. He just kind of chills. He just kind
of just hangs around. He kind of hangs
out. Never like pooped in your bed or anything?
Ate too many Oreos?
No, my dog has never pooped in my
bed. Oh, my dog
has. Bro, your stream title
is boring. But who
cares?
Randomizer gaming with stir.
See, that's how I felt too. Like just like
game with name is like the
worst title. It is, but that's what yours
is. Yeah, but I, you're
horsing in place. Okay. Well,
let's teleport somewhere. Okay.
Well, I want to, let's teleport to the shack.
Like, like, let's just actually teleport
to the shack that we're right next to. New
title? Name it swag gaming
with my man. Um,
I can't, I, again,
as, again, I was at the gym.
My brain is gone. I, there is
no cleverness. Ah, shit, I forgot.
You know what, do you know what
I really want? I do.
I want, I want
pads
for my elbows. Your elbows get just
absolutely fucked up like mine do.
Sitting in a chair. Uh, I have
like purchased like elbow
pads for my chair. Is it, is
that a, was it worth it? Yes,
100%. Because when you sit
here for long enough. I have a double layer.
I feel like it doesn't matter what kind of chair you
have. You always, if
you sit here with your elbows and your forearms
in the same spot, you kind of get that
like, you know what I mean? Like
this part of your elbow. You're gonna get that anyway, but like
it is way better with the pads.
Alright, let's move. Let's get started. It's been,
we've been stalling for 15-20 minutes.
Where, where do we get elbow pads?
Up this way? Wait, no, I want it, I
want it to go, there's like the, the swamp area
this way. I'm gonna put both headphones
in just for you. Well, then you're gonna
speech jam yourself because you can't hear yourself.
No, I actually, I've actually gotten a little bit better with
this. Oh, you've been training?
Yeah, I've been putting both in recently. It still
kind of sucks, but it's fine.
Proud of you. Oh, I thought
there was an enemy in here. You're no
enemy. Whoa, but there's something here.
Oh, my God.
I am so lucky in this
run. I just got, I got millennia's
remembrance.
You fucker. I think mine
was like a lily, like just a flower.
That's one of the most expensive ones.
You should dupe it. Well, let's go clone it.
No, no, no. Oh, you
mean dupe it. Yeah, let's go do that. Let's go.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Saddle up. Oh, my God.
Is this actually gonna work?
Yeah. Am I gonna get like a hundred,
two hundred thousand souls right now? They
might, like the other one you had, the Radon one
you had, I think it was, might be reduced
in the amount. But yeah, you're about
to fucking. Oh, yes.
Escalate. Okay.
Get off the horse.
I can't get off the horse. I don't
think the horse is supposed to be able to come in here. I don't
think so either. Okay, there we
go. Oh, look at that.
Let's dupe it. Wait,
what does it give you if you didn't dupe it?
What? Who cares?
I'm curious if the items are, should
be different. I think it's randomized.
Give one to stir.
Give one to stir. No, fuck that.
This is my shit. Okay.
I'm kidding. I'm kidding.
No, use them both. How do you,
how do you, can I? Can you?
No, you can't. You cannot do it.
The true colors.
I remember this being an issue last time
and my chat was like, I can't remember.
But they were like, you can't do it at this one because it's
too high level of one, but you can do it at the other one.
I don't know, man.
Alright, dude, I have, I have a hundred,
I have a hundred and ten thousand souls.
Alright, let's go die to like a
crab or something. Alright, yeah.
Do you want to go somewhere where it's really dangerous and like
should we put, want some steaks on this or
something? Because this is kinda not fair.
Yeah. There's another cave up
this way, I'm pretty sure. No, I'm not,
I'm kidding. We're not doing this. I'm
gonna go level up. Baby boy.
Little baby boy.
Oh my god, look what he's like
skidding.
What the fuck, what are you doing?
I'm trying to do, I'm trying to do my laugh.
You're trying to do
your own laugh. Yeah, like that. You're doing an
impression of yourself laughing.
Okay, where did you go? Let's teleport back to the shack.
That was the Joker?
That was scary. It wasn't
scary.
Don't I do that? We're super
desynced. I just teleported to the shack.
Did you? I just said to.
I voted to warp. I voted
to warp. We're not
doing it.
It says it failed. Um, it says
you are going into the ocean.
That was very weird. I arrested
the bonfire. There you are.
Okay, so this is important
because I'm about to level up the most,
this is probably the last amount of levels I'm gonna be able to do
for this character. It's not true.
Boom. First of all.
Okay. You have so much growth
ahead of you, honey. Okay, here we go.
I can only level up six times?
Alright, what's happening
here? I could do...
I'll dump it all in strength. Should I
do intelligence? Without any
thought, dump it all in strength. All
in intelligence to be able to use this
item correctly. Please, for the
love of God. Please, for the love of God.
Why does that weapon even need intelligence?
But wait a minute. Me
strong is not supposed to be doing this.
People are pissed right now.
You're being weird. You're not
being strong. People are fucking
pissed off. Alright, well here's the
deal. Here's the deal.
If I put
16 into intelligence, will I be
able to effectively use this weapon without
it being just like nerfed in my hands?
Or do I just
go boom into strength
and go upgrade this greatsword thing
that I have with default shit? Strength.
Strength. Strength. Strength. Me strong.
Me strong. Me strong. I'm doing
intelligence and you're copying me.
You're copying me. What do you guys think?
Do you think... 16
isn't smart. It's not.
What do you want me to do? I want you to put points
in vigor, actually. With all of the
plus to estus flasks you have.
Yeah. I think...
That way you don't die in like one hit to placidusax.
I am gonna do something right now
and people are gonna be really saying,
dude, you blew it big time. But
here's what I'm gonna do. I blew it.
I blew it big time. I blew it.
I have to go to the blacksmith
because I blew it. You blew it?
Where is the... No.
No. Not yet. What do you mean not yet?
Not yet. Hold.
What are you talking about? While we're here, I wanna do
one thing while we're here. But look, I have
this. I can just upgrade this to
probably plus 10, plus 15 right now because I have
a bunch of stones. And this is strength.
You're gonna have to wait. You're gonna learn a lesson
in patience right now. So let's go.
Wherever you wanna go. Oh, look. Look. I found
Millennia's Remembrance. Oh, look. I'm gonna get like
a plus 10. Oh, look. I have like 10 levels.
Fuck you, dude.
Where do you wanna go?
I wanna go to this graveyard that's like right here
with a whole bunch of items on it and a dragon guarding it.
Oh, there is a dragon right there. Okay, cool.
Let chat seethe.
Okay. I got like two useless notes
off of this graveyard. I don't want
them to seethe, but I think that
I think it's worth it. He doesn't have a lot of health.
We're so desynced in this area for
some reason. It might be just this spot.
It seems to go in weird cycles
where we desync, but then we get back to normal
for like two hours and then it desyncs for like an hour.
Oops.
We're fighting it, so...
Ow. Don't go in the
air. Dragon,
you're being quenched.
Try hitting it.
We're in a weird spot. I'm not
the type of character that can fight a dragon that well.
Okay? Hey.
You just... Hey, let him seethe.
Seethe.
I hit it.
Looks to me like the dragon's dead.
What are you doing? I think we're desynced.
Silly is secret.
This is actually a good idea.
Although I didn't really get
much. Did you get anything good?
No, I got like notes
and cookbooks like usual.
Notes, some cookbooks, some
runes. Okay, so that's
completed. Let's go ahead and mark that as
completed. I don't think that's normally
a boss. Do you
do you want to fight a boss?
Because I know where one is right now.
Yeah. This tower of return takes
you... I forget where this takes you.
Where did you even go?
We are really desynced.
Just kind of wandering. I'm in like
a constant state right now of thinking I know where
I am and then going somewhere and going, no, this isn't
it. Okay, so
you teleport to
the northern
lake, northern
lake shore, all the way up
where the runes are, the king's
realm runes. There is a boss
right there. Where?
We need to figure out, like people are saying
there's a hotkey to accept a vote.
No, do road to the manor first.
Let me upgrade this fucking sword, please.
Where the blacksmith is. And then right
below that is a boss we can fight. LB
in the map, apparently. You have to be
in the map. Oh, and
then, yeah, then it centers on
whatever you voted for. Really?
That's cool. I'm kind of the master of trying to
teleport somewhere and just placing markers
on it. The markers are so helpful.
We need to keep doing it.
Alright. Do you have any smithing stones?
Six?
I probably do, but I'm likely about
to use them. No, I don't.
So, this is the idea.
Here we go. The idea
is this. Why is he acting like I never talk to him?
Okay, see this banished knight's
greatsword? I'm thinking
of just
upgrading the hell out of this right now.
Just upgrading this. And infusing it.
Right? Either this or the battleaxe.
And I don't know which one
is better, because I don't know
min-max bullshit. Battleaxe
or banished knight greatsword?
Which one of these is, like, better
to use? I think the greatsword
probably better. Sword, big sword,
sword, sword, sword, sword. Axe is cooler.
Sword, sword, sword, sword. Axe is cooler.
Axe, trust me.
Sword, sword, sword, sword.
I need more smithing. I can't believe
not every person in your chat didn't say the same
thing. I need how many more
smithing stone ones do I need? You need three
smithing stone ones to get out of,
I think. I think three. Yeah.
I need two more smithing
stone ones. You can buy them at the shop
at the place.
Okay. Can I
just go there? Can I just get this out of the way?
I promise I won't be doing this again.
He grinded off stream.
I didn't grind off stream.
I just prepared off stream.
I didn't get exposed. I literally killed the same
enemy ten times and then bought like a dozen
stones at the vendor. Did you accept
it? I thought I did.
Here. I was just gonna fucking banish
you. I have the cheap
upgrade thing and I think you don't was part of
the situation as well. What do you mean?
You have to actually spend like
three, six smithing stones.
Yes, I do. I don't. So that
was the whole problem yesterday. The whole problem was
you have the cheat code and I don't.
Who's this?
Oh, it's okay. This is
very, very odd. I thought it
was a chicken. Okay, how many
of these things do I need?
Oh, I'm back already. Lay out your arms then.
Tarnished. Where are you going?
You've played this game fucking thousands of times.
How have you not figured out where the blacksmith
is permanently in your brain? You fucking
idiot. I just don't know how it's possible.
It's by the fire. To the left of the fire. Don't
forget that ever again. Okay, we're good.
Boom, boom, go.
Go, go. All right.
I got a plus eight.
I got a plus eight greatsword.
I need one more smithing
stone three. Do you have one of those?
Smithing stone three. And just a regular smithing stone three?
I do. Excellent.
If I please have it I will trade you for something that I have.
What do you need? I needed like a spell.
You want me to list out the spells I have?
Do you actually have spells? Do you have any
like...crystal greatswords
or anything? I have...
This one's really important. You need this one there. There's your and I also have
Gelmer's fury you need style. That's not I want arcane pick that up off the ground
It does not belong on the ground. I mean you picked it up starlight. Did you pick this one up?
No that I dropped the stone for you. Oh
Tonish what the fuck is wrong with you Mike? Here we go
I have a plus ten great sword now and it's good and it's it's just a regular sword and I can infuse it
What stone do you need after that?
Hold on. Let me do this first. This is probably this one right heavy will six one sixty seven that okay
I I have smithing stone fours you can use to get to 12. Where is this better?
No, no, I am I'm I put fire on it
I need you shouldn't put fire on it because then I think it's faith scaling. Okay
What do I need fours are there any smithing stone fours flame of red main is insane
I need do I I need one smithing stone four and then I will just have to go
Do you have any smithing stone fours? Yeah, I have two also one down take this as well because I have a
Couple of scrolls like spell scrolls that you should probably be using royal house scroll. I can't leave it. Nevermind
I put it down in the main room. Thank you so much. Okay now
Everything is gonna be good to go. I have a plus 11
This thing's doing like this thing's doing like three four hundred damage. This thing's good to go
All right, the crack blade is shit on bosses. I'm just I just wanted to scaling use fire use fire. Everyone's
Telling you you're wrong. Yeah, I am right
There is one fire that I believe is faith and there's one that's actually strength. I am wrong and I apologize
That's like less damage though. That's all right. Wait, what wait what just happened? This better? It's oh, it's split damage
Craig please
Okay, here's what's gonna happen. Why am I so confused by this? This is 232
232 14 135 versus
214 no, it's whatever. It's the fucking same. It's OP fire. I'm just gonna keep this
This is what I'm using for now. We'll figure it out later fire infusion, please great sword swings. You're picking the same infusion
What? All right. I gotta stop looking at chat cuz like I look over here and I go wait
Why don't I look over here? No, all right. Here's what I'm doing. I'm almost my brain is split between two spots
Here's what I'm doing. That's what I'm doing. That's what I'm doing. I
Can't just like flip-flop for like the next hour. Okay, I'm ready from here
Where do you want to go flame of red me and got nerfed so hard. It's shit now chat
I don't know. I I'm just gonna go with the crack do something that you like. That's what I'm gonna do
So let's now you run it when I go fight the boss to go back to the Smith
I'm gonna go down that actually lightens up the load a little bit. I could put on some better armor. All right, we're good
Just a short 45 minute stalls not a big deal. I thought stall its progression. That's true
We're not gonna do a raid as a guild until your gear score goes up. Tell chat stop being backseat Andes
No, I mean, here's the problem
I keep asking different questions and reading so I ask five questions and then I get an answer to the second question
And I think it's an answer to the first question while people are spamming an answer for the fourth question
So I'm like so confused
It's my own answers to questions that are
That like also played the game a while ago and they've actually patched and balanced a lot of stuff and like I don't even know
What is real anymore? It's my it's my it's my fault though. It's not their fault. All right
So you're ready ready to fight the boss? There is a catacombs like right here. Yeah, it's a it's literally I haven't marked
I did have it marked and it's marked
Um
Where is it writer? It's right here somewhere. Where is it? This place is a bit of a mess. I haven't marked like right here
I'm doing so much more damage. I'm doing like 300 damage a swing now. It's so worth it
This crab coming over here. I got
Wrecked are you alive?
Yeah, uh
It's over. It's not over there. It's over here. It's near my marker
The hell is my mother I
Remember every playthrough I've ever done. I've wandered around this place forgetting where this hole is. It's right here
I it's my markers right here
It's right here somewhere
Goddamnit. What where where is it? Oh shit. Hey, you want to go back to round it?
It's the floor. Oh, it's a little it's an illusion floor. It's illusion floor. I was saying like what the hell
Like some trick to this one. Oh
shit
What the hell is this is an interesting swing? This is kind of a bunny. This is like a goofy swing
What?
Where are you? I make a giant rock candy stick. I'm not getting rid of this
Why did you guys want me to do anything else down here? This thing does 400 damage now. You gotta be shitting me
I can't believe people were telling me to do the fire
When you say down here, okay, so let me come find you. I think guys there there we are
Okay, and for reference I have a plus 20 long sword now and then when you ask me in two hours and you're like
Surprised that I have it. I just want you to know now you have a plus 20. Did you grind off stream? No
Did you see my like super cool rock candy sword? I did not this is so cool. Wow. I actually love this
I didn't even know this is in the game. Huh? Yeah, that's so cool. It looks like a
Like a kebab gone wrong
Yeah, it looks like it looks like a like a kebab you left on the grill for like six hours. All right, let's do it
Okay. Well, this is a problem
Wait, don't maybe don't aggro that don't aggro the the crystal night. I think he's gonna get spawned in. Yep
He is that's when he gets activated
All right. It is imperative that we thought this room is so small
We have to just like co-op the fuck out of one of them early. I
Thought the one with less health
Well, I mean like when we first get in here like we just nice holy shit. Oh
Come on. There's no way. There's no way. There's no way. I
Can't believe that why did it not hit him? How did that not hit him?
It's all right. Now you have a you have a 1v1 now with your plus 20 sword. You can do it
It's just it's a regular crystal night. The worst part about this is doing them both the same time
I'm used to doing it with a shield that can parry this one can't
My damage is too low against him. I like need to parry him. Remember the timings
This shield cannot parry. Oh, you actually can't parry
I'm out of healing
Well, it looks like you're just gonna have to do it. Sorry. I don't know I the hitbox he apparently I don't know
I swung the sword at him and it just didn't I just didn't hurt him
America. Yeah, we can do it. Don't switch my shield. We just need to
Go absolutely hard on the first boss
Missed be gone. I love that word
Missed be gone. I love how you read dead just left your horse like well the horses keep desyncing
So I just got off of it. I don't know. I'm down here. Hold on. Don't go in. All right, let's go
That's rolled right into that
I'm gonna distract this one over here. I still don't know the timings on these guys at all
It's been so long since I've seen them
I'd rather fight the crystal night
The crystal night has so much health. He's distracted. I died. He distracted him right into me
He's just not he kind of just decided he was gonna go after you
Crucible night is being I know he really is he's letting us duel. Oh, this is over now. No, no, no
Jesus that's fucking fast
The misbegotten warrior is so annoying because he does that jump in the air where he he has to jump in the air swing
One of them is insanely fast and one is incredibly slow. Let me uh, I will try and take aggro from the crucible night
Once he spawns that's one of the bosses like the early one that you fight in the the jail
That might be one of the longest times I spent fighting a boss in dark and Elden Ring to be fair
That's like I'm used to shit. I consider this fight to be one of the worst fights in the whole game
What do you mean this this randomized fight? What do you mean this fight this boss fight? Did you not do this either that it's randomized
What do you mean? Did he not do this in the main game? Oh my god, dude
Hold on. Did you have you never seen these two in the same room together? No, dude. You got to play Elden Ring
You got a play that you got to play Elden Ring man
You've never seen these two people in the same boss fight. I don't think so
Okay, so
In radan's area when you go to fight radan, uh-huh. You did not
Fight these two you did you know, did you ever go back to radan's castle?
Yeah, you know, this is a boss fight in the game is the crucible night and misbegotten warrior. Okay, I guess I missed it
Holy shit. Sorry. Oh my god. I'm like jealous of you. I'm actually like incredibly jealous of you
You've got like a lot of game. Well, I've got like full aggro. Let's start hitting them. This fight sucks
Unbelievable unbelievable start unbelievable start he's almost dead
Careful. He's coming this way. I'm fucking this up so bad
If I could just land one fucking hit on this guy
Okay, he's dead. We're good. We're good. We're good. We're good. We're good. He does have a shitload of health
Oh my god, it's the armor. We need like a blunt weapon. I think this is technically blunt. There he goes with this bullshit
Good good. Good. Good. Good. Uh-oh. Oh
Oh
It's okay, but I got I got it. I got it. I got it. Yeah, you got it
it's
You can't win the first part of the day
We're good. We're good. I I thought I was going crazy because
When we were talking about how this was not in the real dance castle, we're Dan. You got me saying it. I'm sorry
Yeah, so the when you first said that you were like, what are you talking about? This is randomized
I thought you were fucking with me. No, I
Don't castle had like all the chimeras and stuff the Kimmer Kimmer is so I was like nah
I didn't explore it too much. Actually, I don't blame you cuz that area is is probably one of the shittiest areas in the whole game
I didn't even know there was a catacomb in there
I I do not blame you for skipping that part of the like of the optional kind of stuff
Well, I'm dead and I got to get my souls on that item
But I do you want me to fire me you have a bonfire go to the castle before the festival
I thought once you get to the castle the festival has already started. I think if you it I think if you beat
Dan if you kill for Dan and then you go, maybe you skip it, right?
Where's the bonfire from here? No, I think a lot of people don't bother going back after the tourney
It's possible this fight only happens if you go to red main early. It doesn't happen after the tourney even afterwards
There's one of the teleporters that just takes you straight to the festival and then it was like, okay festival
Then I did for dawn and then look the whole castle looked like shit. Oh, yes
I already I already did the boss. So like why would I go back to the castle? It can happen after I guess it does happen after
The hardest to find I lost again. I hope you don't I think I know leave me alone. Leave me alone
Sorry, I got so upset with you. We're not knowing where the secret boss was
That's impossible to find something that I did that you didn't do
I'm going to and say probably not and I'm the only I'm gonna give you one reason why that is it's not because of
Playing it but it's because of watching every single fatty video on this game
So I I don't think there's anything that I haven't seen not for my own doing I got what did you get in there?
Like a spear. Oh cool. I got a glass shard
I'm taking up a lot of glass my hand is raw
See, I just thought I thought you were messing with me. I was trying to mess with you back, but then no I was the wrong one
I remember we were talking before the stream started about how I'm actually a from soft from soft fraud. I
Don't think that's true
In Sekiro, you know the big giant fire beast. Yeah. Did you do that? Yeah, I did. I did not do that
There's a lot of things that I've noped out of but you know, I'm a bit of a fraud isn't that smart though
You're just kind of smart because if you go to like an optional area and you just like this is dumb
I'm not fucking doing this. You're kind of like like really shitty from sauce bosses
I actually that that fire boss and secures is way up there for me
Yeah doing the the hate with the hatred at hatred boss, right?
Doing that boss and after like the 20th attempt just going like, you know what I could like go mow the lawn right now
I don't need to do this
I don't think that's a bad thing
So let me clear that okay
I think we have an opportunity to attempt the boss again last to do 66
But I feel like if we do that this early we might get trapped there and it might be like a disaster
So let's um, you know how you you can go up the whole right side or left side of the lake. Mm-hmm
Like let's just go like we haven't done any of that
There's like a whole urn tree and there's catacombs and there's a whole bunch of stuff on both sides
Yeah, let's let's take it slow. Well, you want to you left or right side? Um, let's go on the left side
I feel like there's more things over there. I remember let's start at the
The ruins way at the bottom and just like hugged the left and then you go up into like the albaneric village and all that
Oh, you want to go you want to go all the way down down? Okay. Yeah and on the map remember press left bumper
It'll take you straight to it. Yeah that we hold that left side is um, you're saying I think no map
We have to get a map. What is this title randomizer with stir emotional Halloween special?
That's actually pretty good. That's that's good. It's way better than I did. I am getting a bit emotional
full emotional playthrough
Emotional Halloween special I should be in like an orange shirt to be really fair though that whole Ronnie quest line
I don't think is I at least in my opinion
I don't know how you would do any of that like there's so much of that that's kind of I was like
Why would I do this? I actually did do it you did. I mean I got a lot of hell cave right here
I I mean I had to read like, you know, there's no way you do it like intuitively
It's a total mess
That's what I mean like doing that without any guidance is like I don't even know why you would even do some of that stuff
Why are you even attack?
How do people even how do you I feel like a lot of people kind of stumble upon it like the first people that do
That mission they stumble upon it and they go
What the fuck just happened and then they go oh my god and they and they write it down because obviously the first person
It took me to a whole bunch of places
I didn't even know existed like the whole ant like ants as an enemy type was like one of the last things I found in
The whole game was like, I don't know how I missed like an entire like ant cave
I think that's part of the reason why people like these games so much though is because
It's just stuff that you're never going to do and that's cool. Yeah
Thank God we bought let me cast my magics wrong one. Wait, don't do it yet. I know what you're about to do
Don't do it yet. Where are you? I cast starlight. No
Okay, you got a little bit of a lightning situation up there we do
Let's keep we don't gotta go up there screw them
Thank God you have that spell are we both long sword Andy's we are are we?
Copies me you copies me. I did cuz I I took what you said to heart
What did I say? I'm just like it's just works and it's good and it's not like oh I have to do this
I have to do this just pick the thing that works and it's good. I thought there was a turn in here
I did too. Oh, you gotta go into the waterfall. Oh
Who what am I talking about here?
What the hell are you doing? I mean I gotta get something from the nominees here. We haven't done it once
I'm just gonna do this now so that in a year from now people can tell me this was the worst sound
I'm gonna make sure that category to get filled out at the end of the year. Um, I think we go down
Down. Oh, yeah, I got it. I got a epic. I got an epic loot up here
What? Oh, yeah, you do go down of rune arc nice
There's usually something scary down here. Isn't there at the end of this cave?
I believe it would normally be one of the berserker guys. I
It sounds like a dragon. It's something very loud something big
Has very heavy footsteps. Yo, watch my back
These guys don't get wash my back bro. I can't do that when the thing explodes
Secrets over here. Oh, hey. Hey, I gotta cast my spell wait. Okay. It's getting a little it's a little dark in here
I mean, thank you. Maybe it's like a starlight kid
There it is. Thank you. I'm only gonna do that once. I don't I don't even know what that was. They're all staff
I'm only gonna do that once every ten minutes. Okay, I've gotten like four stabs at this point and one spell
I even upgraded the ones. Oh god. That's a lot of guys. Why why they don't why they don't they don't care
Over here. I'm gonna take their item. No, you angered them. Oh
No, you have angered them. All right. Well fuck him up
Why is this one's huge? Oh, you've never seen the huge albinoeric
Yeah
Have you seen the huge albinoeric? Yeah, nice
See, I got something good here
Oh man, I think that's actually fucking a thousand times better than what I have
God every item you pick up is a thousand times better than what you have
Let's go upgrade it
But I really I really mean it this time like I think this actually is the like unbelievable
It's faith weapon. Whatever. I'm sticking with what I have. What is it?
God slayer great sword
Oh
Oh god
God's flame. Oh flame
Another staff, I'll be careful when we go through the darkness if something's gonna appear
Ooh
Oh a jar
Oh, that's another good one. I can't believe elden beast was down here
Don't say that
Uh, is it time to put pants on?
Yes, it is
Uh-oh look out. It's a snail
This is the gimmick fight. It is the gimmick fight
Just to go where it's kind of lit up
This is like at all like a glow i'm just distracting the guy
You you handle the snail and he's just staying in the same spot. He's kind of dumb
elden beast
Cookbook
Got a flower. This is a question for chat
These two weapons are effectively the exact same weapon, but there's weird
This one scales differently. Do I have the right call?
Is the bandage still better than this?
You could do fire on the other one and do weld them
I'm gonna get this to plus 20 at least right we have to
At least I got ice frying hatchet
I think that is one of the things that actually did get nerfed a lot
That's the speedrun kind of broken speedrun item, right?
The earliest I think that was one of like the first nerfs
That was an epic dungeon there my friend
No, that was good. We got some good stuff
The medallion that's a good question. The medallions might be a problem
We can get there one of them. Oh, you do already have one of them. I have the like left halig tree medallion. Okay
Uh, I think I think you just have to teleport out of this one
Yeah, I think we we need to go get the map. Can we go to like the south ray lucaria gate and just go just get the map
uh, okay, because
Yeah, this is
Irritating me
Did you vote?
Wait
um
Change that go to the the laski arm ruins
You hate my teeth
They're mine. You don't have to worry about it
In the middle of that somebody goes hey dude, thanks for clearing up my mucus. I like appreciate it
Did you no, it's just I just look I look over here sometimes and somebody just writes a random sentence
Like I feel like that person was actually talking to a doctor and they like talked in the wrong channel. He's a bot
Although why would you text that to your doctor? Oh, hey, dude. Hey, thanks for clearing up my mucus really appreciate it
it's like why I
I mean if your doctor helped you with your mucus, I'm sure he'd like to hear that he helped
But if I went, I don't know if I every time i've gone to the doctor
It's not like oh, hey, yeah, i'm gonna text you and let you know like when I wouldn't like my uh throat throat gets better
I don't know where you're going. I got the map
Oh
I'm just trying to get all you want it. I'm just trying to get away from all the
You made me turn around and now i'm getting attacked
Uh
Now we can go wherever you want
Uh come mortar. Can you see where I am? Yes, I can
Yeah, there's like a jumpy over here
And there should be a jail up here
Ooh, let's do it
I think is how it's pronounced. I got 10k souls on me. I should probably like
Use that at some point. I do too
But let's just hope there's not something horrible in here
I don't think this is that bad
oh my god
I thought you were gonna swing again, but
Well, I don't know what this is
Uh, I think it just means I go a little bit faster and i'm a little bit stronger
No, I mean the boss what the boss is doing
No, I think that's what it was like my weapon has a coating on it now
Ooh, do you get anything good?
Not really. I already had that smithing stone sevens
Our somber seven
It was better than what I had on
Kind of they're watching us. They are okay
uh
Very very nice. I don't know. Why is this marked this lake shore chat? Why did I mark this?
You've been marking things whenever they're complete. I felt like
I've been doing complete as a sword. This is means like is it a merchant? Oh the crab merchant is here. Okay
But I I don't I can take this off because I took the um
uh the ball bearing
All right, let's go up that let's just hug this left side like you want to do
Yeah
No, you're gonna have to get over it. I'm not i'm not saying it chat wants me to do something
And i'm just gonna have to you're just gonna have to get over it. This is not happening
You're just gonna have to get over it. Oh god, you got lobstered
Oh god
You're going like a really strange way through this forest
I saw like a a lot of enemies. I didn't want to do anything to is that another? Okay. What's with the dragons?
What's with all these dragons? They keep the same thing
When I was watching a fucking game of thrones
That sounds like somebody that's never heard of the series before
I sat down in the middle
the middle of an episode
Uh, oh
Let's just hold left
believe there's
Cave or something here
No, i'm wrong
Oh, I feel like there might be something. I think we go down
I want to you know that place where you fight like the giant and like the whole horde of people
I like that spot. Hmm
That was always my like weapon test zone because you respawn right next to like the battle
Armazula is gonna be really easy. It actually really might be we might be able to walk through it
It's all the random enemies
It's not gonna be as horrible
Okay, so we need to go
You want to go like up?
I could use that rotten crystal sword
The mob that you were talking about is on the east side of lyrania
Wait, wait, i'm in obany rock
Please take this medallion
You must use it. I love that's my favorite character
Wait, wait, please
What the hell is happening? I gotta get off the horse
It's a fucking bra dude. I mean it
There's so many people up here. We gotta kill that caster, man
i'm getting
Help it
I my game doesn't know what's the target
Oh my god, i'm so overwhelmed
just swing
Okay caster is
cast
get
this
Bat motherfucker get away from me
Okay, it's clapper. It's clapper clapper. I'm gonna spend my souls
My runes that's probably a good idea
Where's the boss fight? It's up a little more right?
Across the bridge and down
Uh, you talk to you get the guy up here
I can't remember why you need them. Yeah, i'm just trying to I just want to level up
I need way more endurance than this
he's in the
can right
He's in the can
Don't interrupt
I beg you
Would you look after this medallion? That's a nice medallion
All right, that's cool. I got a memory stone and a sacred tear
Oh, no, this old man's mind is fucking gone
Take this medallion, please
Like like a turd in his hand like oh, this is not what that is man
That's my first flask upgrade
I'm so glad you actually got one of those because if you didn't you actually might
It might be like a dead run
Needing to drink like six times eventually you might physically not be able to take more than like three hits. Yes pretty bad
It's been pretty bad
But I make do
Item in the coffin
Oh, I didn't pick it up. I was too busy watching my favorite movie
Trolls roar. I feel like that's I don't think i've seen that
It's fun, but bad
You know, I feel like that's the case with all from software games everything is fun
But bad except for two things and they're the best thing and don't ever use anything else
I just wish they made everything bad
Then you need to stop reading reddit
True. Hey one person said true one person said true. Yeah, because you didn't come up with that opinion yourself
What I can't just agree with some things I can't I have to does every single opinion have to be
A completely original opinion on something. You can't just agree with something
I mean
If you don't have what are you baiting me to jump off the cliff for?
I'm just saying like it's you probably wouldn't have that opinion if everyone on reddit didn't have the opinion that x thing
Is the good thing people don't try all of the things and then they repeat the one thing that's good
And then once that thing gets nerfed then someone goes wait a second this one other thing that thing is also good
Let's all do that
Yeah, and then that's the new thing
Okay, but it was always good
I would agree with you, but could you please use any of the crystal sorceries in the entire game?
None of them are good. You know could you know, I mean like which like which ones they're they're good, right?
There there's like
I I don't fit one which which ones are the crystal ones the ones that go like
The like machine gun ones. No, they're the purple crystal thing. It's it's okay
Glintstone is light blue crystal is purple ones purple. The purple shit sucks. All right
Well, i'm gonna okay. Let me fucking put on a different spell even glintstone
There's like a hundred glintstone moves and honestly
There's maybe three or four of them that are like good like good enough to like carry you through a playthrough
Good enough to carry you so you're not good. You need something good enough to carry you
I saw all capitals wrong and then all capitals true right next to each other. That's the worst take
I'm i'm gonna disagree with you
dude
I used rain of stars and I was so excited about it and everyone omega lulled at me because they thought they would like dude
You're an idiot that thing sucks and it was like one of the most expensive
Crystal spells in the whole game every time I got a crystal move. I looked over and just saw
Oh my god omega lull that thing sucks, dude. Oh my god
It's that's one of the worst spells in the game and I was like, okay
And I used it and it did like 40 damage and I was like, okay, that's suck
So I never used it ever again
I'm not doing a paul bearer impression was I?
Well, I think that's a very different take
Some things are bad instead of there's one or two good things and only use those or you're bad
I know you're very different than
Like this one spell isn't good
Well, hold on. There's there's a difference between
Like everything is bad. So only use the good thing
Otherwise, like I everyone would have just used rivers of blood only but I mean people kind of did that for a little while
but
Well, yeah, because people told him it was the only good thing for a while
That's all i'm saying is that it's it's uh
But if you went against rivers of blood if you were talking about like a pvp scenario you were automatically at a disadvantage
Got him
He's speechless. I mean, I don't know enough about the pvp and I don't think you did any pvp. So
I did a ton of pvp. Did you I did? Yeah
Sounds like you lost to a lot of people using rivers of blood
Oh, it'd be so easy if I just used that but like I don't want to because that's cheesy
So like i'm not gonna use it. I have no experience with how it actually is
But like if if you use that it's like so fucking lame. I lost to another rivers of blood user
I won't do it though. I never said that. Okay, you don't have to kind of writings on the wall
Oh, there's no writing on the wall
All I said is a lot of the stuff in this game is really fun to use
But no, no, don't say stir like winning stir. Like what a base take by stir
No renala's full moon if i'm the reddit guy if i'm the reddit guy, you're the chat guy. You're the chat guy
I'm the chat guy. Yeah, you're the check. If i'm the reddit guy, you're the chat guy
What does that what does that mean look over a chat and you're like, oh, that's what they're saying
All right. All right. I'm not gonna I got it
They're the same guy the reddit guy and the chat guy are the same guy
How why are you so good at this? I fucking hate you. Okay. All right, you ready?
So good at what i'm just like speaking common english. Why are you so good at this? All right, where are we going?
Oh, we missed a boss. That's right up in the village. It's too bad. That move is not very good
Uh, hold on as I think I also have the moon staff
I figure which one does like bonus moon damage
Uh, that move actually is fantastic. I used it for almost the whole playthrough
Is that's the the running moon one, right? Yeah, renala
Excuse me. Yeah, I have carrion regal scepter is the moon sorcery one
But I upgraded my carrion glidstone to 15. So how much um intelligence do you have right now enough?
It does not take like 70 to use
True. I shouldn't like another another thing that my randomizer did is it made all the requirements zero on spells really?
Yeah, dude. Your game is like so my game my game's fucked up, dude
Hold on. It's zero
Yeah, everything is the zero
I'm not using it dude. You could like at this point
I would change it but it would break everything and we'd have another like two hour delay
Nah, it's not worth it. Let's just have fun. We're having fun. You know, i'm not a fan
You know if we're gonna like change the topic of like where's hillary's emails right now
I I don't like stat requirements on things. I'm not a fan. I actually like it. Let's go you want to fucking debate
I you know what I love is that we both are really passionate about things that like don't matter. They don't matter
They don't matter at all. It's zero thinking back to the conversation
We had when we were playing ember where we just argued about like vampire survivors
For like an hour is like we both are always on the opposite side of the opinion
Like we both always disagree and are very passionate about something that does not matter at all
Yeah, it's actually really funny
And then I thought today I was like it's kind of weird though
Because if you ask us like what our favorite games are we're both like diablo 2 of bloodborne
Yeah, so we're like in total agreeance. Well, we're also
We don't agree on anything dude yin and yang have to exist. I'm sorry what they do the balance of the universe
I just got it right in the head
Here's the thing the things that we don't agree on like you said are so meaningless that neither one of us could truly get upset
By it, but also we're passionate enough to argue about it, but it's fun to talk. Yeah
We just annihilated that boss
Yep, he was nobody
Nobody and nothing
Are you suggesting the balance of the universe is being held up by youtube bickering about video games?
I don't know about you guys, but I feel like i'm the protagonist
And you're just like
npcs in my world
All right. You know what? I you really might be the main character
I I get I get a lot of I feel like a lot of side character energy coming off of me. You know what I mean?
I don't know. I think it goes back and forth yin and yang
But I feel we're the two main characters and we finally hook up in the end
But I feel like i'm not just stops watching i'm never a main character
But I feel like I I end up being every single side character like combined
The the comic relief like joke character
Nah, i'm like smart and i'm like kind of
Lillian
All right, I don't want to be a man I don't want to be the main character
That sounds like a lot of pressure and the main character all of their family friends and loved ones die
You don't want to be a main character. No, I don't want to be a man
Yeah, you really don't want to be a main character. I just want to be the chill buddy that like doesn't like just kind of like hey
Happy to see you
Sorry, your family died
Don't worry, you'll get the yakuza and being the main character is like
In the middle of a conversation. It's like, oh, yeah, blah blah blah
Every single other person is talking every character is talking and then eventually they all kind of go like this. What do you have to say?
your
Main character is like, oh, um
well
I think that
We should who did that? Oh over here
And see that's why
Full circle. That's why the terraria playthrough makes sense
I was the protag
All comes back to that
Yeah, I want to be I want to be one of the guys that eats dinner at the table
I don't want to be the one that has to decide on what we're eating
Because if I have to decide on what we're eating then, you know
There's gonna be three or four people at that table that are like
steak and onions
I wouldn't pick this
Is it but whose decision was this?
And then if you i'm at the table too, and i'm just like, oh, it's it's okay. I'm all right. I'm all right
It's all right. I am. Yeah
Yeah, I don't I don't want to be I don't have the person that's like hey
um, so
You were the one that ordered the lasagna for the table. Yeah, I like lasagna. I don't fucking like lasagna
Well, I just figured we would all eat it because it's it's pasta and sauce and it's
It's you don't want to be a cheese. I just don't want to make decisions for anybody
I don't want to be the main character
Oh, so like early on in this run when I was like, which direction do you want to go?
Where do you want to go?
That was upsetting scrambled eggs and pork chops are not good
Like that's the decision I would make
That sounds pretty good
I like making decisions on things that I very much know a lot about
Does that make sense?
I'm okay with being the main character in some very very specific places, but that's it. That's it
Don't ask me where we should eat. Don't ask me about anything else. What do I ask you about?
um
something like making like videos
well, I don't know like
I don't know like
Doing like streams like event streams. I know that
I know that very well
You got an event talk to me talk to me
Stepped on that thing
You want to know where we're going to go for food? Don't call me
You want my opinion on any other thing? You want my opinion on literally any other subject?
Don't talk to me my game might have crashed. Oh, yeah my game crashed
Only talk to me about my hyper fixation
You want to talk to me about like cereal mascots?
Did you actually crash I did yeah, are you dead? No, i'm just laughing at what you said
Okay, that was I thought that was the germa classic. I've done something dumb and I don't want him to know laugh
But that blended into the learning i'm relearning the styles
I'm all fucking around though like all jokes aside
It's I make decisions on a lot of things. It's just not i'd rather be somebody that contributes
I'm summoning I put the thing down. I respawn in the same spot where I crashed kind of
But I do have a cup like you said like whatever my things that I really care about
I will take the helm on it. I will
Drive the clown clown car until it stops working. Yeah
anyways
Where do I go to get a couple people to wrestle each other anyways?
The crystal abilities in this game are not good
Full circle is that full circle because you're kind of taking the wheel
And saying that they're not good, but also like you don't really know
I'm just i'm, you know, i'm trying to make a joke
It's not funny to me, dude
Maybe i'm not laughing
Oh, dude, it's a rock a cool rock in here
Honestly, I would have put that rock in this chest some of this like cool shiny rocks
Don't you think that's what would be in a chest so like in front of the goddess like offering statue
I'm going to give him a rock. I mean you're cursed for the rest of your life. What was in yours?
Smoldering butterfly, is that better? I mean it it could have some form of like religious
Like but a rock
But a special rock cannot have that was it a special rock or a rock new topic. Let's go
Uh, do you care about the dragon abilities?
I wish I did because the I I could get like the dragon communion seal and i've been I already have like a flame breath
But no because I do in faith. I can't drop them anyways. Never mind. Ooh
Yeah, I found like a whole bunch of the fire magic. I kind of
You know don't know where we're going
Collecting items some of these cats. No, there should be like a boss down here. Yeah
I think we we opened the door. It's down here somewhere
Try finger
But uh, what about what's it done?
Was there nothing else in here?
Unless there's another illusory wall
I don't think there is here
Look, I'm a lantern
Oh, yeah, it's it's kind of bright
It was behind you that guy said that and is like watching the stream on a delay and i'm on a delay
Um, you're kind of describing the problem. I was having earlier
I asked too many questions in a row and it was getting answers for the out of order
Yeah, what's going on here?
This is the entrance
You pulled the big heavy door lever
You guys having a good time?
Okay
Somewhere a heavy door has opened. Oh, I think maybe because the desync. Oh come to come here. Oh wait when you crashed
I think we never pulled that
Uh, because when you crashed out, it doesn't count technically, right? Yeah, come back up here
Up to the beginning. Yeah, I don't think we'd been down here
Nope, nothing in there. I mean, there's a heavy door somewhere. Hey, we're coming down these stairs
What? Sorry, I was I was when you when I was looking at chat. I'm sorry. I asked him a question
frozen lightning spear
I I got a spear too
No, like the magic frozen lightning spear. Oh I
You don't care about faith, right? Because I did get lightning spear dude
If we kill ranala, I might go like faith because I have so much faith stuff bills are losing
Oh, no
Shit, not my bills
Come on. Got him. That's a big wind-up
There's something weird about fighting a boss from what that's not actually attacking you trying to gauge how close you are
I forgot he did that
Please don't kill me
There's no way we can do this
Dude, i'm i'm sick of seeing these cookbooks
At some point you're gonna get every single cookbook
And then you're gonna get some cool stuff
Let him cook. We still don't have we don't have the crafting thing to craft or cook. There's no cooking going on common bills
l
I guess they're are they playing right now? All right. How are you doing? You're leveling up. I actually
I think I might be able to as well
It's gonna be close
17 18 000, I think it's 18
Or 19
Okay, what's my favorite vegetable to dice onions? Come on
Uh, sir, what's your favorite topping to go on a hot dog? I'll go first
mine is
Dice onions control of the conversation at this point and I don't even get to answer
what's your favorite by the way mine and you just keep talking and then
Like don't even care. What is it though?
No, what was yours yours first? It was yours was
Uh
diced onions
cold not grilled diced onions
And maybe a little bit of tabasco
and maybe maybe maybe a little mustard if I feel like it I
I would usually say like
I don't think opinion's gonna be wrong
But that was fucked up what you just said
Why what about what about just just tabasco on a hot dog or tabasco and ketchup? I don't know
I like never have tabasco at all
You know, it's really good. Um, like a uh, like pineapple I stuff pineapple
I think I would if I had my choice of like the perfect well-made dog. It would be uh, like chili
That's good because uh, I love sonic the hedgehog. He loves chili cheese dogs. I think yeah
So like the hedgehog likes oh, we're oh we're in I didn't even see it change. Um, this guy's pretty easy
What's normally even in these we've actually gotten pretty lucky on these. They're not bad at all
Please do we cast something please let me do something
God what the fuck can he just smash this controller down and he just threw his controller on the end of like the desk
I got a death root. I got literal shit. Do you think it's time to attempt the
the the wall
The wall, I think we're I think we might be able to attempt the the real wall of the playthrough
I feel like we're pretty strong. I think we can I want to finish going up left here
This is the uh, the teleport towers
Get to the end of this path and then we'll go fight
Placid u6 the queen of the moon and then followed by loretta
immediately after um
pineapple
Very very small pineapple chunks not the big rings or anything not like big chunks little pineapple chunks part of like almost like a
Like uh, oh man
I there used to be this place in new jersey where it all began
It was like they would make uh, like icies
like italian ices
But they would put like the chunks of the fruit in it and they had like a pineapple
Pina colada chunks of pineapple in it truly one of the goats hot dogs are it's weirdly enough hot dogs
are one of the only foods that wacky combinations I
Accept them and want them. I don't know what it is about hot dogs
But I think it's just hot dogs are just like ah, it's a bunch of just fucking random ass meat. It's okay
Disgusting is a hot dog to you if it has no bun and no no toppings. No, that's fine for me
Really? I I if I take like one bite i'm like i'm done
Well, that was that was enough
You just mean like just a hot dog with not but do you put it like hot dogs and beans or hot dogs and anything else?
Just no a hot a hot dog like if I hand you a cooked hot dog and i'm like eat this
Can you finish it? Yeah, I would i'd be able to
Like it's like same thing with bananas like a whole banana like bananas are too big. Let's be honest trees
What are you up to? Why is it that big? Do you want to use one of these?
Do we even have one of these we don't but there's like a bonfire up here. I just want to get it
Um, I think there's a chest on the top one
So funny how much people just flip on us this whole stream
Everyone was saying germa l like super germa l now everyone's saying stir l wow
Comment stir l a hot dog without a bun and you're just like yeah, I want to suck it straight down
I don't even chew them. Well, we're not doing like the I I I can shoot him like this
We're not doing that like meme video
I'm just saying okay. And again, it's not we're not talking like a sausage. It's not like a cheese filled
It's not it's like a just basic ass beef hot dog
I mean, I would not prefer it
But I okay if somebody was like hey
Well, how many times you've been in this have you been in this scenario before where you're at a barbecue or you're at a grill?
Like a family get together friend get together, whatever it is and oh, hey
Yeah, there's there's one or two hot dogs just left on the grill and there's no buns
It's too much time too much effort to go through that actual
Impossibility for me to eat those like a hot dog without a bun
It's they kind of gross me out hot dog with even like even a normal loaf of bread slice
Amazing. Yeah, but there's an on and off switch there for me. There's never been a scenario where you're just like, okay
There's only there's like a couple hot dogs left. I could still probably eat one and I don't really care
It's grilled hot dog. Yes, let me give it to me. I'll eat it. I'll eat in three bites easy
No, can't do it. I I would feel like throwing up
Okay
I would I don't prefer it but I would eat it especially if it's grilled if it's grilled that takes it up a couple tears
I think for me wanting to be able to do what we're talking about. Hey, you know, no one's perfect
What was your had a take about bananas? Oh, it's like the same thing like bananas are too big
I'll eat like a a big banana. I'll eat half of it and like that's enough. That's enough banana, right?
Can I change your whole life? Sure. Okay change my life germa. Do you who?
You're you're a smoothie fan, right? Yeah, you are. Yeah, are you like a banana smoothie fan? Yeah
Yeah, yeah
What I would do is I would like cut the banana in half but half the banana and freeze the rest
And then like the next time you have a smoothie you have like frozen banana
Yeah, but how much banana what kind of banana are you doing strawberry? But my game crashed. Oh
Strawberry banana is good. Yeah strawberry or blueberry
Uh, hopefully that didn't am I still yeah, i'm still alive. Okay. Um
Yeah, so strawberry banana strawberry. Do you do peanut butter banana peanut butter?
No, I had it once and it kind of grossed me out, but I also feel like I could come around to the peanut butter
Banana situation. I think that's you just you need to get the ratio right
A lot of people when they make a peanut butter banana smoothie
They make a huge mistake and they add just a shit load of peanut butter and it becomes this thick peanut butter shake
Light peanut butter extra banana. There's your there's the correct ratio you want less
Peanut butter versus banana for me. You know what? Maybe maybe this changes my life. Maybe it doesn't but i'll try it
Because I I think my first experience with the the peanut butter banana phenomena
Like I ordered a smoothie and was not expecting it like I didn't even know
And then I tasted it and was like and let me guess it was like how dare you it was like how dare you
You had to like kind of tip it back and it was like
Like it was like sludge almost right a little bit. You're right. That's what i'm saying. Oh through a straw
It's like do I gotta reinvite you or something? Yeah, I think you have probably put a new thing down here
I'm gonna i'm gonna use the banishing ball. You guys don't talk case when like you here's the straw and it's like
Peanut butter banana smoothie peanut butter, right? That's a pretty bad sound. Are you still trying to like make more?
No
Farming, are you trying to make more sound effects?
I don't know if it really should count as a category if you're just like intentionally farming it
I have to read this but no, I don't it was so stupid
But uh, i'm gonna read it because like it's contextually funny
Uh, but no, i'm not gonna read it. I've already said it so I have to read it
Oh my you have to now you're somebody said bro, it's not your suck game is just really bad
No, but it's possible. I wouldn't want to rule anything out
You don't want to be sitting. All right
All right, first step focus focus focus up or maybe don't focus. We've been doing pretty well
Just rambling. Yeah when we don't focus lightning three light. I ain't gonna get hit. Whoa, that was different
All right, placid do sex
I'm doing so much more damage
Oh my god, this is gonna be all right. I took a hit but you know what who gives a shit
Quick quick talk about onions or something
Uh, so my favorite thing about onions is the way they make you cry
Like a bow
Just honest this felt so fucking easy, dude, don't say that now
See you you said that instead of talking about like something dumb and goofy and now now look what happened
I got like
Games laggy
That shouldn't have exploded on me
This game's fucking broken my game's broke. It's a broken game
Where is he?
Where okay
Playing hard to get
Mind you how did that miss lasers?
No, it's the fire
Watch the tail swipe
Um, he's stuck up there and he's doing he's doing lasers up there. This could ruin the whole thing
I don't even he's stuck inside of the I don't know how we're gonna do this. He's he'll come down eventually
I might even be able to no I my
Pebbles don't go far enough to the wall
Oh, that's too bad. We could have just cheesed him
Thank god. All right
lasers
my eyes
All right focus up
focus focus
focus on the prize
we're at um
This is it. This shouldn't be too bad. You really shouldn't skipping spammer
Remember forward dodge forward on those. Ow
Damn, he got you good
Oh my goodness
That's weird. Oh
All right. Here comes second phase. I'm out of heals just play defensive if you have to
Uh, I hate to be weird and and or cringe. I have never fought this boss
Uh-oh
I don't know this second phase
What have you?
That one I question i'm i'm confused on that one
I'm pretty sure there's a speedrun skip
I learned it and I just skipped the boss
Oh, wait, no. No by the time you fight this boss
You're so powerful that like I actually won like like stun locked insta phased it every time I fought it
So, you know I have fought this boss, but I haven't seen like
I didn't know there was even a second phase
It's kind of more what's getting me
All right. We got we got it. We're good
Nice
I got
We actually got some I got a lot of shit. I think I got one of the full medallions
I have a sacred tear as well. I don't know if that was from earlier. That's a big deal
Okay
I like this weapon. I like the thing it's doing. Yeah, I don't want a blood weapon
Stones
I'm honestly, uh, i'm debating if I should like switch to faith because I have so much good faith stuff
Uh, this is the opportunity for us to both go. What do we actually want to do?
I guess if I do strength, I mean if i'm gonna have like 50 points in strength anyways
Then this thing's I could still use this if I wanted to
This thing is cool
What's the what are my options my actual options?
This is regular smithing stones. This is somber this is somber, but this is faith
I like having one of each type of uh stone
Oh, I have the uh rolled medallion for the grand lift of rolled. I have it fully completed
So we can do that at some point i'll do these two
so I need to make I need 16
int 50 strength and then
Just this just scales off of strength and i'll be good to go. I want to see what this weapon art is
What about the god slayer?
Are you going faith because we maybe we shouldn't do the same thing
Ari, I i'm I I really want to use sorceries. I'm I'm thinking i'm not switching
I have a lot of good stuff I could do if I did switch but I really don't actually want to so if you do
Okay
I now it's coming down to uh coming down to aesthetics now for me cool this thing you raise up and you smash it and um
Fire comes out right what this sword it's like the magma worm sword. Okay, that's pretty cool
Yeah, this thing is really really cool looking
Damn, this thing is pretty sick. I don't know swing it. Uh, we need to leave this area
The god slayer is dex
This is pretty fast for this kind of weapon
I can't remember if this is good or super bad scar the rotten crystal sword builds up scarlet rot
I can't remember if scarlet rot actually matters against bosses and things it does
If you get scarlet rot on a boss, it's takes a ton of damage away, especially if they're susceptible to it
Dex and yeah, this is a lot of dex
I'm looking at you really weirdly, but you know what I mean?
You're looking at me weirdly. No, I looked at the camera like directly into it like kind of like a like a weirdo
um
No, this is annoying. I think i've made my decision
Let's um, let's go to the blacksmith. I think i've made my decision
Uh, yeah, hold on. Let me go back blacksmith. He said
Yeah
Unless you're respecting like right now and you're sure of it. No, you could do that first
Yes, I am. All right. So i'm gonna be using the magma worm, uh scale sword
That's the weapon i'm choosing for the remainder of our run. Are you going like full strength attacking man?
I'm just going full super strength with a little bit of faith
To be able to use the magma guillotine ability
Oh kind of it kind of does make me actually want to go like fire caster and then we could be the like the magma brothers
Yeah, that'd be cool. The only problem is what if we find somebody that's immune?
Um, all right, let's do this. Yeah when lister the tormentor accidentally like just rolls immune to fire
He's like dude, come on. I'm a fucking meteor build
Okay, so let's get how much I should have at least what?
Yeah, you are you are saying a bunch of stuff that I like know. Okay. Okay
Okay, you are saying things that I know that's great cool
Oh, that's that's crazy
Oh, man, man, that's crazy. Let me look over my shit if I actually did a switcheroo
It's uh, I need 15 decks to put this on and then how much now this doesn't tell how much faith do I need here?
Here's what's gonna happen. I'm banishing you. No, no, no, no, don't do that yet
But whatever we're gonna have like a a resource management session
I think we should just like banish so that we can go to round table. Hold I now
Yep, let's see. I want to I don't think i've ever seen this moves weapons move before I feel like I have
Because I why don't why would I know what it is? Well, uh, that's fucking cool and it stays there
That's a great initiator. Watch this. Look what I can do now. Yeah, you do that in real life. You would die
That's not realistic at all
The lava would burn you. Yeah, that's right. That's true. I shouldn't like that. I shouldn't enjoy that anymore
It was yeah, you're right. What should I like?
Tell me what I should like then what what you should like? Yeah, because that was that's like not realistic and stupid
But what should I tell me what I should like?
No, you can like it, but it's not realistic
oh
All right. Do you want to like?
Disconnect from each other and then just upgrade and stuff and then get back to it
Or what do you want to do? Are you did you respect?
Uh, no, I didn't well go do what you need to do
The jumping r2 has wide range. I think a wide kind of area. It has a follow-up. Yeah
Whoa, it does
It's that move that the magma worm does that's cool. All right. Can I how much can I upgrade this?
It does a lot of damage good
I don't know
Okay, I need somber smithing stone five. That's the hang up here
Um, yeah, I don't have that either. Yeah
I'll double check
I don't this is still I think technically better right because it has the fire the separate fire damage
Maybe the ball bearings maybe now for the remainder of this. Do I put any more points in faith?
Or should I just start dumping?
stuff in um
No, just dumping into
Into vigor or endurance probably i'll get bigger to 30 now does that so what what's your plan?
Tell us we're dying to know
Wait, what what's your what's your plan here? What do you what you what weapon are you trying to look at?
What do you what's your strategy? I think i'm just gonna keep doing what i'm doing
Just kind of looking around what the shops are selling. This is a great weapon
I think I should buy this
this too
Um, you might as well just buy make sure you um in the shop. Make sure you're buying the flask
Stuff is showing up randomly in shops for me. Yeah, our shops are different
Yeah, but just in case they're showing up in yours, too. If I see an item in a shop, that's good
I will I will buy it. This one's this one's d. This is pretty standard
Is this the same guy that growled at us and turned purple yeah
It is I can't deny that if I would just if I was if I said no
No, I I didn't do that. You'd be like, what are you talking about?
I am the guy that growled at somebody in chat and my face turned purple
It's this video evidence of this happening. So I can't say it didn't happen
I can't say that it didn't happen. You could have just not read that
Yeah, but then it's fun to read chat. I like I like reading just random chat messages fun
Obviously if it's like a fun comment
Right. Okay. I am officially ready to continue whenever you are. I need a moment. I killed d
Well, you killed him
Like I I one of the merchants had his quest item and then he dies or was that roger?
I don't know and then fia like vanished
Who knows how these quests work?
It's actually so cool that you don't know any of this
I like I like vaguely know
Almost everything but like vaguely. What is this clip? Everyone's linking that art? No
Just dumping into
Into vigor that sir was making a sound effect. He was just
No, no
sir, did you or did you not like a few minutes ago go like
Like you pressed your lips together and did like a kind of like an elephant sound
There it is
See, they thought you fart it. Yeah, they thought I farted when you did that into vigor see no
Sometimes when i'm lifting weights, I do that by accident and my wife laughs at me. You gotta you gotta breathe man
Well, like you know, you got a brace
I know then you like the air releases and
You elephant a little bit stop replaying it. It's gross. It's not real. All right
It's not real. I need to I need to jump. What should I do?
You know, I know what i'm gonna do. Oh the crafting isn't random. I know exactly what i'm gonna do
Where is it? Is it not open yet? Where's that room chat that there it is. Okay. Do you have any smithing sevens?
Just regular ones. Yeah, I do not. Okay. Once I get some sevens i'm gonna fully
Unleash I feel like you probably are i'm good. I guess i'm ready. I don't I didn't really do anything
Uh, if you want to just dump some of your stones, do you have any stone sword keys? I do bottom
Down in the basement. Well, we shouldn't have to use both if you are have you already used yours
I just opened the chest down here at the round table in the basement
There's the two what I mean is like you should have been in we should have been together when you did that
Which fair kind of onion? Uh, I don't know. I can't really tell the difference. There's always like white onion yellow
I can't I don't really I can't really tell. Yeah, it's kind of tricky. Sometimes red onions. Yeah, not a big thing. No
I'll go yellow onion the yeah
Purple onion, whatever it is, right?
I want just
Yo, um
Ready? Yeah, i'm ready. See you see what i'm gonna do right now is i'm gonna invite you to my game
How do I donate? Uh don't wow
You're gonna come to my game and then i'm gonna give the death fruit to the guy because he's gonna give us an item
And I want us both to get it. Okay, is your thing done? Yeah
I'm coming in what's wrong the way i'm walking. I've actually been walking like this
So it's extra funny to me french onion soup is good
You gotta be in the mood for french onion soup because it's just kind of salt. It's just a very salty flavor
It's very good flavor, but it's very salty
All right, ready r1 r1 r1 r1. Was it worth it? No, I didn't nothing. I didn't get anything
Oh, I thought you would get it. Your theory was very sound in a lot of different potential hypothesis
Let's kill this boat guy. We've probably got the damage now and we do does he have more health than he's had before
He had a lot before oh my god. We are doing thousands of damage to him
He did he scale higher or something for some reason?
No, this is about this. This makes sense. Does it I feel like he doesn't have this much hp
That didn't even do that much
And yes, he absolutely did did he?
Watch out skeleton
I know you've heard me say this a few times but um, now i'm not gonna say it
all right
But uh, are you?
Am I you being are you absorbed? Are you being?
I look we're we're concentrating. I can't speak
I'm am I being absorbed like the theory that I remember when I was like, oh no
I'm not gonna say it. I can't say it and you're like, yeah now you have to though
No, I realized also what I was gonna say was like you're factually incorrect
And I didn't want to be spreading misinformation
Good of you on the internet. It's good of you
I try
Can is there? Oh, yeah, there is a backstab you can do
Oh, no, I thought you just did it
No, there is i'm pretty sure there is but I didn't do it. That's my the glint stone special
So maybe not. I don't think I don't think so
Use your weapon art. I have no fp. Does it use fp?
Probably. Yeah, it does
It's a good thing. He only summoned the skeleton for like one attack. Yeah
88 000 souls dude, what is going on right now?
Is uh, he's a pretty
I mean that was more than radon's memory
So that's coming here and level up. Holy shit
That guy was rich. I feel like that's the safe thing to do
This is the thing I want to do
I think that well, let's do safe
20 endurance get to 30 bigger and be good to go and then let's play safe. Let's do it safe. Let's do
safe
Okay. Well, that was a big deal. Um
I don't know if you want to fight stuff here. This is kind of like
you know
the logical place to go is
up over to
plateau
We could just stay. I mean, this is technically I think I have a teleporter that goes to red wait
I don't know southern k-lit is where we need to be. We need to kill radan
Oh, that stinks
Yeah, I should have
What I don't know why I don't I ran all the way and got the radon waypoint and I don't have it
I want to go fight radon just to see like it's gonna be like a random guy in the middle of the desert
That's right. Why am I concerned about this? All right, let's um
Inner ionia is the closest i've got
Really?
You don't have the under stairs or the oh no, that's uh, yeah, I know what you mean radan's not active yet. Oh
We didn't kill godfrey
Wait, no
We need to kill godric. We know we did kill godric. Didn't we? Yeah, we did. Yeah, we did
It's weird because it's all randomized. So we don't even know where what like how what progress we're on
what's the
Yeah, we need to go to the plateau
Also, there's a boss right inside here if you want to do that because we're like, I think it was a dragon. Let's do it
To your right. I didn't want to go in here because I thought it was the commander and I hate the fight
But like it's not
That fight was really annoying
Is this even him this is the glint stone dragon, oh I got comet
That's actually a huge deal
Comet azure
Just comet isn't comet azure like the crazy one
Holy shit
I don't know why I thought that was a good idea guys behind us like throwing shit out
Oh, that's oh there is
They fucking got me
This guy's throwing like boomerangs over here
There's a guy with a ballista too
You want me to well i'm dead anyways, never mind
Okay
I'm not sure that was even the boss because I I don't know. I think it is
Jesus jesus
Shit i'm like trapped. Okay. There we go. This is weird. This doesn't feel right. That's better. Okay, uh
Where we going we're gonna kill this
Uh, did you rest to get rid of your debuff if you had it? That's thank you
Why are you handcuffed to the chair?
That yeah, it's like what's happening. I can't get out of here. Oh, no, it wasn't the boss
It's a magma worm
Commander magma worm. It's a commander this time
well
Okay
I'm not seeing the names of things when you fight them, which is why I don't know the names of anything
You don't see it on the helper?
Nope
Like when it's a real like boss and it has an actual health bar
This one is just like a normal enemy health bar to me really
Yeah
Let's get off the horse. It's like makes it harder
Uh, I don't know what i'm being scarlet rotted by
Is it the guy throwing boomerangs?
I don't know
It's still going up like what fire versus fire
There's something on the ground like what is happening to me
Okay, I guess just like the flowers on the ground do that. I've never seen that
I probably shouldn't be doing that because some of that fire is mine and will not hurt you
I'm like putting traps down for you
Doing a little bit of deception
Did I not hit that at all?
Yeah, I do. I have scarlet rot now, too
Yeah, standing in the flowers
On the edges of this arena are scarlet rot
Shit
Oh, did you actually get a full build up?
Yeah, I did. I wasn't paying attention to it
You don't have a cure. I do
Got a lot better at that timing. Yes, it got me with it
Oh, I thought he was going the other way. I thought he's swinging that way
We're kind of pros at killing magma
Like it's the only boss in the game
Oh
He killed me be careful
I couldn't see where he was swinging it
Oh
I thought he killed you for a second
Okay
Yeah, I just saw I was just looking at his stomach and I was trying to gauge off of
When he was gonna swing by his like stomach undulations and I got it wrong
He's undulating. He's undulating
so
Do I get so I get souls for that?
Weird right because technically i'm not sure I thought that I did when you killed the dragon that one time and I was dead
During it, but then my souls were on the ground
So I think the souls that you were supposed to get you have to pick up now. I actually don't know
I think that yeah, I have zero. Oh, all right. That makes sense
All right, I get it
Wait, why they oh, okay
I was looking at chat. Oh, uh, we came here to go do radan. I
You gotta remember sometimes i'm just kind of like
Walking forward and looking this way to look at what you guys are talking about. I want to be part of a conversation
I want to see what you guys are saying
What are you guys saying?
all right
I feel like people are coming into my chat first time chat from user
Did he ever mention the blender he uses?
like they're just like trying to get me to like
Like bait me into talking about some psycho shit you do
Is that what they do here?
Is that what you guys do?
You guys just be like, oh, hey, dude. Um
Do you ever played mouse trap the game?
Like oh, yeah, I played mouse trap and let's talk about it. Is that what you guys do?
I go. Hey man, like I just got uh back from uh, I just I just took like a flight to
To miami and I had like some of the best, uh, like pizza i've ever had you like pizza
Well, I maybe i'm reading too much into it that I feel like you have a blender story
No
Okay, then he's legitimately wondering what your blender is because he says he made a smoothie and it was bad
It's I think he needs advice
Wait, hold on
Way wrong. Hold on a second. Somebody came into your chat and asked. Hey, man. I made a wicked fucked up smoothie
It sucked. What do I do? 30 minutes ago was like, yeah, I like smoothies, too
uh
What blender does he use?
Why what why who is what silver tier?
What is this red name?
Huh?
Does somebody just fight this like a person fighting here?
I don't know. I don't see it. What the fuck is this? Oh, yeah. I saw this guy earlier. I thought it was you
There's just a regular guy
Why is he naked?
Is this
Whoa?
Who is that?
Uh, anyways
Here's the thing about making a smoothie and don't fuck this up. It's so easy to put hold on
This is legendary put your hand in the blender. No, no, listen. Yes. Don't do that. That's
But listen to me
People I do this too all the time
And I got another remembrance
You're just fighting random guys
Okay
A lot of times when you have a blender you'll put way too much shit in it. You'll put a you
Oh, I guess it's a it's a it's a strawberry banana smoothie may as well put a three handfuls of strawberries in here
Don't do that. You don't actually need to use that much material
and easy on the liquid people just dump a shit load of liquid in there and they have like
Oh my god, and I did the crystal knight kill you
No, I was trying to get up this tower this tower
I I thought it would be easier with random enemies
It's not let me help this person
When you are making a smoothie if you want to thicken up a smoothie a little bit
The easiest way to do that
Is to just use a little bit of yogurt
Just get some plain or maybe vanilla just greek yogurt
If it's like, oh, this is a little too thin. I don't know just like
a little bitty greek yogurt
Bingo done
And then if it's too thick then you put a little water in no don't put water
You want to you're putting water put some more greek yogurt in
You don't know when you're not when don't use water
The base of your smoothie should be only a few things. Uh, excuse me
The base of the human fucking body is water. Why not water?
because
It's going to mess with the flavor profile and it's gonna be too thin. Oh the water is gonna have too much flavor
It's gonna throw everything off story. You can keep using water and keep making dog shit ass smoothies. That's fine with me
So and drink water
So
I'm gonna recommend you oat milk
I'm also gonna recommend you
It happened
It was in your chat and i'm doing it. This is the thing that you told me happens. You are the guy
Teaching me how to punch the thing that the story no, no, that's different
If you had walked up to that guy and said hey, uh, I just punched this thing and I don't get it
Can you you look like a big strong guy? Can you help me? That's not what happened. This person asked you
This person came up and asked you
You didn't walk up to that guy at this restaurant and you didn't walk up to this guy and say hey
I need some help. Could you explain to me what what your strategy is? Let's take two steps back
He asked what blender do you use and you're on about fucking what milk you haven't mentioned the blender
Because you told me that didn't you say this person like had a problem. They messed up
Asked what blender you use you added context to it though
You said oh he he screwed up his smoothie real bad. Can we hear what blender you're using?
I have a vitamix
There you go
Oh, that was easy. That was really easy. I should do that more often
Where are you? You're like
I went up the uh up top. Oh, I reset the enemies for you
There's a chest up here if you want
I've already been up there
Vitamix lul what?
And that's what happens when I read chat. I'm fine. Um, what's wrong with vitamix?
Yeah, I mean they're a little pricey. They are they are but it's like a
If you if you listen if you are making stuff in a blender all the time
It's crashed your game crashed
That's a common vitamix l what are you talking about? They're like they're
It's like an industry standard blender. Oh, I don't know. I use the ninja
Those are fine, too. That's wrong. There's nothing wrong with that
I have one. It's great. Yeah, if you can
If i'm if you're big big into
Putting stuff in a blender smoothies, you know like
Making like soups and shit making sauces and like pastes and garlic and
Making all kinds of cool shit, right? I don't do any of that. I I make smoothies only
Let me tell you ask if you do you you're like you're talking about it
Like you do it like you have experience and I was like man
I've been wanting to make like some homemade chili
For a while, but I also just don't want to do it. I have made I did my reinvite to you
I I that's kind of not true. I do I have made hummus a few times homemade hummus is actually fantastic. Although I
Last time I did it
I put like way too much garlic and way too much lemon juice in it
And I gave myself wicked bad heartburn for like three days three. Oh, it was bad. It was fucking awful
That's why you didn't stream those three days guys. You're like, where's jerma? That's right
Some wicked wicked sick amount of fucking garlic. You could do that in a food processor
Yeah, but you can also make milkshakes in this thing. You can also make smoothies and and it pulverizes shit a vitamix
Pulverize my game crashed
I got a I got a view of that what that looked like I saw that I did like a pog face
It snapped to like a what was that? Did you guys see that? You can just you can be let's be cheaters
What do you mean? Can't you just jump off the mountain and end up in radon's arena?
Maybe I don't know how to all right. I have a question for you. This is very serious
How do you know all these like wacky speedrun strats, but you didn't see like
Loretta why if you know the wacky speedrun strats, then you'd miss a lot of shit true
Yeah, that's what I mean
Like I remember loretta, but you would just like walk into the arena
And then there was like a setup to like hit her three times with a great sword
Then she would stagger then you'd kill her and then you'd just walk out of the arena like she's dead already
So when it was like, oh, there's a face. I had no idea
She had a face too and I probably actually killed her like four or five times. That's insane
But anyways it this shit gets pulverized. It's not just like a little ring ring ring
I'm telling you right now. I'm serious
Sometimes I feel like when I turn the blender on when I turn on my vitamix and it's like this thing's fucking powerful, dude
It's like when you're talking to an npc in a game and you accidentally selected the dialogue option
You've already heard I was like, oh tell me about the castle. Oh, yeah, we're don and loretta and then like, okay
Tell me about the mic. Oh fuck. I did the mixer one again
I'm gonna finish this last thought and then we're gonna stop wait. I seriously I feel sometimes sometimes
You can't skip this cut scene. I'm sorry. It's grayed out. It's like you're tapping start
This is important lore. This is a storyline cut scene
You can't skip this one when I turn my blender on and I turned up powerful
Sometimes I feel like my lights flicker because it's so powerful
Like sometimes it's like oh my here we go. This thing's got like a million
It's it thinks this thing's going and it's like wait a minute. What's happening. These things are powerful dudes bragging right now
Talking about like someone talk about their car what engine it's got. Oh my blender man. My blends are
Can you let's get this thing rocking who wants a smoothie? Oh you do you do here we go. All right
You fucking just blow out a whole neighborhood. Oh god, geez
You're too wild. I'm not really is we're just
This is not even a weird conversation. It's just we're just talking. This is a great script tonight
We're just talking
Super saiyan blender now. I love my vitamix. Don't you dare talk about it like it's bad
I don't even know i'm not invested in this. I just want you to join my game i'm coming
Nuclear powered blender to be fair. It hasn't done that in a long time
But that's still funny
Yes, I don't remember when this activates but we can't use it. I think we we have to go across the bridge
Or can you I remember they like shoot missiles at you?
Yeah, they shoot a lot. We I think we have to go sit at a bonfire in the plateau
There's also that tower nearby that has like 400 million items all around it
Has it done it before it probably hasn't even ever done it. I just like feel like it's happening
I don't know something. It's this thing is powerful
All right. All right, you know what just
So much it changes this perception of reality like my lights are flick
I don't know for real if they are but they could be
Because it's that powerful. No this thing I
This thing has like it's like a 10 speed. I don't think i've ever made it go past like six
I guess you're scared. You have no idea happen if I go to no, no this these things are legit. These are legit
His vision goes dark
They sell it and they say you're only gonna need to go to five we've never tested it at six
We definitely don't want to go to seven and ten will definitely fuck you up
It's like seven eight like
How it starts to shake like a coffee cup is on the counter
The coffee's kind of like t rexon. We don't know what could happen
Oh, didn't you want to come here?
No, but why not? Why not like at the bonnie? I think you can buy different things from here. Yeah
Like you can buy stuff from here, but it costs the dragon
Thingies really because I have a few of them. I got some decent stuff in here actually
Now I can drop spells
Let me ask you if any of these are doing it for you because I could just buy them
I have great heal
You have a dragon heart. I have three dragon hearts. Oh
Great great heal
Uh lord's divine. Do you need me to read what they do? No lord's divine fortification
Elden stars, which is 50 faith. It's the elden beast remembrance spell probably sucks
This is all faith
uh black flame
bestial constitution
Or bestial vitality
I could go for the heel because if I switch I would kind of like to be like a heel bot fireman faith caster
But i'm not sure i'm gonna great heal
Yeah
Okay, let me see if I can put it. Do you want anything else?
Am I gonna turn to a dragon maybe i've got the carrion knight sword in here, which I kind of want but I can't
Um drop the dragon heart
I cannot drop the drop the hearts. I drop the other spell I have to just in case you use it. Okay, let's uh continue
On our quest to how do we activate the dawn man?
I can't believe you got one guide
in somebody else's chat
It was an important topic
He can talk to you. He can take command of a conversation if it's something that he has great expertise in
And that just happened to be one of the things
I i'm not even an expert. I told you I don't even like I I use it to make a few very important things
Dragon
Oh my god
That's a lot of damage
That's the biggest spread. I kind of don't even want to fight him. I'm bored of him
I don't want to play with this anymore. Do you want to leave?
Yeah, okay
We're all we're just fighting dragons and salamanders back to back to back
so
If it randomizes every enemy and it randomizes everything, right?
Does that mean that?
Have we seen what can a duplicate happen? Have we seen a duplicate worm or their four worms don't happen
But there's a lot of worms and there's a lot of dragons. Yeah, that's true
So I don't think we'll see another worm then I think there's only four worms in the game
Weird we have we got them all how have we not seen an ulcerated spirit. There's like 10 of those
uh
We did
Didn't we I think we only saw one
Oh, we've only seen one of the jump trees as well. Do you want uh the wait, is this a
Is this a talisman?
You should probably take this if it is is it yeah, it sucks
Do you want this charm that raises focus? No
Why did I just buy this it was 100 more expensive. I just got lazy because I didn't feel like okay
Why are you killing this merchant?
Sell something I can use
You're no merchant
Let's go. Hey, that's fine
Let's go cops coming you can uh
You can do the dishonorable kills and d rank. I don't care
I've ever been in wow groups. Oh, we're gonna let's go to the crossroads
And it's like once once somebody started killing like the civilians
It's just like people just start spamming dropping group. It was like the biggest troll
with somebody because if you were part of a group
And you people started killing civilians
You would lose honor
So people would just be in groups like oh, yeah, we're gonna go to the crossroads. It's gonna be so much fun
Oh, don't do any dishonorable kills though
And then all of a sudden you'd see
Dishorrible kill disorder and somebody was just killing them and it was just like what the fuck dude like you just ruined everything
You just ruined like a week's worth of work for me
How does that ruin work for you?
Because it would d rank you because you had honorable kills honor and dishonor
reign of stars
bounding reign of stars
There are items on the top of the skull. That's right
There are let's uh, we're gonna go through the town and fight the uh the boss in here
Which is gonna be two bosses and it's gonna be fun. Yeah
Didn't know you were into wow pvp. I mean it wasn't really
But I mean it existed
Oh, we gotta do the thing to open the door
No magical crab
Ghost crab ghost crab magical puke or whatever. Their names are
the puke punk
But that was very weird
Okay
piece of shit
You're in so much. Oh, I I was I had a great view of that
If you had gotten hit by that on the ladder and fell down. Oh my god
You know how many louds there would have been air cannon down there. Watch out. I fell I pressed
Oh, I did press jump. Yeah, you're just watching me do that. There's like three towers to do and you're just watching me do one
You'll be all right
Yeah, i'll be all right
My second jump isn't working sometimes though. It really isn't I think we're lagging a little
And the inputs aren't being there
probably
No, I want to do it. You had plenty of time
Uh, that was it. I think I did the other one
Like yesterday really here. I'm gonna comment that that guy this guy I can lock onto it
I can't get on my horse and I can't lock onto it
Cool. Nice nice shot
All right. So from here we got a this chest down the street
Make sure you get the chest
Okay
browses
Academy scroll
He's almost 40 dot dot dot
Yeah, I know
I know
I know it's unfortunate how when you turn 40 they put you in a box and just push you out in the sea
I'm just floating out there. You just see like millions of other boxes just floating around individual boxes
I thought this was a bonfire
I guess um
We go downstairs. Why is this not open?
Because that one doesn't open yet. Uh, you gotta you gotta go down here and
I just thought that was a bonfire for some reason
Okay, elden beast
with his buddy
another dragon
If it's a magma worm, I I don't want to say anything. Okay. Oh, it's just one
uh
This is bad. But yeah, this might be this is gonna be awful. Look at how small this is. Well, he can't run away
Yeah, but he's he's gonna do the bubble burst explosive bursting move and it's gonna hit us
I don't i've never heard of that
Well, he's doing it right now
Yeah, this isn't real
I'm gonna hit him soon
Jesus
I don't know if that's helping or
His body is in such weird positions on the walls. It's so hard to find like a foot on the ground. Yeah
There it is
I'm gonna do it in three
two
Um not a little late. Yeah, he he moved that was he moved around weirdly and like went up the wall
God damn it. Oh god. This is it. He's doing this the thing I was talking about
I can't believe he didn't hit us. Let's just hope he doesn't do it again. I didn't even see anything
Oh, come on, man
Okay, I thought you'd jump over it. I guess not
Are you serious?
He's gonna kill me
What killed you? How did you die?
What did you die?
I also got grabbed by one
There were two what?
Okay, let me focus here never
What was that?
Nothing what happened grabbed both of us with the same I don't I don't know what happened
The other astle from snowfield was the ground ground was shaken. Maybe it was a desync
Maybe yeah, maybe you did get desync or something. No, they said the uh, the there's the other astle
Duplicates itself or something. Oh and they're just so close to each other maybe
You know because he like changed colors and like clones of him both went for me and you
Okay, well I didn't even have full flasks and you know
Yeah
I'm just saying that that like wasn't fair. I'm out the door
Proof that it wasn't an instant kill move
Yeah, but I mean
It is
Your health is your health was just really low. Yeah, but it is though
How's that not a leg? Oh it is it was weird
He's got to be close to stun
I think he is
Especially in the head
Really? I thought that was gonna do it
Okay, that was weird
Uh as janky as this is i'm liking this a lot more than the real astle fight
That yeah the fight sucks
The real astle fight and the elden beast fight are the same annoyance for me is like
Oh, it's a gigantic huge area and i'm just gonna literally disappear
And uh be across the whole game
You want to run at me again?
I still can't believe that that elden beast fight is not a horse fight. I feel like it was was supposed to be
What the fuck
I can't believe he's not stagger. This is crazy. I haven't hit him in a while but
Okay, see that time two went for me. It felt like they were that was weird
Oh, he caught you what it was
I there was like 15 hands
I like 10 hands came up to grab me
You got this
I drank one too many
You got it. I think he's fucking
Doing astle shit
Okay, no more healing
That was that was wacky. That was goofy. So was that
I hope he doesn't do another aoe attack
Seriously, like somebody's you're just gonna get grabbed
That move is when there's two of them doing it. This is no way. There's no way
I dodged something it felt like I felt like I avoided
Something it feels like they both do it but one of them is staggered a little bit
So it's like grab grab and it's just hands everywhere. I rolled into like the second one
I felt like it's like six to eight of them
Shit, can you block that with a shield if you just hold the shield up?
Can you just like oh or will he just grab you? There's no way
No, where did this yeti come from? I don't know. Okay
How do you how do you get away from you can jump those? Can you I thought I tried it last time
I think so, but you just have to like
Not get hit, you know
True god
Where the hell am I? What am I? Where am I? What's going on with me? Where is he?
Yeah, what's that was weird? What the fuck? He looked like he's picked you up
No, he's he's
In the corner. Oh, this is not good
We should probably just get out let him teleport. I'm walking away
This is the astle fight where you want to zone him
I thought something just broke through the ceiling. It was his fucking leg. What are the hell is stinger?
It really was a good second there. I was like, when did he get like magma attacks?
That meteor shit it shoots in front of them
That's why we're not gonna hit because it's like all target in front of them and we're like so like locked into these corners behind him
You cannot jump that
I think you just have to dodge through it. I wonder there's a trick to it
What's the you just have to run away from it. You can't dodge it at all. Okay
You definitely dodge it but like
It has to be one of the last ones
He's gonna turn into like seven guys in a second. He's gonna do some five guys shit
Would stop doing this move
Why does he keep?
Make sure you're full health. Whoa
Oh my god, there's a hundred of them. We thought there were two it's like 30. It's like 10
We didn't get him on the first sweep boys
What moves are happening?
Oh my god
Die
Okay, he's dead
Nice. Yeah
Oh my goodness
That he that was like seven people eight people no wonder
No wonder we were getting grabbed every time
Got some scrambled eggs. Maybe we own dragon hot. There are five worms. That's so bad
Oh, I need a lot more souls. I thought I did there we go
Uh 30 hp 30 bigger
And now stop leveling that
Cool. I got a pot wagons. Love me
You know the other dragon altar like way in the beginning
Mm-hmm. I feel like we should go there because
They seem to have really good items in it
We can do that
I thought this opened after you killed them. Is there something else?
I thought that was a seal. Maybe not
Maybe I missed
I don't know. Is it a seal chat? It's it there's a seal right? There's one more tower
Which one this one over here?
Yeah, i'm trying the same thing over on the other side
I just do I don't want to do it the right way. I want to do it like the dumb cheesy way
I forget where the right way is
Oh
Oh, I got it
All right. Which one do we need up here? There's the ladder. I believe in you. I'm just riding around. Yeah, there is this one here
I thought I did all of them
They can get I mean it's it's pretty same. It's pretty like samey out here
so
Uh, I mean like I was saying I did some of them yesterday
I like randomly was in the swamp and you weren't here
So, I don't know maybe it didn't save one of them, but I was pretty sure I did
One and we just did two and I think you only need three. I think it's three
Let's continue. I'm gonna rest for a second. Well, that was you
ball
That ball was very aggressive
And very angry
Gave them the ball call
Oh, it's blood
I'm just going up to the church
Mm-hmm somber stone miner's bell
Really? I feel like I that's probably the first two. It won't actually be somber stones. Oh really? That's right. Shit
What the fuck are you doing buddy?
We're gonna kill it. We're gonna kill that girl
No, okay
I thought we were kind of like just accidentally just fire. Just kill her. I know there's the cave straight up here
They're like hidden illusory wall. I know you're one
Yeah special
This one is this one sucks
Unendurable frenzy. I have a frenzy move. What the fuck is that?
Regal omen bairn
The hell is that I want to do a frenzy build if we wanted to do that
uh
What frenzy build it's where about it?
Yeah, I I tried it once with the vikes pike and all like the crazy like
With the eyes the spells is he pretending to know what i'm talking about. I know what you're talking about
Shabiri's whoa and shabiri. Yes. Yeah, you don't oh, I I know it. I don't um
Okay, so let me take a look at the map. I'll be really honest with you. You completely missed
I'm gonna be really honest with you. Mm-hmm
we've
Done a lot. I'm surprised. We've actually done this much on randomizer
Yeah, i've been once you get the gear and you just go to the places and kill the guys. Yeah, it's pretty cool. Uh-oh
Lag whoa. All right. My game does not want me to look over to the left for some reason. Yeah, my game is freaking out
Where'd my health go?
You only had half health when we came up here. I did
I think from the wolf, but you never like healed after that. Yeah
Oh, yeah, I i'm lagging so fast. Yeah, don't do not look that way
Something oh there's something that's spawned in over there. That's just not
The game does not like it
Yeah, so look at this
Look at this
I wonder what it is. What did the game spawn in there? That's making it so horrible. I don't know i'm going in the cave
I'm kind of uh, caving up. I'm kind of curious but whatever
I don't want to hunt down the thing that's gonna like make us crash
It's true
Even in the cave when I look in that direction
Oh shit. Yeah
Should we go kill whatever it is? Is it gonna cause a problem? I think that reset whatever it was. No, no
There is just this is the this is uh, this is our life
It might maybe it's down here
maybe oh
Yeah, maybe like in the boss room. There's like some giant thing that doesn't fit in it
It's like constantly trying to reset
Oh my goodness
Yeah, I don't know. I find that the 30 fps is a little bit more cinematic and you can't really see much better than that
Anyway, you remember when that was actually a debate I do
Well, here it is. I think is this it
Just take you through the fucking I went through the ceiling
I think it is this thing
This thing is not supposed to be down here. Oh god
Okay
when it despawns
That that was it. That was it. Yeah, that was it the fucking turkey down here was causing a huge problem
Okay. Well, we we cleared it
We cleared we cleared the fps boss
such crap
Look at look at this fucking garbage
junk
Another remembrance
No, just like all these crystals crap
Oh like this isn't real like this is a movie set. Is that what I don't I don't know. You don't like crystals
Making a stupid reference to back when I told you that the crystal spells are all terrible
Oh
Did you have a jo crystal?
Dude, you have a you have a turmeric bracelet. No, I don't
You mean oh you mean black tourmaline. It's not a turmeric. It's not a turmeric bracelet
And by the way, I don't have it on anymore. I it's not I
Do you need it for luck?
Wait turmeric wait
Turmeric actually is very good for you. Okay, but like in a bracelet. No, is it there it being goofy over here?
Okay, it's them starlight star bright shine the way through the dungeon tonight. You stopped wearing it because you got bullied
Uh-oh, is that a mog like?
That is not a mog like I I saw the cape and I couldn't really see what it was
Come on. You don't even know what a mog like is
No, this thing has the weird timings
They just do this over and over again
I'm pretty low on flasks already. So i'm hoping that this boss is not like a bird with his head stuck in the ceiling
I think we've gotten pretty
decent rolls on these
it's not like
Placidics whatever is in here
He's blowing the horn
Oh my goodness. This guy just fucking killed me
No, he didn't I thought he did
Help help. They're down here. Help someone you're like you're like a thousand feet below the earth, man
All right. You ready? What do we get? Yep. Okay
Not that bad. Oh, he's a new player. This is a new player
No
Oh and there's no fire on that one
Not that bad. We've been getting pretty good rolls in these
There's a lot of souls. I like souls
That was worth a lot of
blood echoes
Runes. Yeah, let's go farm blood vials. It's back. Yeah, it is. It's because that bird is back
We got to go kill that fucking bird and then come back. Let's teleport out of here. Honestly, let's go somewhere else
I want to fight radon dude. What do we have to do to fight radon? We have to go sit at a bonfire in
the plateau
Teleporting to the church down the hill
Because walking would be really hard. How do I say? How do I say? Yes, there they go
It's the best essential oil to cure bronchitis. I don't
I don't think I take whale oil for anything. What are you talking about? Whale is a great creature
That's one of the biggest creatures
Yeah antibiotics. Yeah, am I right? Yes
Think about it if you want to get big
Think about it. I'm a barf drinker did this
Trying to channel his energy right now
I'm exiting the area
Where where do you want to go from here?
I forget what's on the top though this hill
Need an inhaler
But bronchitis is I don't know
I'm not a fucking doctor. I don't know
Is there anything at all up here?
It was just a question
Let me tell you something about blenders first of all
Oh shit, we got a mog like
Yeah, I think you actually might be accurate. That's a mog like enemy, isn't it? Nope. It's a cool weapon though
Uh, this is actually gonna be hard. So just we gotta like I don't think they can come out
Ooh, that's good. Whatever that that's
I don't think i've ever seen this enemy
Yeah, you have
Down in the giant area when you go across the big chain
You mean where you just like ignore that whole area and run with your horse and just go up to the the giant
what
Did you stream a lot of your elder ring?
Yeah
What level were you when you got to like?
The giant area like what I wonder what level you were
Oh
You mean the place where you just get on your horse and just ride by everything. Yo
Item item item alert item alert item alert item alert item alert
somber five
Are you ready to go beyond?
Or do you not need that anymore? Give it to me
Do you have a six? I have a seven and an ancient
I have a four a seven and a nine
So that will help appreciate it. Thank you
Number go big big plus one level
Uh with somber, that's a big deal. That's ten percent. That is there's only ten levels
That's that is a full one out of ten, which is ten percent. Come on
It's gonna be more than ten percent. I have I have never been over here
I've never gone through there
I've never been up here. I've never been to this tower. Have I even played this game?
I'm starting to wonder maybe I didn't play this game. So when you
Did you play anything off stream too? Just kind of like in your own free time?
I think so. Yeah
You didn't do the thing where it's like oh
I want to see what this is and just go go over there in every single zone. Just kind of what's this
It's a big game
Yeah, but I you I feel like you missed you could just probably play this again and just see it. Sorry that you're mad
Yeah, we're very upset with you for not knowing where everything is
We're very upset. Okay. Well, wait, what is usually here because we came all the way up here
There's like nothing here. Just
Very upset with you that you didn't 100% and get every achievement. It's just it's like unfortunate that I even know you
How many hours do you have an elden ring?
On the game. Actually, I don't know. That's a good question
Probably not that much considering I did
I wanted to play it on my couch
So I got it on xbox
Okay, so you so you own like seven copies of the game get out of the way
There's an item on the ground. Can I pick it up? Thanks. I have a series s
Series s is uh, I love that little thing
Well, I think usually you gotta come up here because you gotta kill the guy who throws the pots down on the road
That's about it. I mean, you don't even gotta I want to fight radon
Jerma, take the wheel
Make it happen. Okay, we need to go to the plateau
So we're jumping off but we've got a series x I don't didn't really have a need for it
series x, um
It's I mean I I have a pc
So if I anything that comes out in the series x I would just get it here
I don't have a ps5. Do you have ps5?
Nope, do you have any of the current gen consoles or no you have a switch? Don't you?
I have a ps4 and they still release like every fighting game on that thing. I thought you had a switch though
Didn't you know I have a switch. Yeah, I've never used it. Is this sealed in the box?
No, uh, it's a wife device
Dude if it was sealed in the box
I would say keep it in the box and seal it because then you know that you got it like an heirloom plays like fire emblem
and
Zelda and all that breath of the wild is pretty fun. You never played it. I tried it on like a flight
I was like i'll take the switch like play it on the plane. Wait, wait, wait star star
Hold on be careful. I'm gonna stop you because you're about to have a lot of people
Very you're gonna get a you're gonna get a stir l here
I was saying earlier like me and you disagree on like everything you liked breath of the wild a lot
Okay, i'm just telling you just be careful with this next statement
It's gonna be a doozy guys. Be ready. Um, my opinion is that
Legend of zelda breath of the wild was ign's number one greatest game of all time
Is number one on their list. That's my opinion
You take all of the video games ever made and the best game of all time is on the switch and it's breath of the wild
Yeah, I disagree with that
I disagree with that good because that list was fucking ridiculous
Every blizzard game was all in like the same like it was like starcraft warcraft
Like they just like I don't put all the blizzard games here
I mean, I I don't I don't think that breath of wild is the best video game ever made. I think it's game crash
Oh
I want to fight. We're done. Yes, let's go up to the plateau
Um, I think I think it's really good. I think it's really fun
If you like elden ring, it's just kind of elden ring with cartoon graphics. I didn't give it enough time
and the breaking items
And stuff, I don't know
That rubs me the wrong way, but I definitely haven't given it enough time to even have any opinion
I legitimately got to the first dungeon
And then just didn't feel like playing the game I didn't like not like it
I think it's fun. I mean i've been streaming it not lately, but I think it's a good game
I have one major complaint about elden ring and it's it's kind of unfair because I bloodborne is like my number one
probably number two whatever favorite game ever made breath of the wild even on the switch sometimes runs it like
Like 18 frames a second. I opened the world to you. That's the only complaint I really have about it
You didn't your first time playing it was on stream, right?
I almost feel like I would I would need to be streaming it to play it
Like just sitting around to play breath of the wild was like, I don't know. I feel like it's so big
There's so much shit going on and I got to collect all these these peaches. I was like, I don't know
But it's a pretty good streaming because then I have to set up like a whole like twitch in my
The switch in my room and get like all the cables and that's just who's got time for that. Yeah
It is a pretty good stream game though. It's a chill game just to kind of just turn it on and play for a little while
Yeah, but they're like I would have to plug in like two cables. All right, so we are we're we do we should not be here
We need to go up to we need to go to the church though. We need to go to the plateau
I think once we get to the plateau, I think we have a cut scene. I'm I'm following you
100% okay
Let me uh, let me make sure I have this right
We have to get to the plateau
We get a cut scene when we go to the plateau and then it's like, okay, here we go radan's available, right?
That's correct. My chat says please just walk over the bridge
Those ballistas might not be manned because of the uh randomizer. That's also very true
Just go
No, that's part of that's part of ronnie's quest. Oh
Let's go to the bridges fucking walk. We have to talk to ronnie. We need a medallion for the bridge. Oh
Oh, yeah, and you like like normally I think the medallions in a spot where you just kind of like always get it
So I didn't really think about it much
But now we don't you get the two halves at the forts
Uh, let me level up first because I don't want if we just get bombarded with missiles. I don't want to get behind me soldier
Shit, we need to kill like one thing. Hold on. Let me kill like random thing over here
I can give you a rune
Yeah
Faster. I don't is that gonna do it?
Is that enough? I don't think that's enough
I can like give you another rune. You just keep arming me for runes. I need like another just give me I need like 800
You can get to the
You can either you activate the festival either by doing ronnie's quest line or activating any bonfire at
Atlas altis plateau. I think the fest the festival is active. It was just that we didn't have the medallion
to teleport
Uh, we let's try to do it this way and if we need ronnie's quest line. I have
I have I have two of the items for it. I think
Go over the bridge. Yeah, that's probably
I'm gonna blast
Okay
Yeah, there's just there's just like a pimple where the ballista would be
I I don't know why I didn't just try it
Yeah, we we kind of didn't trust this somehow
I don't know why we didn't trust that. This was gonna be easy
That was rough. Oh look a dragon
What the fuck
That was planned
They planned that oh my god the ambush. All right. Yeah, we just go don't even fight this
I'm glad you got a 3d movie, too
That had to have been right in your face, right?
Yeah, that was uh
I had the 3d glasses on and everything
You know, what's crazy?
3d like 3d glasses 3d movie 3d video game stuff really just fucking disintegrated, didn't it?
Dude, I was at uh, I was at the arcade the other day
I was telling you and they have a whole bunch of like vr stuff like oh
You can go in like the vr experience the omni room. Mm-hmm. And I was looking at it through the lens of like
This is this already feels outdated
This just feels like a weird gimmick like I know in like 10 or 20 years
that's gonna be like the same thing as the pac-man machine in the corner, but like
Even just seeing it like all brand new vr like like we have a vibe headset
Yeah
I think
Doctor, I was last you've been to an arc. You went to an arcade recently when you did that thing, right?
Yeah, like two days ago. Yeah, like on the weekend. I gotta get you a take on this. Did you need a smithing stone four?
What a smithing stone four I just gone and you need that
I don't know. I need like an eight or something. Have you noticed that?
all the light gun games at the arcades
Have stayed in like 2003 like their graphics are terrible
Yeah, frame rates are always dog shit the mechanic. Oh
Also, this is let me add
They have uh, they had like a whole booth where like eight people could go in and play vr and they've got like slippery feet floors
You actually like run in the games and it's got like foot trackers. Oh, which was also
There's a little miserable
That wasn't good. Also, you're just wearing vibe headsets, but they can't license out vibe games
That I guess they thought it would be cheaper to make their own games
So it's like that you could play beat saber
But it was like song master and it was they're all just like super shitty copies of all the games you would want to play
Oh song master
I got that's like a great online handle name like the song master
What is controlling this globe that's an enemy they they're in the mystic river or whatever. Oh they are
the song master
Yeah, we played elite force which was the generic military death match
It took longer to like get us all strapped in than it did to play
yeah, I
I'm trying to think of what was it when vr came out is when 3d glasses weren't cool anymore, right?
I think they weren't cool for a while anymore. And also they call them 4d glasses now
I remember and this is as I remember going to see I believe it was
I think it was avatar in theaters
The avatar like the first one and it was a big deal because it was 3d and you get the 3d glasses
You're you're right
So someone I know was saying that they went to go see the new avatar and they're handing out 4d glasses
Like they rebrand it 3d because it's like oh 3d is kind of lame now
So we're gonna give them 4d glasses and we were like that doesn't make any freaking sense
They're like no the fourth dimension is time and avatar takes time to watch. It's a 40. It's like they're not like it's sure
This room is fucked by the way. I don't think we should even go in here. Look at all this
They can't even move in here
um
The only reason why I bring it up is because I remember it because it's a long movie
I think halfway through the movie. I just I took the glasses off because I was like I can't fucking stand this anymore
I like my head hurt. I kind of felt like ill
And I watched they're rough
I watched like 20 to 30 minutes of it just all fucked up looking and blurry and spaced out weird
I got up and I went just got like snacks and shit. I think I walked around the lobby for like 10 minutes
I missed like a portion of the whole middle part of the movie
And then I kind of went to the bathroom. It had to been at least 10 to 15 minutes that I was not in the seat
And then I just put the glasses back on
And off hold on. I don't want to die
I I in intervals would take the glasses on and off and watched it blurry and then watch it in 3d
For the rest of like the hour and a half that I was still there
Do you think I'll I just I only ever used them like one time and I do kind of remember
It's just like my head and eyes kind of hurt
Do you think there'll ever be a period where they'll do vr movies with vr headsets in the seats?
And there'd be something to watch or something to like participate in
I feel like that's the next step and that's very possible
I feel like that's some some shit you'd find in like a museum or a zoo like you go into the zoo experience
And like oh you can like pet the penguins and they're like like, you know vr zoo experience in the zoo
I'm telling you that's the real thing
I know it I I feel like i've heard of that before from somewhere avatar 6
You're going to be able to walk around the movie set while the movie happens
I'm just telling you that's what's happening
There's going to be the movie playing and you're going to be able to just be kind of walking around or just looking at stuff
And this is going to be the movie over here. That actually sounds kind of cool
Hopefully in that future you go to the theater you sit down
And then like an anesthesiologist comes over and injects lsd into your fucking jugular
And instead of watching a movie you all just trip together
What's the point of being what's the point of the movie and then on the movie screen?
The hypno toad from futurama
so you say
what's the
I don't know how to respond to this
Instead of everybody in a chair
It's like because it's just an experience
That would be a terrible experience because you oh, yeah all like
You want a room full of like 50 to 100 people all doing lsd. How many of them are standing up?
And like walking around the aisles and shit like I don't want to do i'm not in that
I don't I don't want to be in that fucking movie theater. You're oh you get strapped in what?
Get strapped into the chair
I'm not going to this movie
Nope they're a professional. Nope. Nope
Uh-uh
I like my vr you walk around like the set that
james cameron made
It's torture. That's weird
But shoot would you be able to be heard and seen by other people?
I think imagine like a big vr chat lobby just like all yelling shit and screaming at each other
Well, there's two actors just talking and the movie's going on
But that would be hell proof earmuffs on you stir. You're describing a clockwork orange
Oh my god, it's a good movie
Holy shit. Oh my god
All right. So we're kind of we're doing the minecraft build the wall take the wall down build the wall
Take the wall down build the wall. What do you mean? We haven't made any progress. We need to let's go
We're killing a lot of things. I got a lot of loot. Uh, we go we're going this way, right?
This is it's this way. We just go up here the stairs
And that's where it is
It's in like a hallway. No, i'm telling you right now to your face where it is. We gotta go this way
Where are you going? Where are you? There's an item up here that you
Didn't get I did I did though
And there's the mega slime
Watch out for the mega slime. Oh
I don't have any mana
That's sad
If they ever did that let's say there was like avatar 6 was like you everyone could put the vr headset on and kind of walk
Around while the movie was playing out in like a 3d space around everybody
They definitely would just make it so you couldn't you had to have like the avatar
Everyone had to would have to probably have to be an avatar, right?
You'd have to be oh
So you would get the you would get the point of view of the protagonist
No, no, no, no would be like a side npc and we would all have different points of view and then like when the characters are
Talking it's like i'm talking to you, but you're like jack naley or whatever his name was and then like we kiss
No
I'm talking about watch out
bad guy
I need to what I got scarlet rodditt i'm talking about the movie is just
In 3d space the movie is being is playing and you are just in that space
You you cannot interact you just can be in the space and see like the crazy shit
You can walk around in it
If somebody's talking this looks like let's say you got let's say you get tom hanks over here and he's talking to
Um, who else is an avatar?
Uh, whatever so you got tom hanks is an avatar probably so this you got tom hanks and there's another person talking
and
You can just literally leave the room and just go look around like the world of avatar
And you don't you can just do whatever you want. Oh, so you're saying like the movie scene is happening in this room
But you can just leave the room and look at like an empty field
While like the the cinematic is going on and you're like not even present
Can you imagine how different that movie would be from multiple different crazy places?
You can watch from if there was a big battle imagine just being like no
I'm just gonna go on like the roof of this random building and just watch the battle from there this time
Oh, I yeah, I can imagine being in the movie
Of a big battle an immersive experience of you in like the traumatic war movie
Like the avatars are all getting bombed or something. Oh, no my like urn tree's burning whatever their shit is
Yeah, that sounds like that sounds way better than my idea of like putting people on lsd and strapping them in
Hold on out of the spot
I'm in trouble here
I like stirr's plan. No, you don't stop
That's weird because my plan was not spoken to be liked
That's weird that you like yeah. Oh man, that sounds pretty good
You mean I got to take lsd and sit and like freak out at a movie theater
Sign me up
Well, it feels like okay
Okay
It feels a little bit the same where like vr is kind of like the new experimental technology like we're just starting to dabble in vr
Like why not like also like hard drugs?
but like hard drugs start, you know, they're starting to get like more accepted like uh
Psychedelics, you know, they're starting to be like, yeah, maybe we should like do some psychedelic research
You know, they're not like they're not the worst. But wait, wait, wait, wait. Are you in they start doing public?
Uh, like the public can start getting to the macros to these and we're gonna do like psycho
All right
Are you implying are you implying that movies are potentially going to get are getting more boring or kind of lame to a point?
We're like that's what i'm saying
You just okay. So let's take movies out of the equation. You're just saying that do drugs in a big group. That's your idea
That's the idea. That's your idea
That's just it
Yeah, yeah, yeah
All right
To be clear. I think you got it
So movies have nothing to do with movies have nothing to do with our conversation at all
From your from your side here movie theaters, we're just talking about like entertainment that started with like vr
Okay, the same way that like vr has the goofy like sign up for the vr booth and it's like weird
Yeah, you'll give it a couple years. It's gonna be like sign up this so we're doing lsd at noon
I don't think so. I think so
And you know what?
That's fine. It's funny. So
Vr is a thing now my idea is vr kind of evolves a little and we participate in movies
Your idea is vr fails. Okay, we all do drugs in a room strapped to chairs
Follow where's the logic?
I got the logic for you right now. It's it's loaded up. Are you ready? I'm ready
I'm a billionaire the fight earth is boring. I'm going to buy a rocket ship company and fly to space
That's happening, right?
But you also have like a lower level of rich persons like I can't buy my own rocket to space
I'm gonna go to brazil and find someone to administer ayahuasca to me in the middle of the jungle
What if we monetize ayahuasca from the jungle and just brought it into the fucking psychotorium and did it like a movie theater?
I don't even know what I don't know what he's saying
What he's saying invest invest
Invest
Psychotorium coming to your city
dude
You're psychotorium me out right now
Where's the bond? Oh, there's a bonfire
all right, let's
You haven't heard of any of these like random rich people going to the jungle to like do like a
ayahuasca experience
I mean I hear about you know, oh, we're gonna we're gonna do. Yeah. Yeah, of course I have
Yes, of course
Of course I have I feel like there's a lot more
Of course a lot left unsaid
I've been to brazil
Dude, let him cook
No, don't let him cook
If he cooks it, no
All right. You ready to start this?
Yeah, I love a good festival
Let's all strap in. Yeah
I love a good. Oh, no, he's in a cheese in the chair right now. Oh, oh shit
I'm going to the vr room. I want nothing to do with this. The vr room is lame, dude
It's just so funny to me the very we're talking about movies and
My thing that i'm saying is you taking away the visual just remove the theater part and it's just everyone do drugs together
There's no theater said that the theater is displaying the futurama
hypnotote
Don't you think that would just freak everybody out like who you know what that if it's like, oh everybody
Let's all just stare at this on lsd for four hours
Okay, well then we can pull it back and it can just be like
I don't know a room like a singular room around here
I don't I don't know if there's like a texas thing. There are so many weird build
I don't know what they do
But it's like come in here for your like your health clinic like personal like carbon digital health digital health clinic
And they're like really pristine places that have like nothing in them. If you just look in the class
It's just like a table with one person at it. I don't know what they're doing in there
I don't know what they're doing in there
like like expensive area like
There's never anyone goes in no one ever comes out. I've never heard of this
I don't know. I've I've never heard of this digital health. There's also like a cryogenics place like around here
Is it are you sure they're not sure it's not like a hospital? No
All right, I don't know car cartel money laundry. There's a place near here
I I honestly think a legitimate large amount of places here have to be invested in like money laundering. There is a drive through
Jewelry store. This place has a fucking open drive through who is driving through it's like a like a
Expensive ass like k's jeweler kind of like oh just drive through pick up your jewelry. No problem
There is some fucking like hey, but like hey money being exchanged. There's what's going on
What if you just want like a quick pair of earrings or something? Uh
Gotcha
Gotcha again. I don't know never seen anyone never seen anyone go to that place ever
All right. Can we play can we beat radan please a guy in my chat says it's extremely all caps
It's extremely common nice nice announce your privilege to my chat get the fuck out of here. Where is radon?
Why can't we activate the festival? What are we doing? Oh my god somebody stop him
We have to go down like the we have to go down the elevator
Where's he where's the elevator?
He won't open it's usually behind this guy. He won't open the door. It's behind him
The festival will be declared. He says it's not happening yet. How do we do this?
You gotta we have to go to aldous plaza. We have to go there. We did this for no reason. Okay. Oh crap
Okay, let's go. Well, we got bonfires and stuff. We gotta get stir to stop talking about drugs for a few minutes
I want to go to the blacksmith real quick because I think I can upgrade a lot
What what if like instead of no more restore? What if it was a drive-through lsd?
No, are you serious? Are you crazy? What's wrong with you? Quick quick
blenders, uh
Pasta sauce. Oh, we can talk macaroni cheese. Let's talk about what's talking about your favorite macaroni cheese
I like a swiss. I need a smithing seven. I'm looking for smithing sevens out here a regular smithing seven
Yeah, I don't have that
All right. Well, then let's uh, we gotta go to the altus plateau and like wait actually I can upgrade
Thanks for thanks for coming here. Oh, yeah, because you guy guy guy
Very cool
My insane rent. This isn't even insane. I'm see i'm still on it. There totally are places where you can get like
Now, you know, um, you know, you know what? Never mind. You don't never mind. You know, you just guys
Oh
He's turning
You don't have to believe in me
Uh, i'm just gonna do a smart start up a small little company. It'll be called like tesla or something
You'll hear about it
No one will believe in it
And then i'll like post some memes on the internet and like way more people invest than the company makes money
And then all right now now now the video cuts and it's a news report
Uh local streamer, uh stir has been arrested for setting up an illegal lsd torture chamber
Uh, he's been arrested and he's now going to be in prison for the rest of his life
Where where i'm gonna continue to try and you know expand my operation
The authorities have said that we have no idea what the hell this man was thinking when he decided to do this
It was one of the most unreal ideas we've ever heard again more unreal than like digging a tunnel only for tesla's
Where are we going?
I need we I put you at the wheel and we have not fought radon
You put me at the wheel and then you just and then you started you started screaming in my ear when I was driving
Screams name. I think you should actually do a scream stream
Are you on drugs right now?
All right, let's go. Where were you yesterday?
All right, so here's the deal. We are gonna go to the where do we how do we get here?
I don't know how to get out of here. What do you mean? You don't know how to get out of here
We need we need the medallions but there's that we can go through wait. No, no, no, no, no
We can go we can go here. Yeah, right. No, no, no right below that the road
I have the medallion for that lift what you do. I thought you yeah. Oh, all right
Yeah, let's go. You just follow the road follow the road. So we uh
Main academy gate or can you do no because the bridge is broken. The bridge is broken
So we need to go all the way up the right or you need to
Um, I think we actually do have to go up this way
Yeah, I think we have to do the whole right path because everything there is a cliff. The bridge is not broken
I think we can just go over
Uh, okay. The bridge is not broken. There's a teleporter on the bridge. Cool. Yeah a movie-length car wash in vr
Is the future movie-length car wait you go to the car wash and you put it you put a vr headset on
I feel like entertain you while you're going through the car wash and like while you're going through they're like taking the tires off the car
You're getting robbed if you do that, by the way, yeah, it's like yeah
Come to the car cleaner
Come on in
You just like sitting there all your shit's gone
What I was gonna say is all the paint is gonna get stripped off your car
You guys are gonna be fucked up after that. It's gonna be dense everywhere. All the paint's gonna be gone
Holy shit, man
Like a three-hour movie of just your car being washed your car is gonna be fucked up
Oh, we have the key so we can do this. The stream has gone completely unhinged. Yeah, it has
Well, don't worry. We'll get back on the road. We will it's inevitable. We always do we always get back on the road
Yeah, we're getting we're back on the road. We took a wrong exit
We're calm relaxed. We're done talking about anything
At all
It's all been banned
Do you get an item for this and we just have to go across here and we will activate it night cavalry
Let's actually we probably this pretty easily now
Yeah, they're like not replaced. That's kind of weird that they're not random. That is weird
All right. I thought I was you for a second inside of that. I mean it is horse combat
Oh, it does a lot
I can't there's so much there's so much
Fire light on the screen. I can't see anything horses up. We've been killing the horse the whole time
fine once he falls we just gotta we gotta
Really rip into him rip and tear he's about to fall off
Or run away
One of the two all right. He's off
eat
The lock on yeah the lock that lock on bug is annoying. I couldn't lock on to him and it got weird
Yeah, it keeps like dumping it. I keep this like
There we go
and
Oh somber smithing stone, too
How come stir streams at 1080p 60 fps and you don't because stir
doesn't understand
the quality versus bit rate
thing
What?
What do you stream at?
You stream it like one of the weird numbers, right? Yeah
Yeah, I did that for a bit and then like my settings reset and I forgot what number I was doing
So I just went back to like default
I know
Stop thinking but yeah, I understand that what germa is doing is correct and you're just trying to find
Things that aren't correct, but this one is correct
There you go
case closed
uh these
Work. Oh, no the crab is
Trying to work them. I think
Crabtable, uh, the crab is about is is being catapulted. He might act
Yeah, you want to take a look at this. I don't see a crab. I think he's gone
Yeah, he's he didn't make it. He didn't make it
Oh, uh, I just got urgent heal. Do you want that?
Uh, just hold on to it until I switch if I do
uh
Just stream at the best settings. Well if
the thing about streaming
Is if you go over
If you go over 6 000 bit rate
Then I believe
You are considered to be that's not allowed
I think that there are some cases maybe where I don't know maybe they allow some maybe events to do it
I don't know. I have heard of an individual streamer who was like granted the privilege to get like 10k bit rate
I like a very
rare
Thing everything i've ever heard or been told is that anything over 6 000 is considered like against terms of service
Okay, well I have also heard that but I also used to stream at 8k for quite a while
I have no idea
But if for some reason there was ever the ability to oh, hey, no, no, no, no
Everybody can stream that like up to 20k or up to like 15k. I would do 1080p
Yeah, I think now it actually
Like basically gets throttled that it really doesn't let you go above and it used to let you go a little bit above
I don't know. It's all weird. Where do you use the medallion? Right? Uh, I think it's right here
I think it's this one. Is this the right lift or did I mislead us?
Um, this should be I have rolls rolls medallion. Is this not right rolls royce? It's the wrong medallion
I think chat correct me if i'm wrong. We can go through here. Can we oh, yeah, this is uh, this is the dectus
I don't I only have the left for dectus. We can go in the tunnel and up right? Yeah. All right. Follow me
Yeah, I know. I know where we're going. Then you don't have any of the symbols or the I don't think so
No, I don't have any of them. The one you have is for uh, landell. Hope this doesn't hurt nice smithing stone one
Stop off that
No, no, you have you have to go down through the waterway
Yeah from uh the lake or we could uh, let's go up into the capital. We should
Kill radan or you mean you mean I I really do want to kill radon. Well, let's just get the bonfire up here
I guess we could talk to ronnie. What did I just go up?
Here again
Do you think you'd yeah, I was gonna ask but whatever
I'm being a weirdo
Where do we talk to her? What are we doing? I don't know. I haven't talked to her once this whole playthrough
So I have no idea where she is now. I think you talked to it. You talked to her first, right?
And then I don't know where she is now at her, uh her tower. I think she's at the tower like her tower
Which is here somewhere, right? Isn't it like up here?
Yeah. Yeah, she has the tower next to
Her puppet man
Now I would be her puppet, you know given the chance ronnie will probably take even longer
Whatever not in any rush or anything
I am going to request a bathroom pee break
Uh very soon here though
Okay, I could really use one of those as well for my bladder pees
Oh, yeah, you can write the worst up here
You really shouldn't be able to but
Should go pee I will after we get this situated
Jimmy you've spent 19 years sleeping
What i'm gonna do the math on that. Let's say you sleep six to eight hours a night
Let's say seven hours average right six seven hours average
I'm 37 so that's somebody do that math. How many years have I been asleep a third of your whole life?
How long have I been asleep for 12?
0.3 years. I've been I was sleep. I've slept for 12.3 years
I don't like that statistic
That makes me feel like life is passing by 12 years. I was asleep for 12 years of sleep
Yeah, wake up
wake up
12.3 years asleep. How many years have you spent pissing?
In that that's another crazy one. Yeah, okay
Somebody calculate all this you spend 45 minutes in the bathroom
Every time you go and you go how many times today you're going wait. We need to do this very very
Wait
Hold on if it takes let's say it takes me between
15 to 60 seconds to piss sometimes it's a big one. Let's just say on average
It's like I I thought we went over this that you spend 40 minutes in the bathroom
And then but like just hold on peeing only. Oh my god, this is gonna be so scary
Okay, you guys ready? Let's do it. This is more important than playing the game. I don't care about the game
Just go you go. I'm talking to the people you are you're doing great if it's about 15 seconds to do a piss, right?
About 15 maybe 10 to 15. No
Um, yeah, how many times a day do you pee? I'm a chronic pee counter. No, you could continue
I was waiting for you to say the rest
What is that?
Sometimes when I I don't know when I was young
Definitely not anymore
Uh when I know that it's gonna be a real big pee. I'll just count it
Okay, like how how much pee is this and sometimes, you know, sometimes you hit a minute, dude
I feel like I pee
It depends but if i'm talking about an average, let's say it's five I feel like I pee every
Three to five hours then you also need to you need to
Factor in the long pees. Yeah, that's what i'm gonna do. Yeah. Okay. Okay. Okay. This needs to be accurate
so
If it's let's say you pee every I pee probably every depends on the day
But like maybe every two to five hours every two three four hours
Maybe I feel like every couple of hours to four hours
I'm gonna say three hours average maybe three six nine 12 15 18 21 20
So let's say let's say I pee seven to ten times a day six to ten times a day
We're gonna say like seven is that pretty accurate?
So if I pee seven times a day times like 25 seconds
So seven times 25 is what that's a lot seven sounds like a lot to me. Is it i'm gonna go pee
Right now i'm gonna go pee when the stream is over. I mean, I probably also pee a lot
I've been drinking a lot of water. I've been hydrating. Maybe these people are like I do drink
I drink a lot of water. I do I drink not I don't want to call it a lot of water
But I I mean over the course of a day
I I definitely have at least six to eight ounces of of glasses of water a day
I have like six to eight eight ounce glasses of water a day. I think it would be fair
Let's just say let's just say five or six then six
Let's just say seven seven i'm gonna say seven because I feel like six i'm gonna say six six
Six times 25 is what seconds? Okay. I think I did the quest and i'm i'm gonna go pee
All right, you go. We're we're working through this
Yeah, figure out how long it takes me and then factor that in so it's about
37 to 47 days is how many how long you've peed a year?
No, wait, I thought I thought you meant a year that would be fucked up
So 47 how many how how i'm i'm 37 years old so two and a half minutes a day
How is that over over 37 years so it would be that so 27 days
We said I got 27 days. Okay, let's say 27 days and then let's do the other one the
other
You know number two I would say uh, probably
I this is weird to talk about on stream. I'm just gonna call it something else
I'm gonna combine a few because like I've probably puked a bunch in the bathroom, too
And so let's do all right how long i'm gonna say a day
I probably spend about and like showering and like brushing my teeth
I'm gonna combine everything maybe like 45 minutes to an hour a day
I would say at least one hour a day is spent cleaning, you know showering
Brushing my teeth going to the bathroom
Sometimes they're a little longer probably an hour a day. So one hour a day this 20 so one it's um, 37 years
Well, how many days is that? You know, i'm saying total across the whole day being in the bathroom. That's it showers
That's you know, the other thing that i've been said 1.3 years. So it's one and a half years
So then so let's just let's just round up to the one so one and a half years
I've been going to the bathroom or showering. I've showered for like a year
No
I've been on the toilet for a year and a half
Jesus plus the other stuff so i've spent like 15 years of my life
Sleeping brushing my teeth shitting puking or sleeping or taking a shower. I'll be back. Wow
I was trying I was muted
I said don't tell me this isn't an interesting conversation because it's a very interesting conversation
You know how long you've been doing something over the course of your entire life
It's an interesting conversation and i'm gonna mute you. Okay, because now it's my turn and i'm muting you now
It's your turn. I don't trust you
Like while you're gone, I might like say he's gone. Nope. Goodbye. Goodbye. See you later
All right, i'll be back
I'm gonna start doing that from now on when I come back. I'm just gonna very gently and lightly just kind of go
So people go oh he's back instead of being like hey
What is this title?
One and a half years in the bathroom
I didn't make this title
You still in the bathroom?
You're telling me you just spent 15 seconds peeing. No, actually I did time it. Did you time yours?
No, how could you have not timed it when we were just talking about it I really like
Didn't feel the need to I feel like I have enough data
I've done the work mine was exactly almost exactly 20 seconds. Okay, that's short
That's actually very short for how long we've been, you know going you stay hydrated there
Yeah
I mean I I did do a big full pee. All right, let's stop this and move on
Now what's your favorite kind of pasta? Have you ever cut an onion? All right
We're gonna go to that cave. What cave is that? Because I did the ronnie thing. I think oh wait
Starts. Oh does it? Well, how can we did you get a cutscene? No, what cutscene are you supposed to get?
Don't you get a cutscene before radan's there? I know I think we have to I don't know
I don't I don't remember ever getting a cutscene except for maybe when you go there and they talk about the festival
Let's warp there. Let's warp there. Let's work there right now right into the the plaza
Did you count in thousands or mississippi's? Um, just three three four four five five six
Uh, did it happen usually aren't they usually out here? No
No
And we when you gotta go up to altus plateau and we think we can go back down through the river and climb up
Though that way so what's the best?
On fire to sit at to do that
We'd have to start like all the way at that macaria gate and just go down to the left like here
Let's let's do that. I don't think you can go down here. Yeah, I don't think so. I think we have to go all
the way
That way it works
Wait, wait, wait, wait. No, I know a better one. I know a better one. I know a better one
I know. Yeah, I know a better one
Well, this is right
people go down into the lake and
people are we
Saying a certain place to go to is it well i'm saying a certain place
Do you want to go do the turtles?
All right. So your plan is to go from here and then down and go duck. I see
Oh, sorry. I left first. I forget sometimes like you load in later
If yeah, you are the host it is
I have an extended loading screen more than you do
You don't want to go pet turtles
I love how you're the one that wants to pet the turtles
But you're the one that's been killing the turtles the whole time we've been playing I killed one turtle one too many
What is zeus?
Yeah, what is doing that? This area looks weird
In it
I went backwards
You did just go in the complete. Why was I following you? I just assumed you were going the right way
I was distracted by the zeus
It was just vibing. Hey, i'll tell you
Vibes have been vibes have been pretty good tonight. Would you say that?
I thought the vibes were good yesterday as well enough. You're trying to like compare like you're saying for you
The vibe was off vibe was not off for me
No, no, no, no
The vibes were off and on only at the very last 30 to minute 40 minutes of that of the stream
You know what I mean? Like when we couldn't beat the vibe vibes were kind of off
Vibes are on the entire time
Except for the last 30 minutes vibes are off
Vibes have been on this whole entire time. How do you feel the vibes would be just out of curiosity if
Every time we entered a boss room, we like beat it first try
Is that like good vibes or is that like this is a little bit too
Like we're too good. They need to stop us. I feel like how good we are. I feel like the vibes would be
not
Great
But uh, there's one kind of in parentheses after that
Okay vibes not great, but this is randomizer and it's possible that we just absolutely
Just power stack our weapons crazy and there's like a mad soldier in one of these rooms, right? Yeah, that's not
That's only happened once we're getting a lot of like actual bosses
They gotta be running out of them. Yeah, they gotta be running out of salamanders at some point and then put the other
Parentheses bracket around it. Whatever
Vibes not great, but this is random. I suppose we just power stack our weapons. There's a mad soldier in this room
That's an extreme title that that should be the stream title if i'm really honest that should be the title
God so stupid. Someone should just build a ladder here
I got another seed. Did you get the golden seed there?
It is not a golden seed for me. It's been a golden seed
On i'm not saying that's why you you were getting golden seeds from those. Yeah, i'm getting smithing stones from them
That's why my weapon is plus 28. So that's what's been going on
All right, I want to see what's in this back area
See if there's any consumable items picking up
bears in the wall
There is a bear in the wall. It's got like a fire buff
Okay, that's all
It's a good title. It's a very confusing title if you're
Not currently here right now. Oh
That's scary
You get it
Yeah, I got that mogul like I was kind of hoping that you were just gonna fall on your back by the screen
That would have been funny
Somebody said i've been having the stream in the background and I have this weird subliminal message of wanting smoothies. Did you do something?
It was yeah something you said something like that. I just paraphrased I paraphrased your entire comment
It was in that same ballpark. It was that same world. I think we gotta go up this ladder
That's not even real. This ladder goes up. Watch out. There's goons in here
Actually, this place is way worse usually. Oh cool. I found uh on the traps
is this the place where there's the
That big like a centipede bug thing
No, there's a million little baby boys and they all throw poison at you. Oh, okay
And there's like a bunch of traps on the ground as you run away from them
Is there an item? I think there is
Yeah, there's an item that's it's gonna be
Dung don't even it's gonna be like a glass shard
I remember my my elden ring playthrough. I was saying there's a lot of like moments like that where it's like
Oh, you missed the item going up the elevator to just like
To make it take longer to do something and then you go get it and it's like, oh you found like
I don't know
Nothing. I got a giant crusher the weapon called giant crusher. I think the point is sometimes the journey is more important than the destination
So it's being able to actually see that there's something cool for you to do
It's with any kind of reward
This is an interesting concept because it makes you feel like that you've done a good job paying attention to the game's environment
And I just got the axe of godric
changing character immediately
Again, this guy cannot use an item
For more than 30 seconds
I think that was a pretty good way to explain that
You want like a crossbow or anything?
No
Why not?
Did you need a somber seven?
Uh
I think you're at five. You need a six. Yeah, I need a six
You just go seven
Yeah, I have a seven
Yeah, I think we're both
In the same situation where I need I think I need
Sevens of regular I need a six and an eight and then the final one and I just think it'd be plus 10
I think I have an eight. Well, I don't
Everything's wrong. I want whatever that is
Slider goes up
I need to rest
Now poison's almost over
We were just at a bonfire right before we came through here. Yeah, but the poison they got they got a purple item for me
Battle I would refill my mana. That's true
Oh shit
No, no
What's up, what else is here? Well, it's a little scary. I think it's a free kill though. I didn't fall
Uh-huh
See what i'm dealing with here. Let's see what you're dealing with here a lot of um souls
Uh, there is an item up here. I should definitely come up here. I'm
Wait, how do you get up there?
Around the left side over here in the rocks. It's a koopy normal item
Oh, i'm getting it. I'm getting it
It's gonna be like a spell
It's gonna be like godric's last gall
But again, this is another place. I didn't know you can come up here
You're really teaching me a lot. I'm really learned. You're i'm really educated right now
Is there a mod they're using for seamless co-op? Yes
a seamless co-op
Uh, i'm gonna sing the praises of this mod another time
Randomizer was hard to set up just because it's like oh match the right seed and get all these things in the right folders
And make sure you set the right settings
Seamless co-op
is literally
Two files
It it's you don't have to do anything else besides just get the bit of passwords
it's
It's probably the easiest mod i've ever installed i've ever used
Would you say the same thing sir?
Uh, yeah, I guess a little bit complicated when you're trying to have exactly the same mods like the randomizer. Yeah
But the actual seamless co-op is just like a file in game folder done
It's actually insane word
I was concerned when we when we first started talking about this. I was concerned that
Oh, man, this is a whole ordeal. Isn't it? This is a whole thing
I see I felt bad too because I kind of turned it into a whole ordeal
Yeah
No, how did you exactly what you were trying to avoid, but how would you have known right like this?
There's no way you would have known
Please just let me feel bad. No
Step on me
No
It's undeserved
There's no way you would have known that with these two things together and the amount of trying to figure it
We had to figure it out
I really do. Um, I mentioned it yesterday and then you like ignored me and then didn't hear me and probably
Just like spit on the ground on your stream. Yeah, but i've heard i've heard
Yeah, I don't it could be a good one. What if it's a legendary? What if you missed it? Yeah, okay
lump of flesh
Sorry, I made you do that
Uh, I was gonna say like I don't know if you want to try neo 2 sometimes because I did hear it was really good
and it also has like
The co-op just kind of works
Is I tried to play neo a few times?
Just on my own time
I just didn't I didn't like all the stance switching stuff
I yeah, I was a little annoyed by
How overly complicated it was too. I'm not sure if that's still a thing
I say I want it simple exhausted by that as well. I just want it. I just want light attack heavy attack
You can call me just an absolute small brain andy. That's fine. But like I just want it swing
regular swing
Strong swing and the weapons are cool. It's just
I don't like the stances like up down, you know the distance it's that that stance that stance
It's definitely really cool
It just gives you more tools to play with but I want less tools and if that makes me a dope then so be it
No, that makes sense. I agree with you. I
It was a lot
It was it's certainly a much less like
It's weird to say that because like dark souls isn't a casual experience, but neo was like even less of a casual experience
Where does neo sit?
Where like sakiro?
like is neo harder than sakiro is neo kind of more
Kind of challenging and more skill-based than sakiro was I I didn't play a lot. I don't know
It's harder than sakiro really. Oh my goodness. I don't think I do remember it being very hard
And it has like a whole I think neo 2 has like a whole like end game loot finding like
Find like item stuff farming and whatnot
So I imagine it just keeps getting harder sakiro is easier to be honest, huh?
Wow
What's that?
fist weapon
It is
star fist
Holy shit. These are cool
What this is awesome
time to change
Neo is more bullshit difficulty than anything
It looks really fun. It looks really cool. I just I tried to play it a few times
I just that the first zone
Just I I leave at the same point in the first zone every time
After like the first hour to two hours like almost I want to say up to three hours
It's like yeah, no i'm not into this and I leave
Did I miss an item? It is kind of bullshit. I feel like this conversation is actually turning me more like i've been wanting to play it
I bought it
And this conversation is like, you know what?
Maybe not. I really do feel like and if it's it is bullshit difficulty. I don't know
Well, how does neo one compare to neo two?
Is neo two like a better
less bullshit kind of better game
I think they were saying that that's what
Neo is also bullshit. They're saying it's way better though. Like it's way way better. I heard it was very good
Because around the time that like I finished elgin ring
There was a lot of comments on uh neo two like the reviews on steven that were like yeah
I beat elgin ring and I need it. I like need it more
So we all came here and this game's actually pretty good
So the magma worm is supposed to be up here, but I wonder if it's not a magma worm
I hope it's a magma worm
It's gonna make me very happy if it were a magma worm
I hope I just didn't break something
Are we getting a cutscene or am I in my computer crashing? You might be computer crashing. Yep. Well i'll be here
Okay, i'm gonna beat the boss
Don't go in don't do the boss reveal randomizer boss reveal without the other player. That's bm
Oh my god, it's elgin
Sounds cool, and then you then you beat it and the game ends. Oh, I think I crashed again
Oh
On start spicing things up on startup this time weird
Did you use the right launcher? Yeah, this is hard crashed. Okay, let's try that again. Come on. Come on, please
Okay. No good. Thank god. It looked like it crashed again, but i'm good. I'm coming back
Uh, can you put a new one of those thingies down?
I did
I feel bad for that version of my character because they're just gonna get their ass kicked
I think what happened is we both sat down and we both I I had touch grace was on my um
Indicator and I think we both did it at the exact same time and I think it crashed me
I can't believe this is elden beast. Don't say don't go in yet. Don't go in yet
Uh, I have too many souls and I want to level up. We do this
I can't believe this is elder. Yes. Can I have some runes?
Can you have some runes? I need like 1200
Well, how many how many levels higher than me? Are you?
i'll be right back because I keep I feel like I keep loaning your runes and you're like
700 levels higher than me
I got a new staff
Do you want to look at it? What staff? I don't I probably don't need it. I have the staff
I want just not the magic I want
Okay, that's enough. What is that thing? When did I get this?
Boy this thing gives strength doesn't it now gives decks a bunch of boys
I should probably just put it on
Why not? It'd be more damage, right?
And this scales a little bit off decks. All right
You ready?
All right. Oh my god, I didn't even upgrade
All right, ready
Now I am officially ready to go. Let's go
What is it gonna be?
it's gonna be
That's goku. It's
a
Um, what the fuck?
What the hell happened holy shit
Um, good luck. We're just we're not doing this. I don't think we're gonna beat this one
I think we're not beating this one
We gotta the thing we're gonna break the thing on his ankle. Where is it?
Which ankle is it?
Which leg I can't even I don't want what leg is it on?
It's on his left leg
Is he wearing a tumeric bracelet? Yeah, we gotta get the tumeric bracelet. It's on his left leg
Okay. Well, it's probably on the leg. That's like like a lower half
Good luck, man
We actually did a good amount of damage
Yeah, gonna break the bracelet on his left leg. The second phase is gonna be horrible here
Uh-oh
What the fuck? I don't know dude. It's not where did that fire come from?
This is phase two. It is you're right. He's
What?
That's right. The bracelet's already broken
What he summoned the slow moving things and they like finally caught up to me and it convoked me
We're gonna we're gonna be here for a little while
Yeah, you I I walked in and I saw him shooting in the air
He's like that's weird because he doesn't do that until phase two. He had a great
Uh entrance though probably best entrance of the whole time. We've been playing
Yeah, I don't think this is gonna be hard
As long as we're not being like sabotaged by like someone telling me to like fight the ankle
And like can't find out which leg and he literally only has one leg
But I I thought it was very I don't know that you fight the ankle on phase one
I'm just saying there's a couple of things with your story that are not lining up
Okay, wait i'm gonna put on some like fire resistance or something
Oh, yeah, let's cheese it and like be prepared for the fight like losers. Yeah
Let's like
Prepare for this fight you fucking dweeb
Get in here i'm putting gear on and why I don't
I need to get my fire resistance. Oh, hurry up
Magma giant just get on the horses skip the whole game and then uh,
Missed seven bosses in ten areas and y'all ramp it up already fire resistance gear on
Coming that's the same damage if you dodge it
All right tack the hands
Okay
That was dumb
Jesus how did I not get hit by that? I have no idea
Why does he move his hand?
That is really annoying
What the fuck?
He is really he actually is
Stop every time I go for the hand. I just he just instant moves it
We're doing pretty good
staggered really
Is there a place to hit him anywhere?
His hands. I mean I like uh, but I don't think he has a stab point
Uh, it's bullshit again
Oh my god
What oh
Stop moving. Oh my god. I feel like I just crushed like a bug
He's going psycho mode on you
Yeah, he is
I don't know why i'm casting this magic. It's too powerful
Make it rain
Why does that
That's like why is that up there? Why is make it rain make it rain. Why is it up there?
I don't know where why it's up there in your head
Why not?
Oh now now you just made me laugh and now i'm having problems. I was dodging every attack. Everything was going so smoothly
Make it rain
When was the last time you even played that game seriously?
Uh, I don't know years and years
I actually played like once a year ago, maybe with uh
Like moon was playing
It's still like a pretty fun game
It is yeah, i'm surprised they still get like a whole bunch of content
Nice job a lot of my chat. I don't think god it's it's a quote from smite
When uh, one of the characters who shoots fireballs is make it rain
Yeah, it's agony
Agni has this move
It only in one of his skins but germa. I i'm aware that germa loves it
I mean, it's just I have not heard that in a very long time
I got a sacred tear
I totally spaced out and I was thinking about swag knee. I think I got one too. I don't even know
Oh, the doubters lost out big time. I think here
Sorry doubters. You lost a lot
I my personal recommendation
Is to be a believer
from this point forward
Yeah, I would say so too. I have enough to level up again more strength
Really? Oh
Hold on
It's 26. I think
You know you see the runes needed number all the time, but the second that it goes away
It's gone from your memory. Has it happened to you too?
I haven't I honestly have been like forgetting to level
Constantly, so I really haven't been looking at that. However, I can relate in programming
Constantly open up something then like oh, yeah, I need to do that and i'll close a window and be like wait
What was I doing?
No object permanence
You know, I do envy people that have really really good object permanence
I just how do you how do you have good?
All right
What's the scale? Okay. Let me paint a picture for you
If you you know go somewhere you take you know, you take your car you go somewhere
I'm gonna go the the store or you lost me. You actually lost me already. All right, but just anybody that's listening
Don't have a license. I can't relate. Okay, so then just you just can hang out. I
Always no matter what doesn't matter where I go where I park. I always don't know the exact location of my car
Every time even when I say I look at the parking space. I go this is where I am
I got to remember this an hour goes by two hours go by and then it's just
I know the general vicinity of where the car is, but I don't have any idea where it is
That's not object permanence. Yes, it is. That's that's literally
ADHD that's object permanence. That's you keeping a thing in your brain and knowing where it is
That's object permanence. How's that not object permanence? It's the same thing. That's memory. What do you mean?
Object permanence is like forgetting something exists when it's outside of your view. I don't do that
I just forget where it is. I know it exists. I just don't know where like okay this big stone
Okay, so I guess I guess you're like you're like a five on the scale five out of ten
Yeah, it's not that bad and a one is like a toddler and you're like four points away from that object permanence would be hold on
Somebody said something. I want to read it. You have a bad memory. Yeah, so what object permanence?
Is is how peekaboo works with babies? Wait a minute. Yeah, that is
Object permanence would be if you forgot your car existed
Because he said it first and I saw it and I caught it it was in my mind a little bit object permanence problem there
But I did see it and I didn't I didn't I forgot it for a second. Then you said it
You like absolutely tuned me out. Can I turn my mic up? Like is there a problem?
You said I was quiet the other day. Are you there? Hello?
It's poor awareness
Whatever it is. It's what I have. It's awareness
It's it's all it's awareness. It's memory object memory awareness
Is that better?
Give a shit memory
Yeah
I lose my keys all the time my wallet memory. Yes, it is. No, no
How is losing your keys not memory?
It's not memory. This is a symptom of adult adhd where if you put something down you forget where it is
Not because your memory is bad
But what is forgetting about something else because your attention is on something else
You're not forgetting because you'd never have the memory of putting it somewhere because you're not focused on that
You're focused on something else, but that's memory. That is a that is you're talking about a piece of your memory
Short-term memory is memory short-term memory. Don't let him cook
No, let me eat. Okay. I'm done cooking. Okay. Uh, we I believe we just I think we we did it
We did it. Yeah, I think we can go fight radon. I'm barely certain we can go I think and i'm really really praying
That radon is like a normal soldier in a in a big empty desert
I think your dementia is contagious
I voted to teleport it was something going on. I did too
Did we pick the wrong one? I don't think so
Red main castle plaza. I think that's yeah, that's the one
Sometimes it's just a little weird. It can be a little weird
Turma has to buy a new car every time he leaves the house
Well, I never had a car before
I guess I have to have I guess I have to get one and i've got to i'm gonna drive
Oh, you hear the halo music?
Before we begin did you cut him off?
I'm in the cutscene. Yeah, I am too
Are we skipping?
Yeah, you want to watch his horse?
Die, do you want to watch his horse die? No, I we've i've seen this cutscene a lot
Okay, it's kind of like fucked up. I don't want to fight him yet because I have a lot of uh,
I need to level up. We're gonna win. We're gonna first try dude. No coward coward coward first try coward first try coward
There's a lot to lose
First try coward. You'll pick it back up when we go in again if we die
What we're gonna first try it you you agreed when I said no more doubters object permanence andy you should believe now
Short-term memory andy you think i'm gonna
Come on
Lot to lose there man
I thought I was gonna be alive. I really did
I was I thought it was gonna be like two hp, you know, I need to get my I need to get those back
Dude, you got this wrong object permanence would be forgetting the ground exists
How extreme are we going? Uh, that's okay. That's very extreme
I forgot that I am an object and that actually I am inhabiting this body on earth
I thought I was on the astral plane. I dreamed that I was a butterfly. I feel like there's there's levels
There's tiers of this. It's not just like
Oh object permanence issue. That means you must not understand. Yeah that you're holding a sword
You let it go and then you picked it up and it's the first time you've ever seen it
That's uh, that's augerins. Will they be down first try? I don't know. This is a good
This is tough because we who know it could be
It could be something really annoying
That's the first try. This is the first triangle. I we're not i'm not losing this
I'm committed to not losing this and i'm 100 sure. This is going to be like a crab
And what is it?
Star it's godric
Uh phase two godric or we're gonna summon everybody. We have to see that. We have to see what that
No, we do. I want to see what the outfits are
They're all gonna have funny outfits. That's that's true
The voters didn't know we were summoning all the guys
This guy's got fucking rivers of blood
Just let them fight
Don't even play the game just summon everybody because there's no there's no way they're gonna die
If you bet against this yeah true actually if you bet against this you are you just trying to lose your money
I'm just trying to lose your points
Now here's the real question. Where is godric? Are they just hanging out somewhere? He's gonna be up on the hill
What is what is uh, what does blade have for like stuff? He looks the same. Let's see
Yeah
Yeah, he might be like what are you doing dude? You gotta you gotta walk up there with the boys
Oh shit, he's running. Let's go. Oh shit. He is running. Wait, what the fuck?
Oh
For some reason I was thinking of a different boss. All right, let's see how they do
Wait, there's more people to summon up there. There's uh
Is this
I know there's like a healer, right?
Yep
maiden
All right, let's see how they do
Somebody died already
Dude, if you guys can't beat godric, I don't know how you ever thought you're gonna beat radon
Where's sigward this is a major let your ambitions to rest moment
No, you should have waited
They're dying dude. Yeah, they're not doing that great the healers on the look at the healer behind us
They're stuck. Oh, no, is she stuck? Yeah, she was stuck inside all the rubble. Come on quinn get in there
She's kind of smart
She's waiting for the real gamers to get in there before she buffs us
She's gonna be throwing lightning spears and show. Oh, wait, where's blade going?
Wait, where is he going?
Wait is it
Why is he running over here?
He's just floating in the sky on my screen. I think he died. All right, let's get him
Oh, they said you gotta run away from this shit. I forgot about that
I'm only doing comedy spell
I'm gonna need you to hold him in place
You got him. Thank you
God damn it
When does he go?
Giving the doubters some hope
I like the part where he goes
Scream stream
Yep, are we gonna actually does he do willy do phase two?
I wonder no no god have you been paying attention but he does phase two and half health not at the end of the health bar
He's gonna be a different boss, right? Like wait, he is gonna be a different boss. Oh crap
Uh-oh, how's your comedy looking now?
Even at half health
Like it's not him leaving. It's just him doing a cut scene
Here it is. Oh, he's actually oh he does do it. Have you been paying attention?
Don't make fun of me when you're the dope
See yeah, he hasn't been paying attention. All right, let's summon all of our friends again
Or is that cheating?
I don't know. It's at least like
Just get healed at least
I don't know
I feel like we should fight the character
All right, fine
Too bad. We don't have the music object music is the best in the game
No, don't kill our killer
What did she throw dude?
Oh
Finish him off. Don't usually use my full power
Oh, he killed me with it
I thought he was aiming at you
Hey, I thought I actually thought he was aiming at you
Oh shit, we're gonna lose
Uh, here comes the here comes the throw from the stir
I think it's freezing
You're kind of you are jumping around
Just a couple more hits. You got it. I rolled backwards like a dope
Okay
Hey, I got the wait. I have the right side of the uh, howling tree medallion. Do you have the left side? Yes
I believe so. Okay, we have that
I I again got three golden seeds
Jeez
All the bosses are just spitting seeds out at me. I don't know why that's pretty weird
Can you can you go over the cap in a randomizer or no?
Is it just gonna give you the amount that exists in the game? It should only be that amount
Can you sit at the bonfire? I'm watching the cuts. Okay. Sorry. You're not watching the cutscene. You're just waiting. I understand
um
Okay, I am elden ringing loading screen. I'm loading
It probably looks like i'm hitting like a vape over here. I keep going like I keep going like
It's a fucking drink container. Oh some hot cider
My game is in an infinite loading screen. I think okay. No, it actually
It's this I I fill it up
I was just worried that it might have like crashed because this is when it like changes the world state because he killed radon
There's some bonfire out here, right?
I it's supposed to be
There's something we might actually
Hold on do you is does radon have to die for the game to register that?
No, the cuts everything happened for no crone
Everything did happen. Okay
He said you you were in the cutscene, but where is the bonfire then?
It should be going down here. There's a there's a catacombs down here. I'll get that waypoint
You spectating i'm reading a comment. I heard you you said that you believe aliens built walmart
Um, I feel like that's something I probably said
So, I don't know. Yeah, I think that I guess
No, I definitely did I?
Um, I think that miyazaki. No, not miyazaki. He's the guy made um death stranding for a second
I thought you're gonna say that you you said
Miyazaki made walmart. No, no, no, it's weirder. Many actually said it who kojima kojima said that aliens did 9 11
Oh, where are you? Oh, that's right. I forgot about this cave. This looks weird. My game is very unhappy
I would be surprised if I didn't crash in like five seconds
I think this when I rest it'll kill you it'll murder you
And then you're gonna have to go back out into the desert and get your souls from there
bitch
DLC leak. Oh, we're seeing underneath iron forge duties. Wait, there is a there's a bonfire out here
Yeah, yeah, I couldn't see anything you were doing. Oh, I ran to the
You know, I kind of need to crush your head
What you are poking out of the ground just the top of your head is okay. I need to go over here
Uh, can you even agree to that? I can you probably gonna have to do it again though
Well, i'm saying because it's like a upon fire you don't have
I get it's there. I can see it. I think because you're the host. This is technically your game. So anything you do I get as well
Hailed. Yeah, it does it sometimes let's do it again. What's your favorite mobile game?
right now, uh
Pintar poker lame let's say it but play it and then tell me say it play it and then tell me
Say and play and then tell me pine tar poker play it and tell me
I would love to hear you. I'd love to hear you say that again after you play it. Okay. Okay. Do you like um, yahtzee?
I've never played yahtzee. Oh, that's another thing. He skipped. Oh my god, dude. You never played yahtzee and elden ring
Wait, is this like random? Yeah, this is like random enemy battleground. Oh, they keep spawning, right?
At least they should keep spawning
All right. I just I gotta pay attention what the hell's going on here. What is that? Is there a giant in here?
Uh, yeah, I heard the attack on titan. Yeah, he's down. He's down there
Okay. Well, let's just go to the boss
There's a lot of shit here. This is a big place if I remember
Oh, yeah, it's locked by some contraption. Yeah, we got to go up and jump through a window and out the window
Yeah, there's a lot. This is a wacky one
This one actually kind of sucks. It's one of the harder ones. I didn't spend my 87 000 souls
Yeah, I needed to die where we're going we're going back. Oh shit. This poor flower doesn't stand a chance
No
I'm just going back to the
At beginning
You're gonna feel the cold steel of my katana
Damn, that's like that's a lot
When does the the hard cap the soft cap is for uh attributes?
I believe it's 40. Is it 40 for like strength x intelligence 40, right?
Either 40 or 50. It's 60
Oh 40 60 80. Okay. Yeah, six. Yeah, that keeps diminishing, right?
How's everybody doing good? How you guys doing? How you doing? Everyone doing? Okay. Everyone good on water. Yes. Anyone need any uh,
Don't need anything that did sound like that. Didn't it like I was the host of a party
Everybody good you guys good. You need anything breadsticks. We're gonna get you. You guys good
How come all the shitty enemies are in the path we have to go and they're like not fighting each other
Um, that's a good question
This guy is very confused
Ooh
That still did a ton of health damage to me
Are you like a parry guy? Do you like it? Are you like you like parrying? I like parrying a lot
In any game what game has the best parry? This is a great stir question. I think
soul caliber
I that that was such an unbelievable statement. I'm so confused by that. I died
What what do you mean like what what game has the best parries soul calibers a lot of fucking awesome parries
But that sounds so interesting to me. I needed to explain a little bit in more detail
it's always been one of the main mechanics of soul caliber is if you press like any character can press like
Guard and down or garden up and you have to do the correct parry for if it's a low mid or high or like
There's characters with special parries that have like if you parry it then you like instantly go into another move
And it's uh, it's like a whole, you know
Just built-in system and it's very nice because it's you're like shield lights up
So, you know the timing for it very well and it makes it nice like when you get it and you feel good
That sounds actually really fun. Um, all right, but what about not like not multiplayer?
Just like a like a pve scenario. Well, who what a game has the best pve parry
Soul caliber two in the labyrinth mode. All right, okay
No, I I I would struggle to even think of uh, games besides like dark souls
Well, which from software game has the best parry then?
Trying to remember how it even worked in bloodborne because you didn't have parries you had like you used your gun to parry
I feel like dark souls one had a really just satisfying parry
I'm gonna be wrong though
I really do like just the general dark souls using the small little buckler. Yeah, and you do this thing you go you go like this
Yeah, and when you do it you go we
You make like a noise and it like gets into like noise of the year. We like that, right?
Yeah, I love that
Sekiro is uh
Sekiro is a rhythm game
It's like playing
Sekiro have you not have you not played soul caliber you and I played it I think in the same room at one point
Just like sitting around hanging out. Oh, yeah
We did it like a pax east when they were like showing a soul caliber four
Yeah, i'm not I really don't play fighting games. I'm really not into them
I just I mean some of the ones like I like like smash like i've played it a bunch
Multi versus is fun
But like not the the kind of like 2d plane fighting games where both characters are like this and they like are fighting this way
Well, actually that's multi versus and smash, but you know what I mean?
It's like zoomed in the camera. It's you know, i'm saying it's like the 1v1 just zoomed in camera
Yeah, I don't really like to play those. I'm not very good at them non platform statements went together
No, I I don't like non platform fighting games
I feel like you need a lot of knowledge to play them. Well, and I just don't really have the time
I want to give the time to it. Um
Do you know where the the mechanism is? I know I just I I have never like actually fought one of these enemies
I just avoid them. Oh, that's cursed and i'm dead
I forgot they had the curse. I forgot can you res me? Yeah, i'm gonna res you
Street fighter six. Oh, it's on cooldown. Do you another 20 minutes? Do you like street fighter?
Are you do you like to play street fighter? I'm interested in the new one and i'm always interested in them
But i've never really played them a lot. I have to reset but I was gonna say I mean like evo moment number
I think that shit's cool. I like parries the most in fighting games
so when you go like to when you're excluding all multiplayer games, you're kind of like
Oh, you've respawned this motherfucker right on top of me. He's easy. Geez. I was really upset
My game
All right, vince mcmahon
Um, okay, I got it it was it was like right there so when you
Where the fuck am I going?
I can't going back to the bonfire. Let's both meet over the bonfire then we can just walk to the boss. Okay
I'm guilty guilty. Here's fun, too
I like I like fighting games
What's the best soul caliber?
Uh, you're really gonna ask that you're really gonna you're really gonna put me there in that spot
Um, it has to be two. I found a weapon that you probably are gonna like
I found the carrion knight sword. It's like just a great
intelligence weapon
Uh, wait, what was it carry a knight sword? Oh, yeah. Uh, sure. I want it. I was gonna buy it earlier
It was in my uh dragonheart shop. Oh, okay. Oh, yeah, don't die. You're you're scarlet rod it, you know
You're you're a little stinky. So soul caliber two
Yeah, I mean I liked the newer ones a lot
But there's a lot of things objectively in them that I would feel like a bad person saying they were the best six
The most recent one is actually also I would I would put like two and six. They're both popped for different reasons
Really? So the newer one is good. Yeah, it's just
I don't know a weird amount of support where it gets overshadowed by tekken. I've got soul caliber is slower, right?
It's not like a
It's like a looker
It's a lot slower. Okay, I probably like it if I've really ever how was it compared to like mortal combat because mortal combat is
Not fast, but it's not really slow either. I'd say
Generally, it's probably even slower than mortal combat because a lot of the 2d fighters like that like your punch in mortal combat
Or in like street fighter a punch is like a three frame attack. We're just like it's happening
He punches but every like the slowest moves in the fastest moves, excuse me in slow caliber are 11
to like 15 frame range because I was marv versus capcom is like, um, what is that anyways, um
The problem that I always have with fighting games is especially something like like marv versus capcom for instance
It's just it's almost I can't really even this is actually going to be probably horrible
Yeah, depends on how much uh
Yeah, yeah, dude, you're you're fucking dead dude, um, we don't know we can skip this one
We don't have to do this one. No, we're doing this one. I need to learn like how this boss actually works
There is nothing to learn. It's literally just it just spams every ability it has
Do you have heals because heals actually do a ton of damage to this?
This is one of those enemies that I feel like they programmed like a bunch of extra moves and they forgot to take them out
Like this character's move set has like five extra swings that they just didn't delete from like the lines of code
This is yeah, like a sakiro enemy. You're just supposed to like auto parry everything
I might be able to do it because I have faith. Yeah
Can he be parried?
I
Doubt it. Who knows maybe
Timings are also so weird
And it screeches at you like a fucking child
everything about it
there's like the weird pig scream that like
I could probably do it if I really tried
it's like a
but
It's you you you an o shape with your mouth. It's
I could do it if I really wanted to
But I feel like I don't want to wake a bunch of people up like last time. I think I think you're good, dude
You're really trying to farm the worst sound today. I'm not even
Worse sound of the year every clip is going to be from this stream
Well, dude, I played elden ring for two months straight at the beginning of last year like
30 clips were nominated for stuff. So come on. It's we've been playing it a lot
Uh, hold on. Let me actually
Hold on how much faith do I have because I wonder if that heal really is something I should put on right now
Give me a sec
You're saying something about like marvel or something. Oh, right right jumped by an evil boss. What is the great heal?
How much faith is great heal?
I might ask it for you might ask it back actually wait
I don't have a cat. I don't have one of the catalysts. I have no idea because my game says zero
I don't have a catalyst. I can't cast this spell can I I could give you one because I think this actually makes these enemies
Just completely trivial if you just cast seals with them. I have a dragon seal
It's like warming stone. I i've never done this or oh, no, I did I did get a dragon seal. Okay
Okay, so let me um
Drop a great heal because I might I might I might be
Just teleport just teleport back here i'm at the boss door
Why don't you come here because I if great heal might be able to kill this guy in like five hits
Okay, so why don't you come here and get it because I have to I have to attune it i'm locking back
No, no, no, no, let's let's just we're fine. Okay. I want to hear that marvel thought
Marvel versus capcom 2 is so fast that it's almost hard for me to even pay attention to what's happening
And I feel like the you know what i'm not a big fan of at the soul cali. I don't think so caliber has this
I'm not a big fan of the
Zoom the camera in to show like here we go something's happening. I wanted to see what's going on
Like the here comes a move ring and we go zoom in really close and zoom out. I I want to see the whole plane
I mean it it it zooms in when you guys stand closer to each other if that's what you're talking about
How close do I have to be for this?
what
This thing that fucking doesn't even work
He fucking comboed me man, this is not where urgent heal is not an aoe
Okay, oh, okay supers in marvel where it like yes you go into like super and it like changes the whole screen
Yeah, it's like
The camera goes like a close-up of their face or they're you know doing something
Sometimes I think it doesn't hold another scene off camera
I actually also hate those the new soul caliber does it and I hate them. I I wouldn't say I hate it
I just I just not it's it's unnecessary to me. I agree that like I would rather it be
Like an in-game attack rather than like a cinematic drop a great heal on the ground so I can um
Equip it later when we die in it literally 10 seconds
Uh-oh, he's gone. I'm not what am I not dropping it on my screen? You're running in place
So will this let me see
No, it's a oh, okay. Yeah. No, no, I'm going back this this this should do it. I waste time. I'll be right back
Uh
It is an aoe
The thing is I like watching people play those games
I think it's cool because when they when people do their combos and you get it looks like it takes a lot of
Interesting skill set to do that
I will never be able to have and it's just fun to kind of watch people that know what they're doing flight get mana
I'm a big uh
big soul caliber
Enthusiast so even that like there's like barely any combos
I hate games where it's like 16 hit combo from corner to corner, but even that they've I don't know
It's gotten worse with that over time as well
How close do I have to be to use this? Does it matter where I am?
Holy shit
Jesus. Oh my god. Oh my god. That scared me. It was so ridiculous. Uh, you died
Okay, so that all right, so I don't have any more mana but
Uh, I will if we don't beat it
Oh my god, let me just drink for a second
It's I feel like i'm playing a fighting game against somebody I was doing comedy i'm sorry
All right. Yeah, i'm so glad we can kill this guy in two seconds now
Okay, we're good. Um
Pass that shit to me. All right. No, you're you have faith, right? Yeah
What do you mean pass that to you? You you want to be the one that does it?
Yo pass that shit to me dog. No, this is mine. I'm doing it. All right, let's go
That's like the most compelling argument i've had to like switch to faith and do the healing fire stuff
I was talking about just to just get rid of that enemy just delete that enemy from the whole game. Whenever you see it
Yep. Yeah
You're losing focus because the mask
That's good to know
That sound was so loud too. It was like he got hit
by a hundred damage abilities in a row
Not by one singular ability
I'll defend you my lord. All right, here we go drink
Wow, I never knew that either that's silly
I am
Silly shit. What's amber drought?
Draught what is this? I've never seen that item. Oh, it's uh, it's the like puppet guy
Oh, can you give me that carrion knight sword?
Did you? Yeah
Okay, i'm
Not of this reality
Okay, so you did mention you said hey man, I really want those spells
You it's 15 faith to use great heal. Are you actually going to put like five points in faith?
Are you going to yeah, I have to take it off at the bonfire
Like I from the beginning. I just want it like carrion great sword or something. I think there's a lot of souls
But uh, nobody's finding it. Do you want them both? I'm imagining you probably do sure
I'm gonna give you this other thing too. It's just like frenzy. It's a ton of faith
You're probably never gonna use it
But your spell guy and it was great heel was the one that hit him great hill is the aoe. Yeah
Urgent heal I think is just a heals you I think. All right, where are we going? We killed radon. I think the next logical place
is
Plateau there's not any major bosses that like is before plateau. Um
Um
We're not are you getting runes? Wait, what about the great runes? The great runes are also
Random so oh
Is that gonna lock us out of being able to beat the game?
Potentially, but the merchants do sell hints to like where some items are and if we really need to look there's like a spoiler file
That'll tell you where great runs can be found
But I think we could go tries to put them in places where you'll probably find them. Uh
Knock around is apparently the next logical step so underground or see the plateau go through the capital
Volcano manor is another one too. Yep up in the mountains. I feel like there's a lot of bosses up in the mountains, too
Do you want to do the skip to volcano manor from
Cilia or wherever you know, I mean the oh that enemy is gonna be different. Never mind. We can't do it. Hmm
What's up to you? I I actually totally forget how you get to volcano manor without doing that
I wonder if they're on the map
Is it how do you get to volcano manor normally you have to get the invitation right to like go actually inside of it?
And do the how do you get to uh, what's his name? Uh, the snake guy rykart rykart. Yeah, you need
Like walk all the way up the mountain on the it's it's a long travel on plateau
My toe platy platypus from where you fought the fire giant. Yeah, the mod kept in the volcano skip
you can go without the
Wait, it does someone said that i'm gonna give you the uh, quarterback seat here because i'll do anything just probably just looking at the map
Thinking if there's anything i'm forgetting. Let's just go to the plateau and the npc can tp you to volcano manor
Really, which waypoint is it to where we were you can still do the lucaria skip apparently. Oh
Rhea's in the lake. That's right
The the snake uh, the snake lizard kind of girl. She's in the lake and I think she can tp you there, right?
I don't know. Is that can we can we actually do that because we could we could just do that right now
I forget where she's sitting around somewhere here. Right? All right, go to um good place to go probably the
Laska ruins we'll go from there. Yeah, she's gonna be one of the gazebo buildings. Watch out giant. I'm not following you
She's in one of those
Oh, there's a basement here
Let's do it free shit. Can't go wrong there. Oh freezing grease
I can respect again or maybe you could because I just got a larval tier. Oh, I already I still have one
I think I have two
Uh, all right. You know what? Let's get the map here
Be much easier
Uh, why am I fighting this thing?
Where's the map? Where's the map? I want to freeze frame that you
Got like photoshop smudge tooled across my screen. What about the typing test? Oh, yeah, i'm kind of tired though
We need to do that like on a high energy start of the stream. I forgot to do that
I've been being reminded but like dude
I want to play elgin ring
Like like come on
Yeah, i'm with him. I'm with him now. It needs to be like a fresh day
You gotta be like fully ready. You gotta prepare. It's true. All right, where's this?
We need to go to follow me. We need I want the map. I hate looking at the no I got on
You know what? I mean, I don't like looking at the
Undiscovered area. I hate undiscovered area sister. I have to ask you this question
Hi
Hi, we planned on this. We planned on this weekend being an elden ring co-op stream weekend
But how do you feel are you you want to keep you want to beat this you want to try to beat the game on randomizer?
Uh, I mean, I thought i'm i'm still enjoying it. I okay
I don't know when would be good like when's good like when you want to play again
What's your schedule look like over the next like this week?
Weekend again or something just do it and have it be a weekend thing till we do we beat it
Or you know, you got stuff you got stuff going on on the weekend, right?
I think if you wanted to play again tomorrow, I could do that and then we could make it a weekend thing
I cannot play tomorrow. Okay, I think it would be the most responsible thing to do to make it a weekend thing
Same deal like saturday sunday. Yeah, that sounds good to me. Nice. Okay, so
Where is her gazebo? Is it this one? Is it this one? Is it this one chat? Give me help here
Where is her gazebo? They are never playing this again. Yes, we are bottom right this one here
Why would
Why would you doubt why doubt they are never doing this again? We're playing so much. We're like not going to the bathroom
And it's like nine hour streams. I'm like i'm gonna piss but this is fun
So fun there ain't ever fucking coming back never again
Uh, I think it's this one. It's the one next to the telescope. Oh, okay. It's this one
All right, all the way south. It's right next to the bonfire
Oh, I know I know an area I also would like to do is the uh, we have the waypoint to the underground
That one mine that we teleported to for the sleepy chest. Yeah, but we like never actually did the mine
There should be a lot of stuff in there and a boss at the end
All right. She's in here. Are you are you here with me? I'm
Not you should probably be here in case the host needs to do something. I'm coming. How far away are you?
Oh god, you're pretty far
Okay
My game crashed
Oh, no, i'm gonna get teleported out
I'm gonna not touch anything because I feel like i'm about to leave and it's gonna break the game if I do anything
Am I gonna get booted? Yes. This is seamless co-op also randomizers as well. Those are the only two things we have on is
Item randomizer enemy randomizer and seamless co-op. I'm inviting you to my game now
Thank you
I did not switch to a faith build. I just put enough points into face so I could use this weapon
It's a strength weapon, but it is faith
Same time. I think if I find
a faith ash of war
That's like my sign to switch
Or if I find one of the spells I want it's my sign to not switch
That's like i'm waiting for either of those
The diablo style loot mod might be fun. Where am I?
Yeah, that does seem interesting
I wonder how elaborate it is. I looked into it and the answer is not very
No
Okay, uh, we need to go back down
Uh, oh it's right here. Okay
So what does it do? It kind of you pick up an item and it's oh long sword of the eagle and it's just random stats
On it. I think it's like preset to have ashes of war or like specific types of uh,
Enhancements on it and it could be like a plus one or whatever. It could just it's like just
It's read like it was just an extra layer to the randomizer
Why are you wearing the same clothes from your first playthrough? I don't know. I have
I don't just like wear shirts and then throw them away. I wash them and wear them again a
Week or so later. She wants us to go get her necklace back from a thug from a shack
Yeah, so we gotta go talk to the there's a guy that makes like, um shrimps or something over here. Oh lobster boy
Yes, let me do this too. What if we kill her?
That would be bad because that would probably break the game and the whole reason why we're doing this is to make sure we can
Get to the manor
Promptly, all right the shack if I remember this shack it's right here chat
They close in the game. Oh
Oh, I don't it's randomizer. I don't know. Is it down. It's right here, right? It's like right here
I think it's this one right here. Yeah, it's right here. I wasn't wearing this earlier. I had the blade
Helmet on I had this
Uh, I had this yeah, I looked much different this playthrough. You look cute. I think I think it looked pretty good
All right questions for stirrer. Did you ever come here?
No
Never came here. I have read I like knew all about the shack and what was here and it was like this place is like
It's all foggy. I never saw it
I think maybe once I like dedicated to coming here. I feel like you just beat all the bosses
You just kind of went boss to boss to boss
I didn't do a lot of the quest lines because they're all so convoluted
I did like ronnie's this is important like I never want to do that ever again
How do we not screw this up do we just like what give give me the necklace I forget
Well, how do we make sure we get to the manor? Well, he's selling an item and it is not a necklace
You need to ask him
And he you have to pay him. Yeah, and I go into the shop and he's trying to sell me a laughing smile mask. Okay
Shit rattling paint. Hello. Okay, I bought it
Hold on deal fuck
Okay, thanks for the smithing stone
I think we broke it
I mean he I bought I don't know. Does that technically count?
Does the the quest I don't I wonder if the game is like, oh you bought that thing from the guy
Kill him. Wait, kill him. He might have it on him, right? He won't have it on him. No, he won't
Hey, excuse me, sir
Sir, don't kill him people are freaking out. They're saying don't kill him. Do not kill him. Do not don't don't stir. No
Uh-oh
He's came fight. He hit me first. Don't touch my friend
Even though he's antagonized and he's completely at fault
Oh, and now you're gonna heal during a fight
I got plenty in mine
Oh, it's delicious
Wish you had more than one didn't you?
Why did you do that? That was mean. I got the iron ball. I yeah, it's not gonna
That wasn't I know. I look I participated but he
What was it? Come on. Is it worse to kill the guy?
I don't know. I think it drink elixirs over his body to show him like that. You would have lived
Here's the thing
But I think we needed that guy alive for for some very important reason. We don't need him. I did like a jokey
Like oh look, I'm doing a joke you killed the guy you started the fight and that ruined our playthrough
Our playthrough is ruined
I guess we're not going to play on weekends anymore. They were right. So what what do we do about this?
How about we get to the manor and they're like seven other ways that we can do it. All right, that sounds easy
Oh, wait, okay. I can't buy prawns. I can't buy the shrimps anymore. He doesn't sell them. Yes
He does. I just bought a bunch of them
I just bought a shitload of them. Oh my god. These things are amazing
Yes, he was look the other merchant
Boiled prawn. Oh
No, those are huge. I can't believe you
Killed that guy and taunted and
All the ball bearing we're good. God damn it, dude. Okay, so
that
Randomizer makes that way to do that impossible. So what if we just walk in grabs it better vote try talking to raya
Anyways, no, she's a snake spoilers
um, I played an entire playthrough with a snake and it was one of the most loyal one of the
Smartest and most fun had a lot of fun moments with that snake. What are you talking about?
I played through my first playthrough. I my first playthrough elder ring was was with the snake spirit summons
I summed them all the time. Okay, it was that's the you're talking about how raya is a
Was a snake
She's bad
Why is that? She's a bad type of snake
Okay, she can't be with the other snakes. There's a lot of smithing stones here. Holy shit just empty
We already got that i'm surprised you could open it again, but we already did that in mod chat. I got something
Here's the path to the manor
You gotta move around the mod mods are back seating like you like you were gonna get us there any quicker
Okay. Yeah, there's actually I have a mod gps here. Let me see if I can look at this in a map
I need to dude people were telling me the mod allows you to use the teleporter
Lady at the bottom of the thing with the we could just go that way if that's true
If you're that committed no, no, no, you're I think you're misunderstanding me like my mod like mod chat like my twitch mods
I know i'm saying something else. You're not understanding me. We just double miscommunicated with each other. Okay
No, just once and it was you just the one time you just you didn't understand. Oh, sorry about that
Is he high
No, i'm really not. I don't know why I keep doing that because the cave after you
Bottom of ray lucaria loop around there's a there's a maiden machine
Oh
Dude, that's right. I completely forgot about that. Hey, I got a better idea
I got a better idea. We are going to go. That's what I was saying you
What ray lucaria at the bottom of the thing you go into the machine and it takes you to the place and at first
I was like, let's do that and I was like wait, it's randomizer
We can't do that. The enemy will be different and you were like, oh
And then someone in my chat was like no in the mod
It's the same and I said that to you and you were like, oh, okay
So maybe we can do it. So what are we doing here? There's a fucking boss in the dungeon. Let's do it, bro
You're not even fucking listening. How come you never listen? I did listen. I just
I
I thought when you were saying that I thought you said that it wasn't possible
So I was like, okay, it's not possible
Then when we were told it was possible in my mind, it was like why are what are we doing here?
I thought you were trying to find something here that was like I thought you were abandoning the manor like ah, no
No, let's fuck that. Let's just do something else. I just want to do this
I thought but I thought you were abandoning like us going to the manor like nah fucking whatever
We can't go there. Oh, maybe we can but we can't where was all this backseating from your mods
When we were trying to find radon, uh, it was there. I just uh didn't look for an hour
Okay, i'm just being honest I I when I play dude when I play elden ring games that require focus or like don't get hit
It's it's i'm here and i'm only here and it's the only place that I am
It's also hilarious that you have like a mod chat and you call it your mod chat
But it's actually like can you guys tell me how to play this game chat?
No, no, it's not. No, it is not. No, it's not
You're talking about one or two scenarios over the course of like 16 hours. We've been streaming this
I believe that a lot more scenarios have come up and you just don't talk about it like this whole time
You've been getting hey jeremy you forgot to you need to like upgrade you have a plus five somber stone
Well, you know and you just act like oh, yeah, but oh you don't you like don't bring up that it was from mod chat
He ignores us too sad face sad face
I'm in i'm here i'm in here right now
I can't
Did someone accuse you of not being here? Wait, what?
i'm just
I'm just saying i'm i'm in here i'm focusing here and if you said something I may not have heard it
I may have heard it in process. I'm here and i'm fighting
I hope I can give this to you because I think that's important. I thought that was in the game
What the fuck is that? There's a guy going to get you
I can't leave this now leave we're watching sopranos. You guys are always watching sopranos in the mod chat
Like what is this?
You guys are on the sopranos kick
Woke up this morning
Did you drop it
I can't it's bound now. Well, wasn't this a fun dungeon?
It was yeah, I like this place. Okay. What'd you do to my computer?
I hacked it when I gave you that dot net framework install. You're correct to avoid it
This is that's like a graphics card artifacting or it's a secret area and that's fucking cool
That's the graphical error a secret area. Mm-hmm. All right, so let's do the thing we were gonna do
The thing that I was not ignoring you about the thing that I just miscommunicated to myself in my own head
That I thought we were abandoning that mission. I looked over at mod chat watching the sopranos
Nobody wants to fucking help me. Did they get to the part where tony hits the gas tank? I don't know
Uh, it failed that's from oh, oh, yeah, you're right. I fucked up. Oh, that's right. I forgot that's from when we were
Was it dead by daylight? Um
Dying light too. Yeah, I picked the wrong one. We got a classroom
Not dead by daylight. Sorry dead light
Daylight dead by daylight dead dead light dying light dead light rising rising light over light
Fucking game crashed. Okay. Um, i'm coming back
We're getting extra crashes today
Is it because we're going deeper into the game and there's more places for errors?
I have no idea and it feels about the same to me
I feel like i've crashed a lot more today than yesterday. Come on, please open open, please dude
You can buy spider-man and fortnight man. Cool spider-man one two or three. I don't know. I
We I need to win the wrong spot. Where are you?
I
Matter doesn't it pull sometimes it pulls me right? Does it pull me where you are?
Yeah, I feel like sometimes it's not done that it puts me somewhere
Has it always done that
Maybe it's because it uh, no, it just like puts me in like a weird spot near you, right? We used to try and
Be in the same location, but then I realized it didn't matter. Okay
All right, so we have to get to the very bottom of this shit
I'm going down. You didn't even do it like a chad like I did
Oh, you're such a chad
You're such a chad
Want to jump off in the midway?
Uh, i'm jump i'm jumping you're gonna go. Are you doing it?
Yeah, because over here you get the uh, the secret ingredient
Oh my god, this is a horrible spot right now
careful
I've missed me got
I got some soft cotton
Am I dead?
Oh, I had animation priority. You didn't whose idea was this
I'm actually really glad we came over here because it's legendary here for me at least
This actually is something you might want. I know they nerfed it but still
Spaghetti it's the sword of night and flame
I do want that you probably want this
If I were stir, I would probably say give that to me immediately
I do believe they nerfed it like into the ground though. I feel like I used it
in a
Run that I did off stream
And it was still pretty good
All right. Is this thing actually down here?
So what happens if
It's not down here. It's just an it's just an omega bird
Let wait, let it kill you
Wait, wait, wait, let it kill you
Let it kill you. All right, i'm gonna die here
Let's see what happens. Don't kill this
Still saying exile
Can you like take it? I don't know like punch it
Oh, it's gonna kill you apparently it doesn't care about me
I feel like this thing kills me so fast and now I just can't it won't hurt me
I didn't know that there was more to this area
He's crushed me in the head over and over again
Okay
Did it work?
All right
I
It works
Let it let it kill you
Really it actually works
You just have to die in that area. I guess if the game doesn't really care what kills you
I lost 17 000 souls. I did but it's worth it because we get to be here
That's it's not a lot anymore. No, i'm i'm i'm a verb
A little 72. It's not like i'm
level like
40 or something
I don't mean to like brag or anything, but it's killing me way quicker
Never mind
I'm watching you get hit by it, but you haven't been hit in a while
How are you watching me get hit by it if you teleport it?
Because you just got hit
Uh, you just got hit again
291 damage you can see my you can see the hit points
I
I can see your character dying and getting hurt but you're not you're like floating up here
Hey
There is the light I can now there's like shadows now. I couldn't see anything before really we're in the manor
I actually liked this place
That was cool
But I mean it makes sense. My element is fire. So I mean, of course, of course i'm gonna like this place
Um, i'm more of a wind
Whoa
That that's a rare item
You need to do a full quest to get that shit
Yeah, every time like I hit a wall you also then follow me in hitting the wall
I don't like it
Yeah, my my element is fire. My herb is tumeric
and
my animal is
How do you determine your herb?
What everyone you like the most the one you like the tumeric is your favorite herb
Okay, so why would you why did you laugh that made it really weird
Because i'm looking i'm laughing with somebody said in chat
Somebody somebody wrote like your favorite herb with a question mark like it was just like what is that supposed to mean?
It was uh, it was funny
Okay, uh, did you come? Okay?
A little we're a little desynced
We're good
You made like a bridge of people
Yeah, you just walk right over them
Oh some fun enemies, what what? Yeah, there's some desyncing going on
There likely is
The boss down here is what is it normally? Is it one of those winged magma lizard? How is it?
What the fuck are you doing?
I'm doing it on purpose. Not I just I was gonna I was also doing on purpose like see if you would do it
So we're like double downing double getting each other
Yeah
You were trying to bait me to do it and I was trying to yeah
But I was trying to make you think that you were baiting me into doing it thus i'm the one that wins
There's a winner in this situation. Yes, and it's me
It's so crazy how he won there
I was right card gonna work. What do you mean? I mean, we might still have to hit it with the spear
We also might not I think uh, I think randomizer does obey the spear rule
And it's just anything in that room that room the boss needs to be hit by the spear
Okay
Shield crash
That's a fun ability
I don't think i've ever seen it before
You get that with like there's the big spike tower shield
I was really I was really trying to make it work for a while
Are you one of those people that try to do a shield build where you just put two shields on?
I mean everyone's like tried it. Thanks when we make it out of here
We're still gonna need to loop around the mountain to get inside the actual manor
That's right. Yeah, that's fine
It's a fun little jolly adventure amongst friends
A little bit like a little bit of gallivanting
Oh, you went her first there pal
Okay, how do you feel about cilantro?
everybody asked
Hey, why bother is kind of how I feel like like why?
it doesn't
I
I don't I don't even know how to i don't like it. I don't like it. I don't like it
This is kind of a mess. I don't we're okay
Well, this is how it was designed
Right. It's not like this is out of the ordinary
Like oh my god, what a tiny little area. This is so ridiculous randomizer another this is like
Yeah, this is by design you fight this guy in a smaller area probably
you do
You actually do
He's gonna explode
Ooh
End it with a flashy move. Oh
Cracked pot ruin arc by gosh. We've done it
I know you're desyncing. I've discovered a lost grace over here
Now like 30 000 that's not happening for a while
uh, uh, okay, we need to go
Around the mount. Do you know where you're going because I do you do?
Okay, but I don't want to go where you're about to go and i'll give you one good reason
Why is that because there's usually the mariner boss up here and I want to fight it whatever it is
It's a good point
Right go north through the canyon and hug the left side. Yeah, he's he's just doing his own thing right now
Is this part of the fun of elgin ring just going on an adventure and not knowing what lies beyond
Right over here. There's a giant tree stalker man. Ooh, there is
Which one is it? Is it the it's the future one?
That's that's fun. This one actually it really sucks
Hit me with them. Oh, but you got a fire weapon
careful
Oh, you were born for this
Not if I get stomped on the ground before being able to stand up
Ah
Watch out
It trolled you with it
I had that and I feel bad that I died
I feel like a loser that I died but also you died like 10 minutes before me
Sir, the boss had like 75 health remaining. We go again
Yes, oh the vibes weren't there vibes are there now
Yeah, they're really I was kind of like trolling
No, no shield
That really not do that much
Really not even worth doing that. It's like they're hearing my character go
I'm over it
No
Keep pounding your ass into the gravel
Get away from me
and again
And again
Ooh, that looks cool
Flashy end probably lasted that'd be worth probably a lot, right?
Yeah
I get love work. Okay. That was just the epic combat that I needed to get my blood flowing for our future adventures
What'd you eat today?
uh for breakfast I had
Uh, I had like italian sausages and I wrapped them in naan bread
Damn, that sounds good
It actually really was
Could I could go again? Did you like?
Peppers and onions or anything like that or just no just straight up
It was like in a hurry and I didn't have much food and I needed to eat before gym
So I was like, I don't I don't know
I'm going with what I got. That's not like
Like what you'd want to be eating before you go to the gym, but also
That is what I ate
Hey, there's nothing wrong with that
Do you like hummus?
I do. I'm a i'm a hummus liker. Yeah, because you mentioned naan bread
Naan bread, I've randomly tried it not that long ago and realized i've been missing out at first
I was like hummus is okay, and i've kind of had a lot of okay hummus
And then I got turned on to some like sriracha hummus
It's really good. Wait a minute
Run that by me one more time
Sriracha hummus was the keyword
Say the first word again
um
Say the first word you just said
I uh
I will not apologize
You're a sriracha. It's new to it's new to me and um
You're a sriracha enjoyer
Yeah, that's
That's how it's gonna be said
uh
Bro, I gotta go
I gotta go I got stuff to do later
Okay, i'm not sure if this is
Now i'm confused
I gotta I gotta I think I gotta go
Okay
Do you want to end here?
Do you actually like a sriracha? Oh you'd like a sriracha? I thought at first it was that I was pronouncing it so fucking bad
Jalapeno's
I'll take a jalapeno sriracha
I love sriracha. I i've actually like never had it at all, but I tried
The hummus and it's very good
And I have a local local streamer penta also
I told him I like that his eyes lit up like I have never seen a human being excited before to tell me how
Much he also loves the heb brand sriracha hummus
So I think i'm on to something
I just think sriracha just I think it just tastes like kind of just it's got like an odd flavor that I don't really like
It's just kind of like I I don't even know what like regular sriracha tastes like I feel like this hummus is probably like
It's probably not it. Hey, um, I have something you need to look at
Oh the meteorite staff. Yes
There's a bunch of snitches in my chat
Like
Like we'll get to it. I I would love it if I can also get a meteorite spell
You know, what's funny to me is I think they're doing that
Because I think that they're so concerned they're watching both streams and they see me pick up an item that you could use
And I think they think i'm just a dummy and i'm never going to tell you that I picked this up
It's going to be gone from my brain
So they're just spamming you to tell me to give this to you
Because they know that they could get your attention. So you'll tell me uh is on the ground right where i'm standing
I walked down to the bonfire
Stir just picked up a large club
I did how come nobody in my chat is telling me about this item that I would like every single time
There's like a strength weapon that's found you go
Look at this
And you walk around you swing it like twice and you're like maybe i'll upgrade that and then we never talk about it again
And then we keep using the weapon that you're using
I just like don't want to derail vr. Josh literally said it
Yeah, but I may have been looking over here you got remember for the streamer to see
What you're saying you have to do it for at least 20 to 30 seconds
Because if i'm looking over here and it's like club club club club club
Hey germa, did you pee your pants today poop poopoo? And i'm like, oh this it's gone. It's gone
I don't see it anymore. I look over and that's not it's not being talked about. Did you pee your pants? You poopoo, baby
Uh, no, i'm gonna stick with this. Yeah, I know it's not even like a cool large club
It's just like the most basic caveman wood club
It's kind of the character i'm playing though
It's like me strong supposed to be a caveman
It's the character you were supposed to play not the character you're playing and you were well we're well past that and it's fine
I mean you're supposed to be me smart and you're swinging around a sword
Uh an intelligence sword that has magic scaling on it. This is a huge club
Squished sideways and has fire on it. Okay, but like uh mom says you have to put it down
Poison get out. Oh, this is a fucking place where the goobs are
I'm going goob mode. Oh, we oh, okay. We're waiting for you to do that
Well, I might as well do it too. So you got poison resistance. Oh, I don't have the hat
I only have the I only have the body you want the whole thing
Yeah
I'll be the one who doesn't get poisoned down here. That's too bad because I like the way it looks
Okay
Yeah, you'll be back to the wolf
We look don't worry, but it makes sense. We we look like the two
Jokey dopey enemies in every like kid's cartoon like I got some ceiling wolves. It's like we drop on you. Watch out
Ceiling enemies in here. Look up like a bad guy over there. Oh, there is yeah
Supposed to be the goop. Why am I so always fucking dark here? It's because I rolled
Oh god, damn it
Don't roll. I forgot
Thanks for the starlight
Did you ever have the coke? Did you have coke starlight? Did you ever try it? It was really good
coke starlight after the fucking
The superhero
No, it was like coca cola cable was it was coke starlight. It was very good
I don't i'm not a coke. I'm not a coker. Are you
You're probably you
If you were to drink like a cola, would you was it like pepsi or?
If I were to drink a cola, I honestly wouldn't be
Okay, well here's something that you really want because this is one of my favorite abilities in the whole game
I genuinely mean that I love that move. It's like my favorite spell ice quag
Okay, that like ice glint stone kind of beam thing. They're like chew chew chew. That's probably my favorite spell
It's very fun. I just got a somber six. Uh-huh. What are you giggling at over there?
coke heads in chat fuming
I don't know the word coke heads kind of had me laughing
I used to be I used to not drink a lot of soda. Well, I drank a lot of soda before
but
Like in recent years elastic five years
I haven't really been drinking it that much. I'm not an enemy. I might look like one
um
But the little tiny little cans
They're like a nice little treat like a nice little dessert. I don't drink a full soda anymore
Kind of a little it kind of sits in me like a nice little dessert
I'm not too much of a carbonated man myself
Everyone smile, you know, you never really go for one. He's lying
Germa's lying. Why would he goes hard?
You've seen the cans I drink out of on stream. I've been you've seen them like over the last month or two
I didn't think that thing was dead
I thought it was gonna blow up. I kind of did too and i'm gonna die if I don't
Feel oh, that's right. I did try that weird milk and
It's supposed to be milk and pepsi, but um
This should this thing is probably good for you
Is it good for you?
Golden order seal. I'll take it. It's into and faith
So I think this it's fundamental, uh incantations. Yeah, i'll take it. I don't want to equip it
They discard really should not be right next to leave. I feel like it should be like two
Rungs down on the menu ladder. I feel like they should make the word delete but you know, where's that dlc?
Where's that dlc? Hey, look I was one of those people that said man no dlc. What's going on here?
Look at this game
This game already feels like it has 10 pieces of dlc on it. That is true
Like I feel like this if you told me that this game that I have here was like four dlcs were on it
You that is you're murdering them
This is very good here
But I kind of can't see
I got my guy. I got my guy. You got your guy
I mean i'm working on it
What is normally down here?
I feel like that's normally down here. Am I crazy or is that actually down here? I don't remember
It's two random bug guys
Oh, it's yeah with the oh
You know what I mean the bug guys bug guys
They're like the shrimp bugs and they have the things that porcupine things that
Clean rotten nights the game crashed. No
I think I think you crashed it when you made that noise
They confirm the dlc by saying they're not done with the game
Yeah
But they can take as much time as they want like like look at this fucking game like this so
We're so spoiled rotten by how this base game was I said it before finishing the first playthrough
But
I mean this game the how long did your first playthrough take?
I know you may have like skipped some optional stuff
But it took me more than 100 hours to just do the just play through it normally. I was like 120
Yeah, every other from software game took me somewhere between like 40 to 60 hours. I put my invitation down
150 took me 200 hours 50 hours, but I was google gaming
That's an interesting way to say google game. Maybe you just kind of followed a kind of a guide or something
Google google gaming. I like that actually I should take this off
My load's a little too heavy
Maybe maybe by a little i'm a bit of a baby boy
Still medium, right?
It's heavy
Heavy heavy heavy heavy medium
I have lipstick
Now i'm pretty cool looking
Let's continue
All right, do I have a headache from that green screen car game?
from like a like a
Like five days ago
Hey, just because it was five days ago doesn't mean he watched it five days ago. Oh, that's right
Yeah, the game was out of control
Maybe he has had a headache for five days
That fucking car game. Oh, no, it was backwards. Uh, we need to go north through this tunnel, right?
Right mod chat mod helpers
No, this can't be backwards because we're gonna pick that up
That's gary. Yeah, we're this right way. That's gary's castle. Whoa, take this too. This is another one of my favorite moves
We're just getting all my favorite spells
I was gonna say a second ago every single time you like find an item
You're like, uh, you're either this is one of my favorite spells or uh, isn't it?
Oh, hey, wait guys
Isn't this one like one of the most strong ones in the game?
Like every weapon is the strongest weapon in the game pick this up this thing's actually this thing i'm telling you it's good
This is a joke item. It's not a joke item. I'm telling you right now. That is I promise you
That's the uh, like i'll find fun. Thank you. Finally. Well, finally this is one of my favorites in the game
I've just won it like an actual sword
Sorcery like for the whole game dare you mock me in front of all of my
viewers
They held me in such high regard before you opened your mouth
That was a kind of i've never heard you do that voice before i'm a bit of a psycho
Now here's the real question will the actual super ultra
Comet ability beyond this guy
When we go do it over here, probably not
Sorry, wait, does that weapon count?
As an ice like a moon magic that is moon magic
It does count
I um, I should give this to you. Do you have that? Do you have the hat?
What hat? No, I don't well then take it. He's stirring
You're essentially gonna be playing the character I was playing as when I played through the game
I'm gonna switch on I need to respect
Uh, let me get it this thing
Boosts um sorceries, right? Yeah, it does
Yeah, you're slowly turning into the character. I I did that ice glint stone and this uh moon sword essentially the entire game
I like hate this hat. Do you want to do more damage or do you want to complain about how it looks on you?
I think I might complain. I really hate it
But is it worth losing like how much percent like 10 15 more damage? I think it might be more than that
I look like a fucking rug you can catch it rains. You'd be fine
This is a good hat, how is that? Okay you
It's the same hat just it's different
It's the same but different. It's the same hat that they
That's in the same world of hats that would be sold at the same store
The other one was in the the fucking the profile the shape the actual shape
Like how tall and droopy and lame you can't even see your eyes are covered
You're an anime character. You don't actually need functionality this one. You got a mask. You have full clear vision
It's definitely blocking your head from the sun and it doesn't go excessively high
It's just just enough to cover your head same hat. Oh, yeah, but does that one?
Oh hell, wait, hold on. Would that one make you punch the punch machine?
15 harder and get an even higher score as it's you still don't want it
I don't need a higher score because I already had the highest score of everyone
What if somebody comes over and beats it? It ain't gonna be you you better shut your mouth. You don't know that
I wasn't even fucking looking at the game get them get them guys. I was just like I was just seeing what was going on over here
Okay, what do you what? I don't what do you want me to do? I had 25,000 ruins, too
Here's what I want you to do. I want you to just pick whatever you feel like playing with and let's play
I just want you to fucking die. Did you rest?
No
Why don't you just fall over you got killed by a snowman?
It really is a snowman
There's a magma worm in the lava. There's a big lava pool somewhere where the manor is, right?
I wonder what's over there this time
Oh lava and more lava
This guy's really fucking pissing me off right now
That's a fake dragon
That is a fake dragon
Okay
So we need to hug the left wall. So we gotta go this way. That's what I was told specifically by
me
As I figured it up a good job on figuring this out
You have no right to talk shit about people's hats when you're wearing a cereal bowl on your head
I like all these hats. I'm saying they're all cool
Yeah, I was the one saying I didn't like a hat
So what's over here because there's a boss over here. Oh, it's a boat nice
Uh, that's gonna be interesting. Yeah, he's got a fucking lava boat
Okay, how long can the horse be in here? Um, actually kind of a decent amount of time
Yeah, lava does very little damage in this game
Oh god, that's a lot of guys
smithing stone five
Can we like convince him to move over here or something?
He wasn't moving
Try and convince him as you might as you may just stand over here
It probably slowly row over here it comes
Like a wheelchair you can't we're trying to trick him
You can't row over here. This is land
Oh, what did you boys want me to do over?
What are you doing over here don't splash me don't splash me he's going back in the fucking lava
I was I was actually respecting the lava on the ground and trying to not walk into it again
Oh, really? Sorry. I was like, oh yeah lava on the brain
not
That's my gamer brain my sleepy gamer brain
uh
Alexander is over there usually right at this point in the game. Well, we didn't do any of his quest but
I don't know. What is this area? Never heard of it. Is this elden ring?
Would alexander still be here?
No, I don't I think we actually have to do is um
You see him before this
Um, I think that was the smithing stone. I need it
I'm going to eat one of these for the first time I think ever in the hundreds of hours. I've played this game
The roa. Yeah the fruit
Where is it?
I don't even know what it looks like. Okay. Here it is. Wait
What's the thing that you feed to the horse?
Roa berry
You have to craft it. Oh shit. Okay. Oh, yeah, you do have to like craft it from those berries
Make it oh
I was like actually so nervous to hear that loud sound
How do you feel about the crafting in this game?
Uh, I feel like it did not need to be in the game. I feel like it is
It I don't think it matters at all
And not I it's it's upgrade time for me
I believe it is for me, too
Let's get a bonfire and go upgrade time. It's a really interesting
Mechanic to put in and it's just it's just more shit to do
It's just more fun stuff to do but I I haven't I don't really use it
I don't really some of the pot stuff is cool
Oh craft this craft some of the the grease and stuff, right? But for the most part I left it completely alone
Um, I just really feel like they're only useful in the areas where it's like this enemy
Insta dies if you throw this type of pot at it. Yeah, it's a great talisman for here
Yeah early on I tried to do like a bow playthrough and I got a whole bunch of poison arrows
I spent like 20 000 souls
Like early in the game to get a bunch of poison arrows
And I used 80% of them to kill like one mini boss
So
That's how I feel
Rom software really has had sort of a weird relationship with bows in all their games, haven't they?
They seem to want to make them cool and make them work, but it always seems that they're just not quite good enough
They need to commit to like a mana system
Instead of actually having to be consumables because otherwise you could you could have anywhere between one and like 9 000 arrows to use
Where magic is like limited? It does work as a kind of a secondary though
If you if you're already doing decks
And oh i'm gonna do like a bow a short bow with my off hand or something it it you can use it
But not as like a main weapon to play through the game with and like i'm going to use this and this is the weapon i'm using
But it's weird they they put up like every game they put a little bit more development into what bows are like there's like
Uh radon has like a great bow that has like a special bow effects in it and they're all just super bad
The great bows were actually kind of good in this game just for like knocking things down
Ali you still make it work though if you really wanted to
They even added all the the animations and the weapon arts and stuff, right? Yep. So, I mean, it's cool
It's it's a cool thing
Oh my goodness
This guy is just flailing around
uh
Do we miss a grace?
I don't think so. I think it's if we just ran further
I think there is a boss usually on this road. The um, the giant putrid slob
Would be up here
That is actually a great name for a boss. I'm about to respawn everything
I'm about to save that for myriad
the great putrid
I don't know the giant the great putrid slob, you know the great what did I say the great putrid slob?
That's a great name demihuman queen urn tree the great putrid slob
And his crab friend
You up here. I leveled up
What you what I I literally went to go level I have 50 000 souls man if I I don't want to die here
You think i'm gonna I got 50 000 souls. Do you think i need an update on what you're doing?
Yeah, you think we're gonna take on the great putrid slob without me leveling up once
What if I die?
Look at all this bullshit here
Look at all this. This is a fucking mess
he
Oh my god, come on
Yeah, having fun fighting it alone
I I mean I got I got squished in between everything but
Did you leave?
I was fighting stuff up on the hill. I just wanted to just do the big explosion and get it on camera
I'm not sitting down
The great putrid slob
Also known as the dung eater use your pistol
What?
Weren't you just like super excited that you found like an m16 or something?
I
Swear
Why is he following me around this house?
The word slob is I that's actually one of my favorite words. I think in the dictionary
Uh, you fucking slob
It has so much meaning but it's like so much force behind it
If somebody calls you a slob
It's like hey, whoa, dude, what the fuck? Come on. Like what do you mean? I'm a slob
I don't know. I feel like someone calls you a slob. It's like hey, you got me there
To me, that's like there's something I got to figure out why you just called me that like something disgusting is around me
Something is gross
Like I am disgusting you somehow for you to use the term slob
Well, yeah, that's why you're the great grotesque slob like if you had like a dirty room or something
Somebody came in and said hey clean your room. You fucking slob. It's like
Ow
It's a power word. That's hey
Okay
Come talk come talk over here. Let's see what you get. What the fuck is this?
I swear I played a lot of this game
It won't talk. What talk?
Wait, you have to bring something here. I got an item. What'd you get? I got a stone sword key
Yeah, that's not what is this like a rock normally what the this is this is where you get comet azure that like
The kamehameha thing you wanted. Oh, this is where you get azure, but that's not what you got
Okay, maybe it's just because it's dressed like a fucking wizard that I don't remember it
That's what it looks like in the game in the regular game. Is it? Yeah, I don't believe you
That is what it looks like in the game. That is the character
I don't believe
That's fine. You'll see it. Um, we'll see it whenever you play through this game for some reason like right like right now
Well, it is a wizard. This is a wizard
If you ask nicely, okay, please go to the road of the manor and upgrade my weapon. Yes, no vote in progress
It just failed
It was an epic fail
I'm gonna throw you a curveball here. I catch it. You're out
I'm uh, i'm getting kind of hungry and I think I think i'm getting close to being wanting to probably end stream
um, i'm content with your
Words that you're saying i'm content
How do you how do you feel about um, oh no, I need sevens not sixes. God damn it
Let's do so let's do our upgrades. Hey guys, I think so seven I might let's go find out
Wait, did we go to them? No, he's behind us
I've played this game before too. I promise. Uh, what do you need?
Smithing stone seven and normal. I think i've asked you this like six times. Yeah
No, I don't you all right
So yeah, but you keep asking me this question
But I can't be like stupid and follow you and hit the same wall that you did
No, you can be stupid. All right, i'm about to be really powerful. Let's see. Oh man. I need I need some souls
This this really is like a randomizer experience
I have a smithing stone two three four five six seven eight and an ancient smithing stone
I just I I just don't have seven. I know I said that I had seven but you're not listening to me
Anyway, no, no, I I hear you
I it is a it is a randomizer experience and it is very strange and need to pay attention to lots of weird things going on
Okay, so we're done. Well, not yet. I want to upgrade this
Okay, so i'm done. I think we can separate
Worlds because I think we're separating we can separate worlds
We didn't even do our we didn't we didn't even do our stand next to each other unequip our swords and do a wave
Idiot, you're the idiot. You're the one that said that we're done idiot. All right
Is there's been a lot of fun? Yeah, the last couple days have been
Really really fun. Uh, look forward to more so we'll see you as next next weekend saturday sunday elden ring
Randomizers till we beat the game. I think we'll do it in the next two. I I think we'll do it this coming weekend
I think we're gonna beat it this coming weekend
I do I think if we actually just fought final bosses we could do it in like a day
I don't think we need to rush that that I I don't want to rush i'm saying like
It just depends how much side content we do because there's a million of it
Yeah, I think for the next stream I might also actually do the faith respect. We'll see. Yeah, we will see
But wait, we'll see i'm gonna have to sleep on it. I'm gonna have to really deeply consider take it easy stir
Good to see you again. Uh, it's been a lot of fun. Seriously. Talk to you soon, man. Yep. See you. Yep
Yeah, yeah. Uh-huh. Why am I getting in?
Wait, I didn't do this in my world
All right, okay, let me sell some stuff and we will go from there
Uh sell all right, I don't who cares about these rune arcs. We're not gonna get the ruins anyways, so who cares?
Oh, never gonna use these
I'm never gonna use this that thing is cool. What the hell am I never gonna use?
Never gonna use this. I'm just not going to just be honest. I'm probably never gonna use any of this stuff
I could sell everything here. Okay, here we go plus seven. This thing is very dangerous now. Awesome
B it goes to b it scales b and b faith and strength. I didn't know that so I should now because I have 40
I should be
I should be putting all my points into faith now
Because it'll scale double right? So that's gonna be cool. I didn't know that it did that. That's huge scaling on both
Yeah, but that's gonna be it. It's been a lot of fun. This is elden ring is i'm just glad to be playing it again
To be honest
Um, that's all there is to it, right?
I will see you guys the next time I see you i've got some stuff I need to do in the next few days
We'll probably do the same thing. We did this week, which is probably like a thursday
Thursday saturday sunday scenario. I think that worked out pretty well. That's what we'll do, but that's it. See you guys later
Take care of yourselves. Let me just exit here. Yeah, we'll do thursday saturday sunday
What we'll do on thursday?
That's a good question. We will figure that out over the next few days. Hope you had fun
Get some sleep. I know some of you was we were up late last night
And probably pretty late for some of you right now, too. Have a good rest of your weekend
Although there's not much left of it, but i'll see you later. I need to exit the game
There we go. It's 8 a.m. In your time zone
Wow
8 a.m
You're a whole world away. Yeah. Thanks to the subs. Thanks for watching call you mother relax and i'll see you again soon
See you thursday. Good night. Goodbye. Take care of yourselves