Hello everybody, welcome to my fancy boat party. I really appreciate everyone for co-
A party crasher.
Okay, that's- I think that's facing the wrong way.
It is.
Okay, but this road I'll be able to get.
Who shot? Who's shooting?
Is that a cop? Are you- are they cop- oh, okay.
I want them to come, because I want them to fly off this jump.
Oh, I missed it. I missed it.
God, this paramedic has no idea what he's doing. He's so confused. Oh, but that first guy.
I just saw him go straight up.
Please have another guy on a bike come down this road.
Grunt, grunt, grunt, grunt.
Let's try it at the same time. Ready? One, two, three.
Grunt, grunt, grunt.
Grunt, grunt, grunt. You're not doing it.
I just- I forgot how it started.
You don't know how the national anthem starts?
I thought I knew, but I didn't want to start wrong. You'd be like, you're doing it all wrong. Why are you messing this up?
Oh, you wouldn't be unlike most people that have to do it.
How many times have people screwed up the national anthem on, like, TV?
I might land- no. I thought I was gonna land in this boat.
Oh, I didn't even know you left. Where are you?
Look at what you did to me.
Oh, hold on. I know what I can do.
Yeah, let's just keep shooting at bikers until they do something.
Oh, there's a bike coming from behind.
Alright, so-
One of those guys is going.
Bingo, bingo. He's going.
No, I turned too much. No, no, no, no.
This doesn't concern you, other-
That didn't work.
Oh, that worked for nothing.
Oh, all that work.
Oh, down the drain.
The chase is on. There's another one.
Okay, you ready?
Hold on.
Oh, my.
It worked.
There's still coming.
Do it again. We gotta go on like this straight away right here too. Do it again.
Try to go faster, like a little bit faster. Try to get them so they have a lot of speed.
There we go.
This taxi.
Crazy taxi, man. What? They're just blowing up for no reason.
Oh, my God.
Look at how awkward of a place I'm standing.
Look at how awkward of a place I'm in, Sharma.
Oh, yeah? See you later.
Screw you.
You just gave me a place to stand.
Oh, he kept that going for a while.
I'm gonna land this. I'm gonna land this.
I look like I'm driving the bicycle and I'm just like, yeah, this is a good jump.
Yeah, this is a good jump.
Look at this jump right here. Yeah.
Oh, man. Did you see that jump?
Oh, look at that. Yeah.
Nice.
So have you boys ever been on top of the captain's quarters?
I'll tell you right now.
You're in for a treat.
It is just absolutely beautiful. I know.
Listen, the only select few get to come up here and bask in the beautiful glory that is this top deck.
So what the hell was that?
No, that was so stupid.
I could hear you crashing into Sharma.
I could hear you crashing into everything.
What are you doing?