Yeah, sorry, I'm a little late. But I was in pre-stream chat, and oh, did I get his turn stream off?
Nope. Okay, I gotta get in a better habit of doing this. So when I press turn stream on, go live,
right? It's a button you press on OBS. I press it, and then just move my hand off the mouse.
So it's like, go live, it's still hovering over it. And sometimes I'm talking with my hands right
now. Just, oh, hey, everybody, how you doing? Move my hands around. And if I press the space bar,
the stream will turn off. It's happened once or twice before. Oops. No, we're good. How you doing?
Hope your night's going well. Hope your day is going well. Hope your weekend has been okay.
That's been pretty good. We're going to try to finish the eternal cylinder tonight. I know
that there is potentially another three to five hours, depending on how many, you know,
sauce rants I go on tonight. I think we'll finish tonight. I think we'll get through it. Three to
five, about four to four and a half. We'll see. You should eat leaves on stream. Lettuce, I've done
that already. I already did that. Do you guys not remember? I don't know. Maybe you don't.
One time I just ate. When was that? That was like last year. I grabbed like as big a handful of
spinach or lettuce as I possibly could fit in my mouth and just didn't say anything. I did that.
I've done that like probably three times. I've done that. I've done that joke like three times.
At this point, is it even a joke or is it? I don't know. Not really. I do have tea and I do
appreciate the people telling me to take the tea bags out because I only got another minute before
I need to take them out. Different tea today. This is a peach tea. Oh, hold on. I think it's
got hibiscus in it. Is that good for you? Hibiscus, rose. I think there's rose in this. Is that good?
Do you put anything in your tea? No. I drink my tea with zero sugar, zero honey. I'm one of those
weirdos. Try peppermint tea. I actually really like peppermint tea, but it makes me go to the bathroom.
So not a great stream tea, I will say. You know, I don't want to drink a big peppermint tea
because in 30, 40 minutes I'll be like, ah, see you later. I'll be back.
It was during the later alligator stream. I feel like I did it during a multiverse. No, that was
carrots. I don't remember. But anyways, are you guys ready? Let's not waste any time.
I'm going to get right to it. I feel like during a multiverse stream, I did it.
Carrots and lettuce. Why do you delete tweets after the stream? Well, because,
so here's the problem is I don't really use Twitter that often. I don't know. I only use it to
tweet out streams. My Twitter would just be links to the stream. If you went to my timeline, it would
just be a thousand links to my stream. It'd be awful. And also too, when the stream is over,
I don't want to have, since somebody's timeline be, oh, he's live. Cool. I'm going to join. And
I'm just not. So it's just temporary. Stop talking. I want to see Gunu. I do too. Yeah,
shut this guy up. Let's go. Where did we leave off? I don't remember. Oh, that's right. We got to
this new world. We got to the new area. We're in part three. What was the last thing we had to do?
There you go. Somewhere out there waited an elder who did not know of his sibling's fate.
And the Trebum felt the weight of the bad news. Okay. So he's going to go to the temple. I,
one thing about this game I really do appreciate is this thing. The, hey, here are the two points
of intro. Oh, I, okay. We have to go over there. Don't care. Switch to Gunu. Gunu? Where's Gunu?
Yeah. Yes. Yeah. Yeah. Yes. Yes. Clap. Okay. So I have to go this way, but let me go over here
first. You just sounded like a dog. Wait, we need to eat. Who's got food? You do? No, you do.
Who needs food? Don't just throw the stakes away. What are you crazy? Stop that. We need those. How
did I only get one? Who's taking all the stakes? You. Can we get a recap? Um, okay. We're kind of
at the, we're near the, I think, the final arc of the game. So give me a second. All right.
There are these creatures and they are called Trevums. And that's what we have here. They are
little magical creatures that can, you know, just go watch the intro cinematic on YouTube.
It's probably two minutes. It's going to take me eight minutes of just stumbling around,
slowly talking to explain it. You know what I mean? In the, in the amount of time of me going.
So it's these creatures that during the journey you, you could have already watched the opening
cinematic. That's a cop out. That's fine. Here. How about this? Run away from the giant rolling pin
that is crushing all civilization. There you go. I think that's accurate. Oh, this is a, this is a
cloud. I think we're good. Yeah. I don't think we need to do anything here. I have a lot of
crystals. I got to use them. The real question is, all right, it's under there. That's a new enemy.
What was that? What just happened? Who's the DPS? All right. The okay. Uh, the DPS is
this guy right here. He has a stomp. Can I not do it? Sorry. This guy has a stomp. This guy also can,
uh, can take, um, bombs from this one. So this is like a damage support and I'm the one that
actually shoots the bombs. I think that's the only DPS I have and it's not even DPS. It's just
anybody can be anything. For instance, check this out. I missed everybody run. I would have
gotten booted from red right there. All right. We have to go down because this thing's going to
shoot us. Sick gameplay. It went right through his legs. That's not my fault. Can we make it?
I wonder if I can just make it. What's going on? Did I make it? This is bad. Oh, get up here. Get
up here. Some of you get up here before he breathes poison on us. All right. Go, go. What are you
doing? Ooh, I like that. Okay. Well, don't touch it. Don't touch it. What are you doing?
Why are they standing on it? Did anyone else hear from Australia? Why is Derma playing with
outback animals? You know, I thought, Oh my God, my T, why didn't anybody tell me it's been sitting
for like 15 minutes? Shit. Oh, hold on. Oh, I told you guys to tell me it was one minute.
The tannin is going to be bad. We'll find out. How long has the stream been on for? 13 minutes.
Shit. It means it's been there for at least 15. God damn it. Whatever. I think it's all right.
Oh, tastes pretty good. I think we're dying in here. What an inhospitable place this was.
The air was suffocating and the heat was almost unbearable. Oh shit. The trebum would have to
make good use of their abilities to overcome the obstacles before them. Okay. Um, but who would
choose to actually live here? All right. We actually have to move now. Terrible things.
They must have endured in the outside world. No, this is not fireproof. I don't think this is
fireproof. Is there anything fireproof in here? Is this water hot? This is hot. Everybody get in
the water. I can't tell. I think I just have to go fast. Do I have any? Hold on. Really important.
Do I actually have any healing? I don't have zero healing and there's nothing I can do about this.
Oh shit. Hold on. Somebody don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't
We're fine. Is this it? Fire resistant bark? Okay. Um, we're gonna eat this right now.
Uh, Gino's gonna eat this. Who's gonna eat this? I wonder if only one can eat it. I'm gonna give it
to Vu. Where's Vu? Vu, where are you? Vu, where are you? Oh, did it work? Did it work? It worked.
Oh thank god. Okay. I got fire resist. Now I also have a permanent mutation I can do. Thank goodness.
Where is it? Where was it? It was the thing with the tongue. It looked like the tongue. What the
heck is it? Where is it? Oh there it is. Okay I need three crystals and I can get this permanently.
So who has it? Didn't I keep three? I'll get it eventually. Okay. Oh I do have it. Why is it
showing up as I don't? Huh? That's weird. Somebody in the oh it's probably somebody in the in the
cloud. All right. We're safe. We're good. Everybody eat up. Very cool. I'm very happy about this.
I would say that's pretty sick. Oh I actually have a cool announcement to make. Um, pretty pretty
cool stuff. Those of you that were big fans of the Elden Ring streams with, uh, Stir and I.
This coming weekend we're gonna do it again. More mods. More mayhem. At least for one more day.
So that should be fun. I don't want to take too much of this shit because it is. It is shit. Let's
be honest. All right. There's an elder down here somewhere. Let me pay attention for a second.
Crystals. Where's my crystal eater? They all look really cool. They have scales now. He really wanted
to announce that on his stream but I mean I'm just gonna. He was like I have a huge thing planned.
I'm gonna do a huge announcement for it and I'm like oh cool cool cool and then I'm just doing it.
Oh did I miss a way to go up? Terrible friend. I'm I'm just kidding. Whoa hold on. Ooh this kind
of hurts my eyes. Does this burn if I touch it? Is it? Oh won't lose anybody Andy. Well it said
that fireproof skin. I'm like okay so what does that mean? The hypothesis. Come on.
To make good use of their abilities to overcome the obstacles before them.
All right where's the voodoo? But who would choose to actually live here? Terrible things
they must have endured. Resistance not proof. Yeah but I don't know how. Resist high. I don't know
what the game was trying to do. Who knows? Some games it's like yeah you're immune to fire damage
or you take like 100% less fire. Whatever 90% less fire damage. Yeah at what point does fire
resist become fire immunity? If I wear 500 fire resistant t-shirts can I go into the lava? At what
point is it immunity? If I get into a fire resistant space suit can I and it's airtight
can I can I dunk into lava? Anyways who made the first sauce? Anybody know? Okay let's try this
again. I'm not saying I'm gonna dunk it. I'm talking about video game logic. I actually need
three of these right now. So this is permanent mutation for um the fire trunk. Should I just put it on
everybody? Why not? Well maybe not. I don't need it right now. All right we're gonna have to get
these off the wall. Hold on. Where's my uh p-expert? Is this the p-expert? Is this the p-expert? No it's
not. Who is the who is the p-expert? I know I have one. Did I did I get removed? It might have gotten
removed. I really fucking want those. I'm such like a crystal fiend. I need it. Watch out. Ah whatever.
Can't get them all. I want those extra ones. Whatever. Just move on. I know but I want them.
Wait a minute nobody go near this. Don't I did you hear what I just said? Why would you? Well you
can't hear me but why did you do that? What's going on? Okay um what's get out of the get out
of the light get out of the light get out of the light. This is new. Uh you lost a power. Shit it's
okay. You take this thing. I don't know what this is but go for it. Perceptive eyes to see light
frequencies that otherwise cannot be perceived which may reveal important secrets. All right
here's what I'm thinking glow in the dark glow in the dark eyes jump legs horn snout. Now that's
gonna be pretty cool looking. Okay perceptive eyes. I don't know what that's supposed to mean.
Open this somehow with our perceptive eyes. Can we move this? Oh I'm gonna take another one.
I'm probably gonna need it later. Okay what is that? I don't understand what that's trying to
tell me. Like don't touch that. How do I get through here? Can I break this? I can't go
through here. Okay I'm just gonna I'm gonna go try not to touch it. Whoa wait a minute. What is
what is this? What did I do? I guess I turned it off because I went close to it. I can't.
Stop. Oh my god. Where's my oh my god. What a fucking disaster. I don't know what it wants
me to do. Okay I went close to it so it stops but who gives a shit. How do I I just don't get it.
I don't know what it's even asking me to do. I'm going back. You can pass but who cares. I
could pass before. Just I don't I don't understand what the game like wants me to
do with this information. What an inhospitable place this was. The air was suffocating and the
heat was almost unbearable. The trebum would have to make good use of their abilities to overcome
the obstacles. Like was the only point to get in here and just get the eyes and then leave? Who
would choose to actually live here? Terrible things they must have endured in the outside world.
Dead run. I think that's my least I think that's the part of the game that I don't like the most
is like the hey the light takes away all your powers haha don't give me powers to take them away
that's that's nobody likes that don't give me powers that are cool just to take them from me
not cool haha okay let's try this again uh wait first of all I need these crystals gonna reset
here got that okay were there any weren't the crystals hanging out over here so I can go
over here don't go in the lava let's try this bullshit again I cannot save in a cave it's only
at the beginning of the cave this again okay good mm-hmm so let's rethink this whole process
again I wish I could just tell them to all stay like I can I could just investigate with somebody
so the story here is I have to go across this I have to go in here and scare it okay then everybody
goes everybody go they lag behind okay everybody come on all right here we are I get this new
mutation which is just perceptive eyes I give it to you so where should I go do I have to go
into the lava now and jump around I wonder what game progress is here what do I just leave this
was a pretty major temple wasn't it there's definitely something else to do here okay I'm
stuck on the fucking wall okay everybody's happy everybody got out crying I'm leaving I I want
them so bad but I don't care okay so what's out here let me get a few more of these press B oh
footprints are these there he is we're in this okay I can I can burn that whoa oh I can burn all
those all right there are more of those aren't there can you give each one of these a different
voice yeah my name is we want my name is good my name is boo I'm good I'm Gino global is my name
global what well you gave you gave global the protagonist voice so so is that the protagonist
same two voices gave me a break all right wait why is this closed oh there's another one hey you
guys cannot minus two me you guys cannot make fun of me for that some of your guys favorite thing
in the world is the starting the character select screen from diddy kong racing please hey it's
tip-top please give me a break you all love that shit man's crunch ah I'm not gonna hear that today
who is the eyes you do this way burn this you bring back up that's probably like it's probably
I knew it and I said it out loud before it happened who cares
all right cool oh shit wait don't go in here yet what did you just eat no weird shit in here right
what is that do I need a cube there are no cubes to eat I thought I saved one I didn't save a cube
how come they're all gone this is gonna be a hell all right um good luck but I can't control the
other ones the other ones are just gonna walk into the fire there's no cube here usually there's this
one in the wall okay I can burn that but I'm afraid that someone's just gonna walk in the fire
you know I'm gonna walk down there with the person to do the ignite and two people are gonna die in
lava just reload if they burn that's 23 minutes ago if somebody dies they kind of have to just die
I can't tell them to stay here okay do not follow me do not follow me don't follow me oh my god this
hurts what is this gonna do oh cool okay very cool seeing gunu's theme okay oh there's a cube
over there nobody follow me this is dangerous but I I think I have to I have to go that way
don't follow me I just walked in the lava Jesus don't follow me oh aha all right cool who wants
to be a cube um you could be a cube I think you could be the cube what did you do what did you do
okay uh I need the eyes I guess not you literally did it I don't know what I did what did I do
weren't there a couple of those things in the other room maybe they're not maybe can I stand
on them though yeah these are open now huh all right oh shit did that do something oh fuck you
oh fuck you leave me alone do I have to stand on these god damn it I don't have a thing anymore
puzzle time this is an annoying room okay um do I actually have to stand on this though
stomp it hold on I don't want to lose everybody's powers smoke mutation um I don't think anybody has
that right now no no I think it got removed I don't think anybody has it just go to the door
see what you're saying like I don't need to touch these it made a sound when I did that though
okay there's nothing here um who had that power before you stand on the other button I hate that
mechanic I hate the delete the power button you spend so much time trying to get your guys good
to go and then this is just a thing in the game that just removes it that's annoying I hate it
okay I stepped on them both okay could you please stop doing that oh my god I didn't even do
anything I mean they just what else am I supposed to do it didn't go all the way down you gotta be
fucking kidding me so you just we just all have to lose our powers now lame lame lame that's lame
that's lame stop taking stuff from me that's lame now half of you now now I don't even know
who the fuck had what and now I don't know what's missing from them lame just over there I get the
whole this permanent upgrades now but I don't know I kind of it's hard to keep track of who has what
and if I know you're like the dinosaur one that has the don't get up here get up here I heard him
splash I just heard a splash okay he's alive like I know you as the dinosaur with the long spit
right if it I don't know it gets it gets confusing because now I don't know who had what and now I
don't know what I'm missing the elder saw sadness in the trebum's eyes and gave them words of do
not mourn for me and my brother I wish only that my end had been like his for when we act in the
service of others we become greater than ourselves without losing who we are I was afraid and stayed
behind and I am lesser for it but I can feel the tremors in this cave and I know soon my brother
this does not look like me I've seen like 10 of you say that let me help you while I can you are
here to learn about the great lenders that power a trebum palace wander in the desert looking for
the brightest glare you can find follow the glare until you find a great structure made of glass
you may have encountered one already but to activate them you will need a special mutation
the key to this mutation is held by the great gar gar three lenses is all you need and there
are many left follow the glares find the gar and you will succeed it is a task fit for the great
heroes of old but who says that ordinary little trebum can't be heroes we're junior heroes
uh I want that so bad but somebody's gonna die you know it somebody jumped off who just jumped
off look at all that down there please don't do that I'm not telling him to do that there's a
chest there's a button uh oh what if I lose somebody it's gonna be so he's stupid that was
just he's dead and now he's not coming back I'm sorry guys that's how it works I didn't do
anything he was really dumb and then we're just sorry but you I don't know what you were thinking
you just walked off the edge and that is exactly what I was afraid of so um they just walk off
sometimes and you're gone so before that happens again I'm going to get out of here what's the
safest way to get out of here so nobody falls off the edge I can't save the game the game
cannot be saved indoors do I have to like jump out of here how do I get the fuck out of here
without anybody dying please have nobody fallen we lost uh we lost I liked gua too that's sad
okay there's nothing that can be done I'm not no we're not reloading do you see I'm not going
back 36 minutes where is dead I'm sorry everybody but it's just the way it is dude you sorry you
talked about sauce for 36 minutes I didn't stop I hate that feature of this game it's maddening
it's infuriating to me okay so let's get out of here this was the way up to the elder so we're
gonna go back this way I'm sorry gua we can revive them though I have 25 crystals or something I have
a lot I get out of here this way is it this way how do I get the hell out of here do I still have
the fire move or did that get deleted in the in the fun light did it get removed it got deleted
in the fun light um hold on nobody just fell in right did not tempt me to go this way well if
nobody follows me I think I can do this as long as nobody follows I don't think they're following
the way I had all the crystals on them no okay all right dungeon sucks and balls it's not my
favorite I will say but I gotta go all the way because there's a there's a chest at the end
of this and a bunch of crystals I want it I like this part this particle I don't mind this part
because I get a cool reward look at all these crunchies why am I dying I am dying can I even
make this jump oh no too far away nice what's in this chest it better be good uh-huh yeah it's
worth it I gotta do some consolidation I have a lot of these powers I just don't I don't know what
to do with them all I'm afraid to get rid of anything because the permanent upgrade system
you need to have it in your inventory so I kind of just kind of stuck in a position where everybody
has a full inventory of power-ups that I probably need eventually to upgrade in the permanent tree
I wish there was a chest or something hmm I think that's it get the big guy upgrade and store him
in the cloud I probably would want to do two I think I'm gonna do two or three big upgrades
and then just store them it's probably the play there's a gem right there oh man it's sticking
out of here all right cool let's go back what is that over there do you see that thing what is
that what's that mean what is that why is that there what is that what is this what is that
what is that what is this all right I have 30 crystals we need an upgrade center right now bad
do the eyes nothing here I think we're good this is the exit that's where I want to go you need
to look with your special eyes okay unfortunately we lost someone sad we did that's the nature of
the tre bombs we have to continue our mission I can pull somebody out which I'm going to because
that's probably the only opportunity I'm gonna have for a little bit let's go pull somebody out
actually there's some crystals I want here here you I'm gonna have like 35 crystals what was his
name the person that died um where that was an easy one it's just go ahead come on go ahead come
on where I'll pull somebody out I could revive go ahead but I feel like there's already people here
no I'll pull a glare I can pull groutemo out we'll pull groutemo out all right it's movement time
let's eat and we're moving wait this is the first move in the whole time we've been live tonight
are you guys ready okay here we go uh always grapple grapple where you are I need yeah grapple
who has water one of you has it I know you do nobody has water okay all right let's go
oh I'm such a piece of shit I'm such a piece of shit and I don't even care uh I do need to eat
you've got the food no who has it no stop don't it's gonna do it again just everything is so
fucking dangerous get on a rock or something Jesus Christ come over here go stand over here
I want the person with the food no no no no stop I want this stop it okay Jesus some weird
shit over there what the hell is going on uh who can swim I know one of you can who can I know
groutemo can can't groutemo can swim right no none of them have well the web
global this is not fast enough not fast enough oh crap bye I'll walk around the water it didn't
look like there was a safe place to do it but we've eaten okay um let's go I think that cube is
moving what are you doing get out of the fucking water all right we're good I think that the thing
I'm supposed to find is right here yeah there it is gah who's going to communicate with it first
oh not this I gotta okay this is gonna be incredibly dangerous it's gonna have to be who
somebody has bombs right I gotta make some bombs okay we wewam needs to make some bombs
wewam we gotta make bombs over here you have to shoot it off with the water but I need to be
prepared save the game I think I think it autosaved when I got through the uh the gate
three bombs enough or should it be more probably more is everybody on health I think everything's
fine right yeah okay good luck everybody if somebody dies then I'll just reload
true and based okay here we go oh what's wrong are you okay what just what the fuck did you just get
so scared that he turned into a different animal wait what the hell just happened what did he just
do these crystals are worth a way to um no I think I uh oh at least you can take these and make them
into I ate yeah shit I don't know what this does either all right young uh eat that god I wish I
had a storage or something we should who has space in their fucking inventory um you I everybody has
a full inventory spit a thin thread of toxic liquid dude I god damn it this is stupid I'm
getting out of here okay I got it off you have the mixer mutation thing I do that's true you
don't drop anything right I have so many of these um I'm gonna give it to I'm gonna give it to you
give it a voo filter where is it mixer body okay it's just you know what just get rid of
it all we need water so bad please leave us alone leap leave us alone leave us alone you
weirdo stop leap why are we dying okay very cool I thought aren't we heat resistant this
shouldn't be hurting us I still have a fire trunk I do give Gunna some abilities I need to get to
temple so I can take some inventory or what the hell I even have I wonder if this does anything
is this just a ignite them and run around and kill stuff or will this blow up this um dome I don't
know what the end game on this is you weren't even close he wasn't even close he wasn't even
close to the explosion he wasn't even close what what excuse huh it wasn't even close
oh it's I can oh this is so bad eight it's eight now it's free
no it's actually free okay um time to go there's a hole over here heavy poo sorry to have a poo
not yet well let me get to 40 crystals real quick yeah look at all this I need my um I need my gem
person somebody else take these I don't want them all right let's do it crystals crystals crystals
crystals all right now we wait how come this how is the no dance button that's kind of unfortunate
I think how come I can't press like up on the d-pad and have them wiggle wiggle wiggle that's a major
major um misstep there yeah I get every crystal I know people probably sitting there going like dude
you don't yes you do important for me to get them all look at all this I'm gonna have like 50 crystals
I need a temple so bad oh my goodness okay he's penny pinching no I'm collecting money
why's there scary music all right there's some interesting shit in here all right well this
well this cooks in here um who's got an empty inventory does anybody have an empty inventory
any of you woogwool get over here what are you doing up here woogwool is really cute I like
okay this full heal or half heal and this is all right uh I need you suck up yeah we're just gonna
chill here for a minute there's too many of these I guess I could pick them up with some other people
but everybody has a full inventory we need to spend 10 to 20 minutes just getting rid of all
these items just storing somebody with like the big um the big thing it's like there I like there's
so many items that they need to hold on to but there's no way to reliably hold on to them the
game has this feature where hold on to items and permanent do permanent stuff but fill your whole
fucking inventory permanently you're being greedy I don't think I mean if I okay if I go to one of
these elders and they're like oh all right here's the recipe for the long tail and like I don't have
this and like I have to go find this again I have it right now I've got to go find another long tail
what if I don't find one okay hold on almost done you are fomo-ing yourself
only a few more crystals and then we can leave 50 crystals this is ridiculous all right so let me
see I need oh my god I didn't know I need I had three of those already fuck I had one of those
I don't know man I kind of don't even care about any of this uh okay I needed four of those and
four bug things I think I can get those now pretty sure I have those don't I
two bugs I need uh I need four of these those some of these are outside and then water kind
of cactus things okay Gunu where are you let's go I have somebody that has do I still have somebody
that has the eyes oh hold on I can't control anybody I have to leave this cave okay where's
the person that has the eyes oh for the love fucking god please okay hi maybe I can't can't
use it are they different eyes are those the monster ones where you look at the wrong eyes
don't you have it though do I have to be selecting the person that currently has it
oh okay okay I need like six of these I'd run away okay what does it take to make that I need
four bugs that's up there all right I need to look for the bugs now mm-hmm need two of these
don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't all right this game like one okay
I have a complaint I have a complaint time to complain this game wants you to like explore
and like pick up items but also kill you at every fucking turn if the game wants you to it's like
two it's like an oxymoron the game like oh go searching for these items and watch out die
everything kills you where is it risk and reward but I get I get it but it doesn't mean it's not
frustrating all the time and why am I stuck okay so I have that permanent upgrade that is it's not
like Elden Ring and Elden Ring I can dodge around that guy and kill him very easily I have offense
in Elden Ring your trebum's just fucking get rolled over and die I can spit these little
bombs and shit but it doesn't fucking do anything no more complaining uh this is pretty useful
we'll give it to Gunnu all right I've gotten some good shit are there any other upgrades that I can
get here just so I can clean it clean up my inventory I do there's a cheese one I'm gonna
let's do this now let's just get let's get through this I don't think I can find those here
I can get oh my goodness okay well I'm gonna uh I had I just didn't know I had this already
I'll keep this one tracked I need two more of these stupid crystals all right let's go that
there were some in that hole hmm I need to upgrade so bad let's do that first I've got
so many of these are you still enjoying it I am but I'm starting to see through the cracks a
little I definitely want to finish it because I think it's a really interesting fun game
but I am definitely I'm definitely sniffing out the cracks here no I'm I'm you know what I mean I
I'm I'm just let let me cook right come on guys let me cook I know I don't hate it I don't
I just look at how many I could upgrade a million fucking times okay absolutely doing stamina will
that's completely good but probably food and leadership uh-huh leadership twice let's go crazy
and then we'll do food we're sure to maybe help food probably okay I'm gonna save the rest
leadership and water I actually probably should have done water you're right shit teach me something
the projection from the pool shared its wisdom with the trebum and showed them how to protect it
from the evil light of their enemies okay uh I did get another one of these which this was
somebody already has this what was this oh what was this this was something weird right
all right crystal time are there any big crystals because that would be pretty big because I could
upgrade get that one come on no big crystals unfortunate all right well thankfully now I've
got I can we have 10 trebles now I'm good um I should eat is there any food in here
who cares I just got out of here all right guys let's go that was scary no no no don't I have to
move I didn't I don't I just want to hang out with my little trebum friends I don't want to just get
eaten immediately when I leave where's the next point over there oh shit you need to go to the
cave I need to eat that's more important nobody attack me I'll be very upset um I want the one
that can run fast I'm gonna it's gonna isn't it yeah well we go now this is kind of shit egg
there's an egg how am I supposed to get this egg how would you get this I I don't huh how would
you get this egg I think I'm just dead yeah this is how are you supposed to get this I don't
think you can I don't think that I don't think there's enough time there's an incubator right
there yeah but the thing was already on me I don't think it's possible maybe if I go from this
direction I still have to go down into the kind of little um like give it though let me try this
you know just do a straight shot from here what the fuck this is not possible hey Gili we saved
Gili instantly dead you just woke up and you you you get you probably can't even process colors
correctly and you're dead oh that's so sad okay it's a bond camp oh all right well we need to
eat again you know what it's time it's time to abandon all of these materials it's time for them
to go I have to I can't I can't just hoard them forever I have to get rid of them you can do it
do you think so all right I trust you guys I have a different idea oh you're such an asshole for
putting this here you're an asshole for putting this here you are a dick for putting that here
I can't believe you put it here what an asshole I can't believe you put that there you bastard
are we good did everybody make it okay we have a new friend and this needs a source of heat
it looked like that it was incubating in here am I crazy or this hot egg great gar was neither
a predator nor an immediate threat tire trunk however obtaining whatever secret ingredient
it kept in its air sack would be no easy task for one thing something in their memories told
them that the sack was filled with poisonous gas oh no how does one enter the body of a creature
that can even devour sand storms whoa all right feed this guy a bunch of weird shit
feed this guy cheese feed him a spiky hair and whatever this is all right here you go nice
nice oh it's it's skin oops nice okay so uh we need to put on the poison gas thing
everybody needs this everybody if you could please put it on thank you very much
does everybody have it
that's what I go that's what I imagine he's doing what what that was not what even the
mod the mods are telling me to stop okay I'm stopping I'm stopping I'm not doing it again
what what like that was so weird what how well who's this who's this this is a new friend who
is this person on our team do I not even know who this is hey ah shoot it shoot it shoot it
shoot it watch out watch out watch out watch out I need a bomb everybody get out of the way get
out of the way just run away just run away just run away I don't want anything to do with this
just get out just run get away from that thing what the hell this game got so much scarier
it's still following us yet what trebum were far from delicate get away from us the stench
of these plants was too much even for them they would have to clean them and thoroughly oh okay
let me let me clean this shit well this tarantula is following us oh my god everyone's just gonna
die now I does anybody have a bomb or something I don't think the fire will hurt ground pound
maybe I need to select whoever has who has that shit who has the ground pound is it not we want
get the fuck away from us get out of here god okay all right all right I you are too bright I
all right we need to clean that what are you doing we have to clean this and I'm imagining
maybe this makes it so I can be resistant to it okay clean it how do you clean it water
oh no what just happened to it oh it got turned into some bullshit all right hold on
I'm getting sick of this okay I give me the people are just dying how are you still alive
bro run the tremor need to clean the material that they find oh my god everyone dies
I'll clean over here and pick this up explore while you look out
there's something behind you poor tremor oh don't touch that it's it's icky look out behind you
explore though what the fuck get me out of here like seriously I okay well I need I need to clean
one okay clean this one I need one of you pick it up and just get it over just spray it all right
nice and clean now eat it oh my goodness is that is it does that smell me is this gonna hurt
okay okay oh are we dead here are we all gonna please don't die um okay eat this okay so that's
cool now we can explore can we do that before it was a different one okay well I guess I can poison
this now everybody all right okay very cool very cool let's get the heck out of here before
something bad happens where are we going I need water need water where is there water come on
fuck fuck no uh the new ability has water if I eat this I mean oh my goodness it does all right
I I'm gonna I want to save like at least five of these thank god he sucked up all this I almost
called it crap we're okay now the main goal here is what exactly that looks dangerous I don't want
to touch it don't touch it don't touch it you're gonna get killed it's gonna like snap all right
I'm gonna try to go back up hopefully I'm not screwed down here look at this nonsense I don't
want to go down that I'm going back up can I get back up please thank god okay there's a big
shining light over here check this out if you see some kind of oasis of water definitely scream
well you don't have to anymore because I think is this water all right now we got to turn this on
wow we did it excitement rushed through the trebum as the massive lens came to life and started
rising into the air they had to get off quickly as staying on top of the majestic construct as it
rose would be quite dangerous the trebum marveled at the miracle their ancestors had wrought
was that supposed to kill the incredible things had they built that were now okay everyone's
all right question for another day for now the trebum had two more lenses to find two more lenses
huh okay all right I'm invested again where's my fast runner there you are who knew you look so
different huh interesting can we get up there we need water yeah but look this what is that
I want whatever's on there use the tornado ability maybe I can
on the flower why would you tell me to do that whoa what kind of contraption is this shit
why is it done what get one oh come on oh no move out of the way you dopes yes all right
everybody get out of what is your problem what is that guy's problem it's just food it ain't even
cool all right let's move shaking my head all right let's go okay there it is let's cross
I want we have to fill up before we get out of here why is that thing keep doing that
oh it's because I smell okay right you're stinky ah interesting bridge um I mean that looks kind of
cool look at that there's a whole thing down here too dangerous this made it been a mistake
I can't tell if he hates this game or not I don't hate it we're just kind of at the last
arc of the game and it's gotten a lot more difficult I would say well difficult is the
wrong word it's a lot more uh like particular of like things I need and things I don't need
I actually the world is a 10 out of 10 the creatures the audio the graph everything is
beautiful everything is wonderfully crafted I like the story it's I think it's cool so far
I would say the gameplay loop is the only thing that's a little lacking for me
but I still think it's fun
okay uh I can't go too far is there an egg there's an incubator right here I don't see an egg
shit egg no it's on top probably but whatever uh I don't want to run too fast if you've missed
the last couple of streams I know it's probably very loud but I can't go too far or I'll get
struck by the purple lightning I have to stay in between the purple lightning and the roller
goals over there yeah slow down uh who has food nobody have food all right gonna start moving
here in a second in just a second don't go too far all right eat you doing okay yeah I'm good
I'm just chilling it's kind of a long way to go still
I have to read this he said dude this happened to my buddy Eric once do not kill this shit
that's so dumb get the fuck out of here I can't even laugh at that comment is everybody oh
dude this happened to my buddy Eric once and now people are gonna die and I know where I can go
people just die oh fuck that that fuck that I don't I really don't want it it's not bad but
dude this happened to my buddy Eric once this is a good time to pee and get a drink
probably please leave us alone oh my god what is all this shit everywhere what is this
just everybody I'm all right just go I can't go far I need I mean obviously using the weaponry
is just completely unreliable I'm gonna shoot this bomb it's gonna miss go under their legs
and it's gonna kill everybody do I have this I don't have it is there is that item somewhere
wait hold on where's the eyes that item might just be right here oh god damn it which one of you even
has this power does anybody even have this power anymore or did it get removed from me
I don't know nobody has it the orange one does no that's the other eyes no I think it's gone
we won't had it before he died that's sad he's getting the food get the fuck we won't why
poor we won't gonna be cool watching you die wait you're you're not like an act are you
I'm just making sure I'm just making sure I didn't know if it was every single one of them was like
that that guy scares me a little where are you going don't roll over there that's like so
all right that just looks that looks fucking weird it's not funny it's just bizarre it's a
strange looking I'm I'm not laughing at that I'm laughing at the absurdity of how I feel I honestly
feel like he could have got away from that is just what I'm saying I feel like he kind of could have
got away if he just went this way you didn't have to you're fucked up he was kind of just like yeah
fuck it whatever he's very slow yeah yeah yeah that's true I think it's just they were both
moving so slow that I forget that we can move so fast what a peculiar sight the voice and their
memories whispered the servants of the cylinder were gathering in numbers to hunt and trap the
trebum now was the time to seek safety and wait for the hunters to desist huh
what I mean I need food don't oh my god oh my god dude I need to eat food bro listen to the game
while the narrator was talking to me I didn't even know what the game was telling me and the
guy is just upon us shining this dumbass light on us I leave why is why am I dying oh fuck you
fuck you it took the are we all who's dying it took the power away it it took the heat resistant
power away and I'm very upset about it does anybody have that is anybody holding it acid spit no
you do okay who eat this uh who needs it if one person needs it then we're good right
I'm pretty positive about that thank god there's a hole over here please get up hell yeah okay
goog or whoever's in here well this one's free vogue roux oh you're cool looking hello vogue
roux welcome to the team vogue roux cool pattern um I need to go back to eating shit all right let
me get in the right spot I think I have a full party now right all right people are missing a
lot of stuff I could go and do the permanent mutation or I could eat some stuff I'm I feel
like I'm gonna be getting to a new area or a new kind of part I'm kind of afraid to eat very much
right now I can get one more dude all right let's get in the right spot and go oh the whole right
shit oh fuck whatever I need to eat yeah I think I can make it it's not this one's not that far
okay very dusty what how what what did you do what what happened why I don't okay I'm not
resetting for that I'm sorry that's the way it is I'm sorry guys we can't rescue everybody
the game is hell bent on making sure that people just die and save everybody oh there's another
one of those I wish you would just leave us the fuck alone all right we have a new we have two
new friends right here the voice and their memories warned the trebum that there was a
sinister presence in this place there was no telling what kind of danger lay under the dunes
of this desert oh what's this stuff oh treasures should I break these or should I turn them into
crystals what do you guys think oh go to gog wo mu all right gog wo mu welcome to the family
gog wo mu is room for one more it's the turtle mutation I don't think I need that somebody needs
to be a refinery woval could you be a refinery please we'd appreciate it shit um I also don't
have the thing to spin this because it was taken away from me this is it right here isn't it which
one of these I kept I held on to them it's the one on woog will right oh look at this look at
this one why do you have these eyes I think I think this one ate one just something just
just to eat something let's go there's school looking here we go nobody in this oh the trebum
were terrified of the monstrosity watch out this is gonna kill everybody game over this was a
powerful servant of the cylinder okay sent to prevent them from completing their quest
yeah no matter how small and frightened they were what do we do about this had to find a way
of fighting it okay um you shoot shoot shit at it shoot run over its fingers I'm gonna run its
fingers over I don't think there's any avoiding somebody dying here I hope I hope there is
where's the heel woog will oh shit somebody flew off what was up with that
oh my god you fell off l stop saying that no casualties so far I don't want to speak
too soon here it is everybody good I think everyone's okay that's gnarly I think it's gnarly
go down whoa is there nothing else I can what the fuck was that there's got to be something
down here to do right that has to be that's a lot of that's a lot of crystals okay got plenty
of food all right I need two more crystals anything else to look at maybe I can kill it
can I kill it kill it just making sure I don't miss anything I feel like I'm not coming back
down here ever again ah ah okay I'm getting out fingertips on the finger itself it has a face
wait what face what do you mean face oh my god okay I'm getting out here oh there's another
chest where go back I'm freaking out right now hold on where do you see a chest where below
oh my god there is another one please tell us more about the pet beetles um the death
veining beetles I I want to get some blue death veining beetles they're really cool
I'm gonna get four of them three or four of them probably just checking to make sure there's
nothing else up here and looks like there might be okay the last one that I need is over here
I need to eat very badly like exceptionally badly like the ball in the hand I need to eat
all right let me just get the full everything finally some steaks yeah blue death veining
beetles they're some of them can live more than 10 to 15 years from my understanding which is
kind of crazy for a bug I know some of the bigger insects can live a while right you have
three oh you're you actually have them that's cool how do you feel about it we're dying of heat
now of course we are um can I do anything about it I need to get in shade or water I don't think
I have a mutation for it who has the health somebody has to see they pick stuff up on their
own and just fuck up all their inventories okay buggeroo buggeroo I need you no that's
vowoo buggeroo I gotta go where's that other one do I go wasn't it oh it's over here what about a
hissing cockroach hmm I'm not so sure I do want to check the thing in the hand to make sure I
don't think I can do anything with this no I cannot we gotta go where's the bouncy thing
okay onto the next one and it's that's three right it's three I need to do just in case I need to
eat it all right don't waste any time I'm hurt all right oh you eat one too why not
oh of course I need a fire does anybody have that or do I have to activate it who knew you can have
it is it a boss it actually it might be just saw one I'm imagining it probably is dude god damn it
we're gonna burn to death out here just do them all move out of the way get out of the way out of
the way out of the way out of the way out of the way people are just gonna die I what if we just
all die like why don't I have the thing for fire resistance I am so mad at this game for doing the
power delete thing people are just we're just dying I need to find one I don't even remember
what the fuck it was like I genuinely don't even remember what it was there's so many things in
this game to remember um we're all gonna die so I need to reload but where what is it so go look
memorizing the entire fucking encyclopedia to know what item to get skin tree bark I thought I took
it already why is it not giving it to everybody I already took one of these like five minutes ago
who had who did eat it what happened did it get it got deleted the dead one had it oh come on
really is that what happened that sucks maybe I can just start the event and it'll it'll be fine
uh I think that is I think we're all gonna die good luck maybe it'll prevent it this happens
maybe we can cut it off and we'll just go will we get cutscenes and live or are we gonna get
cutscenes and die began rising into the air to think their ancestors had created such things
with ease perhaps one day they would regain this knowledge and create miracles of their own
shit uh find water find water find like that matters what about shade does this like count
as shade over here everyone's dying everybody get under here quick before somebody dies please
stand underneath please stand underneath it you and the people that aren't standing I cannot
tell that I cannot control that person to get over here I'm gonna control this person they're all
gonna run behind look stay under here nobody move please he's not like a frustrated dad on a road
ship trip it kind of is are we healing at least please tell me we are um I have a heel uh I what
who has a heel use the orange ball this thing germa and his annoying children
the power-ups heal you they do but I'm afraid I'm gonna lose whatever just eat this just eat
a bunch of shit I have to just give it to people that don't have anything because you know I can't
let's hold on eat those eat that just everybody just eat whatever eat whatever's in your goddamn
inventory all right everybody go for it eat whatever's in your inventory just take everything
in your inventory sick cool how come this is not healing this game fuck this game fuck this game
fuck this fuck the last like two hours of this game can I just tell you fuck this game fuck the
last hour and 45 minutes of this game like what what the fuck and now everyone's gonna die
and I kind of don't know what to do do I have to go back like 15 minutes to like go find the
heat resistant thing because one of my heat resistant people died so now everybody just
dies that's fucking horse shit I'll be honest with you that's absolute dog shit okay well
everybody stays alive for now does anybody have three eyes to find the fire tongue thing
is vu here no vu's been gone no vu is here Jesus so vu has it right now doesn't he no
somebody else did I do not have the thing in my inventory the person that had it in the inventory
is dead um super awesome it's really cool I need three of these oh complain complainer Andy stream
yeah you have amber I thought it was the tongue that did it isn't it like the tree bark oh that's
for the third eye oh okay where is the stupid ass item I'm so like fucking mad at this game
I went from like oh I love this game it's so cute to like give me the fuck out of here what the
stupid fucking bullshit the game should have ended fucking two and a half hours ago I would have
loved it okay so let's find one of these things this is gonna be a nightmare um maybe one of
the caves nothing's showing up I wonder what the range is for this pick up food I'm just
trying to get any I mean I obviously hi I think it's down in caves it grows in a cave I wish I
could can I move the map no of course not he's malding I mean I'm I'm kind of annoyed it's it
feels like this should it doesn't need to be like this I'm fairly annoyed right now I will tell you
okay so I need to maybe I can just speedrun it Grootemu can eat this I guess not like it
matters okay hold on why is it why am I stuck I don't I think I have to go underground there's
no most those that like tree bark shit is seems like it was underground I think I just gotta go
I just gotta heal and go heal go go go go go go to try to get to another underground area
I think that's the only place I've seen it so let me just turn on the other thing
who has the heels nobody am I soft locked if I I think I'm soft locked I've soft locked the game
unless I can do this really fast I'm gonna have to go back like 45 minutes where is the other hold on
all right new plan all right here's the new plan here's the new plan I'm just going right for the
thing where is it there's only this one more lens then I'm just gonna get the hell out of here and
hopefully I can just get through this where's the other lens where was it was like over here
somewhere I don't remember usually it has a big shining thing on it you already got the lens
this safe did I all right I'm just gonna I'm just going I'm just getting the fuck out of here
all right come on that's it one amber and three cheese to make a permanent heat resistant I need
to unlock it first don't I shit I I it's still the desert there's a hole saved there's a hole
right here there better be one of those fucking tongues in here or I'm gonna be pissed okay all
right nice very cool what was that um doesn't count as food dude what is happening out here
get in here you're like getting blown up okay there's lots of these it's in here all right um
three cheese and one amber apparently is it but I don't have the recipe so I can't do that I'm
gonna give it to somebody though all right who is down here right now this is all right gunu
vibes are off um yeah they are they are a little they are yeah now I can feel it vibes are off
there's so many crystals down here okay you know what this game really desperately needs
and pick pickman figured this out like 20 years ago there needs to be a button for me to go
and everybody like runs to where I am like pickman figured that out 20 years ago um okay I need the
person down here that can actually whatever they do automatically I mean eventually it seems like
if it was like this where are the other seven people hey give this man a true I like that
no I didn't want to eat it I wanted to get rid of it but actually probably not bad to have
I don't have the processor anymore yeah I don't have the gem processor anymore what does it take
to actually mutate it that's mixer minerals okay I need two of those I think they're down here
I think I saw them is your favorite cheese uh it depends on the day I'm a big swiss cheese fan
but only sometimes are there nothing I don't want that thing I do want to go in here
an egg it's like an egg what is that huh 10 sorry bro RU uh I got that I think it's just
crystals what please tell me there's other crystals in here so I can upgrade that thing
to produce them and get more crystals I think I saw them somewhere but this please
stop I can't stand on this okay somebody has this man just take it you're fine all right I
need to get under this I could eat the third eye but somebody said that the actual heat um
recipe is the third is the third eye thing the amber thing and three cheeses were they lying
I don't know I don't think they did that seems very specific to life that's a very specific lie
I don't know if I don't know if I buy it look at the tree I don't think some of these aren't
unlocked do I have it unlocked no I don't think so top middle shiny skin grass skin fur skin
smelly hardened the right toxic trunk that's the fire on the nose it doesn't protect you though
hardened yeah but I don't I don't have the recipe yeah the whole point was to look at what the
recipe is I don't have it that's why you told me to do that and you can't even see it oh excuse you
crystals yeah I don't I didn't see any others is those ones over there are not the right ones
any over here I passed them yeah I feel like I saw them down here my brain just I don't know
where they are um no it's not those ones oh fuck off no the other elevator around the other side
okay what about up here I don't think I even went up here fuck really you're gonna give me more of
these them here right here yes I need two okay there's two how come it's not counting why is
it not counting it I need to eat I know I gotta I just went like just go to the one that went up
the elevator all right so where where is this shit mineral processor yeah finally all right you want
to be the processor it's gonna be you now give him all the crystals make us some money please
appreciate it all right let's find food quickly I don't have enough to go in there to do anything
although maybe no would there be enough on the ground maybe to level up one thing I wonder I
have a full party I don't think I'm gonna do anymore did you have dinner yet um I ate earlier
but in a little bit I want I do want to get to the end of this game I want to see what happens
I'm very I am completely invested in what happens in this game story hey 19 oh I'm not going to do
that would you eat one of these guys no of course not um maximum water I'll do that teach me something
the projection from the pool shared its wisdom with the trebum and showed them how to protect
it from the evil light of their enemies oh I already knew tornado trunk teach me something else
like fire skin in the fire zone get it all right I need food food I did water so that's good
okay slurp some of this up we need to share this I don't know what this is but you're gonna eat it
this is new and actually you take this what is it sausage crush small creatures while rolling
cool I love it uh it was nice knowing you you're guaranteed to die at the next um
cylinder move it's guaranteed that you're dead at the next cylinder move so everyone wave goodbye
to the uh the one with the cool hair all right for Tim let's get the fuck out of here see you
later Colgate Andy all right and what was the fast one don't why they all walked into it all
right come here very interesting is there a way to get over there yes full food take some more
just in case all right here we go you ready one two three plenty of time oh that's a big canyon
never mind um I'm going for one on the left stay back oh my god it's pretty close dude come on
how a gunu died but the one that rolls slower doesn't you can't be serious no
no shit who knew who knew who knew who knew who knew what the fast one come here all right I
guess they left the problem was I tried to go right and I corrected to my left
mm-hmm cool nice job good work everybody his face was different
oh that was just crushed everybody oh don't even not this shit eat I need to eat hurry up eat eat
eat who has food who has food on them somebody does right oh you bastard what was um there's no
lightning there isn't any lightning that means I just go I think yeah hold your nose hold your
nose this is gonna be close I don't think I'm gonna make it it's gonna be close go
no there it was floating above a towering pillar why is he so slow lenses that the
trebum had activated would the lens be able to do what the elder had promised him could it
really help power a nearby palace why was he so slow it's not right you need to go back
it's not right if he keeps dying here how long ago was it there it was floating above a towering
pillar was one of the lenses that the trebum had activated where is he oh no he's dead
shit I'm just gonna I'm gonna run with gunu because I feel like gunu for some reason is I
don't know why is he there where where's gunu oh gunu is lit up I okay gunu is lit up he looks
so different I missed the old gunu that's what I mean he's so different there it was trebum decided
they were going to try to go into the distance to see the palace don't look back in trebum always
forward always don't forget that item and don't forget this item and don't forget to eat that
item and don't forget that item but watch out for the light light will take your powers away
but eat that and make sure you don't lose that item why is he Deckard Kane I want a really dumb
way but I'm good that's so giddy and often everybody make it through it's not just please
ah everyone's safe it was floating above a towering pillar was one of the lenses that
there it is had activated would the lens be able to do what the elder had promised him
could it really help power a nearby palace I hope so oh I need to eat yes what is electrocuting me
what's electrocuting me what's electrocuting me I need to eat something there's got to be something
to eat something to eat right here steaks at last victory was achingly close three towers
waited patiently for the lenses all that trebum needed to do was climb each one and let's go
that the wrath of the cylinder would be kept at bay until they were done activate that thing is
really goofy looking it's a big ice cream oh damn it I think that's correct they seem to be in luck
the ancient device still worked and the two other lenses what was wrong with painfully managed to
drift into the skies yes there they were just waiting for our little heroes to reach them
why is he tilted this way okay so there's one that way I'm gonna go this way I already need
to eat food again I just ate like 10 steaks let's go two more go little trebum what is this thing
I don't know what it is but I'm gonna eat it it's a torrent I already had one
but it's not food either eat the fish I gotta get to go too far out there I can't really see
food there's got to be some food hanging out somewhere right here come on
looking for like a patch of mushrooms or yes okay this is gonna eat until it's full
these steak trees are the best okay get away from this shit all right go go go go go we're good
second uh light source let's turn it on vibes returning by the way vibes are returning like
I can feel them reactivating vibes are returning just in case anyone was curious elevator
hmm uh did you powered um save undersea internet cable there's nothing over here
there's nothing over here there's nothing over here this is this is fate this is fate there's
nothing here other tower first maybe I guess I'll try that I'm all right how am I already hungry
again it doesn't make any sense what does it what's it this one's better isn't it oh that's an
I can revive all right well I gotta I'm gonna just go around the other one I guess I'm gonna
do I really have to go all the way around for this and then come all the way back
you're joking with me right what about the internet cable vibes are in danger
not quite not yet getting there there is a boat here though hang out on the waters of the okay
there is one here you know again you know what I mean like I did it get everybody to come circle
around me they wouldn't just stand in the sun be one more lens waiting to be awakened
only one more struggle across sand or water and they would have achieved the task they were
entrusted with it was so hungry but the memory of the two brothers of the desert gave them the
strength to keep going everyone's just like starving right now yeah he just fucked me up so bad
somebody just wrote just eat dude omega lull just eat dude omega lull like that you that was
funny just eat dude thanks or anything it works now come on all right all right are you aiming
at him die die I feel like I'm playing house of the dead this is just every light gun game
holy shit the trebum in shock and having barely survived did not know what to think
one of their most dangerous holy shit lay dead uh hold on the eternal cylinder was immobile
get on his calf and eat the floating palace where they had expected to dance and sing
for all those left behind was out of reach what oh my god then came a call
it was very subtle we ripped this guy in half but grew stronger and stronger was it the ones
trapped in the cylinder calling to the treble was it the voice of their memories urging them on
the portal into the cylinder's dreams lay open they had not yet reclaimed all the abilities of
their ancestors wandering that strange world once again would take great bravery
but with all they've been through they had gained the courage to do what needed to be done
it might be reckless it might be dangerous but they had to step inside one more time
all right step in step in do we know writer come on who knew plus oh I don't like this
once again they had you have you have returned can you hear me everything is falling apart
existence is suffering the cause of suffering is attachment to ego ego is the separation of
consciousness from universal oneness suffering will continue as long as consciousness remains
separate only the unification of all consciousness will end suffering birth is suffering aging is
suffering illness is suffering death is suffering separation is suffering suffering will lead to
hate there is one consciousness leads to the dark side of the one is the consciousness of this
universe and there is no distinction between self and the other object and subject that which
receives and that which is perceived the variety of forms is a cause of suffering all forms must be
made alike all forms must be made one shouldn't have eaten all those random fucking stakes on
that tree
this is like a regular door will continue until all things are one the window when all things are one
when all forms are perfected within the cylinder then the cylinder will cease and there will be
peace all is one one is all one is nothing nothing is all what if i have anything to say about it
me all right come on come on that was a good one
get in the cylinder gunu you must make it for the cylinder
i don't know i don't know i don't have the strength to do it
yeah
the cylinder was trying to compensate it was clear that the voice was getting weaker
didn't work this is the massive i want to never mind i don't want to read that uh can i have a
confession to make i've never played any of the mass effect games all the way through none of them
conspiracy of ghosts happened how long had they been in the cylinder's mind doesn't look too good
it felt like a short time to the trebum but when they returned the world had changed
it seemed as if parts of the cylinder itself had spilled out its dreams corrupting the land
the cylinder laid still but there was no sign of the mathematician we vaporized them
time to go the cylinder kept moving that the mathematician had been struck down meant nothing
to it it was the master it was eternal its servants were only tools if they broke they
would be tossed aside yeah i i can't move did you guys forget did you guys forget that the
purple lightning kills me if i go too far ahead you must have forgotten you must have forgotten
look at all this food
bunu is back how are we already hungry again isn't that just a ton of food
my goodness whoa that's a face that's kind of crazy looking i want everybody to be big
how do you feel about tortellini oh how i can't believe you just said that that sounds so good
all right whoa all right i want who else should be big you i think i was wrong why don't you do it
instead is there also wrong why he looked like that why does he look like that okay i'm going
to assume that we're probably at the final arc i can't imagine there's much more after blowing
a hole in that guy's chest you want to end this game so badly no i don't this is the heat area
was very it was dropping the vibe on me it was dropping the vibes on me it was still so hungry
how are the vibes now i think they're good we got ice cream all right obviously this is a new
thing to unlock and i honestly i'll be clearly up front with you didn't even see that thing
come down here there we are new thing stealth legs oh it's bug legs frog legs
okay what's my task whatever had changed the outside world had crept into this place as well
maybe that is why the air smells so bad or maybe this place had become
a tomb just the way he said that was kind of funny it smelled so bad okay we got crystals
going in here suck these up if you would gonna bet there's one or two more upgrades left i would
guess upgrade stations whatever you want to call them that's good for now i wonder why these are
down here all right so what's the deal what's the deal here sorry i saw that and had to get it i
mean i oh okay there's a lot of crunchies down there don't let me forget them jesus it's health
feels like a pretty decent amount of health too hold on okay i'm gonna do some management here
give me a minute hmm very interesting now what is this weird just bounce them this really is a
breath of the wild shrine was i supposed to be standing on that oh give me the knowledge
give it to me i realized i went the wrong way immediately but i kind of had to commit and try
to jump there's a hole right next to us nice map all right there was the crystals down here
weren't there they were over here if i remember correctly which i think so yep nice okay very
cool it's time to continue so what do you think really happened i think the treblums are society
and i think the cylinder is destruction uh i'm gonna go to the hole first always go down the
hole if you can extra crunchies dude that's a seventh grade essay right there yeah i i didn't
i was supposed to write an essay on on like uh the economy or something right and i i just played
the eternal cylinder for like five days i didn't do my homework so i was like fuck hold on i got it
and i just write it about this game don't act like you didn't do that come on let's not pretend
like that's not something we all did and if you if the paper was written good enough there was
nothing to be upset about and plus i don't think the teacher really like whatever teachers i don't
think that they knew what the eternal cylinder was right and obviously this game didn't exist
you know 10 20 30 years ago but it's not like oh yeah that's not what happened in that game
they would have to play through it to understand it so you kind of you you were good did somebody
suck up that pumpkin oh this is the extra length right um all right get i don't want this shit
get out here this is the extra length i definitely want to keep that though you wrote about the tf2
economy you know i will tell you though you get a somebody you get a young person interested in
something and they can tie it to real world kind of educational stuff that's a win that's a win
that's not a loss writing about the tf2 economy i would have sat there and i would have written
down 100 pages and i would have loved every second of it right okay crunchy deposit yeah if it's
written well that's what i mean as long as it's written well and you can make a couple of good
points with it i don't think there's anything wrong with that who knew i need you all right i
have so much healing what about if i liked crazy taxi see it that way you might get two sentences
out of that one i don't know if you could get a whole paper out of that i'm not sure are you
maybe i guess you could tie it to i don't know i don't know man maybe i think there's a line
that you have to be aware of like you can't you cannot just be like oh no no no i had to do all
this research you had to play cod for you know fucking like 60 hours over the last week couple
weeks yeah i had to do that because you know i'm gonna tie it into the paper like um i'm i don't
know about that okay i think cave has been explored yeah i think i did a little bit more
time on my paper um i was thinking maybe i'm not coming in on fucking monday tuesday and wednesday
i gotta play a little bit more cod to figure this out don't kill us i don't know why they would have
that accent like a 40 year old guy from boston yeah i don't know if i can teach i don't know
teach i don't know if i can come in i gotta play fucking car to do this paper sir why are you here
why are you in this classroom i need to write a fucking paper whatever i'm writing a paper right
now relax yeah we're we're going over right now um king tut that's fucking easy all right i'll
write a paper about fucking king tub dude that's simple that's the easiest thing i've done all week
okay by the way that that guy never comes back that guy interrupts the teacher over and over
again during the one time he shows up with just absolutely completely off base everything's just
wrong and he just never comes back and then like a year later hey dude what what didn't you have
didn't you go to like some class yeah yeah a long time ago i have a paper due for about
fucking i don't know uh some somebody something in egypt or something i don't know i don't fucking
care i think it's doing like a week he's still working on it yeah he's still working on it
i love that he's still working on it he's got the title and you look up you look up for this
motherfucker's typing in like 16 point font it's got one sentence say uh you're gonna have to
redo some of this oh give me that 10 words and call it a paper i always got such unbelievably
awful writer's block whenever i had to do papers in high school in college and everything i'd get
oh we need a you need a 10 page paper or a certain amount of words right word count whatever it was
i'd get halfway through this shit and i would just couldn't keep going i'd get six pages done
and i would have said all my thoughts all the things that i cared about and it was really
really clean and it was really well written but i needed another like six or seven hundred words
and just i i don't want it's come on i i i've made all the points i need to make so then what you
end up doing and this is you know let's talk about education for a second when you get to that point
where you have a 10 page paper and you got seven and it's perfect you then have to go back and go
into it and add a bunch of fucking filler bullshit you got to add a bunch of filler words and it
ends up one sentence and you end up stretching it into four paragraphs for one sentence each word
becomes its own paragraph when i had a concise clear very well written seven page paper does it
have to be 10 can i can i just can you just grade me on the merits of my points and my thoughts
does it have to be 10 pages what if it was nine pages what if it was 9.999 pages
what are you gonna do give me an f all right um i got a lot this one is probably going to be one
of the last upgrades of the night let's do this first the projection from the pool shared its
wisdom with the trebum and showed them how to protect it from the evil light of their enemies
nice i know not every single teacher or professor was like that you know i i think i had plenty of
teachers over the years that were just like yeah just dude it can't be like two i don't think i
want more uh trebles i think i'm going to health health and food like if it's a 10 page paper and
you give me two pages come on gwen that's not gonna that's just not gonna fly if i was the teacher i
would just write back and you know what let's say let's say let's talk about the due date all right
so due date comes around let's say the due date is what's today today is uh february february 5th
if the due date is february 6th and you give me three pages that's what you that's what you hand
in and it's due what i'm gonna do is i'm just gonna say three pages come on gwen and i'm gonna
say you got another three days come on i'm gonna write come on i'm gonna write come on gwen and
i'm gonna you're gonna get three days water is not a problem but food is what if they turn that same
three pages in after three days that was fair it was very fair but i'm sorry i that you you failed
i'm what do you want me to say you can't just hand the same thing in you can the same thing in is
there anything behind that is there any like oh hey let's talk or is it just hey yeah i got it
it's three pages it's like man wait what do you mean i'm gonna save the rest in case somebody dies
and i need to save somebody cool but if there was something wrong what if yeah okay if if it's a big
difference there's a big difference between something happened in my personal life and i
need extra time versus i like got high on the sofa for three days and ate four bags of potato
chips there's a difference between those two things i need to give this to you what if it was
a perfect point they were so good the paper was so good i mean what two page it depends on the
topic if the topic required 10 pages like there was 10 pages of sourcing and and material to go
through it if they if it was a big big subject to be to do a big kind of thesis on you know five if
you got to like four or five i would be like okay what if you what if you literally cried reading
it because it was so moving well then i don't i then yes okay i'll give you a c plus watch out
i'll give you a c
oh i'm sitting here thinking about just sobbing over a two page paper on like economics
fucking moving shit i can't believe it this is so insane i don't even what is no oh my god this is
so moving this paper about this paper about like the treasury yield curve is so i mean i don't even
know what to say at this point yeah you nailed it you nailed it where is it okay what if it was
three pages and on the fourth page was a 50 dollar bill well that would be um that would be very very
bad teacher malpractice of the truala had once filled the trebum with fear but now it was a sign
that the world though infected had not surrendered to the cylinder yeah i mean you gotta add a few
zeros and i'm returning that to you i'm returning it to you there's gonna be four thousand dollars
in there and i'm gonna go i think hey excuse me um there you what do you think you're doing here
putting four thousand dollars in here trying to bribe me student no no but it was it was five oh
how much no you put four thousand dollars in there and it was really really messed up and let me tell
you stuff like that could get you in a lot of fucking trouble you're gonna scam
five thousand dollars for a high school paper no all right i don't know if it's late but this is
doing this is doing it for me tonight that's economics oh another puzzle room hey i have i
got a great idea how about just just do the work you can the best you can and hope for the best
that's pretty much it that's all there is to it a lot of people a lot of teachers a lot of professors
if you were to sit down if it was like hey this is only six pages and it's supposed to be 10
i did my best i thought i made pretty pretty good points yeah okay 10 grand is this a new power
no what is in here i don't remember i can break these somehow have i seen this power iconic vision
oh you can see through oh i see what's going on a lot of crunchies in here okay i think i have to
shoot somebody or throw somebody through am i just need to spray it they get us to shoot water
through that what do i do with this what do i do with this andy place to put this there's a lot of
crunchies in here the trebum wondered at the strange mechanism their ancestors had created
it made them think about time and how it changed everything the old world had passed and now the
new was struggling to be born oh cool okay so i need another one of those circles uh this there
was a i saw the solution to this and i forget it was pointing wasn't it pointing like this
which way was it pointing fly on the board on the log and the frog was it flipped might have been
flipped they were on the 10 and the 11 let's try it let's just go look crunch oh okay so it's uh
10 and then seven i already forgot which one was which but it's okay i believe this one was in the
right spot i need a cube oh no was there a cube somewhere i didn't see uh oh it's time for some
tea um i might go refill my tea vibes are back it's been a way i haven't taken a break let me
just finish this puzzle and we'll take a break i'll get some tea and we'll conclude the game
eventually i need a cube they always put one in here always always always always cube yes
crunchy overload deposit very cool anything else down here i don't think so how's it you
should shower uh i showered seven or eight weeks ago the trebum were relieved to find an elder
alive in the cave but what she had to tell them was sober yeah i'm good the end draws near my
friends the elder said the mathematician may seem dead but the servants of the cylinder are not so
easily defeated i can feel your despair but trust me there is light i shower every morning only
darkness you have accomplished a great deed for our people you have reclaimed our powers from the
cylinder no one has done such a thing before now you need only board the floating palace
and leave with the secrets of our kind restored but you cannot do this on your own you will need
the help of our oldest friends find the creatures that feast on the fallen trawler and steal from
them what they have stolen with that ingredient you will acquire a great power the power to
communicate with the trawler they are the only ones who can lift you into the heavens
and carry you to your salvation they keep attacking all right we're going to find this
creature to attack this creature to find this creature to then attack this creature to get
us power from that creature make another deposit okay i think we're in pretty good shape full water
full everything i think we're good although is there something up there something looks like
it's up there no oh it's just his head yeah all right let's go dude this happened to my buddy
eric i'm gonna be thinking about that all night just like dude what does what does your buddy
eric do where is like what planet is he from the trebum tried to imagine the creature they were
looking for what an enormous monstrous beast it must be to devour the mighty trawler even just
imagining such a creature was frightening but they had never let fear stop them before and they
wouldn't start now okay all right time to move this is yes beautiful like i said the the art
direction on this game is is a 10 out of 10 creature sound effects 9.2 this guy over here
three desert area two overall pretty fun snow area seven first zone nine this zone right here
8.7 the narrator 9.5 all of the trebum friends 9.6 what's the average lava zone six point by 9.6
and not 10 because there was two times and i was interrupted by the narrator and it made me very
upset gunu are we talking gunu 0.1 gunu 1.0 gunu 2.0 or gunu whatever this is losing your abilities
zero that's gonna bring it down and upgrade gunu prime would be fat gunu yeah the i think that's
that was the most interesting gunu like a 9.0 he did die he did he walked into the cylinder like
four times and we had to restart the game which come on win no i like it i think i like this game
just that section in the lava and not the lava in like the heat area feel like i was soft locking
myself and it was kind of frustrating no i think all in all i think it's really i think it's fun
what do you got this looks like me the projection shared a recipe with the trebum
one which could protect them from the light of the cylinder's servants something that also about
this game also that is a little not necessarily confusing but they have this elaborate system to
do these permanent mutations but it's almost unnecessary i almost feel like i would rather
just be able to not have this in the game and just be able to give people stuff and they keep it
this feels very unnecessary because the game is not going to be much longer and i feel like
a system like that to me is put in place in a game that's i think a lot longer because i've
really only used it a few times it's not like oh my god i have to use it it's an interesting
feature but i feel like some of it was almost mandatory but most of it isn't all right so what
are we doing do i want another uh this is probably the last upgrade here you just you do too much
save scumming that's why yeah that's true that's fair let's do this one more time probably go up
to 10 dammit a wheel yeah i'm peeing and pooping all right relax i'll be right back i'm gonna get
some tea we got uh probably i don't know if it's maybe like another hour or two hour and a half
we're definitely getting to the the the culmination of everything in the game with
this last bit here so i'll be right back just one sec i'll be right back one second just um
imagine i'm already gone i'm i've already left just imagine i'm already gone taking a nice break
all right actually i'm gonna let it run so the uh the miner can um can mine the material all
right i'll be right back see you in a sec
um they're dying of thirst oh that's my bad see chat it's my birthday is it it's wait a minute
what everybody hold everything it's your birthday happy birthday come on day two come on you
ha come on hey you come on happy birthday all right we're ready to rock and roll or what
holy shit i just got flashbacks to that fucking qrs song come on come on q uh that was a
fucked up stream how many people were here for that one mind show yeah that was that was an
unhinged broadcast okay are we ready get some food all right if i go strikant so i gotta go
over here oh my god why did nobody say anything didn't anybody say anything why did you just let
me do that for so long somebody said nice gameplay oh no they said cool gameplay dude i thought i
thought they were just gonna be like mean but no it was you it was literal you like where is the
gameplay oh this might be death that was really really sloppy this disaster that's bad i gotta
restart it was incredibly sloppy but maybe we can do it no i got back i got plenty of time
hey can somebody uh please in two minutes tell me to take the tea bags out just hit every object
over here now this is pretty that was a great scene could the creature that the elder had spoken of
be nearby i don't know i mean probably um if these are here i'm gonna imagine i need it
so i might as well just give it to guna who you're addicted to tea uh i can name you quite a few
things that i would be way worse i'm okay with that interesting new power oh didn't even hurt
didn't even hurt maybe i can turn it into a bomb let me put it in the uh mixer hmm oh it is making
something small energy bomb that's it you played borderlands i have played borderlands i didn't
really get into it it was kind of i don't know too much bullshit all over the screen and i know i
just said bullshit the game i don't hate the guy okay whatever everyone's gonna hate me no
all right tea bags out tea bag oh thank you borderlands has that problem for me where i don't
know how maybe some of you maybe some of you guys will agree with this i really don't like games
and i might be contradicting myself because someone's gonna be like you love this you love
this games that have ultimates where it's just oh okay it's a one minute cooldown and then press
this and and you just kill kind of everything i don't i'm not like a big kind of ultimates
and maybe it's because i feel like they they make a lot of the game really easy where it's okay every
30 seconds i have this move that makes me do like a million damage i'd rather be precise and have
precision headshots where is this thing can both oh yeah yeah both can exist i just i like it when
a game does not have ultimates if well in a in like a single player pve kind of game pvp right
ultimates are built into every sort of league of legends type game any any game that's like a
competitive multiplayer has them right or most of them do i took the bags out i know we're good
bags are out bags are out we're good we're good go to oh go to the heck up there right where's
this thing oh that's a raid that's a big raid that's a vinesauce raid what's up what's going
on vinnie i hear you played this game too i hear that you've played this before turn a cylinder
thanks for the raid welcome i think i'm in the final arc i loved it hated it loved it again
we're back on the love it we're back in the love it arc like i think actually i'm having a good
time again vinnie hates this game vinnie hated this game wait hold on wait wait wait wait wait
hold on wait wait wait this is wait hold on a minute actually true true no no no true true
true wait hold on did we begin to hate the game at the same spot i'm very curious at what point
did did vinnie say this i'm very curious he thought it was too long he admits he hates it
no no no no no no no no hold on we gotta we gotta correct the record here there was a point where
i was not having a good time it was during the desert hot part where i didn't have the right
thing and i soft-locked myself and it was annoying and i was annoying feature but that was it and
then after that vibes returned we got to see one of the big um big uh enemies that had the big mouth
and that was pretty cool and i'm the vibes are back and i'm oh vinnie didn't bounce back
it's so funny that i'm playing this game well you're gonna see the end of it again because
we're at the end here but thanks a lot vinnie appreciate it hope you're doing well hope your
stream went well uh always good to see the vine sauce crew here where is this thing
there's supposed to be some gigantic monster that eats the triwala i don't see it anywhere
oh you need to eat look up it's playing minecraft hey don't eat random stuff all right you're just
okay wait wait oh you do have the food oh never mind okay now look down oh there it is this thing
jump up and down right here this is a weird floor i'm gonna say it has something to do at this floor
is it part of this weird floor wait what's that what a strange place the trepum thought but even
stranger were the feelings that stirred in their memories like a voice from a lost world
we like kids or something are we children what are you doing back what why why do you hate the
playground don't reach for us their worst fears had come true oh the mathematician was alive
and now he had brought forth this wheel no not the light i hate the light the light sucks
what do i do about this i haven't even eaten we're starving all right all right wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait i've got a bunch of bombs where's the demolition person you all right
foo you know what to do bringing down this towering monstrosity seemed almost impossible to the
oops but yeah suck me up suck me up have a solution if you're clever enough and this one was no
different the creature grabbed at its prey so blindly and so greedily it could be made to
absorb almost anything absorb who's dead wait that hurt that hurt who's dead but whatever follow me
follow follow follow follow follow suck up these things oh no no who's that do you have to get
sucked up maybe have a spiky head wait who has that somebody has that gog gog womu gog womu
where's gog womu where's gog womu can you morons get over here i'm sorry i'm sorry i said morons
but get over here i i did call the morons but i what i meant to say was where is getting frustrated
again where is this fucking treb whatever they are where's the cube yeah all right suck me up
suck me up that work the healer you suck at this bro what i don't i really don't think i do
i think it's just fucking goofy okay i think it's a little goofy if you have to let i think it's a
little goofy is what i think all right got it i think it's a little goofy the trebum decided that
this was not the sort of place where they might find a creature capable of eating a trowala
no this place was tainted nothing alive would want to stay here they would have to continue their
search for the great beast did somebody pick up a item that was on the ground it was like a red
heart or something what was that who picked it up yeah poor vu poor vu it's okay it's all right
not forgotten we had vu since the very beginning we will write their name in the history books the
bravest warrior of all the treblums and guess who's gonna write it he may have done all the
work but he's gonna write in the history books who swept in at the last minute sacrificed himself
oh revive who doesn't have that somebody's like electrified skin can do it right no
their body is like buried in the dirt no i yeah i'm not gonna go i'm not gonna be able to find
vu i am not gonna feel fine to do i'm sorry we have to live with it bye boo we're gonna unsub
if you don't revive who well i have something to tell you when uh when go vu died i remember
this this amount of um this amount of people i'm gonna have to restart this by the way
when go vu died i you didn't say are you gonna unsub if i don't bring go vu back
vu was an og yeah i can bring him back nope that's caving to chat
i'm dead towers had fallen and the light was lost there was no more point in running
the cylinder would consume everything well that's unfortunate i'm gonna throw up dude it was vu who
made the first sauce yeah maybe i actually do need food though we can revive at one of those
shrines i'm not against it you better be on your best behavior you guys eat so much now oh crap
remember the blue smoke that's right i forgot in a little smoother i see something in the
distance no go vu wait it keeps moving oh fuck i forgot it keeps moving wait didn't it keep
moving remember wait last time it was like oh and it destroys everything you can't stop it
last time i got there it did it it went through it oh it's because i didn't go on the pad yeah
all right where's my there's my smelter i just want to eat in peace i just want to eat in peace
and i'll be followed by these weirdos let me eat oh there is a shrine here isn't there is he
gamer fatigued no no i'm just chilling i'm just hanging out i'm good interesting there we go i
don't think i want to upgrade this again because they just kind of die when you have too many
somebody said earlier they don't think that i'm supposed to have this many out at one time
i feel that because i feel like when you get over seven or eight of them one of them just kind of
is a little too slow and gets a run over um hmm food one more time yeah pretty good
i mean there are a lot of crunchies here but i don't think it's necessary i think we're good
the projection shared a new recipe with a trebum which could protect them from the cruel light of
their enemies wheel body oh very very cool take some extra snacks take some snacks and get out
of here yeah i already i already got a willow right down there ropo i'm gonna use grapo for
a little while i feel like we've been neglecting ropo i uh no my tea's nice and hot hey don't
worry about my tea worry about your tea there's a couple of holes i'll do this one close to it
please tell me what the fuck is going on i don't think i can there's a lot going on in this game
dude what they're really only four of these in here no this is not okay does anybody have the
three eyes really no this is exactly what i was talking about it's like i i need five there are
four here so hey stupid video game player you dummy you didn't keep one extra turnip with you
the whole game do i have the ability to do this i don't think so i need three oh
oh i'm gonna give it to gunu because gunu's the fucking man gunu's the fucking gunu's the man you
know what i mean you're the man you're the man on there's not there's probably not gonna be any in
this whole zone i'm telling you there's not gonna be any in the entire zone i'm not supposed to eat
them it's gonna go in the hole there's not one just hanging out here somewhere all right i need
to go this way a bunch of baloney there's a bunch of baloney i'll make that really clear to everybody
what's down here oh there as well hey everybody should i play hollow knight remember when i played
that uh four and a half years ago and never finished it got like a third of the way through
it i do it you got a lot of bullshit on you here i think i have some doubles don't i okay cool
because i'm just gonna be playing random games just kind of turn the stream on just play just
relax and stuff why not just do all the shit that i always said i wanted to do why not right this is
the year of gaming i'm gonna be very honest i'm gonna be very honest with you let's go yakuza
probably i am in the zone to play games and just chill out that's what i'm all about now
that's what i'm i'm all about here bro please play skyrim maybe i will just do like a random
skyrim uh playthrough who knows oh it's right there almost there oh my god i can't believe it
there's a turnip dude is your turnip nothing well they're all over here look at this there's
so many of them key tope uh i think those are pretty abundant that's not it what is that weirdo
all right um there's a few over here just watching creep and get the hell out of here somebody just
blow a horn at this piece of shit please or something who even has anything don't you dare
dude zero zero it's that's the way of you bringing the zero back get oh get out of here
get out of here get out of here who lost their powers now let me re-figure out the whole fucking
crew again i gotta go find i have to hide somewhere i don't know oh you can see me right of course
again he's mad i hate this part of the game this is this is by far the lowest point of the game
is this delete power from you bullshit it just takes me out like i have a group of people i have
a crew i'm making my troubles are you taking this shit from me it's like now i don't even know who
has what power i don't know what the fuck is going on i got an egg vibes are immaculate right now
i just no they're not are they actually scared of the fire what the hell just happened can i just
get my new friend please and then we can get the hell out of here oh sorry that power is gone you
should stop playing it i'm like 20 minutes away from beating the game i think i can put up with
i think i can put up with it for like another 20 minutes okay first of all where's the horn
i don't even have it i'm just gonna hide
i don't care what this bath petition ends up being i'm throwing a grenade at him at the end
of the game no you see it's humanity no i don't i'm throwing a grenade at you you're getting a
grenade i'm telling you right now you're getting a grenade at the end of the game i thought the
wait didn't the cube have a horn i don't think the cube has a horn is there a hole i can fall
down do i have anything i can use here pose god damn it why i can't all right all right all right
you gone good this is gonna be difficult this is still this car is still this fucking combustion
engine piece of shit is still behind us run out of fuel already what about the egg i don't i don't
care about the egg right now i i i need to get the hell away from these things stat pronto
the vibes are going into the red yeah right now you guys are looking to the vibes meter
and you're not telling me you know you're not saying it you're not telling me but you're very
concerned right now because right now your screen is blinking red and all you hear in your ears is
really loud just kill me this is so far away i got a job interview tomorrow you should wrap it up
i hope you good luck i hope you do good i hope you get the job and everything or what's
something you like hope you get pretty decent income and everything but i have trevums to save
how the vibes are off on that one big time i should i swim across with i don't know i feel
like it's too far i don't know i feel like this is way too far to go it's already right up no he's
a faster one the problem is leaving the bubble i you have to leave it so far away i can't get a
good make sure to run to the blue smoke yeah but there's only one there's this one over here and
there's one more on the way i'm already fucking dead i might have to swim across
yeah i've no i there's no way i would have made that i think i have a swim
no i definitely wouldn't have made it who has swimming ability oh oh none of them do
because of the yellow light of course how could i have forgotten that's oh my bad
actually the vibes aren't even down i've accepted that the vibes i've accepted where the vibes are
and it's okay i'm actually in my vibes are pretty good right now yes i mean the vibes are turbulent
but then i wouldn't call them bad the vibes are turbulent not bad good tea well that's obviously
not working so i need a new strategy maybe all the way to the right but that's a long way to go
i'll try it i think that's like 50 longer i'll try it vibes are fine okay yeah let's go the vibes
are putrid like if you scoop the vibes up did they just kind of fall through your hands sludge
like just falling through your fingers you have to scoop it up scoop it up i don't think you can
get it all they smell yeah they smell terrible smell they smell rotten like rotten fucking food
why is this so much more difficult than every single other one the last 13 hours of gameplay
am i missing something here this has been the only one that's been this much of a pain in the ass
it's definitely left it has to be i was gonna skip the first blue
um smoke and just go up this corner here i telling you i think swimming is the way to do it i just
need swimming i feel like i could get over there fast enough this might be the one yeah i am so
far away it's not even close this is not even close what is going on right now it's not even
close this mechanic has happened like 40 times over the playthrough and this one i just can't do
it the only one i haven't been able to do use fast legs and regen i think i had that before but
no you know what i'm swimming across this shit watch this i'm swimming across this with with
fucking grappo all right grappo it's your time to shine do i have any of those things that make me
have a fish head i would look in here but it's gonna activate it let me just let me just test
this to see what this looks like i didn't mean to fall in here yeah i need the stamina who could
have done this first try if i had the stamina thing for the hmm i might have been able to
done it i might be able to do it if i had the stamina fish why is there a giant lake in the
middle i'm like just my brain is sitting here just thinking damn it why is there a lake in the middle
i mean it could be a small lake somebody's dead somebody died you have to go so far
parallel i just i'm gonna just find the fish really i'm just kind of banging my head against
a wall for no reason eat this and then eat that i want to look cool while i do it all right there's
no way there is no way that i do not go across i have infinite stamina and i have webbed feet
and i'm shiny as fuck i'm ready go on faster go faster this is not increased swimming speed
in fact i feel like it's slower swimming speed how is this faster somebody said please just roll
i i mean i've tried that like a fucking dozen times why is this one so much harder the vibes
that shouldn't take you out of rolling now that you that that's a bad one to get you just have to
cut across i saw the blue and i'm like should i get the blue no it's over my buddy eric is
disappointed well i'm disappointed that eric is disappointed how does that sound
how's that sound what are you doing i feel like i got caught on everything the physics of this
role is just so catchy and bouncy what the fuck i mean i made it but at what cost store them and
just do it alone we continue who died at last one of the creatures was walking around carelessly in
the corrupted plains of what was left of the world all the trevum needed to do was to steal
its core or more precisely the core it had stolen from whatever poor trefala it had eaten
yeah gunu's fine the creature it's okay slow and uninterested in the time does this have stealth
legs had a frightful layer of teeth protecting its prize could a nimble enough trevum snatch
that prize right out of its jaws all right gunu go in there with your default body your default
legs your default head who else we got we've got default default default i forgot that you had stuff
and i said i thought something was wrong with you default all right let's go well now we're gonna be
get away from me all right i'm just going in i'm going in and i'm just gonna suck it out this is
the play i just blow it over i wonder if i can just blow it up does anybody have to jump this is
definitely what it wants me to do now we wait 40 minutes for him to do a full entire revolution
around the whole place are you mad um nah nah i don't think so are you annoyed no not really
if i had a floaty thing i could go up there the floaty things over there did ever unlock the
floaty thing permanent upgrade i don't think so i don't believe i did but um it's right here
it's all right i got it oh joyous indeed the trevums found the weird liver that was inside
of the scary monster it seems they don't know exactly where they need to go maybe if the yellow
light came and took all their powers away they would find a new way right eat this as soon as
it kind of looks like a fucking dork to feel a call as if it was being drawn to some place nearby
it was now the master of song the master of song it's me voice to be heard it's time for gunu to
sing the song oh somebody's pissed off a memory awoke within the trebum of an ancient ritual
a song at the top of a trebum tower to forge a bond between trebum and
come back is it are you all right oh my god i just got sniped from across the whole game
what was that that thing jumped across the whole map jeez oh my goodness what is that huh i'm trying
to take over my fucking brain i was all right place your bets is it gonna be a yoshi story song
is it gonna be super funny and cute is it gonna be like i hope the top of this tower
right here in this place and with the proper mutation now was the time for the trebum
to sing who calls for us in this time of darkness who has learned the ancient song
have our old friends remember us here our voice trebum there is little time left and much is at
stake it was long ago that you will send to the heavens your song traveled far into the cosmos
and we listened here on your world we made a new begin the sorrows of our history
we began to the friendship and harmony but the beauty of your song pierced time and space
far into the darkest and coldest corners of the universe that's how the cylinder found us
and when it came from us the bright future we had dreamt of is gone but silence may be safer
but what is a life without song you reached out to the stars because you were full of hope
and that hope must be preserved we know what you are trying to accomplish
and we will help you your help to see me strike at the abomination and then meet me where only
shattered pieces are left of the evil that i haven't done i love oh they're like you're beautiful
song it was just me kind of going like for one second oh my god quick touch the brain
touch the brain everybody touch the brain you you can come to in fact you'd be the first one to
touch it in case it's poisoned we can break we can we can turn some of these crystals
and if we live be as shadows of our ancestors but when the cylinder streams spill into the world
the glimpse of hope tumbles out with them fragments of our past have fallen into this land
and only you can reclaim them using the cylinder in its eternal arrogance does not want to lose
what it has conquered so it has formed these strange alien heads to protect the fragments
soon it will wake from its slumber and reabsorb them oh half of us are dead
it's that let our memories become yours and then seek out two more that is all we require
two more enough for us to be remembered ourselves again do this for us and we shall
carry you to your path now go seek two more towers and call for our help and then all this will
find me do i eat this thing i'm gonna break it the voice urges them to go forward and reclaim
the memories of the triwala well given this to gunu for a while legs what does that do
okay look for water look for water you are dying of this hurry there's not much time
i drink poisonous water we're better to find out now i cannot well i mean i was standing in that
cut scene for a while that i got pretty fucking thirsty man um i think my character is passing
out look much easier this one is i have to get another one i see yellow light i get angry i see
yellow light i get angry and if you're gonna take the triwala power from me no you are not no you
aren't with this shit right now um what was that um i wonder if i can just get it and get out of
here no i can't i have to do it this is not going to be that bad as long as it's not on one of the
big cow ones that go those ones are awful what is it something over here that's fairly annoying
but i have a good spot okay goodbye pretty clean okay as that any items or anything
no okay now get me in there i need to eat this has to be the end of the game i would be i would
be shocked if after collecting whatever these two more things are there's no way there's one there
and one there are you enjoying the game i i am enjoying the game i do think it's dragging a
little it's dragging its feet a little here this this has got a yellow light on it okay
it's got it's filled with poison and has a yellow light all right wait i already i already have one
it's on my head right now i don't need another one i don't need another one no i definitely
don't need another one let's go i need to eat that's really important anybody have food just
gonna find the platform that makes okay never mind that makes this a lot easier then for some
reason i thought i had to attack kill and take it from two more people that's all right this
shouldn't be that much longer then i do want to go this way really kind of this is a shitty area
hmm there is an upgrade station but i don't even know if i want to do it i think i just want to go
just just do it yeah let's just get the hell out of here yeah what's going on with the stamina
i feel like some people have a lower stamina or something because the wheel is not full on some
characters does it take longer to recharge the second wheel i saw that okay there's one there
and there's one there is it actually gonna get me it's gonna kill somebody we have to move on
we have to go sorry groppo groppo's dead we have to sing the song now has the trebum reached this
new area they were glad to see two great no stop i stop talking to me i i know where i have to go
has the trebum reached this new area they were glad to see two great towers nearby
this was a fortunate turn of events as soon they would be able to fulfill their promise
to the triwala but something felt wrong there was something unnatural about these animals
could it be that the eternal cylinder was aware of the trebam's actions aware and was trying to
aware look at all this bullshit look at this they so badly want to remove this singing song helmet
from my head look at this they just like so badly want me to get this taken off so i have to go
in that monster's ass or whatever it is it's mouth i know i know the answer the answer to
this question is no i'm just gonna save scum all right well we'll get it we'll get another one
we got another one i got another one where am i god take it off i don't even care take it off
yeah take it off it doesn't matter i got another one up my sleeve sorry elevator's broken hello
staff are asking for a raise one of your staff has died the mighty triwala had been cast down
was this the end was all in vain so it seemed at first but a small crack had been opened
and a ray of light had escaped the darkness in a world where titans clashed and monsters battled
it was only the smallest and most unlikely of heroes who could make a difference gotta go in
there i want the triwala try again i think there's more than one i think there's like
a dozen or something i think it's like a whole entire species all right somebody has to float
up there who's still alive bowie bowie you are always my favorite don't let anybody tell you
differently look at how cute he is what's in here sometimes it is the actions of the tiniest of
creatures working together that can change the future when everything is broken they are the
only ones who can fit through the cracks yeah the trebum had fought this creature before and beaten
it they would do so again for themselves for the triwala and for the future for the guild
guru cannot die but what is happening i'm just gonna i don't know i can't move i can't move that
he's doing this stun move and now i'm gonna explode and kill my trebum allies dude do something i'm
trying he does this stupid thing i'm where are the crystals where are the crystals
can we how can we help you you guys are good i'll get through it bro you're gonna turn the
game off you cannot come this far and turn the game off i will never be able to live with this
i would never be able i wouldn't be able to look at myself in the mirror i'd be like you let you
sorry bastard be pointing into the mirror and say you let those trebums down and their world got
destroyed by the giant rolling pin and you could have stopped it but you didn't you let them all
die sorry not tonight not tonight the trebum had fought this creature before and beaten it
they would do so again for themselves for the triwala and for the future why did it just
delete it from my you gotta throw the red stones i fought this guy before but is way more irritating
in this room for some reason i'll pick up one of those crystals and it'll just disintegrate in my
hand vibe watchers skip this one it's a lost cause the trebum had fought this creature before and
beaten it they would do so again pick it up for the triwala oh my god i'm starting to think that
i don't care about the fucking triwala or the trebums anymore just roll the pin roll it over
everybody i'm starting to not give a shit about the triwala you know what rolling pin all of earth
eh well whatever shoot dude it's so fucking weird i promise you
his guts came out what his guts come out his fucking skin came off that's awful that's morbid
why did his skin come off what the hell it peeled his skin off hold on that's not happening give me
somebody else okay goo goo one you know what just put on some put a costume on who cares at this
point nice nice oh all right pretty cool costume let's go the trebum had fought this creature
before and beaten it they would do so again for themselves for the triwala and for the future
it's no it's i feel like this is detrimental he can't even see dude you don't understand
if you were playing this right now you would be you would be saying holy shit this is
fucked up why i'm pressing a and it feels like i'm pressing b i'm pressing up and it feels like
i'm pressing down i'm telling you if you had the controller in your hand right now you'd be saying
the same shit you'd be saying the same stuff i'm telling you right now you would be sitting there
going yeah this is a fucking mess you i'm just uh you would be i'm saying to you you would be
let's just chill out all right let's hang out the trebum had fought this creature before and beaten
it they would do so again for themselves for the triwala and for the future oh my god please stop
that like so when he does that move the entire room pushes you around it also deletes if you
have one in your hand already this is uh you'll know what i mean by that
use the jump pads when i touch the jump pads i lose control of my character and he just spins
in the air i can't breathe in you just fucking fly in the air and have no control of the character
in a random random ass direction use the bombs it takes like 10 seconds to eat it and then it
takes 10 seconds to explode i think i'm do i just i just think it's not let's go trebum had fought
this creature before and beaten it they would do so again for themselves for the triwala
and for the future my eyes are itchy i'm trying as hard as i can right now oh fuck off there's no
aim in the game either he tripped over a rock and died good who's eaten whatever this is give it to
gunu i'm afraid it'll override something i feel like it'll override something i'm gonna give it
to you you've been very polite holy shit he looks cool balloon head come here can't activate it
okay this is it if this is not over after i do this one this next one over there don't it's
almost like you're watching right now that wasn't even hard it was just okay it wasn't hard it was
just dumb that's it it was just kind of dumb all right you want me to say it i'll say it
all right last one this has got to be it come on up here i didn't think he was going to do it
all right let's go final song here it comes
so sad that was actually gonna feel bad struck as mighty as ever the fragment was exposed and
ready to be taken oh that was sad all right let's go come on it's so close all right i need to kill
this thing because it's just gonna continue to fuck with me the last piece what wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait excuse me sir yeah i have to have all three on one that's not accurate
the trebum had recovered you fucked up no the voice said they had to keep going we told you
find the chihuahua and renew the ancient bond of friendship that was once the pride of this world
the tree get away from me stop leave me the fuck alone i'm trying to process what just happened
okay i'm trying to that guy just erased like 500 million years of history okay that fucking ball
of goo or whatever that was just disintegrated like a million years of history somebody in the
chat let's let's relax for a second um am i in trouble here do i have to rewind like 20 minutes
or is it fine i do i have no right okay okay thank goodness okay cool
it'll fix itself all right all right okay okay thank goodness thank you you see you thought
sharing was caring you split it up between the three of you it was a mistake only one of you can
traverse the chihuahua gate all right let's go up here i need to eat yes i do we are so close
everybody we're there we're right there look at look at where we are here it's right here it's
over right there the palace there it is i keep seeing people saying tree tree tree why they why
you saying tree what why you saying tree tree the mutation tree you didn't wait yeah i have the
trunk on does i have three of them mutation true what did i unlock something the body um i don't
think i can you need to put the body on gunu oh no look look in the left side of the left corner
of the screen no we're good we're good i'm finishing this right now i enjoyed my time with
this game that's what i'm gonna say i enjoyed my time enjoyed my time a lot of it hey hey if we
didn't get this bar we wouldn't have seen gunu get sniped from across the game we made a lot
of memories i had a good time it was nice a little bit of it i was not the biggest fan of but
i think it's it's the style i think it's got a lot going for it i think just the world alone is
worth experiencing like a lot of the other ace team games but yes i do think the game could have
seen in mod chat right now the consensus seems to be i almost feel like the game should have been
yeah like two hours shorter i feel like this last part of go get the three things we we already got
the three things and it made us go get three more things at the end it's like i don't really
really want to go get three more things we already got the three things but is that a complaint or
is that a good thing because it's just more content more game more stuff to do i guess take
that as you will yeah the first half of the game was was phenomenal i loved every second of it
i think it's just once a lot of the power started to become stuff that you couldn't hold on to and
you needed to get the permanent stuff and go find items but finding items was kind of difficult
i think it got a little bloated at the like 70 mark nearby there was another structure
like the one they had used to summon the trawler in the depths of the frozen tundra and so the
trebum knew that the end was near but um everything we said so far i enjoyed it i enjoyed it
i think it's it's a really quirky really funny really interesting concept it was good do i think
it was great probably not but it was good oh wait a minute these are the only family members who
will travel to the palace we gotta go get we gotta go rescue people i don't know oh our friends i
don't even know if they're i don't think there is a revive thing here yeah we got gunu it's fine
so
all right everybody quiet big reveal time
is that using to us you are long bro saying to us of who we were days when the trellum
and the true well lived together under the same stars final boss maybe the evil
hey
what do i do you must survive protect the memories just stay alive the trawler will help
all right let's go pretty cool that was pretty sick come on everybody stay alive we have to have
at least the three or four of us there's five of us but you know what i mean even if i didn't
count two of you two of you right now are freaking out saying why did he say that
that hurts anybody have help anybody have healing no stay alive get him right in the face oh god
get climbing up scrunchies just a little longer hang on come on gunu stay alive
you have to be the one that makes it you're the only one that can sing the other guy oh
oh no oh no they're all dead i'm dead full wipe was it scripted holy shit it's just me and you
who are you what's your name vogru of course of course it's vogru come on we gotta go it's a
person person camera tv it's just kind of a regular person thank you my young friends you
have accomplished what thousands of civilizations before you failed to you've shown that the cylinder
is imperfect it may not have lost the war but it certainly lost a battle and that's never happened
before there's so much more i wish i could tell you but there's not enough of me left
and i have one final goal so forgive me for inserting myself into your memories
and for having to leave them again so soon
see if there's anything else here hey eric if you're here yeah i just want to say that
like we're cool are we cool eric are we cool wait where's gunu right you're not going to go push
it again oh uh-huh look is everybody actually that's none of us i remember that one that one
was in it too oh look it's barney and guwug his dasher his daughter bluetooth i don't know one
in the back and so the trebum who were not the strongest nor the fastest and who did not have
sharp teeth escaped the eternal cylinder they did not become one but stubbornly stayed many
and they learned to be loyal not only to their own kind but to others their great victory over
the inevitable was the victory of generations of the elders and the trawler and my own people
whose name i cannot remember but even as what is left of me fades away and though one day the
cylinder may resume its destruction i know that i was part of this family if only for a little
while and that gives me hope humans made the cylinder it was like a fucking crazy awful
project very got two out of hand they started flattening planets they went to this place they
flattened this was somebody's planet and this human and uploaded himself into the cylinder
and he tried to he's trying to stop it he's the narrator the whole time and that's really cute
the humans always the humans i seen you beat a game for once uh i would definitely that's
gonna be way more that's gonna be happening way more frequently that third the the this kind of
third arc wasn't a huge huge fan of first arc was great second arc was great i think i just got a
little overwhelmed and confused and that yellow light that yellow light was just it's just yucky
it was good i i would play it again if if i didn't play it before i would play it and again i don't
want to criticize a million things here the permanent upgrade system really just felt
i just feel like it didn't even need to be there i wonder if the developers are really concerned
that if you found your favorite little friends and you gave them what they were you wanted to give
them that it would get boring because the idea is that you lose them and i was safe scumming so that
i was kind of messing with the intent but that was a fun i was solid i i am happy that i played it
let's put it that way forget about like the 30 or 40 minutes of frustrations i had like four or
five hours ago think about the first time i played it the second time i played it the whole package
was was just nice it was a nice game it was way more than 30 minutes what no it wasn't it was
like 30 it was like 45 maybe tops it was like a whole hour yeah but i mean it was two hours no
it wasn't yeah maybe it was like two hours but spread out over seven hours he hated it no i
really didn't i really didn't i promise i didn't so i have a question so were we inside of the
cylinder when we went into that mathematician's head because that was it kind of looked like it
right weird like maze the inside of the cylinder was a weird super maze that was the cylinder's
memories it looked like a maze on the back of a cereal box and well hey i will tell you i'm
going to play ace team's new game that new uh xeno clash game looks really really cool that's
going to wrap it up here i'm not going to give you a score i don't think i should i enjoyed the
experience it was better than a six it was better than a seven i'm not going to score it it was
lower than an eight it was better than a six but it was lower than an eight that's pretty much it
you just scored it well yeah that is true yes all right i did it's a seven whatever you'll figure
it out it's in that range you'll figure it out you can figure it out it's in that range music
was great art was great character designs are great it just dragged a little and it was it was
some of the game systems were a little confusing but hey that's your six to eight six dash eight
and that's what i'm gonna score it six dash eight i didn't say seven said six dash eight all right so
let's let's talk about some of the stuff going on in the future we uh i want to play how do
you guys feel about this there's a few things i want to do i'd like to play hylix that's been
recommended for a very very long time i keep hearing how that game i have to play it like i
have to for years people have been telling me to do that i want to play binding of isaac i've kind
of got that itch just really want to do it just even if just hang it out for a little bit and
just doing some runs breath of the wild i'm like burping i'm sorry i want to do breath of the wild
holonite i don't know if i want to do outer wilds dlc hitman the new hitman
jesus uh that new hitman freelance mode i feel like would be fun to do for a stream
frog detective three sorcery i did promise that frog detective i was going to do that in february
i promise i will dark and darker is available this week do you know when when is it let me see
because i i want to play it so bad dark and darker wednesday actually wednesday all right
i'm playing that i'm playing that that's what we'll do on tuesday tuesday we're going to play
dark and darker i don't want to play it i've been dying to play it i've also been really really
enjoying the night streams i think i'm going to keep it going it's definitely i feel a lot
i don't know i feel i just feel like kind of comfortable you know what i mean this weekend
stir and i are going to return to elden ring randomizer which will be in the afternoon so
that will be an afternoon probably saturday sunday stream or maybe even we'll see how fun
it is that will definitely be in the afternoon but yeah that was the eternal cylinder thanks to
people that recommended it right up my alley and that's it just kidding now that's it so i'll see
you guys on tuesday which is the day after tomorrow it's technically tomorrow it's monday
so see you guys on tuesday for dark and darker looking forward to it should be fun
thanks for sticking around thanks for watching what about breath of the wild
yeah i'm gonna just there's gonna be a lot more just impromptu i'm just turning it on
pizza tower is another one just to kind of jump in so i was it don't be surprised
over this next period here of the stream if you check sus and it's just like i'm streaming today
i'm streaming tonight tomorrow tonight you know whatever that's gonna happen
there's a lot of stuff to play though um i'm down i'm so happy that dark and darker is here
so is it is it like kind of an alpha test or is it a demo is it going to be limited or is it going
to be what's it look like here yeah because the this next fest is back again we could hop into
some of that stuff too we did that before it's the third beta all right cool i'll see you guys on
tuesday goodbye good night take care of yourselves make sure you drink some water
kind of a longer one tonight get some sleep or good morning if you had probably just woken up
thanks everybody that came from from vinny from vinesauce get to watch uh my ending of um
eternal cylinder maybe we'll see you again it's always good to see some of those familiar vine
sauce friends take it easy though have a great night