What is, what kind of intro is this? It sounds like a bunch of birds. Oh, it's like people playing like they're like
Why is it like a giant YouTube button in the middle like, oh play the video. Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to
Football lol. That's not even what it's called. It's called football. This game is a game
Where you play football or soccer if you're an American. This is the part where you make duck noises.
I know this is this is the part where you make duck noises
So you don't even have to do it now because you already said that's the part where you make duck noises
And it's already been done, right? So this game
So if you take a look here
this is the
Power-ups that you can do during this game and you're wondering what do you mean a power-up?
Well, each one of these things see this mine right here. I can we don't control any characters
Nobody controls any of the actual players you just control the weird power-ups and the stupid AI tries to score goals on each other
Okay, good luck. Good luck
You're just gonna get fans
Good game. What?
Win by five. I win. What did you do? I won. I was like spamming you guys with like ants
Okay, I have the star. Yes, screw you
You're not doing this. I'll do whatever it takes
You can't do it now
Oh
Get off the field everybody get the field spam cows
What's the score?
Where's my it's down here?
alright, where I
Can't believe one just went in right there. I
Did I win? No. No, you didn't what it's nine to seven. What's but we need to just win by five, right?
Yes, you need to win by five. I'm like running out of resources. Yeah, I need to build resources
Everyone get out of here send everybody the sidelines
Okay, I'm back I think my game just like a hard crashed dude your net moving is that's not fair that's really good I
Click that got the window and it messed up the recording. Just keep doing that
What is 13 my way? Who's winning? You're winning by two?
All right
Keep doing that. Does it use points? I'm out of those points tie it up to a 1312 right now
I gotta win this you think you can stop the cows. I don't think I can do you think you can stop
I'm sitting on the wrong side. Oh
You see that kick
13 13 this is gonna get real boring real soon
You're probably out of cows
You could just why can you just keep moving your net this is bullshit
Come on come on. Oh
14 13. I'm out of resources, too
Now we just have to watch a soccer game. Oh
Danny DeVito is moving down mid lane. He's passing it to his teammate. He throws up a force field throws up another crown
Would you get these crowns? I told you you could buy hats hats. You could buy hats. Oh, why are you okay?
One of the very first things I explained this game has hats
I'm just gonna time-lapse the rest of this cuz we're just gonna sit here doing nothing. There's no more no more fun stuff
Wow star wins
Yeah, I know. Thank you. Thank you very much
No, no drop them drop them in the portals
I
Don't know it's a really stupid plan. I'm going to lose I'm gonna lose. It's 16
I only got the balls
What is going on over here? What is this? Why is it like a fountain of soccer balls you see?
I don't I don't know why you did this. I don't know what decision you were making
So yeah, you gotta sit here for two minutes while I'm up 36 to two are you okay with this I
Was sitting here thinking of a real strategy. I just feel like an idiot now
See I'm trying to win over here and you're just like
Have you met me before do it do you know who I am? Oh you want to do cannons you think oh you want to drop
Firepower you want to drop some fucking firepower. Is that what you wanted to do?
Have I scored any points and my score to call
Still get a chance here come on come on pull it through 15 seconds pull it through we need a few more come on
Come on come on
Get it in there get the ball in there
You fuckers
Who's gonna go into?
No, who is it gonna come into I don't know yes, I don't know
I don't know whose goal is whose I have no idea
I don't know it's like you know that game with the cups when you put the cups around like the thing and you move the
Cups around real fast. No, I don't know. I don't know who's is who I have I had a plan
I had a plan here both of our nets
Which the one on the bottom is yours one of the bottom is yours?
No, it's not is it is
Why they're not shooting
Why do they not shoot
I dropped 36 of them
Shoot they don't shoot right away. I dropped like over 30 of them
Oh starting off really slow a couple of guys kick around a ball
What is what did I get on defense everybody what the hell am I guys just like shitty what's going on here
Sing on D. You might have to give them some help. We should probably give them a little bit of help here
Okay, I can't see what's going on and this is gonna throw up I have a hundred and seventy more of these