You know what else I want to do? Hi, sorry if I startled you. Um, the whole wrestling,
hey, what song is this thing? Does anybody know? Remember when we did that video game sound effect
thing where I had to figure out what game it was from or what character did it from? Oh, here's a
sound effect. And what is that? What's that from? Are there more of those? I want to do one of those.
Is there is there a good one? There are a few more of those. If any of you guys know any,
there are mods if you can get me a good one. One that I haven't done. That'd be fun to do.
It's sporkle. Yeah, it would have to be something that they can play sound effects through the
browser. What's what's sporkle? I mean, look this up. Sporkle. It's, it's just a trivia site.
No, I don't want to do trivia. I want to do sound effects. Then I have to guess what the sound is.
Okay. It looks like Kyle is famous as one. So I'm going to open it. Give some time to maybe get a
couple of these fun websites. It's getting loud. All right, play. What you're describing is true.
No, but it's not trivia though. Trivia would be this plumber back in 1985 or 1983 got his start
jumping on goombas. And it'd be, oh, okay. That's I know that. Let me see what it is.
Search it up on sporkle. You piece of shit. Sporkle is based and pog. All right. Hold on.
Do they have what I'm describing? Hold on. I want to find the one I want to find.
Hold on. They do. They have that. All right. Okay. Okay. Okay. Sporkle is cracked. Do I need
an account? Wait, what? Is this for real? Okay. Hold on a second. I have to turn off ad blocker.
Okay. The play that is not cool. This is like, hold on. I guess it is. Play quiz. Hold on.
Hurdle. You should do hurdle. All right. Here's what we're going to do. I'm going to I'm going
to play Kyle is famous. I'm not the stream is going to be not two hours long guys. We'll get
a couple of good ones. But I got to I got to do something. I got it. We'll curate a few.
All right. I'm back. Capture this. There it is. Okay. So this is a choose your own adventure
game where you have to make decisions. You have to make choices. I said I was going to fix the
camera but I didn't. Okay. Here we go. Somebody said they went to McDonald's. They enjoyed the
double cheeseburger and the four piece nuggets that they ordered. So I thought I would follow
German's advice and offer my thanks to the chef. The lady at the register just stared at me like
I had two heads. Oh, come on. This is voice acting is famous. Okay. Sure. Tell me if it's
too loud. Kyle is host of the most popular talk show in recent memory. Stay up late with Kyle.
Okay. What are my choices? Stay up late with Kyle has grown in popularity quickly in the last year
and the public has noticed. Okay. Inside has called Kyle a most excellent dumpy white man.
All right. Cool. Top tech noted that Kyle is inspiring youth to explore stem fields.
Is this AI? Is this randomly generated? Most other talk shows are dedicated to discussing
Kyle and his personal details. This has to be randomly generated, right? Most online videos
are best of clips taken from Kyle's latest broadcast. Okay. The eye of the world is upon
Kyle. Okay. Tonight is Kyle's most important guest interview yet. All right. Stay up late
with Kyle will be featuring Rachel May. She is a kind and lovely. I have to click on this.
She is dear to the hearts of many. This interview requires preparation.
Okay. Wait, what did I miss? No, no, no, we're good. Kyle cracked his eyes open knowing today
is his last chance to prepare for the interview. Okay. So I got a show. I got to prepare for the
interview. I got an interview to do. Let's go. Kyle has 30 hours left. He must choose his actions
wisely. Okay. Okay. First decision in the morning was made wisely wither away or exit the bed. I
mean, we're going to exit the bed. Kyle ex exited his bed and took a quick glance around his bedroom.
Uh scavenge. Kyle quickly crouched down on the floor realizing his immediate need for bugs.
Kyle started to pick between the fuzz of his bedroom carpet hoping to catch a stray beetle or
two. Okay. Soon he had a small handful of various insects dead and alive. I eat them. Kyle threw back
his head and crammed the sticky wriggling mass into his mouth. He felt refreshed. I did that for
five hours. Wait, wait, hold on. There's a system in this game where. All right. I did that for
six hours. All right. Open the closet. It was dark and he could only really see his hanging shirts.
Choose an outfit. Kyle decided to take some time to choose the perfect outfit.
Suit of armor. Kyle was unsure of what exactly to decide to wear his armor, but it felt like the
right thing to do. Okay. After much squeezing and sweating, Kyle managed to wrap the metal suit
around his dumpy self, which would be hard. I get it. I get it. Trust me. All right. So the desk
write notes for the interview. Kyle wrote down his first question. Um, I are you a mother?
Kyle wrote down his second question. You ever eaten a raw whole egg? Sure. Kyle wrote down
his third question. That's your funniest story. Kyle wrote down his last question.
What's your guilty pleasure? Kyle ripped his page of notes out of the notebook and got up
from the desk. Okay. Actually, am I wasting time here? Should I not be doing this? All right. Draw
open the side draw of his desk and grab one of the items stored there. Uh, a key. Kyle grabbed
the small key he kept in his desk. Cool. This is not bakery simulator anymore. No, it's not.
What about use the key? Oh yeah. Get the change to Kyle scooped up the change scattered around.
All right. So let's go back to the room. I did everything. Let's go. Okay. We have to exit.
I only have four hours. I think I have to leave. Check the lock. I walked over to the strange door
in the hallway, but found quickly that the door was walking around eating bugs and sitting in.
It's been 30 hours. I have to leave the apartment. Uh, visit the tech store by batteries with change.
I can do that. Okay. Now what? Kyle hurried to the set. Sitting across from his host chair was a
glamorous woman with an air of genuineness. As Kyle approached her, Rachel looked up and smiled.
Okay. Good evening, Kyle. She said, looking him in the eyes. I've been looking forward to being here.
Last second batteries. That's right. Kyle responded. Um, well, this is the funny like,
this is the funny answer. So we're going to do the regular answer. And I as well. Rachel
answered. Kyle extending his hand and greeting. You are a most welcome guest. Shake hands. After
other mild exchanges of pleasantries, Kyle and Rachel were prompted to take their places for
the broadcast. Okay. The moment after seating, the studio lights brightened and the cameras clicked
on start broadcast. Good evening, everyone. Said Kyle looking at the camera. Welcome back to stay
up late with Kyle. Kyle vomited all of the horrible things he had eaten earlier onto the floor.
Rachel looked at Kyle concerned, gave a couple coughs and decided to play it cool and keep the
show running. Kyle stopped, then vomited again, then continued with a shaky voice. Tonight,
I have the pleasure of interviewing the lovely Rachel may who needs no more introduction.
Kyle motioned to Rachel who smiled and waved at the camera. Hello, Kyle. She said, I'm glad to be
here. Well, you finally fixed your mic a lot to discuss. So we might as well dive right in,
finally said Kyle. All right, let's go. I'm very ready, said Rachel with a winning smile.
I can't just draw. Kyle produced the notes he had taken earlier. All right. You're eating a whole egg.
Hey, Rachel ever eaten a raw egg whole? Asked Kyle. I'm like shell and all. Asked Rachel.
Kyle continued. I had like a lot. It's really bad, though. So sometimes I spit it back up.
You guys want to hear my mouth going like there was a silence. It actually gets easier the more
you do it. Continued Kyle without losing momentum. So don't start. I say Rachel chose not to end.
Where the fuck do we end up? Where are we? Where are we? Where are we? Where are we?
I think the story I always remember is the first time I tried to make dinner for my family.
In the soup I made, I swapped out the water with milk and tipped the whole jar of salt in the pot.
While my family was sick from trying to eat it, I swiped their things and locked myself in my room.
OK. Rachel laughed elegantly. Kyle decided to move on. Kyle asked another question.
What's your guilty pleasure? We all have one. What's your guilty pleasure?
Hold on. Let me do this right. You need to be able to see the microphone.
Then I got to be like this. Ready? Well, that's an easy answer, said Rachel,
dipping pickles in chocolate sauce. It might sound strange, but it's tangy and sweet at the same time.
I eat it far too often. Rachel smiled sweetly.
After reading his final question, Kyle looked up from his paper.
Well, Rachel, he said, I think that's all I was planning on asking you.
If that's the case, Kyle, may I ask you something in return?
Asked Rachel, smiling one more time. Why exactly did you decide to wear a suit of armor today?
Before Kyle could answer, the cameras shut down. The broadcast was over.
Kyle returned home knowing the interview had gone well.
But as he lay in bed and drifted to sleep, he felt that perhaps something was still missing.
Did I lose? He's moving like a TikToker. I'm having fun doing this. Can I do the
I'm doing the voices thing still? Is this still funny to you?
That was the most unfunny bit. That's welcome. Okay, I'm going to do it one more time.
Okay, one more time. That's it. I'm going to get really animated.
Kyle hurried to the set. Sitting across from his host chair was a glamorous woman with an
air of genuineness. As Kyle approached her, Rachel looked up and smiled.
Good evening, Kyle, she said, looking him in the eyes. I've been looking forward to being here.
Kyle responded. Kyle stretched his arms wide, tilted his neck upwards and was interrupted by
his producer telling him and Rachel that it was time to start the show. Kyle shoved his producer
out of the way, spread his arms wide and began to scream loudly. He began to rotate slowly,
screaming throughout, lightly brushing his hands against the faces of Rachel and his producer.
After several minutes, Kyle was finished. He slowly put his hands to his sides and smiled.
I'm ready, said Kyle. Rachel blinked at Kyle, shrugged and walked over to her seat.
A moment after seating, the studio lights brightened and the cameras clicked on.
Good evening, everyone, said Kyle, looking at the camera. Welcome back to Stay Up Late with Kyle.
Kyle vomited all of the horrible things he had eaten earlier onto the floor.
Rachel looked at Kyle, concerned, gave a couple coughs and decided to play it cool and keep the
show running. Kyle stopped, then vomited again, then continued with a shaky voice.
Tonight, I have the pleasure of interviewing the lovely Rachel May, who needs no more introduction.
Kyle motioned to Rachel, who smiled and waved at the camera.
Hello, Kyle. She said, I'm glad to be here.
Why would sound come out and I don't move my mouth? All right, I'm done. I'm done with this one.
Fuck, I want to play this game, though. I kind of want to. Let me just play it for a minute.
Let me play the game for a minute. It's actually very well done voice acting.
Well, I'm sure we'll have a lot to discuss. So we might as well dive right in, said Kyle.
This is not bakery. No, this is not still bakery simulator. Wait, I'm still like,
voice. Hold on. This is the same person, the same guy that did Gabriel. He did who did the bosses
from ultra kill. Are you shitting me? I told you that fucking guy was talented.
What happened? Why does this look so weird? No, this looks what happened. Oh, there we go.
Okay, I'm going to play. I'm going to play for like 10 minutes. Can I play? Leave me alone.
I'm playing. I'm very ready, said Rachel with a winning smile. Kyle produced the notes he had
taken earlier. Okay, I'm not starting with this. I'm not starting with this. What's your guilty
pleasure? We all have one. What's your guilty pleasure? Oh, well, that's an easy answer,
said Rachel, dipping pickles in chocolate sauce. That's really not that weird. That's really not
that weird. It might sound strange, but it's tangy and sweet at the same time. I eat it far too often.
Rachel smiled sweetly. People put all kinds of weird shit on pickles. Okay,
Kyle asked another question. What's a funny story? You've been involved in a lot of different things,
said Kyle. But what's your funniest story? Well, that's a great question, Kyle, said Rachel.
I think the story I always remember is the first time I tried to make dinner for my family.
Okay. In the soup I made, I swapped out the water with milk and tipped the whole jar of salt in the
pot. Oh, while my family was sick from trying to eat it, I swiped their things and locked myself
in my room. Oh, that's what I missed and I skipped. Rachel laughed elegantly. Kyle decided to move.
Yeah, he moved on. I asked another question. Are you a mother? Rachel, I and many others. Did I do
something wrong? To know, are you a mother, Kyle? Well, being a single woman with a career, she
answered. That's not something that has crossed my mind. Who is this again? Who is this? Who is
this person? Rachel smiled genuinely at Kyle. Re-do the whole game. Oh, right. Very reasonable indeed,
said Kyle. Kyle asked, Hey Rachel, have you ever eaten a raw egg whole? Asked Kyle. Um, like
shell and all? Asked Rachel. Kyle continued. I have, it's bad. I think I spit it back up.
There was a silence. It actually gets easier the more you do it. Yeah, I remember this.
Rachel chose not to answer. After reading. Okay. Well, Rachel. That's how we're planning.
If that's the case, Kyle, may I ask you something in return? Oh, why exactly did you decide to wear
a suit of armor today? Okay. Before Kyle could answer, the camera shut down. Kyle returned.
All right. I screwed the whole thing up. I'm going back. Repeat. Reset. No, no, no, no, no, no, no,
Kyle. No, no, no, no, no, no. I screwed it up. As Kyle approached her, Rachel looked up and smiled.
Okay, here we go. I'm going to wither away. Kyle decided to stay put and wither away. I wasted way
too much time withered successfully and died. Wait, what is it? Kyle is now a ghost. This does not
relieve him of his responsibilities. Oh, okay. All right. So what do I need from here? I'm going
to choose an outfit. Kyle decided to take some time to choose the perfect outfit, knowing how
important appearance is. Kyle miraculously crammed his dumpy body into the suit. The chest pockets
were filled with random knickknacks. Okay. So now I think I'm going to leave. Wait, sit at the desk
and get the batteries, right? Change. Kyle scooped up the change. Get out, get out, get out, get out.
Okay. Move to the kitchen. Open the fridge. Kyle opened the fridge, intending to find something
to eat. Eat crust on the fridge wall. Eat the fridge. How do you eat? You can't eat the fridge.
Can I? No, I would eat condiments. That'll get like all the gross. I didn't brush my teeth yet
out of my mouth. If there's one thing that will cover that up, it's a bottle of ketchup.
Kyle started to grab condiments from the fridge, squirting them into his mouth with both hands.
Okay. Ketchup, horseradish, and mayonnaise entered Kyle's mouth at a rate that soon
overwhelmed his ability to swallow. That actually sounds good. I'm not kidding. Kyle spewed the
excess condiment slurry across the kitchen, covering the furniture and walls. Okay. Kyle
continued until all of the condiments had been emptied. Not to eat by itself, but just put that
on something. That doesn't sound like a bad combo. All right. I got 10 hours. Check the pantry. Kyle
wanted to access the pantry, but found it was locked with a small keyhole. Mayo, horseradish,
and ketchup. That's probably... Horseradish is delicious with anything, and ketchup and mayonnaise
is just Thousand Island dressing. So it's just Thousand Island with a little bit of kick to it.
What's the problem with that? All right. The key is for the pantry, but Thousand Island sucks.
Big Mac sauce. Yeah. Kyle wanted to... All right. Yeah, I can't. All right. So let's go back to the
hallway. I only have a few... You gotta get out of the house immediately. Oh, I can haunt.
Kyle felt a sudden pull on his heart. Had he abandoned his job as a ghost? Was he fulfilling
his spooky, ethereal role that he'd accepted while lying in bed this morning? Kyle realized he had
no other choice. He must spend his day spooking about. Okay. Kyle decided he should make a plan
about who or where he should spook. At the interview. Kyle thought that it would be best
to continue his daily course. That makes sense. But with a twist. Today, he would still go to
his studio, but instead of conducting an interview, he would haunt. Thousand Island is incredible.
Yeah. What are you guys talking... Thousand Island is good on lots of stuff. Excitedly,
Kyle made his way to the studio early to find the best spot to conduct his ghostly duties.
I don't love Thousand Island dressing, but I don't hate it. The studio was empty.
Being so early, the crew wouldn't arrive for several hours. Okay. Kyle gleefully skipped
around the building, finding the best spot for himself to hide. Okay. After searching for some
time, Kyle decided to hide behind the guest chair. Okay. Rubens, yep. Kyle quickly placed himself
down and drew his legs to his chest. Soon, the crew began to arrive and set up for the interview
that night. Invisible to all senses, Kyle went undetected. He watched as cameras were set up,
screens were turned on, and pages were flipped. Within an hour, Rachel walked into the studio.
This is it. Hey, everyone. Said Rachel, smiling kindly. I'm ready to get prepped. Who do I need
to talk to first? Kyle's producer approached her. Thanks for being here, Rachel. You should
really talk to Andrea about makeup first, and then wait for when Kyle arrives. Here I come.
Kyle, knowing he was duping everyone, began to giggle uncontrollably. He's doing a little
bit of trolling. Yeah, I'm doing a little bit of trolling, whatever. It was then that he,
like clockwork, ceased to be a ghost. Why? The studio grew silent. Everyone stared at Kyle,
head down, clutching his legs and giggling at the floor. What is TF? Kyle froze. He had found
himself in a situation he had not encountered before. Kyle started to crawl out of the studio
on all fours, hoping his small form would avoid attracting more attention. Why can I not see that?
Everyone wordlessly watched as Kyle slowly made his way across the stage,
through the production set and out the door. As soon as he was outside the studio,
Kyle broke into an all out sprint. I still have money. Kyle made his way back to his apartment
as quickly as possible. Kyle sat in his kitchen and processed what had happened during his day.
Am I still dead? He vowed that he would never haunt anything again. How many endings are there?
Dude, Kyle is literally me. How we do we got? Oh, we got we have we have the wrestling one.
Should I try the wrestling quiz? I feel like I would do pretty good on it. All right, let me get
it. I'll try I'll try it. I can't promise that I'm going to do well. But I think I'll get probably
half of these. You have a reptilian brain. Okay, sparkle. Let's get it. How do I do this? Tic Tac
trivia. Oh, this is but wait, there's a lot of six letter word in 1980s songs. Okay. Television cakes.
This looks fun. Pick that movie. This looks fun. This is fun, isn't it? Let's pick that movie.
Dude, let's go pick that movie. Hold on. Um, how does it work? Let's pick that movie. Can you pick
the movie that fits each clue? Alright, I'm excited. Alright, hold on. Let me get this set up.
The movie quiz. Okay. How do I where is it? Let me close this. So that 100 people left. That's
all right. It's fine. Where the fuck is this window? I have so much trouble capturing windows
on stream. It never seems to work the way that I want it to. Where is it? I can see it in my
preview, but I can't hold on. Okay, it should be there. Come on. I want to play. It won't show up.
I can see it in the preview, but I can't see it actually on the the window. You're doing your
best. Yeah. Make it work. I'm trying. What do you think I'm doing? There it is. So what the fuck?
OBS, what are you doing? It says it's got it. I don't get it. I'll try it again. Hello, it's my
birthday. Someone help dad. It should I should be pulling this. It's just not. Come on. What the
heck? Hold on. Um, let me see if I can do this. Every time this happens, I have to restart OBS.
And I really don't want to do that. I might have to though, because I think it's frozen.
All right. All right. All right. I, I'll be right back. I physically can't capture this.
Unless I restart OBS. None of you leave. If any of you leave, I'll know. If any of you leave,
I'll know. Don't go anywhere. If any of you leave, I will know. I'll know. There's 20,000 people.
They'd be 20,000 people when I come back. I'll know. I'll be back in 30 seconds. I just have
to turn it off and turn it on again. I'll know. Don't you dare.