I want anybody to see my armpits, so I'm not lifting my arms up.
See my armpits, so I'm not lifting my arms up
Can't breathe without these
Just a little too big
Oh a mailbox
Yay
Whose house is this? This is my house. Let me give it a check. Stay in there. Hello. Can you hear me?
Why don't we give it one more check?
I'm here
That was a voice crack in the first 10 seconds. It's not bad. It's not bad at all
I mean, I kind of feel like a dickhead just by the way that I'm dressed, but you know, whatever
refrigerator
Oh refrigerator
Oh
Stove oh, yes, I love stoves
sink
I can't believe it. How many rooms do I have just one or do I have two? How many do I have?
Oh, it's a nice bathroom
spacious
Comfortable I can utilize this
toilet
Shower and sink. Does this sink work too? What do you think? Should we try it? It does
A workable sink
I feel pretty good
But that that could change really really quickly. I'll look into this one here. Um, take care of me
Don't fuck around
You've got three streams to do this
I'm just gonna go i'm gonna go in the kitchen. Whatever
Why not? Is there anything even in the fridge? I don't even know what's even in here
I see something I like in there wash my hands really quickly
Welcome to the dollhouse though
Got a few things you might need to take care of got a few needs
I just saw somebody said starve him
I want that person timed up for an hour
so what I want to do is I
I want to go
What I want to do is I want to use the bathroom
How am I using my hands
Oh, you know what? I don't even I don't even need to hold it
Well, I want to give it a give the toilet a flush why don't we?
Oh
Whoo. Oh, that was a long one. I think that took a little while. Hey jerry get this thing out of the way
Do I have to wear? Oh this shit the whole time by the way, do I have to wear this the whole time?
I'm like, oh my god fire right now
This helmet this helmet is making me sweat
I like the shower
It's beautiful. That's really what it is and i'm taking this off because I I I don't want it on anymore. I just don't it's too hot
That's just the way it is
So I'm i'm looking what i'm looking for for you to do is i'm looking to take care of me
Take good care of me
Don't like I want to be I want to sleep well eight hours a night
I feel like i'm presenting like i'm I feel like i'm presenting a uh, like an infomercial
Hey, does your toilet does your toilet do this? Does your toilet do this?
Well good because that means it's working
What do I want to do?
This is what happens when you when you're just in this world
What happens is
It's got a really bad migraine that's making I don't want to go that way though. I want to go back in the bathroom
What am I doing? I want to take a jog for what why I don't I don't jog
Okay, i'm gonna go
I didn't even lock the door
I didn't even lock the door. I gotta lock the door. Somebody lock the door. Why am I doing this?
I don't want to fucking go here
There are cars on this road. There are cars on the street. All right, when can I stop doing this?
I'm starting to stink. All right, i'm going back in i'm going back in
I'm going back in i'm not wearing that helmet either
Anybody in here? Hold on. Wait, i'm gonna have to get i'm gonna have to get an electrician to look at that
Oh, I smell awful
I gotta like feel awful, too
Let me wash my hands. That was a fucking big run
All right
We can just chill. I don't have to do anything. I don't have to go anywhere
Oh, this is awful
Can I go? No, why can't I not?
That one I can't I don't know what that one doesn't do anything. Why?
Do
Why am I going outside?
Why am I going outside? What are you doing? Hey, I don't
Wait a fucking second. All right, i'm not going out there yet
I don't want to go out. This is a beautiful day out here
Look at those birds
This is pretty nice. I like this
Look at these flowers
They're beautiful. I smell so bad
Take care of me for god's sake
What about how about another one?
Going back in that was beautiful though
I have sweating through my clothes
And I mean that in like in real life and in fake life
So it makes sense that I would be like this
You'll have a series of choices. I hope you choose wisely
and
When you have these choices to make
I really hope that
I feel like shit
I hope that when you make these choices that you do them in a way that it can succeed all of us
I think I need to fucking lie down
Um, what was I saying?
I wanted to uh go for a hot jog or something
I feel awful
I'm getting like a bad headache and shit. I'm like really tired
I really just kind of want to like that's probably
There's over here. I think this is a that's a good spot. I sure went
Oh, it was fucking hell. I feel like somebody just punched me in the face like three times
I feel like I just I had this weird vision this weird dream with this like sleep paralysis demons just surrounding me
Ow my knees
What's that? What is this?
Is this a what was a stool?
I don't like that there. That's not where that should be. I don't like that
I don't like it
But i'll tell you what I do like. I like sassy sunglasses
How am I supposed to go to the bathroom in this?
I am
Disgusting someone please help me. Can I please just put me into a bathing scenario?
I am here washing my hands desperately
Let please let me bathe
Put me into a scenario where I can clean my body
trash
Sink
Oh, I need to clean myself. You can't just let me fucking feel like this
Give me a break
Uh, I better I hope that nobody comes over because this is absolutely revolting
What if my mother shows up? Huh? What if what if my mother decides to come in here?
You think you know what she'd say?
She'd be disgusted. She would put her face in the air and she would run away
What if my mother shows up?
What if my mother shows up? All right
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, not with the stool there. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Okay. Okay. I guess I have to go to that from now
Just on the stool now i'm peeing on the stool. We gotta move the stool. I don't want to pee on the stool
Very good, very good. Very good. Very good. I can't even use that. That's supposed to be a place to sit down
That's a place for me to sit and relax
Can I can I take a shower?
Can I just take one? I want to
I want to right now. I would love to take a shower right at this moment. I want to take a shower. Put me in the shower
I'm waiting
I'm waiting to go in the shower
Now I don't want to go to work. I want to go in the shower. You know, I can't go in front of people like this
Shut up, dog
I like mailboxes. I love them
What? Oh, thank god. Are you is it like am I going where I think you are?
Am I going where I think you're going?
Please tell me you're going this way. Are you going this way? Please say yes
Don't make me like take a shit in the toilet for like a second. I haven't even taken shit yet
Whatever, you know, you know what i'm saying? Thank god. Am I going there? I am going there. Thank god
Oh my god, they picked it. Thank goodness
Thank you, thank you. Oh this feels so much better
Hey, look at me look at me
Well, maybe you do right maybe I do sometimes
Sometimes you just gotta let the water hit you right in the face right in the face. There it is
That feels so much better. Oh my goodness
I'm not naked anymore
All right. We're good. We're good. We're fine. We're fine
Oh, I feel so much better. I'm fucking hungry though
If i'm not going to go to work and i'm not going to make money then you got to make me food
Stupid I should have called you stupid. That was mean
I suppose sit over here
Put the hat on
I can't
You make get I want food and I want it
I don't need to go to the fucking bathroom again
Something's going on with this toilet. Something's going on with this toilet. So, okay
All right. The toilet's like pissing at me. The toilet is effectively peeing at me and um
I didn't even sit on it. It's just broken
The toilet's broken
What the fuck? I didn't even I couldn't have a chance to sit on it
Oh my god
I don't know how to turn it off
What the fuck? I didn't even sit on it
Okay, I think it's I think it's clean. I think it's good. No, it's not. No
It's fucking still pissing out
I've used this toilet twice
I don't know what to do about that. All right, i'm going over here
It's just like peed all over me
I was gonna use the bathroom
All right. All right. Bye. Yeah, i'll put your put the clothes on. Okay. Hey, let's put them on
Can I just take the stupid thing out? I hate this thing
What am I gonna do about that? I can't go to the bathroom. I need to eat
Make some decisions
How am I gonna call repair man when I don't have a phone?
I'm gonna have to like scream out the window
I I need a repair man, but I don't have a telephone
Anybody in this neighborhood is a repair man or a repair woman. I could really use your help right now
Fuck you dog
What do you say I have a telephone but if you could show up that would be fantastic
I'm starving
I haven't eaten in two days. I haven't eaten in two days
What the who the zoo's at?
I i'm feeling like faint. I haven't eaten in two days. I feel fucking terrible. Who's at the door?
Hello
um
I yeah, I guess but not really. I didn't I haven't taken a shit in it since i've moved here
Uh, so that's I guess technically
How much is this gonna cost
I I haven't taken I haven't gone to the bathroom by the way. I'm sorry
I looked like this. I was it was it was chosen for me the toilets in here by the way
Yeah
I don't know what's going on. It just started leaking and
I'm really i'm really happy in fact that you live in the neighborhood in fact
You heard me and you were ready to work and you had your work clothes on and you had to buckle with you
That's really really helpful
Yeah, it's just going I don't know what to do
Yeah, it's just spraying water
Yes, it is. I haven't used it. So I don't know what to do about it
I have no idea what you want. This is what i'm supposed to do
Uh, it just cost money
How much money does this cost?
There's so much water over here
What am I doing?
What you I?
Oh my
Look over there. Don't look look
Don't look don't look over here. Don't look over here. In fact, let it get out get out of the room
No, yes
Oh, don't don't
Fuck the toilet fix. I don't know
don't I
I don't want to go in the shower
Okay, just let me go back i'm fine i'm back i'm back ready to go
You motherfuckers, I swear to god i'm fucking starving too
Where did you where did they go? Where is she?
I didn't i'm fucking starving right now and I need food and I need it now
Make it happen
Thank god
Finally some mac and cheese
mac and cheese
Thank god
Finally get to eat some damn food
I guess i'm trying out my finger
Just get some
Okay
Shit give it a minute. I'm not having a good time right now
I didn't want to fucking I wanted to pay the person
I mean for the love of god, I just want to fucking have something
Okay
Do some food and shit and like I would I'd like feel fucking terrible
And I don't fucking care. It's fucking not having a good time. This is good though
I I need something to do mate. Give me something to do
Get this hat off too. It's it's constricting. I don't like it. I don't care. I'm not happy. I can't do that
I'm i'm still stressed
I'm not do
Oh, I can't
I what's on me? What's on me? What is that? Does it break into my fucking apartment break into my house?
Okay, um
I don't hate it
I think it's kind of ugly
and it smells
uh
Okay
It's kind of comfy
I like it, but I
But I don't like it
I don't want to sit on a dirty bed in a dirty fucking place. Okay
I am nothing is i'm not having a good time at all
And I blame you guys
I blame it's your fault that I don't feel good because you have so many opportunities to make me feel better
And you put there's a mattress and like a stool that I piss on that's fantastic. I
Whatever
I don't even fucking care
I don't fucking care at all actually and you guys fucked it up
Does the toilet even work? I don't even know I didn't want to fucking do that stupid shit that you guys did
Okay, well it works
It works so good. It works twice
No, I don't have anything to make them
Fuck off
I don't care
There I made the bed for you
They fucking waived me to live
Who what? Um, who the who are they?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, no, no, no, no, no, no off the bed
I don't want a cookie get i'll get that cookie away from me. I don't want a cookie
fucking weirdos
That's hilarious hilarious. Get away from me. I don't want it. Ah, i'm in here. Don't come in
Give me a weapon
Okay, it's a little funny. It's okay. It's a little bit funny
It's kind of funny
This is actually kind of cool
You're crazy, uh, I didn't that's okay
Oh man
What uh, what are you doing? What are you doing?
What the fuck are you doing?
Um, that's
No, no, no, no, you can't you can't just take whatever you want out of there
You can't just take everything you want. You can't just take whatever you want
Get me something. I could just swing at him
I'm going outside. I'm going outside. I'm not fucking doing this. I mean, you're funny. It was pretty funny, but please leave me alone
Please leave me alone. What did you do to my front door?
I gotta go to work
What did you you motherfuckers broke my front door?
I can't even fix this
I I why am I still holding the balloon?
Why am I holding the balloon still?
I don't want this
Not to go to work. Uh, I don't have to go to work, right?
How much money do I have left?
This is my no, no, no, no, no, no, excuse me. This is my house
I'm like, why am I hiding outside of my own house? I'm hiding. All right
I need to eat out of that peanut butter later. Now. I'm not going to
Get out of that peanut butter
I'm not going to work
I don't want to go to work. I'm not eating out of that peanut butter. I know i'm supposed to but i'm not going to
I'm fucking telling you right now. I'm not eating that peanut butter. All right, i'm going to work fine. Goodbye
Take this and fucking leave whatever you're fucking taking over. I can't wait for me. I'm going to work
You
Thank you, thanks for the ride. I know it was a little weird. I'm sorry. I know I just had a lot of shit going on
And i'm sorry that I may have smelled up your entire car
But it just they're gone already, but whatever. Thank you. I'll see you again whenever I go to work again
Mess
Somebody's gonna have to clean that up
Just want to let everybody make sure everybody's aware of this this peanut butter all over the door handles
Um
And it's actually like actually gross. So i'm gonna have to figure out what to do about that
And this is this is a disaster
great
Cookies everywhere the peanut butter. What did he drink? This is he drank a whole beer in like five seconds
I'm fucking tired. I'm disgusting and I need food
Okay, they're still here
um
What's what's going on in it? That's funny. There's just clowns drinking beer in my house
Yeah, that's that's hilarious. All right down now out get move move move
Out out out
Why are they still here?
I'm too tired for this shit get out
move
What was that?
Because everybody got like shot
This is a mess in here
It's a mess
Am I taking a shower? Am I gonna get in there?
I'm getting in
What are the what they say am I getting in?
Oh, i'm gonna get naked
Okay, getting naked
in the shower
There we are. All right, this is feeling much better
Please don't get the clouds out of here. I think I could like sense them
I can actually sense the clowns inside
And um, somebody's in here. Don't come in. Um, somebody's in here
Somebody's in the bathroom. Don't come in
That's very universal. I know it so I okay
Okay, we're good. Ah fresh but very tired
Very very tired. I just why is it fucking wet peanut butter on every handle?
You're not gonna drink milk out of the jug
You're not gonna drink milk out of the jug like that's just fucking gross
And I don't even know which one of us farted but somebody did somebody farted
All right, please i'm starving and just leave me alone
Take all you okay. This is fantastic
All right, get out of the house out you're out you're out you're out out
Out get out of the house now go go go you let help him, please. I won't even touch him. Just get him out
Next time I want to stick big enough to swing
That's yeah, but I feel good by the way. Thanks for the help. I appreciate it
I think somebody said red andy
It's hot up here
All right, I need to actual like wipe these down this fucking peanut butter everywhere
I'm exhausted and i'm starving
You're gonna have to pick one because I don't know what to do
Let me just wipe the handles he
He like got his hands on the peanut butter and it was just disgusting
I'm so tired. Give me something to fucking play with or something, please
For the love of god
It is filthy in this bathroom this water this dirt
No, i'm not
No, i'm not gonna do that
I'm not gonna make a peanut i'm not making peanut butter and jelly. I'm not he put his hand in that
I'm not gonna eat out of that
He actually put his hands inside the peanut butter and like he ate his with his fingers put his hands back in
So I have to eat it. I've done they want me to eat it. They're eating a peanut butter and jelly sandwich
Let me at least get the peanut butter off the handles
Disaster I gotta take the trash out too eventually. I got a lot of shit. Hold on. I look at all this
This is ridiculous i'm gonna fucking pass out too
I don't want any of this
Drinking my beer
Can I find it
That's his finger that's his thumb
That's a that's a literal thumbprint in here
Like I literally a sitcom audience just laughed over here. I just heard it
That was revolting
damn clowns
I'm so tired
That you have no idea
I need a utensil to do this with at least
Oh shit plastic plastic plastic
Plastic, I don't want to cook this get this out of the way. Why would you cook a peanut butter sandwich?
I'm not cooking
I'm not cooking anything
Who does like a peanut butter sandwich on the stove?
I need this bad, but let's go around the fingerprint. Oh, I can see it
I'm just gonna have a little
I need to I gotta put this somewhere where I can actually use it
Here
What a sad peanut butter and jelly sandwich, but there's no jelly
And a clown put his hand in it
This is good like that
It's really hot in my house. I don't even have air conditioning
I know there's milk in the fridge, but the clown drank that too out of directly out of the jug
He ruined everything he ruined my entire fridge
That motherfucker did what?
This is good
I'm fucking tired
That's bringing me back to life
Thank you
I have to pee bad though
Or I don't know I have to do one or the other
It feels much better
I need to pee
I need to use the bathroom
I didn't even sit down
Why is there already something in here?
I'm not doing that, but I'm not doing that again. I'll pee in it
Okay, I'm not gonna do the other thing
That feels better
I'm so tired
I'm so fucking tired
Um
Nothing in here. I keep waking up to new shit in my house
Really not
today
Everything here that was supposed to be here
Those weirdos were here, but
Great. That's where that goes
What about out here? Oh popcorn. I love popcorn maker
What?
Oh, this is awesome
Popcorn it's a popcorn maker. It creates popcorn out of thin air
Uh the mail too
Why is there food in here somebody like left something in here, um
Okay
This is from the neighbors. I guess well, thank you. Thank you. Wherever you are. I really appreciate it
Thanks for coming and fixing the toilet, too
I know you can hear me because everyone has their windows open and everyone's ready for work
At all times apparently
How much money do I have?
I need money
What are you what are you guys buying you're buying all this shit what am I gonna do with the popcorn maker?
I mean, I like it. I love it. I mean, I I love I love popcorn maker
but um
I mean
What am I gonna do with this?
Did you buy me popcorn kernels, too?
because
I mean, this is cool
Let me plug it in. I don't I this is a disaster in here
It's a fucking mess
I can't do anything
I don't even have popcorn kernels
I'm putting it up here
Maybe i'll use it. Maybe i'll use it later
I can't even go anywhere
I don't I don't like this living situation at all. I don't like the bed being here. I don't like the you know what?
This is disgusting. I don't know where this is. I don't know where this is from. I don't know where this with what this has been
But I don't want it in my house
I'm sorry, i'm just gonna be honest
time for work
I'm coming. Hold on a second. I gotta test my doorbell. All right. All right. I'm gonna be late. Okay. Okay
Tough day at work
See you at the party on saturday. Did I really want to invite everybody in that car? Probably not
Oh
They still out my why are they still here
Did I leave that leave my phone in the car?
What if I did though? What if I never could make a phone call for the rest of my life?
What if I can't make a phone call for the rest of my entire life?
Right, like I have to go to the fucking phone store. I gotta get a new phone
I have to like call and redo everybody's numbers and stuff. I just I don't want to do that
Give me this you won't fucking
We
No
Can you guys buy a lock for the door?
I'm not answering the door
I'm literally not I just I don't have to answer the door
I'm not answering
They can stay out there. I'm not gonna let them into the house because like I saw I don't want another finger in my peanut bar
These are good
I'm not letting them in unless I would have it last time
Come on. It's really
Oh god damn it
You can't come in here you can't come in here you can't come in here
I don't know how they got in
Why are they allowed in the house?
What happened what happened?
What happened what happened somebody's touching my face somebody's on me somebody's on me
I'm not gonna eat a piece of pizza with whipped cream on it. Okay, get the fuck out of here
I'm not gonna eat that. I'm not gonna eat
I'm not gonna eat this. I don't know what this is. I don't know what this is. It's like a kid's school project
No, get away from me
I don't even know what what they're doing here
I don't know why they're even in here
Why don't I have permanent clowns take this back? Okay. I don't know what you have but
I can't I can't see
I can't see I need help with something, please
No, no, I'm not taking a shower. I'm hiding
Are they gone?
Oh, no one gave it away
I gotta find a fuse box. I gotta find a fuse box. Oh my face
The fuse box is back here
Close the door
Close the door. It's over here somewhere
I think I found it
God damn it. Where is it? It's back here in this little cubby hole
Ow, ow, ow, ow my fingers
Oh shit that hurt
Oh my hand
All right. How do I get back into the house?
My hands. All right out out out your power's back on get out out out of the house
Out of the house out of the house out of the house now out of the house right now
Now don't come back and you're not invited to the party. Oh god
Don't come back
I burnt the shit out of my hand going back there by the way. I'm so tired
I so i'm exhausted. I can't i'm not gonna you want to play outside great
It is soaking wet out here
Uh
Disgusting i'm playing outside apparently
Why do I think that's playing?
Christmas time
I love Christmas
This is you got to choose sleep sometimes guys because this is how you fuck me up for the rest of the week
Ah pee
Oh
This is ridiculous
I've only lived here for like fucking four days
it's like a
throw a party
Oh, hey, haha, make sure the doorbell works i'm not even gonna do it so what happened the popcorn machine
What's new?
Oh
phone telephone
I can make telephone calls. I don't have to scream out my window
I messed up something over here
I ripped up some tiles. How does it work?
Hello
I don't know how
How's the phone?
Hello. Yes, this is uh control speaking
Hello, yes, this is control speaking. How is the spaceship doing?
I don't I don't know I don't know how to use that
Wait call
Oh, I gotta piss see how mom's doing. Hey, ma
Hey, hey, it's just it's it's jerma. Well, you know, it's jeremy ma
Well, you know me as jeremy, of course mom. Yeah, i'm doing okay
I'm doing fine. Yeah, I just um, I just moved in
Been here for four or five days or so
It's been great. It's really good to hear your voice, too
I'm sorry. I kind of like disappeared
Yeah, I haven't had no way to communicate with me at all
Now it's very oh, yeah, it's that's funny. Wait, what did dad do? Are you kidding me?
No, it's good. I just wish there was more electricity. I have one outlet
Yeah, I've never heard of a house before that had one outlet
But you know this plumbing it works. It's comfy. It's cozy
Mom, I uh, it's been really good to hear your voice, but I definitely have to go
Uh, i've got to go. I've got to get off the phone and
Yes. Yes. I've got to go
I've got to go. I've got to get off the phone
I've got to get off the phone if we're going i'm i'm i'm going to go pee with you on the phone and i'm gonna hang
Up after goodbye mom. It's not just gonna see you
I ain't gonna i'm not gonna piss or like shit on the phone with my mother. I'm sorry like I
You picked it too late
There you are. Not gonna happen
Ah, it feels pretty good. That was a good call though. Good. It's good to talk to my mom
Ah
It feels good now
Life is good. I feel good
I feel like I look good
Too much stuff though. I just I wish I could just get rid of this stuff
Do you see what happened over here?
This is this is a slice of pizza here with like whipped cream on it. I don't want that
I want to get rid of it
I don't want that i'm in my house anymore
Time to go to work
Let's go
Be there in a sec time to make some money
Bye bye, thank you for the ride again
Tired hungry all the above all of the above ridiculous
That was a rough day at work, too
But I made some money, you know, and that's the good thing
That feels better
Oh my goodness, I feel like a thousand dollars more than I did earlier
Oh, thank god. I'll have some of this
If I can even get it in
It doesn't do anything. You know what? I'm gonna have some cereal
Cereal sounds good to me
Am I peeing?
What am I peeing? What happened? Why was I just peeing? Oh, it was a sizzle
I was like, why am I pissing?
All right
I think wait should I shower i'm not done
Uh, I'm not I can't take a shower with the food
All right. All right, maybe I can
Oh
Oh, it's getting all in there. It's getting off soggy. It's not getting soggy
That was like ketogryphs
I just realized that
All right, it's getting soggy
Oh, but killing two birds with one stone though. This is good
Ah
Starting to feel better life's coming back life is coming back into me
Oh
Ah, just tired
unhappy
What what's in the mail?
What I got a piece of mail
What's it say?
$500
an inheritance
$750 I misread it in my glasses
$750 from dear uncle Ted
No way what an inheritance
What did he leave me?
His white set
Was that rain?
That's a huge deal
All right
That's money
That's big money that man. I I was I was sad before but that's another 750 dollars
How much money do I have my bank now?
How much money have I got?
I got do I have more than 500 bucks?
Like a 1200 bucks
Holy shit. This floor is filthy
Oh
Hello, ma. Yeah. Yeah, I heard I know I heard about uncle ted
Yeah
Yeah, I know he's he yeah, he sent me some uh, he sent me something. Did he send you anything?
No, yeah, I got 750 dollars in an envelope
It was a check but still
How you doing?
Yeah
Yeah, no, I mean that's it's it's really nice of him. But
All right, what he gave what did he give you?
You got 10 grand
That's awesome
Hell, yeah
That's awesome. Well, that's that's sad. But you know, that's uh, yeah, I got I got money
He said I don't know how how when did he send it?
Why would he send it?
Oh his inheritance. That's right. That's right. That's right. Yeah. Yeah
So it was split up across the whole family
Oh, you there's a house too. Wow, that's very interesting. Yeah. Yeah, I know it's that's that's sad
Well, I mean he he left he left some stuff for everybody. That's it's really cool. It's really nice of him
Yeah
Yeah, you have to have yeah, i'll talk to you soon
Yeah. All right, ma. All right, ma
Yeah
Yeah, we'll figure it out. Yeah. Love you too. That's right. That's what you say. You love you to your mother
You haven't talked to your mother lately say call her and say I love you do it you do it do it tonight
Don't wait mother's important. She's very important right in the bed. Finally the first night. I've actually been able to sleep in the bed
It's been a very long
That was the mattress that I that was the mattress that wasn't me
That was the mattress. It's like the fart stream
It's the fart stream. I gotta get comfy. Hold on
uh
Uh, that was pretty that was not bad for the first time ever being able to sleep on this bed
Uh, I feel a little groggy, but it's okay
I didn't have one of those weird sleep paralysis dreams
Not last night
Huh filthy? I hate it in here. I can't even be in here. I literally cannot even be in this room
What I don't know what happened. Can I at least get rid of some of this stuff?
It's ridiculous. It's that's just
No
I'm cleaning up a little
Just to be able to walk around again
Uh what it looks very broken from what I can tell
Am I gonna can I even go to work?
I don't think I can even go to work if you wanted me to
I'm going i'm going out the window. I'm going out the window. I can't you didn't close the window
I'm going out the window
Yeah, i'm going out
Seeing fucking ace ventura when he's coming out the rhino's ass
Oh
Hey, yay bed bed
I love I love what you've done with the bed. Why does everything have to go to the yard?
You have to put everything in the yard
Any mail today? No. Well, at least I can't i'm not climbing back in so send me to fucking work
Okay, i'm not gonna i'm not climbing. I'm not gonna climb back in the window. I'm going to work
Okay, well i'm not climbing back in
I could sit on it though. I could hang out on it
The side just sunk. Oh, that's what this is for. That's what fell out. That was the very loud noise that I heard
I heard an incredibly loud sound
This bed is fucked. I
I wouldn't i'd rather lie on the dirty one. I'll be honest
What I got mail
What's the mail?
I got a hundred dollars
From dolls rs
for the
The thing I left at the shop that I had a consignment
well
Cool. All right more free money. I'll take free money
Should I go to work too? Send me to work
I can't I i'm not I literally nothing else i'm gonna do out here
I'm not i'm gonna have to use the bathroom too
feeding feeding you money
So you can make the right decision
I don't think I could even put this together if I wanted to
That's the last part of the day if I hear the fire i'm coming over there. I swear to god
Oh, it's just the bottom. All right, then I could no this is the fucking this is a train wreck under
by the way
This is an air mattress
This is not even a bed
Look at what happened under here
What happened under look at this?
Do you see what I have to deal with right now?
This is I can't put this together
I'm gonna sleep on it like that
It's just absolutely destroyed
I don't know if you guys can hear it, but it was seriously it was like
It was like an explosion back here. Like it just fell apart in their hands
work
Oh is it
type of work
I see the car pulling up
Hey
Pick up this guy. You know what I'm saying?
car
They're not are they on the road? I don't even hear them
Oh there
There you are. Don't worry about what you see over here, by the way
Just don't don't drive far enough to see by my driveway
Let's go
Yeah, this is a dick move. No, that was a dick move what you did
Not everybody not everybody thinks that's funny. So I just want to let you know what we'll see at the party on saturday
You're still gonna go
I can't
I gotta pee bad
You know, it's funny. Even if I wanted to move this I wouldn't be able to
I'm not going through the window that hurt even if I wanted to move this it would be hard for one person
I don't know what to do. I need to get in there
What do I do help?
Hey, excuse me. Excuse me. Help me. Excuse me
Ha help. Ah
Right. Oh even like
There's a there's a water fountain over there that I hear I heard a water fountain
Hey, how about hey, hey, I wonder if it flushes
That's so stupid
Oh, i'm not having a good time though
Give me something to play with
It's so much fun
I I don't I wouldn't go back in there, but I just don't want to go in the window
I will this fit over me
No, I don't think so
I could go like this
No
This is kind of fun what i'm doing, but not really
It could it this actually could be a hat but i'm not I somebody just said it could be a toilet seat
It's not going to be that
I i'm not going to use this as a toilet seat
Oh, this is kind of funny hat. This is a funny hat. I like it
This is a funny hat
I can't even block the door. I could very easily just get in there. I could
but
Make food I can't
um
Just see what if I can I eat these these flowers edible?
I don't think I can even tight. Can I at least can I eat one of these?
What happens to my to my uh hunger level if I eat one of these?
Hold on. Let me see
Ow
It's like stung me
All right. What if I take like a bite?
I'll take a big bite
It's not good
I I can't go. All right. I'm climbing the window again
No, I don't want to climb in the window because then I won't get the comfortable bed
No, it's I I got I don't want to get hurt. This is day one
Oh shit
But these have been out here for like five days
Haven't these been out here for like at least five days, right?
Can I actually eat these or is that gonna be bad for like what if I just pretend to
I don't know how long these actually have been here for
Now i've had another bite
Oh, that was really good
I want to just like jump in
What?
What are you doing?
You want me to run run run away
Like now you want me to run away
That that's
I can run down the street. I can't get back inside
That's very obvious. This is a nice house
How am I going to get back in here run away?
I've been walking around the neighborhood for the last like six hours
You know people have come out and just looked at me and been like what the hell is this guy doing out here?
Seems you have chosen to upgrade the house
Uh, and what does that mean?
Uh, that means that that is the end of the tutorial
so
Thank you for playing in our tutorial version of this game. Hopefully it worked out pretty well. I think it did
uh and in
Two days
That is where the real game starts
so
I this was a ton of fun. Let me look at the right camera right here. Here we are. I had a ton of fun
Thanks for watching everybody special huge huge huge scam
Well, I want to say thanks everybody watching we have two more streams of this
And it's going to get even more wild
Uh, I we're literally going to dial it even higher and higher every day
Uh, so i'm keep talking to the wrong cameras. I don't know what's wrong with
We're going to dial it up every day every single day. It's going to get more ridiculous
So we want to make sure that everything worked as intended before we got started
so
I cannot actually get into this house. So i'm not going to even try
uh trial version of full game unlocked
Special huge. Thank you to twitch for partnering with us and a coinbase
Without them this would never have happened and there's way more to see over the next two or three days
So what that means you'll see in the next few days, but we we got everything
What was that?
You paid to end the stream you paid to end the tutorial is what you did
Uh, but yeah, i'm really really happy
I really think that everything worked out pretty well in this kind of tutorial version of the game. So i'm very very excited
I hope you had fun
We got a lot of data
So we got a lot of things that we might have to work on and check out and see how they played out
But uh for the most part, I think it was pretty fun
So we'll see
So we'll see with the upgraded house in a couple of days
With even more wacky wild stuff
Thank you everybody. We'll see in a couple days. Thanks for playing the tutorial
I can't go back in there
Huge shout out to twitch huge shout out to coinbase for letting us do this shit
Huge thanks without them. It's impossible
We'll see full days