Hey, what's going on? How's it going? I am holding back some excitement here. I am so excited
because today I'm gonna be playing Super Mario Sunshine for the first time in my whole life.
I turned 37 this year. I have never pressed jump once. We're gonna do it together
on Super Mario Sunshine. Can't wait. I'll be right back. See you. Okay. Are you guys ready?
Are you ready? Should we watch the opening cutscene? This is back in 2002. The opening
cutscene just kind of plays before you press start and it replays sometimes randomly. That's
how opening cutscenes worked. Take as much time as possible. Take as much time as possible.
You really want me to do that? Wait, the cutscene is five minutes long?
What has there ever been a five-minute Mario cutscene? What is this, Kojima?
Come on. I don't have time for that. I don't want to do any of that other shit. All right. Well,
this is not the cutscene. How do I get the cutscene to play? Are you ready?
Here it is. Adjust the screen a little bit. But here it is.
Are these spoilers? These are spoilers. I'm not gonna look at the screen. I'm not looking at the
screen. I'm just fixing the aspect ratio. That's all I'm doing. There could be something on the
screen right now. I don't know what it is. I'm a little liar. I can obviously see the screen
because I'm moving it. I'm moving with my hand. Don't worry. I can't see the screen.
All right. We wait for the cutscene. Hold on. I'll get this. You gotta get it perfect.
This is the most classic fucking GameCube video game ever. You think I'm gonna have like a fucked
up aspect ratio? Nope. All right. Should I press start or should I wait for the cutscene to play?
Start. Do you want to create a file for this game on the memory card in slot A? Yes. This
actually looks pretty good. I've never played this. It's actually kind of insane. I've never
played this game. All right. A, B. Let's go with B. Start. Oh, here. Oh, yeah. We got the opening
cutscene. Oh, shh. Quiet. Our subtitles, subtitles. Our subtitles. Oh, don't worry. It's gonna be four
different words. It's oh and whoa. Please explain. What the fuck? Oh, shit. They don't just talk in
one word. Like, ooh, they used to do that. Is that Mario talking?
Concerned with the well-being of the princess in this dreadful heat.
Master Mario, if you would, cross over to that shore and find some assistance.
Yes. Mario, be careful. I have a bad feeling about this.
Holy shit. It's so fucking fluid. Holy shit. It's so fluid. How do I get out of the water?
You have to do. It's the most fluid game I've ever played in my life. All right. Let's go.
He's struggling already. They all talk. It looks like this gunk is coming from somewhere below.
It's really slippery. So watch your step. You don't even haven't done something in your whole life
and you've anticipated this moment your entire life. And now that you're doing it, you're like,
fuck. I don't like the anticipation. This is like, I don't want to do this. I want to constantly
never have played this game. All right. Let's go. What about you? What are you waiting for?
Do something. This gooey paint of yours completely covered by friend. Well, come on,
kids. This is paint. What's going on over here? Help. Help. Are you crazy? We're the ones who need
help. Take that water pump and clean the airstrip. You. You. Where's the pump? Like insane? Step on
it. I mean, the pump is right there. Do I have to like turn it? Use the pump? Can I just use it?
Where's my, uh, where's my thing? Even the flood is right there. I thought this was a person. I
thought, okay, I thought that was a person. I thought this was a person. I've never seen this
thing. What it looks like. I thought, I thought this was a duck. I didn't think this. I thought
I'd never seen this thing up close before. This thing talks. I thought it was a fucking backpack
in Smash Brothers. I didn't know what this was. It is the backpack from Smash. Yeah,
but I never see it up close. I just, I get annoyed by it. I've never seen this up close.
You press the R button all the way down. You can stop and shoot. You can then use the control stick
to aim in any direction. Press the X button to switch to the hover nozzle. You can then press
the R button to hover in the air for a short time. If this tank is empty, no water can be sprayed.
To refill tank, enter a body of water and press the R button. Yup. Instructions complete. Proceed.
Mario. All right, we need water. Got it. This is the most fun game I've ever played in my whole
life. I have to clean everything. I'm going to clean every single thing. I can't play this game.
I have to leave. No, I can't. This is Luigi's Mansion 3 all over again. It's never going to
stop, guys. I'm never going to be able to do this. There we go. All right. I can't do it.
I don't think I should play this. Right in the face. This is so cool. Did this win any Academy
Awards or anything? Did it win like game of the year? Sorry, I'm talking kind of loud because I
bulked headphones in for the first time in like three years. I am talking like this a vacuum cleaner
running and I'm sorry, but that's the way it is. Yeah. Ooh, Mario B. Where's the, um, the only song
I know? I don't think that's, I don't like how that thing talks. I mean that, that like Kazooie
motherfucker, like they knew what they were doing with Kazooie. This is Banjo Kazooie with Mario.
Why am I arrested? Court is now in session. As you are no doubt aware, someone has been senselessly
defacing Fair Isle Delphino using some paint like substance. The accused is charged with
moving our beautiful home and yes, endangering our very way of life. Indeed, how can one not be aware
of what is going on? Though it is daytime in Delphino Plaza, our poor residents tremble beneath
the veil of darkness. Expert shine scholars have determined that this darkness has arisen because
all of our guardians, the shine sprites have vanished from their gathering spot at the shine
gate. The reason? It's quite obvious. This horrible graffiti is to blame. Behold the sketch of the
perpetrator based on eyewitness descriptions. The truth is obvious. The guilty party sits among us.
It is none other than Mario. Is that my lawyer? Peach is my lawyer?
This feels fan made. Is this what the real story is?
This appears to be quite a predicament. Malices verifies that the island's inhabitants are indeed
troubled by pollution. Pollution itself is not the main problem. Mario, you witnessed this object at
the airstrip, correct? It is a shine sprite. Shine sprites are the source of power on Isle
Delphino. They used to gather in great numbers at the shine gate, but the graffiti incident
has polluted the island and most of the shine sprites have fled. There is no longer any power
to support the peaceful lifestyle of the islanders. Big Bits came in from Phylactery.
The only way to ensure the return of the shine sprites is to keep the island from becoming any dirtier.
The perpetrator is likely at work even as we speak. Mario are being treated as a criminal.
Tomorrow we must do our best to resolve this situation.
Holy shit. Uh, but Phylactery Lich gave $50. Five thousand bits. Hey,
Jerm, I'm glad to see you playing another cleaning game. Anybody in chat that likes to,
anybody in chat? And I think there's a few people in chat. Thanks for the, just for that one.
Thanks for the five fucking thousand bits, dude.
That's a lot of money. Thanks a lot, dude. Again, dude, every stream, so much money.
Oh, this is it. Yeah. Holy shit. Okay. Where am I going? Clean up the town.
Buy, uh, salsa. Whatever this is. Pepper. Salsa pepper. Hot pepper. Strawberry. Throw it. I'm
overwhelmed. All right. What am I doing? For you. Well, well, well. But isn't you, you have that
tourist map. Did I tell you to press the Z button to view that thing? This is Delfino Plaza.
Delfino airstrip. This is so cute. Click. Delfino Plaza. Delfino airstrip. One. Total one. Okay.
Can I go and zoom in? All right. Tourists get off the ferries here in Isle Delfino's largest city.
Attractions include the Shine Gate and Grand Pinata, Pinata, Pinata statue. Is that, wait,
am I, okay, I might be losing my mind. Pianta. Okay. All right, let's go. I got full water. What
about Toad? Toad, anything to say? Everyone on this aisle loves to do the box breaker.
Just jump up and press L. Just mash. Why don't you give it a try? Mario. Mario. I like the way
that Flood says that. Mario. Ruin it. All right. What am I doing? Cleaning. Well, I'm pleased to
see you're safe, I must tell you. We were walking around town earlier and it seems the area near
the Shine Gate is still quite bright. Perhaps you should check it out, Master Mario. Oh, Mario,
you're okay after all. I just knew you would be. We've got our first cleaning job. First cleaning
gig. Don't hold the R button so hard. How do you do anything? And why is the sky so dark? It's not
sun-drenched. This is hardly my idea of a relaxing vacation, Mario. I'm gonna go home right now.
Oh, I can't do that. Oh, that guy was in the mud. You good? All right. Oh, you have to clean people.
What do you have to say about that? Phew, you saved me. Thanks a bunch. Don't you have to hold
it down to even, yeah, you have to aim. So water kills these guys. This is so fun, just to clean.
Do you get a bonus or anything for cleaning? Yes, I know this is another cleaning game.
Yes, okay, don't worry. We will go back to like the blood and violence and like murdering people
with Axis video games some other day. But this is like we're cleaning houses and shit this week
and the week before and the week before that and cooking and stuff. Whatever. I feel like some people
have gone missing near the Grand Pinata. I'm never gonna say that, right? Thanks, Mario.
You know what I feel like I'm playing right now? Fighting of Isaac. Of course, I don't know why.
Why am I getting that vibe? I don't know why. Can I open your mouth?
Do you want to play something else? Play the rest of the junk? There you go. This is so fun.
How did I not play this ever? How is it even possible that I didn't play this?
Spin the stick. It's Metal Mario. Oh, I already know the spoiler here. Yeah, I already know this.
Go! A kidnapping. Stop the criminal with some water. All right. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. Go! This is fighting of Isaac. Why? Why is it the same game in my brain?
Why don't I just hover? These are useless cups. You want to shoot water while moving. Oh, right.
I'm like cleaning up the whole town. All right, do it. More. Ow, ow, ow, ow. Not fair. Completely
unfair. You shouldn't be allowed to use tools like that. Sorry, I'm sure I saw that person out
on the airship. I'm positive he's responsible for all this casing. Dibs. Alert. Princess Peach of
the Mushroom Kingdom has apparently been kidnapped. Well, that's old news. The suspected kidnapper was
last seen escaping through the Eastern Fruit Market. Yeah, I mean, isn't that where I am?
Let's chase him. Well, I don't know where he is. This is the Fruit Market. He's got a negative IQ.
He went to the... What was it? Did I have to just run straight? I didn't see him. No, I was
looking... I'm so... I'm all over the place today, guys. I'm like looking at all different places.
I was looking down. I was looking at my phone. I'm like all over the place. I wasn't looking at all.
I have no idea. He's heading for the square. Go get him. I was looking at him. The camera was
pointing at him, but I wasn't looking at the camera. I was looking over somewhere else during
that cutscene. Where's my... He's not even looking. I wouldn't even look at the screen. I swear to
God. He escaped into the graffiti. Try spraying it with water. It didn't work. Oh, wait. Bianco
Hills. Episode 1. Road to the Big Windmill. Oh, yeah. It's like paintings from Mario 64, but
they're graffiti in this one. This is probably secrets, dude. There's another link.
All right, let's test the sink, by the way. Jump. Jump. Jump. Jump. Jump. Jump. We good?
All right, let's go. Oh, you're back again, aren't you? You seemed like you were in such a hurry last
time I saw you. It's probably like secrets and shit everywhere. Oh, wait. It's a spring.
Whoa. Hold on. It's a thing that you can walk on. I gotta get that coin. Holy shit, he found the
slide. Can I go down the slide backwards like in all the other Mario games? What do you mean he
found the slide? It's right here. Dude, he found the fucking slide, dude. This is the first thing
you see in the whole game. Dude, you found the slide. Okay, let's keep going. Do you need the
coin? Anybody? There's a trail here that connects to the big windmill. The group made it too dangerous
so the door's been closed. Might be able to get through at the water wheel up ahead. You guys evil?
Oh, just like in the original Super Mario Brothers versus game.
You knock things upside down and you can hit them. You murderer. All right, let's go. Let's go this
way. Blood all over the wall. Oh, it's dirt.
Dude, they come out of there. This game is too violent. It's good. It's good. Don't worry. All
right, what am I missing? People to talk to? Windmills are big spinning things that use wind
power. Water wheels are big spinning things that use water power. And all of them will spin faster
if you give them a good squirting. Hmm, really? What are you saying? If I go like this?
Do that from here? Got it. Oh, can I jump up on that? Plus one coin. Nice.
Oh, that was so cool. All right, let's get that one coin. Use the hover nozzle. Good.
You did it too slow. I'm on the rooftops now, though. All right, what's his name? I don't know,
Ugly Mario, whatever his name is. Ugly Mario went the other way. What's he called in this game?
Evil Mario? What's that? Amorphous Mario? What's his name? No, not Wario. The guy that's like
goo and evil. Dumb Mario. Shadow Mario. There you go. Wait, can I? Oh, look at that. Windmill? Oh,
come on. Really? There's something up there? Who got me something on here? Oh, look. Wait,
there's a big windmill. I'm going this way. Wait. Yeah. Press X. I found a big pole. Nice. Check
this out. Whoa. Oh, wow. Look at all that dirt. What's this? A super coin. You got a super coin.
Collect 10 of them. Collect 10 of them, then visit the Pope House in Delphino Plaza.
Ah, I'm going to just crack my hand. I'm ready. Let's go. Anything else up here? Wait,
there's a water mill. I fucked up. It's okay. I pressed. I tried to do something fancy. It's
all right. Let's do this. Is that not helping at all? Dude, that's so much more efficient. All
right, suck up the water. Now, does it matter that this is salt water or fresh water? Does
that matter? You don't want to use salt water on the plane. What's the average play time of this
game? Anybody know? Was it like 16, 18 hours? It's going to take me a very, very long fucking time.
I can't help it. Same reasons why I had to stop playing Luigi's Mansion. I have to do it.
Look at this. It has to... Oh. All right, let's work on this. It's got to be 100% clean. Does
this hurt you? You're never going to get this clean. Yes, I am. I'm going to get rid of the
dirty melted chocolate ball. It's all right. Teach him spin cleaning. Whoa, what did I just do?
Am I firing a gun? Is that like a cannon? I just pressed A. Is that like a... Oh, it's like a
shotgun. Got myself a moon. Wait, this is not Mario Galaxy. Not Mario Galaxy. Mario...
Mario, it's a weird wild world. No! That was all the way down.
We had a Wink. We actually had a couple. Yeah, Winks are not on sale yet. I didn't tell you the
plan. So plan for Winks are going to go as follows. At some point over the next few days,
it was streaming Mario Sunshine until I pretty much get it done. Then we got community content
night this weekend. I'm going to block off a probably 20 to 30 minute section of community
content night, whether somewhere at the front or somewhere at the end, where I go full cam
and just sit there for 30 fucking straight minutes while Winks are at least 50 to 75% off.
It's the only way that it makes any sense. You're going to fuck up your eye?
You blink every day a trillion times a day or something.
Debs alert. Isle Delfino police are investigating a possible connection between recent graffiti
incidents and the loss of contact with Bianco Hills and Rico Harbor. Right. Okay, so this is
what happens when you have your phone on airplane mode for like a day or two and you don't realize
it and you go, oh fuck, I only turned off airplane mode. You get news stories from like three days
ago. All right, I'm going back in. This is a Mario game, man. You got to do them all. Down
with Petey Piranha. Road to the big windmill and then down with Petey Piranha. Up all the way at
the top of the windmill. Looks like he's got his, he's entrenched.
All right, so how do we go from here? How do we go from here? What was that?
Can I move this log by running? No, I can't.
All right, so we got to get up there, but this is now open because we cleared it.
Okay, I'll see you in about 20 minutes. What if I, okay, so if I press them together, I'd like,
can I like spin? I'm just trying out the technique here. If I spin the analog, do I like,
spin and press R.
Whoa! All right, that kind of worked. Jump, then press R. Dude, you're getting blasted.
I'm, I'll be all right. Spin, then jump. Really?
No, that's cheating. Why's it not working? No, when you clean, okay, when you clean your room or you
clean your bathroom, you don't just hold two cans of Lysol in your hand, hold them both down aerosol
and just spin in a fucking circle and, no, you don't. You get on, you get on like your fucking
hands and knees and you spray and then you, you wipe the grunge off. Mario, danger, danger,
bridges out. Use my hover nozzle to cross the bridge. No, why would he do that when I can just
do this? What if I, I'm running out of water. He's going to ignore me. Look at all the noise.
Is there water up here? You can run while spraying. I know, but I like to, I like to
really get in there. I like to really like get in there and see. Oh, I'm out of water. I know
there's water right here, but is there any up top in the windmill? Oh, almost. All right. This is
freaking me out. I hate this. I need to clean this. I don't, I need to clean this. I thought you said
there was water up here. Is there water up here in the windmill? I don't see any water. Oh, I'm
going to die. I can't die in a Mario game in the first level. Dying to Bianco Hills.
No, I didn't. I'm preventing that, but I'd love to get this fucking other coin. All right. Wait,
hold on. Is this shit over here? I've been with these guys. Wait, what's that?
Somebody over here. How do I reliably jump out of the water? I'm getting them. All right. What's
this guy do? There's a guy over here. Get it. I can't get up there. Okay. Whatever. Sorry. Yeah.
This game is silly. Nothing there right now. All right. Let's, let's go back and do what I was
doing. It's all right. I'm getting distracted. Bring the lily pad. What in the name of fucking
God, it just happens. These spikes. Okay. Well, double jump. I didn't, I didn't even know that
it was going to happen. Let me fill this guy's veins with water. Maybe try using the hover nozzle
here. Look at what I just did. All right. Here we go. Use coins.
Shit. Um, oh, I already have a hover. I forget this is not like a regular Mario game. I can fly.
All right. Right through the middle. Could you help out with the big headed creature up there?
You're the only one we can ask to lend us a hand. I know it's a pain, but you think you can handle
it? Of course I can. Wait. The super coin. The M. Re. The M. Re. Re. Get the M. Re.
Ooh, it is right up there. All right. Boss battle incoming. Three, two, one.
Breaking. The piranha is like a baby, right? It's like a big goofy baby. That's how I see it. I'm
going to be the impression that, that, that like Petey Piranha is a big unruly baby.
Why would water hurt plant? Would it make it stronger? Thinking face. What are you doing?
He is a baby. Stomp on him. All right. I get it. I get it. I get it. I'm going to fill his mouth
when he opens it. Okay. I get it. No, we don't. What is that? Is this going to be present?
All right. Open your mouth. Holy shit. This is actually what you have to do. This is horrible.
Oh, and then, and then step on his belly button. Oh, yeah. Right here. Get it. Get it. This is
that kind of fucked up again. He's actually, he's concerned to do it now. Oh, come on. Come on.
Open to rank three times. That was cool. Oh, that's like all his guts.
How many of those stars are in the game? 120. There's 120. Wow. Something's opening up here.
No, doc. Yes. Alert. This just in. The boathouse west of town has disappeared.
What do you want? Scroll faster. Let's go investigate. Mario, what's going on over here?
This darkness makes me feel gloomy and depressed. It's been this way ever since our shine sprites
went away. This is your fault and you don't even look apologetic. Something about being available.
Open. Shotgun. Oh, that was a collective. Oh, no. Fire. Screamer's ignoring the game death.
What are you talking about? Screamer ignoring game death.
That's not even. Why? It doesn't. You guys are so fucking ridiculous.
All right. Look, we have a new one. Do I want to go in there or do I? Yeah, I want to. What
happened to finishing the old one? I don't even know what you're talking about. I've never fucking
said anything like that before in my entire life. You're making shit up. I don't appreciate things
being made up about me. Cooper blooper breakout. Oh, this looks interesting. What's in there?
Does it have the tiger in there? What do you do with coins in this game? Are they like every
other Mario game besides Odyssey where it was a useless collection for no reason? Besides the
heel? Yeah. All right, Jeremy. Jeremy, what the fuck are you doing? You used to, you got like
three or four, five years ago, six years ago. You used to get like 40 kills in one life as a demo
man. But what are you doing? You can't even like pay attention. Jesus. Or one, two or three.
Wait, this is trash, right? It's like sea trash. And I know it is because it's squid and octopus.
Gross. What's this? Oh, calamari is delicious. It's got a super coin. Hey, I think you're in need
of a pair of my special sun shades. Oh, well then again, maybe you're not ready. You need to spend
a bit more time here on Isle Delfino. Come on back when you think you're ready for a pair.
Is this so I don't look directly into the sun? What's that for? All right, let's go break out the...
What's this? Do I just keep going? Where does this end up? Is there another way I can go up here?
How do I get up that? With the boxes. Luigi, help me. I'm in the sewer. How many times do
you think Luigi got a weird phone call from Mario where he had to... If people talk a lot of shit
about Luigi, I'm included. I talk shit about Luigi all the time, but he's definitely the one
that gets the phone call that's like, Luigi, I'm under some boxes in Delfino Plaza. I'm in the
sewer. And Luigi's just saying, oh my God, I'll be there in five minutes. Are these all covered?
I gotta move all these boxes. How far does this go? What the fuck? All right, move all boxes.
Wait, can I go up here? Luigi, please. Luigi, could you also bring me some cliff bars?
Mario, they don't have them at the 7-Eleven down the street. Oh, well, according to my finder store
near you, it's at the 7-Eleven, eight miles away, Luigi. Thank you. I know you'd be doing it for
your brother. These are terrible voices. Wait, you flip the gate. Can I climb up? No, it's locked.
Mario. Do Mario and Luigi live in the same house? They don't, right? That's never been cleared,
has it? Okay, they do. They do. How big is Mario's bedroom? Luigi's bedroom. Who gets the master
bedroom? Is it Mario? Where does Luigi sleep? How many rooms are in that house? It's even bunk beds.
Do they actually? Luigi has three mansions? No, Luigi got stuck in three places.
Through this gate? Okay, that's cool. That's not Luigi's mansion. That Luigi gets stuck in three
places. That's it. Wait, have I gone in there? Yeah. All right, well, what do you have to say?
Watch out, there's a fucking ghost behind you. He doesn't- he does own them, though.
Oh god, how the fuck do I know this? I played the first, like, 45 minutes of Luigi's Mansion 3.
Oh, you think the area was pointing that way on purpose?
R-r-really? Oh, that's just you being an asshole. Okay. Oh, you can climb up here.
Have we got to go- can I punch through? All right, where's the, uh, the guy- this thing that's trapped?
Over there? Back there? Where's the actual goal here? Luigi wasn't in Mario 64 because he was
trading cryptocurrencies. Okay. No! Wait, Luigi's blocking. Is that such a shortcut?
I remember when my brother and I used to play Mario 64 and he would- I was terrible.
I never got it. I was like, I can't jump on anything. I keep missing everything. Why? I
don't have timing. He's like, he's like, Jeremy, man, just use the shadows. Once you see the shadow
go over the bottom, you know you're in the right place. Thanks. Yeah. And it worked.
And then he, like, gave me a little, like, quick little- just little punch, like, hey,
man, let's- you ready for dinner? Oh, yeah. Mom's making lasagna tonight. What? No way, man.
Race you upstairs. Go, go, go, go, go! No, me first!
All right, what am I doing? I forgot. Smash this.
I have the shortcut to here. Ooh! Isaac! One up. He's going above. Can I make it from here?
Can I climb this? It was hovering me. It was hovering around me in a circle. Guys, this game
is just blinding by me. I don't know what you think we're playing. Wait. Use the hovering nozzle. I
know. It's gonna take a little bit of me getting used to. I just- I've never used it. I've just
first time I've ever played a video game. I don't know. I just- I've never even opened it. First
time ever opened. Back to what I was doing. First video is a sealed copy. It was. This was $480.
Sure, could I have bought a used one for, like, 22 bucks? But I wanted a real one. I wanted to
be able to pretend like it was me opening it the first time. So I opened up the sealed copy and
shit and pretended like I was, you know, like, hey, bro! Look what I got! No way! What is that, man?
Hey, Mario Sunshine! Oh, what? Punching the arm. Dude, me and my friends have been looking for that!
Yeah, you already play? Okay, I'll switch off every life, dude. What are you guys doing?
You want me to toss you all the way across the port? Sorry, but I don't have that kind of power
yet. Think I can throw you? I heard that you can raise the sub by spinning that thing.
How in the world are you supposed to do that? You don't happen to know, do you?
Oh, stand back, everybody. I got it. Super coin. The thing is, the trick is, it doesn't stay.
Oh, fucking Jesus. So much anxiety right now. So nervous! I'm on crack today. I'm gonna be
honest with you. I'm like, I'm like on crack right now. Like, I just, this is crack spring. I already
know it. Oh, fuck. It's gonna get me with the money. Revan! Unfollowed. No, I'm talking about
metaphorical crack. Not the real stuff. Oh, good. Hell, mom. Hey, bro, what's that? Sealed? Oh,
what is it? What's in there, man? Oh, crack. No, bro, no way. We both do it together?
I know we're in the middle of a crisis and all, but do you think you could help scrub off the walls?
You got a minute there. There's no rush. Bro punches arms. Sir, you don't understand. It's
metaphorical crack. Super coin. Dude, mom says we're having crack for dinner, bro. Punches your arm.
Dude, oh, what? No way. I'll race you up there. No, yeah, actually, I will cause I'm gonna get
that crack. There's only so much. All right. Do I grab this? Do I have to pull this out? Oh,
it just ripped its tail off. See that fucking jump? I knew it was coming.
Hand stomp. Check that out. Wait, I got, I already know what to do. Check this out.
Just rip his face off. Here we go. Ready? You stomp his hands. I got this. Squish. Come here.
Get this thing out. Oh, fuck. He's mad. Right in the face. All right, let's go.
Now I gotta pull each individual tendril off. Now pull his eyeballs out. Is this the streamer that
beats Sid the squid in under 10 minutes? Yep, welcome. Thanks for checking out the stream.
Back in like 2014, I did a, I made a video where I killed like 50 people in one life with the
Huntsman, which was, and it was on a map that was huge, like Badlands or something, which was like
almost fucking impossible to use that item. And like people talked about it for years. People
actually talked about it. I see the video pop up in threads. Gotta shine. He's googling his own name.
All right. You want, you want to be honest with you guys. You wouldn't, you wouldn't type in like
germa985. You know how many times over the last 10 years, I've been doing this for 10 years,
sometimes I'm like, oh, I'm curious. Like germa985 sucks. Germa985, bad video. Germa985,
cool. Germa985, it's like Huntsman. You know, you just, I'm like, what are people saying?
Germa985, bad YouTuber. Like, okay, what the, I want, I need to know why.
Germa985, handsome. I'll type that like three times.
No, I'm not even saying that one. Blooper surfing safari. You are your own market research team.
Yeah. I'm the only one that works for my own personal company. I don't have a market research
guy. That's me. I'm just germa985. I stream on Twitch. I don't have like a marketing team.
I, fuck, I wouldn't even looking. What would, can I like leave here and see? I want to see
that cut scene again. I was, I was not even looking at the screen again. I'll find it, whatever.
You know, there sure are some odd folks out there. Paming little bloopers is bizarre enough,
but riding on their backs. I tell you, some folks are just playing Looney.
Got it. Thank God this game is idiot proof. Wait, I have to ride a frog? That's right. I'm the big
daddy of blooper surfing. You like surfing? Hop on a blooper and give it a whirl. Oh, but one thing,
big daddy waives all liability for accidents. Now hang loose, bud. All right. Green, yellow, or pink.
Well, it's going to be a Germa985 color. That's a Germa985 color. That's a Germa985 color. That's
not a Germa985 color. Can I jump? I got it, right? That's it.
Wahoo. You want to go for a ride, bud? Go ahead and jump on the blooper you like best.
Give me some super blooper surfing and win yourself a prize.
I thought I had to jump him. I thought I had to jump him. I thought I had to jump him.
Blacks, I thought I had to jump him. Can I go faster? Yeah, if I hold, I can hold up.
All right. Now that I know that, I can do it again. It's probably just going to be under a minute,
right? Pretty weak, bud. That's not even worth talking about. Come back after you've conquered
the kiddie pool. Wait, I get sent all the way out to the, all the way out here. What? I've got,
I've got some fucking like cup surgery to do here. Hold on a second. Give me a minute.
Why did I even do this? I'm fucking, I'm stupid. Okay. I'm going to paint you a picture here. Just
think about this. Listen to what I have to say. I have a container that's like a coffee container.
So I drank all the coffee out of here. It was like half full, whatever. It was not very much.
Kim and I, Kim and I split this. So I got, I brought another little can of coffee. I like
the cans of coffee. So I was like, oh, when I'm done drinking this, I'll just refill it with the
can. Why would I open up this container to pour this into another container? Why wouldn't I just
drink it out of the can? Just drink it out of like, it's designed to be drank. Yes, there are like
cans and bottles of coffee that you can get them anywhere. You can order them on Amazon. You can
get them special loaded. You get a bit like grocery stores. Guys, you can get like cans of like cold
brew coffee. You're unique. Is there a link? Let me just double check. All right, let's do this again.
It's time to go mess it up. I don't even need to just go fast. Chain squid? No, no, no. Always
green. Pink, pink, pink, pink. Fine, I'll do pink. Oh, you want to go for a ride? Try it again.
Fine, I'll do pink. How about a different speed? That's a lie. I've never heard such a
crock of shit in my life. Somebody said press A. A jumps. Why is pink slower? Press X. Okay,
shit. Press the power button. I'm doing, I'm doing green.
Green is faster. Look at that. Green is actually faster. You're grinding that
blooper's face on the ground. No, come on. Do it. I'm sorry. I have to fucking do it like this.
It's been like this since I was a kid. Well, again. Oh, you're not a kid anymore.
Says you. I took the Toys R Us commercial. Literally. They fucked up a whole generation of us.
I'm never going to grow up. I'm a Toys R Us kid. I don't want to grow up. I'm a Toys R Us kid.
I'll always be a Toys R Us kid. And then that company got fucking liquidated and now
we're all fucked up. Thanks a lot, Toys R Us. That's why I'm okay. I'm going to move on from this.
What is this thing? This is one of my nozzles. The, oh, you cannot use it yet. It's only a hologram.
Doesn't know. It's okay, Jerma. Come to Canada. We still have Toys R Us.
That place was ridiculous. They left. Idiot. They didn't do anything.
All right. What was this thing that I'm doing here? What do we got? Anything new? Guy throws me
onto the boat. Christmas. All right. No, what are you doing, Mario? Why don't you get off? I didn't
say to get off. Wait. Anything down here? All right. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
What does that do, though? Does it slow me down?
Is that, can I hover? Why do we know? Oh, it's if I touch the top. Oh, if I, okay. If I touch the
top, I get, I'm understanding the mechanics of video games now. No, I, I, okay. Anybody else have
this problem in Mario? It's been like this since I was a kid. Since I fucking went to Toys R Us.
When you jump and you make a jump, you have to, you press A again for some reason. You're like,
here's the jump, jump. Nope. No, I didn't want to. I press it twice sometime. Like even after I land.
This is a me problem. Panic jump is great. Yeah. It's like a panic jump because I think my brain
doesn't understand that I'm going to make the jump that I just did. So it's like, wait, you
should do that again. All right. What's going to like dump on this guy? And now where are we going
to go that way? A turn. I don't fall off. Easy. Hey, hey, hey, wait till the next turn. Don't
just panic. All right. You have some brain fluid. I had half of the burrito this morning. Does that
count? It does, right? I can't believe they got rid of the punch. I was just going to call this
Mario cube. I don't know why. Mario cubed. I don't know. I can open this though. This is one of my
nozzles, the gad science hover nozzle. So how do I get it? Oh shit, this is not good. What did I just
get? What does it do? Is it just a refill? Just a refill. Oh, okay. What's your problem? Oh, you made
it all the way here. Hey, by the way, have you spoken to that guy on the roof over there? No,
I haven't. Okay, I just murdered. I guess we died all over again. I have to go from here to
can I get this? How in the world can I get up there? I don't want to do that. Stop doing that.
Stop doing the cool thing. Stop doing the cool thing. I just want to do the regular thing.
I'll get it. Wait. All right. No fucking up this time. Shit. I was too busy
looking at the guy that I killed. Turn Mario. Oh my god, Mario. You got to get a cliff bar in you,
man. By the way, I don't eat those. I'm just saying that for some reason. Any protein bar or meal
replacement bar takes me so long to eat. Please get here. It takes like 40 minutes to eat a fucking
cliff bar. They're so dense and so nutrient packed. When I take a bite of a cliff bar,
I know I'm going to be chewing that thing for at least two to three minutes. Nope. Nope. Nope. What
am I doing? Wait a minute. Oh my god. What's happening? What the fuck was that? Grab that,
Mario. What the fuck is going on? Why wouldn't he? Sorry. Everything's fine. Oh, god damn it.
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know what happened. I'm apparently going this way though
for some reason. Where the fuck am I? Wait. What the? Wait. I'm going backwards. This is the way
I need to go. Guys, I'm a little confused. Okay. I saw the lily pads and I had to jump on them.
I didn't do anything. I just pressed up. I was holding up. What happened? I was just holding up.
What did I do? I don't get it. What happened? I'm holding up right now. Why did I fall off?
Did I touch? Did I grab that guy's leg instead of? What happened? What happened? Holy shit. He's not
pretending. No, not on that. I mean everything else. As a streamer, let me level with you here.
Do you know how fucking horrible it would be to be sitting here and pretending to lose?
That would be so exhausting. Don't you think? That would just be
exhausting. I'm up here right now. I'm going to just jump off and be like, no.
That's exhausting. But I just did it. Listen to your brother right here. I don't need to go
from here up. Can I get up there? Hold on. Can I climb this? I'm just seeing if I can climb it.
Oh, this is tricky. Oh, shit. Okay, I gotta go that way. Oh, fuck. I don't like this place.
Slow. Slow. No need to run that fast. I'm just going to jump into that. That doesn't hit me in
the head. Oh, super coin. I gotta get that coin. I'm freaking out. Look at this too. There's three.
Look at how many coins in here. Don't fall. Manga S. Don't fall. Manga S. Okay, the goal here
is to go that way to get the coin. Slide it up. What's that? What's that thing? That's a tornado?
I don't know if that's a tornado. Okay, I didn't know that thing did. I thought it was going to
blow me up. Oh, it's exhausting. I got to pretend to get up here and fall again.
So just draining me mentally. This place is kind of weird. Oh, shit. Oh, my mic is on.
That's another thing, right? You know, like the hot mic thing. If I was sitting here live to almost
6,000 fucking people right now, why would I ever, under any circumstances, hit the mute button
and think that like, oh, now I can say literally whatever I want and my mic is turned on.
That's so bad. That what? Because you're stupid. Oh, is that why? I can still get it. All right,
I need to refill. Yep. Dude, I actually don't. I hate this part. I hate not well and stuff too.
Yeah. Hot mic. Oh, you hit the mute button and then talk a bunch of shit about everybody.
That's a good idea. Where's that button right here? Press. I mean, I'll say everything that
I've ever wanted to say bad about everything. Oh, hot mic. Oops. Almost like you should prepare
to not say anything stupid when you're hooked up with a microphone on your neck.
Don't fuck this up. Okay. What does it got? The wind guy. I'm just going to run and then run back.
This is a stupid idea. Jesus. There were just three of them. They go away. They go away. Okay,
now get that. Look at this. Two more. Look at this shit. Doesn't do your brother.
Now we walk back up. Do we? Walk back up? Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I can spray
this. That means I can spray this, right? Do a backflip. How do you do a backflip in this one?
How do you do a backflip in Mario Sunshine? Can you? Is there like the same way? Left trigger.
Left trigger is his camera. This dude can do the quick jump on him. Oh shit. Oh shit. Oh shit.
Yeah, crouch jump. That's what I mean. God damn it. I'm going to fucking die. I'm done.
Well, at least I got the points. Whatever. There is no crouch jump. Oh, that's disgusting.
This is exhausting. One of these days I want to like have like a fucking fake audio leak or
something of me. Like I'll record it through like a fucking cell. You know what I mean? Like
I'm calling somebody else. And you just have to be like, hey, yo, what's up? Hey, yo, what's up?
Yeah, I'm seeing what you're doing today. I just got done spraying and it's fucking so annoying,
dude. It was exhausting. I don't know if you have that. I'm just so sick of fucking like pretending
to fall down off shit. And I know you do it too. Like everybody does. We all do it. And I know it
brings some fucking views. But I'm just so sick of it. It's so fucking exhausting. I'm not doing
it anymore. Like I'm just going to do what I want to do on screen. But I think it's probably going
to be like painting, sculpting and shit. I'm just so fucking sick of like pretending to be bad at
video games. It's so annoying. Hey, I'll call back when you get this. By the way, this is the
fourth time with an important message. I know like maybe it's a little weird but
you haven't called back in like four days. Just you know the number. Just coming back, dude.
Chance. Okay. Bye. If you're satisfied with this message, please press one. If you'd like to
neurotically listen to everything you just said to make sure you didn't sound like a total dickhead,
press two. Thank you. Here's what she said. Please psychoanalyze every second of this
conversation you have with nothing. Count the amount of times you say uh. Was it too many?
May as well redo the whole message. Someone just said you're fucked up.
I got all the coins though. So it's worth it. Dude, you're fucked up. I got all the coins though.
So it's worth it. Okay, we're gonna follow the signs now. I got three of those coins.
I'm excited about it. Let's go talk to this guy up here. Hey, it's just like in the movies,
you know the scene where something's on the manhole and they can't get it open.
Oh, this is a shortcut. Oh, over here the whole time. That's good to know.
Get the coins. What is on? What does Android coins get you in this? An extra life? Are there
even any extra lives in this game? They're one-ups. There are. Wait, you get a shine. Wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. What? Didn't I ask if coins were useless in this game and everybody
said yes? Everybody said yes. I was like, dude, are these like useless? They don't do anything.
Five guys, deception and lies. Hey, we found the guy that just turned the stream off.
Now I want a hamburger. They found him. Thanks for making the stream two hours long. Don't
say anything about delicious foods while I'm screaming. That's a rule. I'm gonna put that
in the fucking rules. Don't talk about delicious foods. Otherwise, the stream will end. What kind
of a fucking weirdo would you like what I have to actually be? We have simple rules here, you know,
no bullshit, no like toxicity. Don't be like an asshole. Don't be like a racist dickhead. Don't
like be a bigot. Like really like simple like basic shit that we could all just do. Also,
don't talk about food on my stream or you get banned in the stream ends. Oh, no, just basic,
just stuff that everyone like fucking agrees with. Okay, that was risky, but I did it.
The inverse does work though. Holy shit. What is this? You got the rocket nozzle. Power up with R
and blast off. I thought you weren't watching a vlog. Holy shit. Okay. Do I get? Oh, it's a
permanent. It's a permanent upgrade. Cool. So the red ones are permanent upgrades?
I thought I had to do that. I thought that was an indicator that you had to start. Okay,
look fine. All right. I got to, I got to move. Okay. Fuck you, man. I hate these guys. I don't
like these guys. Right into the hole. Okay. Oh shit. There it is. This is like the mousetrap
board game. It actually kind of is. Good observation. Give that guy a fucking sub somebody.
No, I will. What's his name? You do it. What's his name? Who said it? It's already gone. Who said
a liar? Oh yeah. Oh yeah. A liar. Huh? Okay. I'm a liar. It's me. What would we have? What? No,
we need to, somebody find who that was. They're going to narrow it down. What'd they say?
They said something that what'd they say? They said something. He said it was the mousetrap thing.
Yep. All right. So who should we think about the mousetrap? The secret of Rico tower. What was it?
Somebody's got it open. Who's got it? It was, dude, this is, this level is just like the
mousetrap board game. Laughing my ass off. And it was like, who was it? Okay. This level is just
like mousetrap. We got it? All right. We got it. Okay. I got it. Write that name down. How do you,
how do you give a, all right. Write that name down. I'm going to write that name down over here.
Write that name down. Where are we going now? We're going to the shortcut.
Can you imagine a Mario game that they didn't put this in? Do you think they get like annoyed
that they have to put this in every single Mario game somewhere? Did they ever think about that?
And they're like, oh, we have to, oh, wait, wait, we've done everything we've done so far.
Game's done. Oh, we have to put in the game somewhere or everyone's going to be mad.
Just throw it in here. That's it. Who cares?
It's true. I would be mad. See? Boy, that sun is bright. Yeah, I need the sunglasses. This game
sucks. Shit. Where's my microphone on? I bet you're muted to say that. Hey, what's up? Not
available. Take the call right now. Leave a message and you get a chance. See you later.
Hey, what's up, dude? I'm just calling again. I don't know if you, I guess you didn't get back
to me from my last message, but I'm really getting fucking irritated at the streaming thing.
And specifically, I don't know if you've ever played it before, but for some stupid fucking
reason, people love Mario Sunshine. It's like the worst Mario game. And I'm just playing it
just to appease everybody. Like, I don't even fucking want to play this stupid fucking game.
But I mean, I'm gonna and I have to because I started it. So if you have any tips on like how
to make it like a 60 star thing or something, you played it a while ago. Just give me a call
back whenever. Just call me whenever you feel like it. Preferably like soon. Yeah, you know
the number. Just give me a call. And then tips on how to get to like all the shines as fast as
possible. We know you don't have friends. We know you don't have. Oh, yeah. Write those names down.
They're getting subs. I'm kidding. I'm not going to do that. Where am I going? Where do I go? All
right. A liar. Yes, that was a lie. I'm not going to give like a fucking thousand subs right now.
Should I go up this? What was the goal again? Goal? The secret of Rico's power.
Over there. Wait, get that thing. Helipad. Bagby with German lies.
Holy shit, I can jump on this. Okay, that I was not. That's not a springboard. That's a valve.
That's misleading. All right, let's go. At the top of that. I punch through here.
Oh, shit. How do I? How do I punch through? How do I flip this B?
Oh, I'm going to do shit now. Change this to.
So how do I do it?
Hey, Chad, what's the best Diablo 2 character to start with? Sorceress.
Lightning Sorceress, you'll kill everything instantly. No matter what.
Okay, so we need to go over there, right? I'm going to go this way. Can I make this jump?
Should I jump from there to there? That's not the tower. What is this tower? Over there?
That's a tower. Oh, point. The game music is really loud. Is it? A little bit.
Can I change that? Another shortcut. It's perfect now. The game music is kind of quiet. Can we turn
it up? Imagine if I had a Patreon that had like a $5,000 tier where you like I like flew you out
to come like meet me like they all do. So the reason why I say that is because I was about to
just say $5,000 Patreon tier fly that guy out in like Patreon tier. Like I was making a joke about
that but I had to make that I had to tell you about that first so you know that's not real and
it's a joke. So I gotta make sure I explain that completely before I say it. Kickstarter donations
here. Yeah, that's mine. No, that's fine. I'll take the minus two because I am not going to say
that out loud. Like without giving a huge like stupid explanation for it. No way.
Okay, I like this is like our shop to give that guy a shop.
Hey, that's like a that's a that's a joke. Right. That's easy. Like
$10,000 Kickstarter tier that guy is like that's I can't even make that joke. I'm not going to
make that joke. All right, I'm gonna get to the over there. Oh, look. Well, you did. No, I didn't.
I explained what would happen if I did make the joke. Oh, pull it up. Pull it up. Mario up, up,
up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up. No, no, no panic jump. Fuck. He's like a coin.
There's coin in here too. Wait, why is it what's going on? Oh, I thought that was just a I thought
oh, it's not just a refill. It switches to oh, shit. Okay. I thought it was I thought it was like
just like a oh, that makes sense. Now, it makes sense. It makes sense. I'll go get it. It's fine.
I never hit I've never even hit jump in this game until two hours ago. Come on.
All right. Gonna be fucking exhausting, man. That wasn't good enough. Gotta be like this.
I can't see. All right. Now, let's get the heck out of here. This guy sucks.
I don't even know what his brother's channel is. That's my brother. What's he up to now?
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa. Hey, whoa, we got a big we got a big group of people coming in.
Hey, what's going on, guys? What's up? What's Jeremy up to? Oh, he can't jump.
Oh, I'll handle this. Oh, shoot. Comes in. He's like, hey, punches. Hey, dude. Hey, hey,
let me get the give me the controller for a second. Right, guys? All right. All right, bro.
Hey, take it, man. He does a first try. Hey, just like pats me in the back like yeah, there you go,
buddy. Hey, raid my channel. And I'm like, yeah. I earned this. And that's like the last thing he
hears if I scream and he closes the door. All right. I got it again. Now, just it's simple.
You just have to jump like this. Simple. Wicked easy. It's wicked easy. Oh, come on. I don't have
much water. Yeah. Hey, hey, hey, hey. Where? What do I do from here? Like, okay. You know, like the
oh, he says this is a neighborhood. Slow down, dickhead. Right. I'm not going to hear you.
You even if you scream at a car that's like going by, they're going to hear you scream.
This is what they're going to hear. That's it. Not even it'll be like. All right. What do I go
from here? I'm on the tower. Yeah. So now what? Smash it. Throw in the hole. Oh, the I see what
you're saying. I don't have enough water to do this part. Sorry, just should I do it with oil?
Oh, my God. Don't drink the oil, Mario. All right. All right. I got to focus. No,
no more fucking around with people speeding by my house, driving as fast as they fucking can
dangerously. What an asshole. But like, all right, let's keep going. It's actually kind of hard.
It's actually kind of hard. By the way, I haven't played it. Listen, listen, everyone. Relax,
relax, relax. I know I'm going to freak the fuck out right now, but you have to remember something
very important before everyone starts throwing rocks at me. Listen, I haven't played a fucking
Mario game in 15 years. At least I'm telling you the truth. What is this? Oh, this looks easy.
You got the Rugrats remix.
Where's the biehue? Where's the biehue? There's no biehue in this one.
Holy shit in my fucking diaper.
We're going to be here a while, I think. Can I just walk over it? No, that's a bad idea.
You fucking gotta be kidding me. What? How did I miss that? What? Well, that was just so off,
apparently. The shadow didn't show up. Listen to your fucking mother. God damn it. Itchy fucking
whole body. My whole body's itching. All right, I'm good. I'm sad that there's no biehue. I would
be so much better with the biehue. Thankfully, I can do this as many times as I possibly can do.
Yeah, I can do this an infinite amount of time. That's a lot of greed right there. My god.
Oh my god. Oh, shit. That gets hard at the end. Jumping diagonally over there,
that gets a little tricky. Okay, let's go. Real voice. Real voice. Oh my god. Excuse me. I mean,
hey, what's going on, everybody? I'm a black intruder. Hey. Oh, dear. Oh, boy. Oh, crap.
Wait, they move. They move. That's what's going on. That's the problem. I figured it out. They move.
They're moving. Oh, shit. They're moving back and forth, not just spinning. Oh my goodness. Oh, man.
I have to try a new strategy this time. You know what? Let me tell you. I'm fucking exhausted.
Hey, this is the last message I'm gonna leave, but I'm not exhausted right now. I'm so tired.
I'm just pretending every day.
He just dropped on his own. Shit. I'm telling you, he dropped on his own. Something going on with
like the way the game's emulated on the fucking GameCube 2 Wii. I swear to god. I'm not even mad.
This is fun. This is what happens when you play Mario. Okay, I didn't want to do the weird jump.
Okay, let's just settle down a little bit and like... This is original hardware.
I'm not even angry tilted. I'm like comedy tilted. I'm... This is funny.
It's making me... This is making me laugh, not even making me mad.
All right, if I don't get it right now, then I am gonna give
$40 or $50 towards when me and my friend go to get lunch at that new lunch spot. Like, I'll pay.
Bad greed, but it's all right. Oh my god, I fucked it up. It's okay. No, I didn't. I'm good.
Calm down. Right out. Relax. Oh my god, it's gonna make me fucking puke.
It's gonna make me fucking puke. Where do I go from here? Over? Where? Over there?
That seems so far away. That almost was really bad. Dude, you styled into it.
Friend pays for lunch. Oh, nice. Hey, he's not even watching. Hey dude, yeah, you want to check out
that new lunch spot? Yeah, yeah, we're gonna check that out. Oh, oh my god, that was delicious. Yeah,
thanks for paying. Wait, what? You weren't watching? I beat that like secret level in
Mario Sunshine and I bet that you would be paying, but you bet. Well, that's fucking hilarious, dude,
but you took me here. I'm going back here. Dude, what do you mean dude? This one is the hillside
cave secret. This is another secret level, but Larry, finish the joke. There is no finish the
joke. What are you talking about? The joke is that was a prequel to me calling him five times and
leaving voice messages. What's the punch line? What punch line? It wasn't a joke, was it? I don't
remember. Was I making a joke? Not really. Finally. Oh, I got to hear it. It's been, come on. That's
what I was looking for. It's in the game. It's just recycled audio. There it is. Yeah. All right,
so now we want to go. What's over there? Make a joke or I'm gonna unsub. Write that guy's name
down. He's not, he's not, you think you're going to unsub? Oh, that's funny. Not on my watch. I'll
make sure you stay subbed. What's that guy's name? Write that name down. I subbed that guy forever.
Like I do. So he can't unsub. Should I do the thing? What is it? It's not really that big of a
deal. I mean, I just murdered that motherfucker. Yeah, that's how you do this. All right.
Is that it? How am I not hitting these? Don't jump? Oh shit. I thought you had something.
Give us a wink. I got it. You're going the right way, right? Always listen to your brother. Watch
the shadow. Don't even watch anything else where you're going. Just watch the shadow. So this is
not even correct. Can I still get that from here if I do a big one? Don't jump! That panic jumped
again. See? Everybody knows. Everybody knows what I'm talking about. I was there and I was like,
no, I'm not there. I'm not there. Why does he always stare at the camera with an angry face?
Hey, I'm actually, I'm, I have a criticism of this game. Where's the Yahoo? They took it out.
That's like the most favorite move ever. Do something funny or I'm un-VIPing. Nope.
I make the VIP look. You don't go to like an exclusive club and say to the bouncer,
hey, I'm VIP, but take me off the VIP list. Nope. Okay. The game is out to get me. The
bouncer is going to be like, what the fuck are you doing? All right. Here we go. There's another
secret level. Oh no. It's one of these. They're all like this, huh? Holy shit. This looks horrible.
Actually, this doesn't even look that bad. First try. Where is he? Where is he? Okay.
Oh, this ain't even that bad. It's just weird. Okay. It is kind of bad. Was I going under? I
thought I was going under. That wasn't bad at all. You can make that one harder if you try to jump
on the top of the things. The other one was way more difficult, probably because it's a harder
level. Didn't get the one up yet. That's less important than redoing the mission like three
times. That was like level one or two. So is that it? Are there three per stage? Is it three, four,
five? Oh, red coins of windmill village. Eight. Oh man. Eight shines. You need to do the first
seven. I see. Oh, here's the red coin. They stole this from Yoshi's Island. All right. Where they at?
One, two, three, four. Self plagiarism. Oh, isn't it right there? Any back here?
They stole Mario from Yoshi's Island. See, you get it. Only more people could get it like you.
Sub them. Wait, they're not subbed? Pardon, no. What just happened? What's happened to me?
I'm, oh, I went in looking for this one. Uh, one over, I don't see any. Checking the perimeter.
How about this way? I see one over there. I've never even been over here. What is over here?
Oh, there's a red coin over there. Oh, okay. Oh, it's a blue coin. Two blue coins. Okay,
there's another one right here. Go grandpa, go. Go grandpa, go. Two blue coins? Holy shit.
How many is that? Make it two, 12, 15 coins. I think I need, I need 16 coins and then I can move on
from here. I'm not getting it. Finally. There's the money. There's the money. There's the money.
Five community subs just came in from Radist Raccoon. Do we also have a ton more money
somewhere? Am I making that up? I made it up. Uh, thanks Radist Raccoon for the five community subs.
Welcome guys. We gotta, uh, hope you got one. I think I can think much better when I'm alone.
I used to go to the hillside cave for a good think. Now it's just too scary.
Well, if you had gone in there, you would have got the fucking thing that's worth like
at least 80,000 United States dollars. One of those shines, but I got it. It's mine.
Oh, that's cool.
All right. First impressions of Mario Sunshine. You ready? I'll give you my first impression.
All right. It's been almost two and a half hours. Okay. Um, it was horrible. Okay. This is horrible.
This is, uh, it's, it's very good. It's very good.
I, we'll see. We'll see. I need three more red coins. We'll see. I played,
I played Mario Galaxy when it came out and it was like, wow, this is
that's the last Mario game that I actually like played all the way through. So it's going to be
a question whether or not I think this is better than Mario Galaxy. It's going to take a little
while. It is, it's not, it's not. Well, that's for me to decide. Remember what I say becomes a
fact. That's how it works. Holy shit. I don't know you could do that. Wait, where did that even go?
And remember, you have to have, you have to think one's better than the other.
There is no like, Oh, I just like video games. I like them both. No, no, no, no, no. You have
to say this one's better than that one. Where'd that other coin go? That blue,
where'd that blue coin come out from? What is it? Oh, I got to ring those bells. Give me that water.
Oh, you're going to find the X. Okay. You can't, you can't just like them all. You're a centrist.
That doesn't make any sense because they're all Mario games. No, a true centrist position would
say that I think Mario and Sonic the Hedgehog games are equally as good and there's not one
better than the other. That's me being, that's a centrist. They're both all Mario games. Where
are these last two coins? I got to go home. I need to get a good view. How do you, how do you
switch to camera mode? Where's camera mode? I just, I had it before. How do I do it? Why? Okay.
Well, there's not one over here. I'm going to go that way. I guess.
Hmm. What about over here? Anything over here?
Oh, I thought those were bananas. All in that village. Oh, shit.
This is the X, but where's the, oh, this is the X. Okay. Let's get it.
Now it goes that side. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Sure. I mean, I think it's bullshit,
but whatever. Yeah. Get in there too slow. Yeah. Just do it again. Just do it again. These guys
were just pissing me off. You guys are just pissing me off. You got to go up around quickly.
It's just being annoying. Fucking Binding of Isaac. $50. We had, oh, we had, we had some big
bits and then we had five community subs. Back to back right there. Five subs. Thanks for five subs.
From Jerma sucks. Thank you. And then we also had 5,000 bits. 5,000 bits from Super Guppy.
Thank you. Super Guppy for the $50 fucking dollars.
And your message says, Hey, Jerma, it's been a while since I donated. Just want to tell you
that how much I appreciate everything you do. And I'm going to be missing these streams while I'm
deployed. I was wondering if you had any plans to play the battle for Bikini Bottom
rehydrated whenever that comes out. Yeah. They're remaking this shit, aren't they?
Yes, definitely. What is it going to be on? What is that? What platform is that going to be on?
Everything. Just everything. Okay. If I could do it on PC. Yeah, I'll definitely play it. Is it
going to be on stream? Yeah. Why not? If not, that's cool. Well, we're definitely doing it.
I was going to get it for the old consoles, but why would I do that when I can play the new one?
I appreciate everything you do and all the laughs you've given my girlfriend and I
from the bottom of my heart. Thank you for being you hands down the best streamer and
the only one I watch. It means a fucking lot. I wish you the best of luck. Good luck with
your deployment. Thank you so much for watching. And that means a fucking lot. That's a, that's a
really, really nice fucking thing to say. Thanks for the $50 dude. You're the only streamer I've
watched. That's, well, that's, well, that's really, that's good because like if you, if you watch
anybody else, you'll see how shitty this stream actually is. Don't watch anybody else ever. Don't
ever click on another stream because then you'll see how bad these streams are. I'm kidding. This,
we've got the best of the business here. You know what? You don't, I got to give myself a little
bit of credit where it's due. This is the best in the business right here. Where's this last coin?
Ego maniac. Oh yeah. Ego maniac. I'll be leaving a voicemail on one of my friend's fucking phones
later about that one. You better believe it. Oh, I'm almost out of water, but I don't need that.
Get there. Oh, I got to get that coin. I don't even know what the hell these things do.
I have no idea what these do. All I know is that I want them. I don't even know they do.
They're just blue and that's enough of it.
Hold on. What? Well, isn't that interesting? Cool. All right. I see a blue coin over there.
I don't even need that. Let's do it from here. And there's a last red coin. Oh, isn't that cute?
But it's wrong. I know what that is. Red and Stimpy. Get back. Write that person's name down.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Two stupid dogs. Yeah. Sorry. That's incorrect. Well, it wasn't that cute,
but it was wrong. It was. Fucking idiot. Stupid. Fucking idiot. Fucking idiot. Fucking dumb.
That's fucking idiot. Yeah, I know. I deserve that. I want that. How do I get that from here?
I need a super spring. I don't think I can get it from here. No, I can't get it from here.
Get the stuff. Up. Go up, Mario. Come on. Go up and get the stuff.
I fucking knew that was going to happen, too. Like, I could see it from a mile away. I just...
I'm going to run out of water. He sucks. Stop saying that. Don't fucking say that.
He sucks. He sucks. He sucks. He sucks. He sucks. He sucks. He sucks. Don't fucking say that fucking
thing. Don't fucking say that anymore. All right. I have to focus. I'm not focusing. That's the
problem. What happened there, Mario64? Wannabe. He does hate this game. No, actually, I don't.
I actually really like it. I enjoy the streamer. Is he a cool dude? Up to you. Make that decision.
I can't make it for you. Tag me when he lies. Tag me when he lies. Why? What did I do?
Why? I don't get it. All right. I'm going to... Let's check this thing out.
Petey Piranha strikes back. What does this mean? Petey Piranha strikes back. He's all the way over
here on a little island. This one is awful. Why? Let's take a look. This one sucks.
Okay. Well, let's find out why.
We're here. Other side.
Let's lurk the chocolate off the ground. Yeah, I just think of Willy Wonka whenever I see this
stuff. Where is he? Get a good view. Oh, God. That's not how you work that, Mario. How many
times do you guys have a car door to yourself in your face? Raise your fucking hand. Raise your
hand. I know. I've done it a bunch of times. How many times have you closed your car door
and it hits you right in the chin? It's happened at least once or twice to all of you. I know it
hasn't. It looks like we've got a lot of liars in here. Tag that person when chat lies. Where is he?
Embarrassing. So you're telling me that you've never had like a bag of groceries in your hands
or and like you closed your car door with your hip and you like scraped the top of your head
with the door somehow or like the bottom of the door. You've never done that before. Not even one
time. This doesn't happen every day. It's happened every once like maybe three times in my whole life
but it's definitely happened more than once. How do you do that? Because you're like you use your
like arm elbow and like hip and you like go too hard you've been you hit the back of your head
or the top of your head. It happens. Or like your chin or your neck. Not the top of your head. No,
I know where this is going and I'm gonna stop it right now. I'm talking to... Where's Petey Piranha
too? There? I'm gonna get the rocket. Can I get the rocket for this? Clown car door. Mario. All right,
this is that's too strong. Dude, that's fucking lie. You know what I mean? Like, yeah, I can even
fucking do that. Your brother coming in and doing it for you. I have no idea where he is. You saw it
before? Yeah, but I'm going right away. I'm going up there. We're just going. We're just done.
What am I? How am I dumping my pants? What am I doing?
Oh, let's see. Let's go up here.
Camera. No. Wrong way. Wrong way. Wrong way. Wrong way. Wrong way. Wrong way. Wrong way.
Wrong way. Pleat. Pleat wrong side of the map. What's this? What do you want?
I saw it. It's that big hit of thing from the big windmill. It's back. How do you see this and not me?
Wrong way. Complete wrong way. So I have to go this way? Just go to the sludge. Wrong way.
Wrong way. All right, here's the sludge. Wrong. Wrong? It's not over there. Is it over here?
Wrong. Wrong. Somebody tell this guy's going the wrong way. Go to the cliff. Wrong.
He's on the cliff. I mean, it was surrounded by cliffs. Up there? Is he up there? Is he up there?
He's up there? Is he up there? Wrong. Wrong way. Yes. Yeah. I thought it was like down. All right.
All right. Is he up there? Okay. Oh, well, come on. I zoomed out. I didn't know we were over there.
All right. Now what do I do? Big arc. I'm just jumping on his head.
Well, I know where it is. Let's go. You think when Mario falls out like that and all the toads are
over there, you think he's just like shakes it off? I think he's just like, don't fucking look at me,
man. Did they know that I failed? Like if I fall back out of that like painting on my back,
isn't it like, holy shit, is he all right? Should we like talk to him?
Or is it just like, don't fucking talk to me. I'm going back in. Don't even look over here.
I wonder if it's like that. If it happens like three or four times on the road,
you think that one of the toads eventually would be like, Mario, do you need some help?
Mario, do you want, do you even bring it up? We found the slide. All right. Well, I need the
rocket again. We found the slide. Play wow. Did somebody just write play wow in this? What?
How would I do that? Ever again. Mario, are you all right? This thing doesn't even work. Malfunction.
Okay. I remember. Okay. So of those 6,000 people that are here right now,
how many of you were around for the Kara's an era? Hey, these guys are just dying.
All right. He's coming over here. He's coming over here. Oh, where's he going?
Pick his ass. Why is he just flying around? Shoot him with the. Where is he?
He's supposed to like go terrorize the town. Why do I get more? I need more pigs to fire. Don't I?
Oh shit. He's on the ground. Oh, what the fuck?
You're on the ground permanently. Oh, I got hit by the pig.
All right. Watch out. Get out of the way. If I can just spray him. I don't need a pig.
Oh shit. Spray him. Spray him. Spray him. Spray him. Where the fuck is this guy? Wrong way. Wrong
way. Wrong way. Wrong way. Wrong way. Wrong way. Wrong way. That's right. Blank it wrong. Give me
the controller. Fuck. Take it. Jesus. Take it. You're doing pretty good. All right. Cool. So you're
following his shadow and just aiming straight up. Okay. You missed. You fucking missed. I have to
chase him. Why did you step in the mud? Oh, did you switch? Well, you accidentally switched
to the other one. Why'd you do that? Why are you so bad at this? Have you not hit him yet? Finally.
Jesus. Open. Open. Open. Open. Open. Open. Open. Open. Three. Where's the star? Hey, can I have
the controller back now? Okay. No, no. I give it back. Give me the controller. Just give it to me,
dude. Right here. Let go. Let fucking go of the... Just let it go. I want... Let me play. Let it go.
Let it... Fuck. Come on, dude. Don't... Fine. Fine. Fine. All right. I'm done. I'll just be like...
I'll just get it. Fucking idiot. Your dad's never let you guard down. I got it. Big bro never let
you play. Don't you guys understand the little brother, big brother strategy?
Oh, hey. You can play for an hour and a half straight, big brother. I'm the little brother.
Oh. Can I play? Okay. After the next level. Oh, okay. Do you want something to drink?
Yeah. Actually, grab me a Coke. Sure thing, brother. Get a Coke. Put it down right there.
There it is. And that takes two hands. One, two, open tab. The controller is yours. Hey! What the...
Or just mention going to the bathroom. You know, just make it like really obvious that you just
were in the bathroom. And when people start to think about them being in a bathroom, like, oh,
like, yeah, sorry. I'll be right back. I'm going to go take a piss. A piss. Pee. You're going to pee.
I pee. I have to pee. Pee. Pee is in my body. Pee is in all of our bodies. My kidney produces it
and makes it in my blood. I have to pee. I pee. I have to pee now. And then you come back like,
yeah, yeah, I was back. I just took a big piss. Oh, yeah, yeah. You'll get the controller. Oh,
fuck. I should do that too. The secret of the dirty lake. I'm just doing all Bianco Hills.
I didn't even look. Fucking come on. That was proof that I didn't even look at the screen.
You know what I mean? I don't even know where to go. I know there's a dirty lake here.
Secret of the dirty lake. This doesn't look very dirty to me.
Call me when he gets to the Tinko level. This is a dirty lake. This looks like a dirty lake. This
water is absolutely less clean than the last one. Thank you. Giant arrow signs. This is a dirty lake.
Wait, this one, someone's fucking with me. This sign's pointing back now. It was this lake.
Oh, I want that bling. Holy, I have 25 of these blue coins. I thought I had three.
Wait, why am I getting hurt by the water? Is it too dirty?
It's dirty. I gotta clean this water. Just drink it all. What am I doing? What am I doing?
I'm trying to jump on this fucking guy. I'm dead. I was trying to jump on the guy's head.
I wasn't even looking. There's a wink came in, so I gotta get it. I wasn't looking.
I'm getting out of here. I have zero lives. What happens when you get to zero?
Nothing, right? It's a Mario game. What's this for? I don't know. I'll take them.
Holy shit, that launches you really high. Hold on. Do it again. All right. What do I want to do? Do I want to go clear that thing?
Or do I want to just go back to the other levels? Or what do I want to do? Let's see. What do I feel like doing?
Can I eat? Can you eat these? Let's go back here. I think I only did like one thing here.
Rico Harper. Gooper blooper returns. Do another race. Oh no, this is the other one. This is this
thing. Okay. All right. Gooper blooper. I thought you guys said this guy's name was Sid the squid.
This is bullshit. His name is Gooper blooper. What do you mean no one said that? Why would I have said
that for no reason? I wouldn't just randomly make up the guy's name. Sid the squid. You made it up.
I didn't make it up. I didn't make that up. No, I didn't. I did not make that up. Somebody else did.
All right. There's Sid the squid. Is this part two? Is this another fight?
That was the easiest one. Should I get the rocket? Probably the rocket, right?
I guess not. I can just get up from here. There's a jump right there and now I know it's a fucking jump.
All right, here we go.
You must find a way to fight it. This is the way to fight them. Rip his face off.
Kidding me? Are you kidding me? Oh no, phew. Easiest boss in the game. I'm about to win right now.
Oh, you got to get off. You know how many old game facts reds about this guy exist?
What? I'm having trouble. I can't beat the squid. I don't understand. I pulled the cork out and I'm
spraying him. I don't know what to do. Messed up keyboard typing response. The person's definitely
like 13 and that person knows everything. And it's funny because I do that shit all the time still.
I actually write like that still. If you have a part of the pre-stream chats,
you know that I do that all the time. I mess up half the words I type on a keyboard. I do
incorrect punctuation, wrong capitals. Sometimes I capitalize a word in the middle of a sentence
for no reason. I don't know why. It just like feels right to do that way. I'm going over there.
No, no, I'm doing this one again. Let's see a new area. We've been on the same areas for a while.
I'm just like a weird completionist for no reason. New area. Let me take a look. What?
Does Peach have anything to say? Oh, I'm getting that feeling again. This is not good.
Has something bad happened again? It feels like it. Mario, please check it out for me.
I'm texting you this shit. Hey, Peach almost died from a squid. I've been in the hospital
for three days. I fell off a cliff. What are you talking about? This was made in like 2004.
And wow, unbelievable how a game from 2004 holds up better than a lot of games I've played in the
last, you know, German 2006 streamers. Here's a little experiment for those of you guys watching
right now. One of the last games that I played on this screen that was made after 2011 or 2012.
What was it? How long was it? Jump King? Okay. Sekiro? That was, no. No, are you serious? That's
what the last game I played after 2012. Out of Wilds is probably the last one. When did
Out of Wilds come out? Like 2018, 2019? Red and Evil 2? Out of Wilds? Out of Wilds was like a
few, a couple months ago. Yeah, that's pretty accurate. Rain World? Yeah, I only played Rain
World for like an hour though. This guy has no joke right now. Didn't both? Let's play it more.
I was, we were on Mario Sunshine. Universal Paper Clips? Yeah, that's true. I did beat that game.
I mean, is that a game or is that an experiment? I did the same thing.
Yeah. All right, what's this place? Tell the shit stain story. What the fuck are you talking about?
Dune Buds Sand Castle Secret. Frog Detective? That's true, yeah. We're not only a 2006 streamer,
we're just mostly a 2006 streamer. This place is cool. Oh, what's that? Triangle.
Oh, I don't know where that other triangle is, but it ain't over here. It's gotta be close though,
right? This side? It's probably right over here. No. Variety Influencer? Where's that triangle?
Right there? Where is it? Right up. No, that's an M. You're going out of bounds. Almost 30 of these
coins. How are you? What is that? Holy, what is this giant satellite? It's reflecting into the sun.
Where's that triangle? It has to be close enough to get it before it despawns.
I don't know, whatever. All right, we gotta find that flower that's here.
Holy shit. What is that? Should I be standing on it? Does it like launch me?
It does, but where do I go after that? What's this thing called? Doon Buds Sandcastle Secret.
Are there more than one of these? There is. Oh, well, that would be a Sandcastle Secret.
Oof. This is an oof, I think, coming up. Do they move? Okay. They don't move, so I think we're safe.
Okay. Well, they don't move, but they disappear. Okay. Let's do it.
Let's do it, man. Okay. Let's go. It's not that bad. It's not that bad. It's not bad.
Just gotta go here. Oh, fuck. Oh, my God. All right, we're good. We just gotta...
Who cares about the one up? Nobody does. This is not bad.
Get it? Get it? Get it? Fine. Why don't they have any contests and like conventions?
I can't wait till the first Nintendo con happens, like maybe a year, a few years from now.
There's going to be the, come on stage and do your best.
People are going to get up there and it's going to be awesome. I will be in the front row of that
audience. They'll do like that, like a, like a voice acting competition. Like they do with all
these. I will be in the front row with binoculars. Like I can't wait for this shit.
And if you get first place, you get like a Mario pin. Like, come on guys,
some of these convention runners that make that like a $5,000 prize.
You'll get, people will try as hard as they fucking can. Stop running.
It's got to have a guy, the guy with a mic. You got to like, hold on. Let me get this right.
The guy that has the mic that's like taped to his mouth. It's like this. Hold on. Does it work?
How's this sound? How's that? Is that?
It's not like a carnival. Oh wait, sorry. Now it should be better. Now it should be better.
It's step right up. Step right. Yeah. I had the, I had the megaphone thing on.
I screwed it up. I'm sorry about that. It's like a large number nine.
I'll take a large number nine, please. Uh, yeah. Can I get a, do you guys, you can still have coffee?
And you guys have coffee. It says you serve breakfast all day.
I'm one of those fucking weirdos that comes at like seven 30 looking for all the breakfast items.
Okay. Sure. Just right now. Uh, can you put the ice in it? Can you put some,
can you put some ice in the coffee, please? Nice coffee. Yeah. Light ice though.
Bye bye.
Holy shit. That is what I was going to order. Okay.
Wow. This place is sick. Alert alert. Just look at the top of the tower.
Wait, you can't, you can't even hear what I'm saying.
It's unintelligible. Is it? I can't even, I don't know. I have no idea what it sounds like.
Oh fuck. I wasn't looking again. All right. Some weird thing has curled up on the tower and
taken a nap. This is in danger of the legendary sand bird egg. I gotta get on the uh, the
satellite. Look at this guy.
I'll have you know that if you use the dune bugs wisely, you can reach heights you never could
normally. You know, like the tops of huts and places like that. Am I about to kill this motherfucker
right now? Move out of the way, dude. Oh, I hit the wrong thing out. Again, let's check this out.
You're a sociopath. How do you, no, you can't just, you can't hear me say like, you can't,
okay. I'm not, I can't look at Kylo Ren drive-through impression and that makes me a sociopath.
Hey, look it up. Oh, I love this thing. Look at this guy.
Spray it with water and try to upset the balance. Oh shit. I just upset the balance.
Well, fuck. How do we get rid of him? Um, I gotta get over this way.
Oh, don't fall. Don't fall. I gotta go over here.
I need you over here. Hey, stupid. Hey, stupid. I need you over here. Stomp that. Stomp that.
I just did. Oh, there's the other triangle.
Oh, please. Oh, you upsetting me. What the fuck is happening? I can't jump on him.
Alright, now I gotta get this to tilt over here so I can jump up there. Is that enough?
To go like, yeah, walk with who? Dude, I didn't know that's what this was gonna do.
Alright, now I gotta do that one. I'm almost out of water. Wait, should I go all the way up?
No. Irma, your brain. What? Can I get that from here? Is this his first time? Yeah,
I've never played this. Yeah, it's my first time. Can I get that from here?
He's got an 8-inch brain. What are you talking about? You have to knock them off.
Really knock them off? You have to get the dudes off the mirrors? I thought they were
just helping me. I thought I would... What do you mean I have to get them off the mirror?
That's a lie. I just need them all over here so I can jump. Like this. Ready? Oh my... That's
not correct. Okay, slow down. Spray it in the face with water.
I know what I have to do. I have to get them off the mirrors?
I went too hard. I went too hard. I went too hard. That was too much weight. Alright, let's do it.
Okay.
Nobody tell him. Tell me what? Don't hold that shit for me. Come this way. Get over here. Here we go.
Nice. Smart. Nice. Smart. Play it smart. Play it smart. Play it smart.
I actually... That's... Oh god. Damn it.
So, I have to move this shit out of the way, right? Was I timed out? I don't know. I gotta move this mirror out of the way. It's keeping them... Let's not help them.
Tell us the shit stain story. There is no shit stain story. What are you talking about?
Tell us the... Oh, tell us the shit stain story. Oh sure. Okay, one time I shit my pants.
And didn't get rid of the underwear or something. And then, oh, haha, that's it. What are you talking about? I have no idea what the fuck you're talking about.
How are you?
What is making the...
Oh my hell.
Alright, will you guys relax over here? Come on. I want to get on this.
Come here.
Look, there's a nice hasty Mario over here. Don't you want to come over here?
Alright. See ya. Get the fuck out of here.
Okay. Weren't winks supposed to be discounted? No, not till community content night. I decided to move it.
Where's it going though? Where do I pick that up? Oh, all the way over there.
Fucking wink arrow. Worst arrow.
Alright. So, hold on a second.
I think I know where that is. Across the way. There's another wink there. Like, over here, isn't it?
Where is it? I saw it over here.
There's a knot right there. Alright. How do I get over there faster than that?
Hash V button.
What a good strategy.
You fucking idiot. Do you not see what I'm doing here? Being a weirdo.
Why can you do this?
Yes.
All these basics. If you get it, you do. If you don't, I don't care. I don't care. Ooh, crap.
Can go in the submarine thing?
Alright. So, let me...
Is it a turtle? Is it a turtle?
Okay, is Bowser a turtle or is he a dinosaur? Which one?
Or is he a combination of both? He's a turtle.
He's a koopa. That's right. A made-up animal. So, no, I could say crab. I could say dinosaur.
I could say turtle and it'll all be accurate. Okay. Wiggler ahoy. Full steam ahead.
Koopa is a made-up animal. A koopa.
Fist.
Yeah, I went when Charles Darwin was at the Galapagos. I don't think you remember. I don't remember him riding down Koopa.
Get on. Oh, come on. Get up. Wait. What the fuck did I just do? Something. Oh, I know what to do now.
I'm picking it out on my own.
You gotta launch him.
Flip him. Flip him.
Wow. What was that? Did you hear that crackling?
Ooh, that crunching.
Oh, the crunching's killing me.
Oh.
It's an emulator audio.
That's not a fucking crunchy ass audio.
It's not an emulator. I can show you the disc. It's in there. I'm laying it on a fucking leaf.
Oh,
Jesus Christ.
Come here.
Oh, get this over with so I don't have to do this anymore. It's crushing me.
It's like chewing sand.
This one. This one. This one. This one. This one. This one. Over here.
You're almost...
Stop rubbing your socks on the rug.
Flip him.
Why would he flip?
Am I doing this wrong?
Flip him. All right. Get up there.
Come on. Yeah.
This is the last time.
Last time.
All right.
Why was that so loud? Rubbing your socks on the ground on a dry ass day.
Uh-uh. That's so funny.
What are you doing over here? What are you? A little... A little... Bye, JP.
What? Don't come this way. He wants me to go over here. That's a fucking crab's face.
That is not a turtle's face. That is very much a full... Like the crab has that...
That's a crab face. Might be a turtle animal, but it's a crab face with crab eyes.
I will win that argument every time.
You want me to take you to court? Would you like to go?
The sand bird is born.
Take me to crab court. Would it be crab court or turtle court?
No, it would just be regular claw.
I'm... Okay, here's what's happening right now.
This is something that it's pretty interesting to think about.
I am
triggering an automatic response from a lot of people where they hate hearing somebody sing.
It's an interesting phenomenon.
You hate hearing somebody like sing. It's like, ugh, shut the fuck up. I don't know why it happens to some people.
How do we get in there?
Bounce.
My friend is like that.
Make it!
Okay. Oh, I can go that way.
All right, we're in.
Sing more.
Uh-huh. What the hell is this?
It's like Shadow of the Colossus.
The legendary sand bird is climbing around the tower. Watch your feet.
All right, so what's this? We just get
coins?
Get eight coins. Easy.
He's probably gonna...
All right, I was gonna say...
I got hit by the cloud. You can get hit by clouds.
Don't you pass through clouds?
That's inaccurate. Clouds are not solid.
Ba-da-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba.
STOP. STOP. Somebody stop him.
That took... you know how hard that was to do? That was really hard to do that and get through the whole thing.
All right, where's... I'm becoming a crab level.
All right. Well, I'm just... I'm having fun. Where am I going?
This is where I was...
I wanna try the level again. Do that one more time.
Do that in two tries and you gave up? Well, I didn't give up. I was gonna come back.
Actually, scary face.
I yeah I look like the fucking penguin I look swollen I don't look a little swollen
that's yeah that's that's the I shit myself well here's your all right yeah that here's your uh
like shit stain story I was streaming dude and fucking holy shit can you imagine
playing Mario Sunshine something's in the water today you know I mean I think something's in the
water today what was it what like did I what did I have to eat today what happened today
something's in the water I think I think there's something in there it's the 5g oh yeah they oh
yeah five they did just put 5g in Vegas you're right yeah 5g is in Vegas I think they just turned
it on like today did they all right let's go bird you do the 5g gum joke again no I don't think so
okay let's make this holy fuck the tail I think it'd be horrible hey hey give me that uh I don't
know what it is I have like glass breaking sound right at the end of that it's like yeah it's a
little weird I'll get it right here where's the last one he's turning fuck he's turning
oh my god he's turning he's turning all the way Jesus what god he's flipping upside down
he's flipping upside down is the last coin under on his backside no where is it
I gotta go quickly oh oh okay now tail now where can I jump onto one of the platforms
I'm gonna jump on one of these well let me get them all first let me get the hardest one first
give me the tail give me this one I don't like holding down on the controller I like pressing up
six seven all right now where the hell is this gonna where we go where we going I need to look
no fuck no what I'm trying to grab onto like his like stand on his so I have to while he's
turning I have to jump and then hover and then land on his back to land on a clock can he land
on a cloud the clouds disappear though yeah my plan was to try to stand on the top of his wing
but before I could jump I just started sliding all right let's go sand bird is born apologize to
toad no at this point you get the fuck out of Mario's way you see Mario jumping and flipping
okay if you if you went to a gymnastics competition you know they're at the floor they do the floor
routine are you gonna fucking stand on the floor in front of like where they're where they're going
no why would you do that I have a good idea the person's doing seven flips in a row and
they're doing an insane floor routine I'm gonna stand in their way that's up that's your fault
at that point I got another coin I'm gonna try this is my last uh after this continue I'm gonna
move on to the next place this is like too high next game what what I only have 14 stars why would
I have to I'm not gonna quit Mario Sunshine no I'm not doing that this game was 280 dollars
oh whoops I needed to be on that I fucked it up we're good it's a lie I know it was of course it
was of course it was a lie it was like I don't know 40 30 20 factory sealed imagine buying a
factory sealed original untouched copy of Mario Sunshine and opening it when you can just have
one for like 10 bucks but like 20 bucks or something all right let's do this not the tail
the head all right we're going for the head we're going for the wing we're going for the wing which
ways it can turn go over the head we're going for the head fucking panic jumped again oh I didn't
I had it what the fuck oh it was right there it was like oh god damn it I would like to duct tape my
fucking thumb I want to make my thumb wicked heavy no no reverse I want to have like a bow
flex machine attached to my thumb so I have to like press down to jump and it's this resistance
because then these little like oh tap tap oops no I want I need resistance training I need to have
my thumb weighed fucking up in the air so then you don't do panic jumps anymore god damn it
that was it too all right slow it down slow down dude we're doing the head we're doing the same
place I'm freaking out he's shaking me he's trying to shake me why even jump oh no what
what why why that time did it not work I walked over the first time and I walked over the second
time and he fell off the hover if you fall off you can't hover immediately the hover if the
hover if I fall if I slip the hover I can't turn it on immediately I had it that first time I
it's sand bird jump and hover it no I can't I'm way that my thumb is weighed up right now I can't
do it okay come on uh but I don't what if I go from there do I just stay on them I can't see
that's that's really awkward to do this oh no no no no no I don't like that I'm not doing that
again that was that's really weird and hard to do that shit what do I do from here I have to just
okay it's wind and shit all right I'm done I'm done I did it today where's it we're going
are we going we're going it's over on a tower I'm all right I'm all right I'm all right I'm okay I'm
okay I got it yeah I only died a million times yeah I I don't know I thought it was gonna be on a
cloud all right I just want to see what's in this one I want to see what's in it I also have to I
it's been four hours I have to go pee and get like a water all right we're gonna do that now
we've been taking a break in like four hours uh two pianissimo is sand sprint
the race okay all right let's go to the sick break I'll be back see you in like a couple minutes
sorry guys I fell asleep on the toilet you know how it is okay uh we're going this way
where's my thing what what oh I thought I had to go up oh that's the goal uh okay I thought I had
to go up there and I am too he on tcmo and now we shall race to that flag I'm assuming I can't
use my water only one can triumph by the way the current record is 35 seconds are you at the ready
then set and go I don't even I don't know where where is it I was trying to just cheat but I guess
I can't do that all right how do I die I thought I was gonna just get over there right there
cheating into hell imagine if I hit the flag
fucking crazy all right do that again can I just drown just be faster just to finish
oh what I thought it was a well I went the wrong way just give me the thing so I can get up there
his penance because you said his name wrong what is his name how did I say his name wrong
finish the race I'm gonna I'm going but I can get there from here can I will this be faster
if I went this way why is the game slowing down so I could probably do it that way emulator time
233 yeah yeah I know I've never done it before we want to do complete it immediately
we need a world record all right fine you'll get it right here
all right Pantissimo Pantissimo let's go
well I am Pantissimo and now we shall race all right so race to the finish
how does he get up there how does he get there how do you do it oh you go through here you
sneaky bad oh wait I just hit him oh you sneaky bastard huh that's how you do it 35 seconds
world record all right I get it game over screen how do you beat the world record and lose
yeah that's come on what's up with that
yeah who's world record was that why is he faster than the world record
I do Pantissimo I see it I see it all right all right why
why why it's not no it's funny all right I'll allow this one it's funny
let's go I already forget the whole route I forgot I forget the whole route I forget the entire route
I have no idea where I'm gonna go I have absolutely no idea I have no idea where to go I'm gonna lose
just kidding nobody's done it as fast as me you are pretty good you have some speed
you have grown ever so slightly in my esteem slightly we will meet again and goodbye
the world record is 10.5 seconds actual world record is 10.5 how do you have to do that in 10
seconds now there's an exploit it keeps showing us this the turtle crab ship boat plane that's I
that's accurate that's accurate what I said I don't take that back that's an accurate statement I just
said it all the things it could be but I want to uh one more red coins boring get me out red coins
in the coral reef under water yuck red coins underwater that's a yuck I'll get that though
it's a big swing look at this is another one right there I'm the blue coin master give me the
fucking coin what the fuck that was very odd how does this shit work swing it do I have to like
swing yeah it actually I have to use momentum too much we're good all right red coins the coral
reef red coins in the coral reef where's the coral I'll get those coral reef is behind you
why I'd want to get that blue coin am I gonna neglect it blue coin how would I do that
or another blue coin I gotta get a bunch of these all right coral reef time eight coins right
this is gonna be a real pain in the ass don't sneeze underwater or mario will die what happens
if you sneeze underwater yeah that's bad for anybody not just mario that's just bad in general
if you sneeze underwater you go like you're dead instantly right you breathe you inhale so quickly
and with such force when you sneeze you you instantly die if you sneeze in the water
all right we got another one in here come on give me this
flipping through walls now are we game flipping through fucking reeves
was how was a coral reef reefs or reeves or reefs reefies reefs was reeves reeves coral reefs
coral reeves coral coral kiano reeves give me that fucking thing
yo come here give me that coin why is this thing a sentient it's not a fish it's a coin
coral reeves coral reefs or is it like sheep like coral sheep like a coral reef
could be more than one reef you don't say like sheeps okay two more one more it's a plural of
germa not germans no it's germamites all right that's good flashing yep shine the plural of
germa is jex it is not get on that boat i know now i will because now that's it's that's it
oh there is it's shadow mario after him toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy
boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat oh he still got it this many years later
where'd he go shit i lost him is he behind me i hear him i hear i can hear him where is he
oh where are you i can hear him oh there's a staircase where is this motherfucker i can
hear him got you shine all right so this is fun this is kind of good notice me notice me i did
he's only eaten mince for a week the watermelon festival wow it was a wink the water mouth i
suppose now open why must i stand here i'd rather be drinking a smoothie go get one i just did
what did you brad didn't break anything next time where's my audio my dog just heard your voice and
thought you were in an intruder what does that even mean stop stun lock stun lock stun lock
stun lock stun lock stun lock why is this possible why why am i like a weird tick tock like
watermelons we have that on video now what do i have to judge who has the best watermelon
this one how about it mine's the biggest right i mean right this thing is in the bag man in the
bag well yours is actually the biggest is it who has the biggest what's it for come here what are
you guys doing you just got jumped on by mario you just got jumped on by mario no one's gonna
believe you you guys have no more belief mario did a mario jump on our heads that way what he
wouldn't do that yeah i swear to god dude like bill murray sat down at a table with us and like
screamed fuck you in my face i i and he said even no one was gonna believe me when their whole thing
with like bill murray used to do weird shit and like he would say that you're explaining the joke
was that a joke or is that a thing bill murray did he took a person's french fries and said it
reddit moment did i get it from reddit mine was so much better all right a watermelon festival all
right so just stomp all watermelons and then nobody wins all right what do i do what's the
point of this the watermelon festival is about to end hurry what what means about to end i just
go it just started i have to hold on what do you have to say i think i have the biggest watermelon
right now but what will i do if somebody brings a bigger one we'll just get a bigger watermelon
fine i can do that come on well you fucking idiots didn't think to look one step to your left
you know just roll them roll it over you know like oh no take my watermelon that's mine hey
get away from me get away from me give me that back all right i have to kill all these birds all
right i have a bigger watermelon look what do you think oh you have to have judged all right fine i
was just i was just going over there that was just we had a chili contest and i just walked over to
where all the i didn't drop mine off to the judges yet what i did is i walked up to where everyone
else was and made them try it too oh hey why don't you try some of my chili i know i haven't
been to the judges yet but just want to make sure you understand what's a good chili try a spoon try
a spoonful of this oh no no no that's too small tiny really i guess i'll have to choose one of
those three over there wait what it's right just just take it just take the fucking thing it's
right here see one up there is it the one up there punks thank you appreciate it what the
fuck did i just hit a bee why that bees everywhere now spin do the okay why am i
getting attacked by fucking the beads where's that watermelon i saw up there all right this
thing is huge this thing is so big all right where is it that way you got it oh somebody just broke
it okay well let's go get it again it died off screen why don't you know that that means it's
not actually dead you've ever seen any tv show in your entire life what just happened hey get
away from me stay away from my fucking produce get away from my produce all of you and birds
fuck off no one's touching this shit get away from me we're going a long way i just hit him
all right i knocked him out no no no no don't touch that produce somebody over here stay down
you get the fuck out of here don't touch it get away all right slow slower i thought i hurt
somebody behind me that was such a pain in the ass i don't want to do that again don't mess this
up what do you think i'm trying to not do all right can you take a photo from here guy that
judges it like if i drop it in the water like where's the crane why do i do this by myself
all right let's start the corner now
oh all right here it is i win whoa now that's a big old watermelon like i've never seen
i don't even need to get out the caliper for this one you win
was it to make juice oh nice so i did them all there's no more uh missions in this uh level right
this album don't fall in i was just standing in
in 100 coins i don't think i'm gonna do that i didn't do that in any of the other mario games
ever played i want to let's do this i want to see the other places all right where's the crab
plane boat ship turtle there are two hidden shines that's cool why am i traveling like this
fucking weirdo tomatoes spray water and slide it's an island over here what's this hello you
want to work for me for a little bit i'd love for you to bring me some fruit i'm craving some
coconuts bring me three would you bring me some coconuts wait they all go in i think it is you
just got three here take it two just fell in here get in oh my god mario just throw it in
drop it i can't let it go why can't i just point no no i wanted all right i got it great
subs how many subs we get let me see we'll get 10 community subs 10 from germa sucks thanks a lot
germa sucks thanks for the uh 10 subs more than that you gave like 15 i need help again this is
where i'm gonna do i'm gonna make a dodgeball nes dodgeball nes reference here
go go go go go go go go and you turn and throw it backwards that's actually like one of the best
games that come out on regular nintendo and i don't know why the hell they didn't make it and
like do it again that's one of the most that game is crazy that game is so good why would they not
make that again or do it in another spot but that game was so fun all right let's do the let's get
in here because dodgeball sucks the game dodgeball for regular nintendo is one of the best video
games hold on i was gonna talk really fast slow it down i thought that was a sword i was like
holy shit he has a knife secret hideout must be there okay how do i get there that's how okay
uh henna park mecha bowser appears mecha bowser wait it's a theme park you know i was gonna make
the reference that i could see this like the superman ride of steel ride from here it didn't
this is cool the entrance to the park is just straight over that way you can't miss it you
still did well i was gonna do it a long time ago too bad i should have probably laughed and been
like that guy's way fucking funny i like him i should probably stay here fuck all right okay
okay
hey you what's wrong hello there water what is it saying whoa that's
let's have mo let's have a dip wasaba dip i'm loving it i'm loving it i don't think that's what
it is hello doesn't the sunshine feel lovely oh they're not saying anything i think it's just
oh okay uh i need to get in too this is to get back but i don't want to go back
i want to go and fight mecha bowser what was it you guys saying hit uh while i dive i can
dump and spray slide into a spray spray water then slide you dive into your water you go fast
wait you're talking about like i go like this and then dive into the oh shit that actually
kind of works what the fuck what why can i go this why can i do this that's unfair all right
well we're going what do you have to say wait i just learned my new tech yeah think of all
the shit that just went down mario's pants well he's got overalls on for a reason they're pretty
secure holy shit well uh shadow of the colossus what a spectacle is this a new show of ours
you guys are great whoever hired you needs a raise i love how you played the fearless
hero and he's like a bad version of you but you both look the same and stuff well as director
of this park i want to ensure your success oh how about i provide you with a hero's vehicle
um we're riding the roller coaster bullet bill approaches from behind
all right how do i stop him how do i stop him okay we're good you gotta shoot him in the chest
what the fuck was that all right missile that was the oh okay i need a missile for in there
to press a button in the head i doused the flames oh okay no
okay got him i hope it's only three times oh all right bullet bill approaches from behind
now we'll do it again let's set up for this wink was there this wink shit is the worst thing to
happen to the channel well don't worry because it's going away in a few days i'm taking it off
permanently don't worry get over there got him oh that one hurt oh maybe maybe that'll turn to a
gif hop hey maybe that'll turn to a gif hop to pop up dude you're going viral what no way
hop oh man okay we're good i don't like it i'm like rides that go upside down i don't
fuck i'm amazed you can tell uh mario tell us the flames tell us the flames mario mario quick
tell us the flames did i hit the railing
i don't like rides like this another missile please hurry okay we're gonna
have to spin around one more time no we don't that's it
mama what happened whose kid is this really is what i want to know you know what i mean whose
fucking kid is this bowser has like 12 kids santa isn't real and then he's just wait wait he is
nope bowser's putting christmas presents under the tree you little shit you win the game over i
win each step down a few steps and in corona mount of corona mountain oh shit how do i get
to come around as a princess okay sure a bunch of money just came in right here
10 000 bits a hundred bucks that's a fucking lot of money that's an insane amount of money
from gameplay loading thanks for the 100 bucks and gameplay loading says
that's a shitload that's a nice nice bidding nice bits nice baiting what do you mean baiting
hey i have enjoyed your streams and videos for quite some time now and it it is players and
entertainers like you that make my job as a designer fulfilling game dev in chat actually
even if you only pretended to play the game i work on for 30 seconds a couple years ago
and maybe did a dance from it cheers mate what game is this wait what what game
you pretended to play the game i work on for 30 seconds a couple years ago
and you did a dance what dance i wonder what it is well thank you whoever you are
game dev in chat thank that's a lot of money and i appreciate it i wonder what game it is
doki doki literature club i mean that that is true i did do that for like
10 seconds did i dance after that though i don't know he did a dance wow all right that's
that's pretty crazy thanks a lot again for the hundred fucking bucks oh we got a cargo what do
i do with the cargo do a dance right now why so you can replay this back and it was mario
sunshine the whole time all right where am i gonna go what's what's the deal what's the deal here
did i open anything up gelato beach i did i haven't done the harbor for a while
pachinko pachinko pachinko all right wait wait where's pachinko go to the beam of light oh that's
the sun jeremy that's not what they're describing oh i need sunglasses where's the sunglasses guy
i want to talk uncork the waterfall and i've been kind of i have an unfortunate thing to say
right now i've been kind of hiding the fact that something weird happened not hiding that's the
wrong word uh something kind of strange just happened like 30 minutes ago or so 20 minutes
ago uh my like this is hard to describe i don't know this is new and weird it's kind of freaking
me out uh my like the throat my like the muscle in my back of my tongue and into my throat it hurts
uh this is new like as if i pulled a muscle back there as this is brand new i don't know what's
going on here i don't know why this is happening no no not a sore throat like the muscles in my
actual tongue behind my it's this is weird it was it hurt it was like oh that hurt but i didn't do
anything i didn't say anything i was just sitting there just playing i hadn't even spoken yet it was
very weird no no no it's this is like muscle pain and the reason why it's kind of pissing
me off and freaking me out is because the whole costochondritis thing like i've had pain in my
ribs that just came out of nowhere for no reason and i'm gonna be real mad if now i just have like
muscle pain in my back of my tongue now like you know what i mean like what the fuck
i'm just freaking me out well uh i'm all right but i might have to stop screaming
no it's not like my voice it's not like my vocal cords it's like weird to describe it's kind of
annoying he's making it up to leave no i want to play mario sunshine i want to i've been so much
fun this sucks um i'm gonna monitor it for now but i want to let you guys know what's happening
because uh i might have to stop in a little bit it stays this is very sudden and very new
lay on the floor for a minute he has a muscle cramp in your tongue well the reason why i'm
bringing it up is just because i just got those of you that don't know i just got diagnosed like
three or four months ago with costochondritis which is just like mystery inflammation in your
rib cage for no reason and there's no start there's no stop it's just there so it's just
like eh is this like another thing now that's happening it's pissing me off pissed off right
now pissing me off anyways mario sunshine let's go what was this what was it uncork the waterfall
all right let's go where's the waterfall is it all the way up who are you oh welcome master mario i
presume we have heard much about you yes and all of it good as for me i am just an old man who loves
nothing but fishing but lately i have had a terrible problem please look up there oh well
okay there's a cannon up there i don't know who did it but someone corked our waterfall
this no doubt is why our lovely bay has become polluted stay away from web md no dude i've been
to the doctor like 17 times in the last two years i've had a colonoscopy i've had an upper endoscopy
i've had fucking x-rays of my whole body don't worry it's not like hi i wonder do i have this
we got a pretty clear diagnosis on a couple of things but this is like another thing that
just kind of came out of nowhere for no reason so write it write it down put it on the list
please fulfill this old man's wish cough hack hack pith what's that you'll do it oh that's no
he's talking to chad dude don't go on web md you're gonna be fucked all right let's go from
to be where the guy on the i need to heal first of all i gotta turn off this
wait can i fill this fill it stomp on it let the big brother take the stream over
there we go all right hold on can i press that were they doing an upper endoscopy in
a colonoscopy at the same time trying to meet in the middle everyone just want to see if we can do
it i'm period that's so stupid now we go wheel can i weigh the wheel down
i don't want to run under water i make that i didn't think i could make these puzzles require
huge iq yes they do yes they do god what is this this looks interesting
oh it's a spring grab the edge mario thank you bullshit what's the point of this
i make this what's that i can't even fucking hit the wall and hit the wall and hit the wall
and then bounced off and i couldn't hover really why can i not turn off don't jump on the wall mario
under any circumstances different right now this is one of those circumstances
oh no i already got down why okay there's like a fucking secret right here
one coin that's it what the fuck one coin all right don't fuck that up again please thank you
wasting water oh what is this can i not use this anymore no why is it currently stopped
what oh shit all right hold on let me come here all right let's do it don't fuck it up i fucked it
up almost out of water shit okay now uh we're up there i think so oh fuck you got the rocket nozzle
sure save and continue all right what am i gonna do just straight up well yes because there's all
these coins right here get it best of all there we go all right no is there anything else up i
don't think so i gotta go this way from here oh wait shit i got it what that's so far away now
we had a hundred dollar drop just come in right now a hundred bucks from shady seas
i can't go in this water i can't go in this water i can't go in this water i can't go in this water
thank you shady seas for the 10 000 bits thanks for the huge money drop they say i've been living
with costacron drivers for a long time and it really sucks your streams have helped out a lot
when it's flared up really bad hope you're doing better now and take some time off if you need to
recover yeah i'm all right i'm good it's just it's just irritating so i don't worry i'm doing
physical therapy for this shit um i've been going for the last couple weeks like two or three weeks
but uh that's why you know it's not like it's a concern but this is i really do hope that i just
kind of tweak something randomly for no reason because oh first it was in your back now it's
in your rib cage now it's in your tongue wow hooray life really is pain oh shit made it
it's maybe it's gonna maybe it's working its way out of you maybe it's trying to get out of your
mouth all right let's go up there all the way up let me go all the way up first
this place is crazy you gotta get that big cork make sure you read read read read read
chat read it read chat we need to read read we're gonna rip out that cork all right is that a cork
or is that an onion that's not a waterfall yeah i'm trying to find them i'm trying to look to
see where the waterfall is where is this waterfall over here i don't see any waterfalls i'm staring
at it oh up there right that i thought that was a fucking honeycomb like a beehive or something
all right so just wrap all the way around or should i try should i try to just
just yolo jump this and get up there what do you think let's go
i fell off the edge i didn't even jump i fell all right let's get that big cork what do you want
oh you mario that guy down there is my teacher i mean my grandpa hey that cork is farther up ahead
be careful though there's a weird guy perched on top of it they'll start tossing explosives at you
if you get too close i thought you might need help so i got you this spring sprayed it'll shrink
really oh that's cool it's pretty sick can i just bring it with me okay throw it over there throw
it down i should throw it over there throw it down because if all do i even need this oh fuck
eat shit i know what to do no stop with the three two one i hit him is this not
i don't think i'm hitting this shit i got it
i mean that cork oh thank god did i fall all the way down i jumped over the edge
we're good wait no i think you're blue coin that was cool but what's up there i don't know
that's a good question you want me to do that again and that very clearly was like hey please
do that again all right the boss of tricky ruins after the old man can i talk to the kid
all right what do you want me to do you have returned our waterfall to normal bravo what's
that the ocean's still dirty strange it looks like my theory was way off yo oh hack this that's okay
i think i've got a lead on the real cause now this may not seem like much of a reward but i'm
going to reveal to you one of the noki bay's deepest secrets grandpa i got like 30 of these
this bay actually contains the tomb of an ancient noki king when you spray water on the wall
paintings the path usually opens it's almost like magic and one path leads to a hidden shrine
honestly this is all true maybe
found it it's so fucking loud
i just exploded it your eardrums that was bad for me too that was bad for me too trust me
okay always remember if it's bad for you it's very bad for me too i'm i got a direct line here
you know what i mean oh fuck well you gotta do it fast then huh don't you cover your ears
i'll do it for you what the hell are we going spliced wait what what are you talking about
you're cheating now you're watching speedrun eyes opened up a video
audio splicing i'm not splicing any audio what audio you hear is being spliced not splicing audio
or did it i mean i want that right f squid f squid f squid let's keep going there's another
thing to spray over here yeah f squid you're right now i know what you mean dead dead dead
grandma can i ask a question yeah what is it ask i wasn't ready for that one
shit sorry oh no oh no oh no it's gonna crush me i made it this is the secret
i don't need water is there you got water near you oh water give me that all right spray his face
rip his legs off i got a strategy on this guy it works every time there was a camera doing this
now we gotta wait wait till they all get up come on and go oh he
i thought he was playing off of real hardware uh i am i'm playing off of real hardware it's real
that water be flowers everyone germa lies i don't need to prove this i've already shown it
you guys know it's real you guys know it's real it's real there's no crumbs in the wee
i can't guarantee that i ate a whole lot of weird shit up here and put my hands all over the
controller and stuff back here again all right you got it wipe your hands after you eat i do
you know you can't get rid of that shit red cool is his red coins in a what red coins in a bottle
i got it yes i surely do have it what have i got the answer to our polluted ocean the answer is
you you must go to the ocean floor that's impossible for your own the at the moment
therefore i've made an area for you to own your skills boop bop boop bop beep boop wear this and
you can stay under water for much much longer the flood to move around and get red coins don't
overdo it you run low on air just grab some regular coins to refill okay oh you mean actually
inside of the bottle i thought he was talking about um you go really fast no um excuse me
what are you doing just get them mario oh he's got my head move this way all right now you can
float one in here he's shaking the bottle you know they're like hey you fucking little dickhead
now i've got you oh this is this makes me want to puke too no leave me alone where is it
i just saw it where the fuck is it give me a coin was it gonna play league of legends um
oh yeah yeah um sure in a hundred million years if i still am streaming connected to some
device that can keep me alive in the next hundred million years i'll play it in a hundred million
years i'll play for 20 minutes where's the last one he's gonna go afk well i don't i didn't i
never had to play it i just had to be in the client 20 minutes finding a game yeah what i'm
gonna be playing ranked emperor of mankind you're gonna get kicked for toxic behavior i just have to
play though favorite character the guy throws the cards like the gambit fucking rip off whatever
his name is eely mouth's dentist i'm gonna go up there oh mario you're finally setting up for the
ocean's bottom grandpa's waiting for you up top oh don't forget to wear this rope is a shortcut
to reach grandpa hey thanks kid i'll only spray you mainly for one second nice and quick all right
all right ramps he's all the way up top it said some shortcut you gave me dude it actually wasn't
a shortcut at all i didn't feel like going the real way all right what do you want me to do
you look like you're ready the gunk in the ocean is caused by a giant eel it's moving into our
ancestral home at the sea floor and it's nursing some nasty cavities let's take a look the newly
uncorked waterfall created a gap in the pollution and you can use an entrance jump right in die for
the bottom of the ocean and clean that eel's teeth all right gather your courage and dive
some dark souls looking shit here this is kind of cool all right clean his teeth uh we're getting
kind of like the mario party music toxic materials approaching so don't touch those
clean his so this toxic gross mouth this is like dirty teeth how do i get him to open his mouth
oh jesus uh whoa seems we are being attacked by black forming bacteria
holy shit you have a dirty mouth i move i'm gonna drown okay open whoa oh
should i is it easier to do it like that just fly by am i cleaning them it's hard to even
it's determined where the hell i am yes straight down come on go mario's fucking drowning mario's
drowning kind of hard to turn like this okay how many more i got the cup of this
this gold tooth is clean only few more come on get it ah almost all right i should get it now
got it come back up here i still have teeth to clean guy with a mustache cleans your entire fucking
mouth that's yeah that's what's happening right now all right there's a couple more dirty teeth
this one here all right there's only one more it's two more actually come on don't get sucked
in mario don't get sucked in all right last one all right heal i'm running out of coins
oh no no what if his teeth fell off oh he didn't treat his mouth well for like 20 years it's not
my fault i didn't do anything i just cleaning and there we are take care of your teeth or you're
going to fucking jail there's a heart oh look at this there's a little heart here thank you
thank you he was just upset about his teeth i don't even need him here's there it is
but what about the heart it's okay
another spot is opened up and no still here do pachinko please how do we get out i'll do
i'll do it so all right after this i'm going to do pachinko wherever it is oh we have another
race to do this is going to be horrible i already know he's up there hey what's going on two
i am two ain't easy bow yes that is me and now i challenge you to a race to that flag
easy i was gonna dive into the water and swim that's time it's 40 seconds you're at the ready
got it ha ha two panties emo i win we may race again watch for me ha ha all right that one didn't
even count that one was so fast all right now it's all right where is it where is it how far away is
it go to the cannon right it's on the boat it's here get on that boat is it right here under the
oh it's right there okay so when the boat comes by i'm i gotta be on the other side
i'm gonna be ready right here do it at the boat show at the boat show okay sorry sorry
at the boat shop oh he did the singing thing again you oh you're fast wait it's it's an actual
chinko machine how do i get up there is there a jump pad where oh man what
it's all right can i steer at all i guess i kind of can all right i got four how have i not got
the one that's right here no no no no no go back no no no no no no no i refuse i refuse i refuse
i refuse i refuse i'm cheating no i'm cheating come on what what you can fall through you can
go down the whole thing i didn't know you could go down the whole thing what is it opening at the
end this is gonna be bad he didn't know he didn't know he doesn't know he doesn't know he doesn't
know he doesn't know he'll never know he doesn't know he didn't know i do know cheating cheating
cheating cheating cheating cheater he's cheating he cheated this one doesn't count monkey
he's cheating monkey he's monkey cheating monkey his emulator
uh what the fuck why can't i move these two are the hard ones i'll just slide down
him nope nope no what's going on he's freaking out
this camera angle i just pogged my pants me too man both of us all right you gotta stop it like
right oh it's hard to do all right down the middle actually yeah do it right down the middle
so okay now i'm gonna get this one over here dude i can't even fucking see
what is going on he was he was scared up for it oh whatever that was i'll do that another time
what the fuck uh no i'm gonna do another one i'm going back here do it now now i can't do it no
i can't secret of the don't you want to know what like the dirty diaper lake wait i didn't do this
i thought i did this oh fly anybody else in this game is sick hey anybody else in this game sick
anybody else in this game is sick where am i going super jump or yeah sure all right we're
gonna go over there this level is stinko we want pachinko i will beat pachinko before i stop playing
super mario in total take this out before i land that was seriously the fucking best thing ever
yeah i don't care if i got hurt there that was i didn't touch the ground you know what i'm saying
that was amazing i will beat pachinko before don't worry i'm gonna have to go to like
tongue stretches what the fuck is the man with me all right uh where is it wink we'll do a wink
nah i don't feel like it nah no i'm good i don't feel like it get up here get up on the lily pad
dude i don't understand what's going on how do you pull a muscle in your tongue how do i pull like
all these muscles in my chest and back it doesn't make any sense i feel like mario does right now
another one what was that you even exercise anymore yeah i i've go to physical therapy
but do it for times a week all right back in there no pachinko no no no no no no no no no no
what is this place no i don't do this red coins on the water uh what the wow it's rico harbor how
do i get out of here how's the root beer in the humidifier story you making this up
i wish root beer all right fine i'll do pachinko fine fine i'll do pachinko wait do i want to do
that maybe it's not going as fast as i want it to go oh wait but you know what you're right
pachinko's under the bridge for god it's in a weird spot where am i going yeah i don't know
where the fuck i'm going help them they're on fire i don't know i can't do anything what am i
gonna i want to go over here all right give me the boat i'm trying to jump control is like
the control is broken get in there you have to do it first try or i'm going to bed
fucking stuff fucking dumb fucking idiot game fucking stupid fucking game
which side does it come from here it is great camera work right right at the review right now
great camera the camera is the best part of mario sunshine it's the best it's got a great
camera system that's what i'm gonna write when i do my review oh man it's gonna be scathing review
it's gonna people are gonna read it be like whoa he really didn't like this and be like
i'm typing wicked out on the keys hey here comes the boat you tell me i can't get in there yes i
can i'll just fuck it up that's unbelievable just go get through first try you can't do it first
try it's impossible there's no first try a pachinko machine you need at least like
three or four pachinkos i just figured out how to do this i figured out how to do this
i can't fit in there how can you how do i not fit in here why is it like an invisible wall
what oh come on there was a vini first tried this i want proof of that and i want 100 dollars
i want proof and 100 dollars why do you think why like why does anybody why do you need to have
that i don't understand i should not have fucking said that that was stupid i forgot you i can't
make money jokes because somebody will do the joke but the joke is it's not even a joke i now
have an extra hundred dollars now because you did that bilateral it just gave 100 dollars
it's 100 bucks 10 000 bits they say you rang well i didn't did i i did all right give me it
it's right there no come on how many lives do i have do i have no more lives okay i have another
one where the fuck can i get out of this what do you get for doing this do you just get one
shine for doing this i would put that into not worth doing category yep huh okay i just have
to make sure i actually go into one of the holes if you don't make it into one of the holes you
just screwed it's over it's not not over it's not over i'm gonna i can make it onto the left
watch this why can i leave i can't go to the left i accept your fate no because this glass
i accept it shit just build speed for 12 hours
uh
build speed for 12 hours
keep linking it boys don't worry this is the pachinko level this is the dreaded pachinko level
guys need to know should they be shaving them it's sexy of its tricks you just feel sexier
i'm getting bombarded and all of a sudden i'm being bombarded i go to the barber every two
weeks people okay here we go this is first try is it actually first try
same can happen to me yeah i'm sorry what was the problem i think shadow mario is just magical
right right this is the pachinko level this is the dreaded pachinko level
pretty sneaky edit there i caught it i'm a video fucking guy because i don't know
this was three years ago spliced let him sleep hey remember you played mario sunshine three
years ago i i want i do that i did that now you did i did this for them to first try hey why
all right um what did i want to do secret of the dirty leg that's what i want to do not
pachinko i'm not doing it i am not going to do pachinko we're gonna just see where the dirty
lake and then remember we'll go hey we're going five days in a row this week probably maybe three
maybe i don't know we're doing because i just wow what a backtrack backtrack andy uh backtrack barry
um i want to beat mario sunshine this week so i might go four or five days in a row and then
we're doing community content night so you know i don't know i want to beat this before community
content night in before no stream for the rest of the week i would not start this now
and then not stream tomorrow and the next day and probably the next day and the next day
i'm into this i want to do this all right most more importantly i need to
all right where was it it's like over here isn't it i don't know the dirty lake the dirty lake i need
the i'm gonna keep this i don't want the rocket that was a dumb mistake how's my throat doing it
still hurts but i'm kind of just gonna see what happens when i get up tomorrow i should be fine
i don't know it's just like weird this just doesn't make any sense this is like i've you know i've
been alive for 34 years this shit is this this shit like it's just never fucking happening i like
it's just weird all right let's go i need to go to the dirty lake which is the other way
got boomer pain now yeah probably all right where's that dirty ass lake
over there i missed did i miss bits where oh i did why is this down here uh that was a hundred bucks
another hundred look look at all the red there's so much red today i red red red red red there's
like a hundreds of dollars of red uh core monster ten thousand bits fucking hundred bucks
there's another hundo in it for you if you beat pachinko i will but maybe not today
we're in this for the long haul guys i'm this is the stream the next like four at least probably
three or four days in a row at least this is what we're doing i'll get sorry i was spurting your
face that would have been really rude there it is all right go over there it's all right i still
made it the hell you got the turbo nozzle turbo nozzle press and hold r to power up the turbo
nozzle and do a super dash well we gotta go in here first oh this is one of these levels uh oh
uh oh uh oh holy fuck panics panics there's some panics there i bet germa can't do this first try
well you can't bet that i'm not gonna do something after i fail it you gotta do that well before
like but whether during this first the first loading screen yeah i fucked it up i thought it
was i just don't know why i didn't always miss you bet i can't do this within five tries
probably right sometimes you got to go fucking risky shit like this
oh why did i die that would have been fine he just instinctively pressed buttons in mario i don't know
why it's probably the right play though let's be safe did i not make that really serious
i needed to be like uh yeah you actually you have you probably have to go to the other one
i was trying to skip it it sounds drained no it's just this no i'm fine i don't want anyone to be
concerned about me i'm all right i want to do this i already am so he's coming down from the
crack that's the problem he just he smoked so much crack and now he's like on the down
i've been having a lot of fun though this game is fun it's fun just to play and just dick around
and stuff he needs more crack i was probably gonna end soon anyways i wanted to do i wanted
to like separate this out between like three to five like six to seven hour streams there's
plenty of content to do every day he's really gonna stretch out mario sunshine yeah i mean
yeah yeah yeah all right where am i going over this way stalling well it's not stalling it's
just spreading stalling would be if i sat at the starting soon screen talking about how i can't
wait to play mario sunshine for 45 minutes i turn i started playing almost immediately so that's
the difference i'm gonna try this at what here's plan try this one more time like this i am going
to go wait what's the matter you want to leave all right give me a second
i was like i want to get out of this room you want to get out of the room okay come on
so
all right he's good oh he's diluting his content here he's diluting i'm not diluting
diluting let me dilute i'm not diluting oh i mean i'm i'm in mario yeah that's that's that's the whole
point he's mega milking his content i shouldn't be laughing at what you said but i am i shouldn't
laugh at that i should not be laughing at that statement he's actually playing mario sunshine
yeah that's fucking great this game's awesome i love it so far all right here we go spin and
here we are all right that's the plan here we go get the one out
really okay now what happens over here what does this thing do what is that oh god that's um all
right i can go down a wall run holy shit is it moving those cubes probably shouldn't even be
jumping that was bad what was that weird timing right there this is all the timing's all fucked
up look at this shit what what the hell was that this is what was it that timing that was weird
that was my fault yeah it was that was my fault i take full responsibility for what just happened
oh yeah let's try this again we're just gonna run uh okay they do they sweep across
go holy shit that thing tilts us sideways wow it was starting to turn until
oh they threw i gotta run into the corner when that happens
at least i'm getting this every time so we can do this infinite amount of times
they're trying to teach me then it went out the corner shit i'm gonna lose it i'm gonna fail it
again probably i wouldn't be surprised okay here we go oh okay what the hell i had to hit my head
on the ceiling okay what happens here so i don't know this i don't know that i don't know what to
do i'm gonna which one this one which one oh yeah oh yeah all right now jump off for a joke
save the game save 26 stars 39 blue coins and that's what i'm gonna call it stretching content
is what we call this uh it's six hours this is gonna be like a that's that's that's normal
that's under the six to seven hours that's what that's a normal stream for me don't leave
you scammed people out of pachinko no i'm gonna beat that tomorrow this is not a normal game
jeremy no it's mario sunshine week please that guy's on fire i got him i got him i think does
this guy want to be on fire i think this guy wants to be on oh well you saved me thanks a bundle
holy shit that's makes it even 40 points all right i'll see you guys tomorrow uh sorry about the
weird like tongue thing that was weird i don't know why i'm apologizing for that but
kind of stopped the stream for like five seven minutes but it's all good
uh i'm gonna go drink some tea and hopefully this is not a thing that sticks around
because that would really be annoying but um i will see you guys tomorrow around the same time
mario sunshine continues don't put hot shit down your throat if it hurts
no no i don't i i drink warm tea i don't drink hot tea don't leave five more minutes
oh this isn't the snooze button oh well no well i'll be back tomorrow i'll be back in less than
like 16 hours like 12 hours hit the snooze no no i'm going no no snooze button no i know i love
this game too and we're going to enjoy the fuck out of it for the rest of the week i'll see you
guys tomorrow have a great rest of your night goodbye we'll finish up with the bits and
everything and hang out for a little bit see you guys tomorrow i'm not going to keep playing
without you i promise i'm the i will literally turn it off right now ready the game is game is
saved save continue sure okay turn it off i'm gonna promise you look it's okay it's going off
hold you thanks for watching see you tomorrow disconnected video cables i had a lot of fun
though this was i had a lot of fun this is a great game to play i love it i think it's fantastic
and i hope you guys enjoyed it we'll continue tomorrow but let's go back we had lm man uh for
five dollars earlier terma you are a greedy tyrant uh i disagree i disagree thank you for the five
dollars wembley t tv thanks for the 250 germ i had a dream about you last night with your head
on a naked willem defoe body and you were just the dance just dancing i woke up screaming
get this nightmare out of my head well go watch go what i don't know go watch like a documentary on
on how trees grow or something i don't get to watch something else the reason why you're having
these dreams is because i'm up there you gotta before you go to bed you gotta watch something
else you gotta watch like so let's say you watch a stream and streams over you've got to turn on
like like a baby tv show like nick jr or something or uh i don't know something else to get like
more characters in your head right before you go to bed i think the problem that's the problem
watch like spongebob but no but then obviously it'll be me and spongebob like sword fighting
so i don't know if i can solve this problem for you i can't get that out of your head
that sounds pretty cool so i can't help you i can't help you uh eat less macaroni and
cheese right before you go to bed back fighter thanks for the five community subs just five
subs thank you will got thanks for 250 hello king there it is again the way mario launches
himself with his water pack reminds me of my last episode on the toilet um i was playing
indoor mini golf and eating pizza slices served on plates for everyone to grab
i was convinced i had the coronavirus anyway keep up the great work king king
your streams are as epic as bacon more more uh whatever thanks hey cream corn thanks for the
250 did you write off the carnival stream as a business expense uh yes at least a lot of it
some of that stuff you can't write off it's too bright off it's not like you'd be like okay
and this is what happened and there's there it is it's over you kind of need to go piece by piece
but i have i have a lot of the documents and things that are ready to go so don't worry about
that but for the most part yes i can do a lot of writing off on those things but i did say
remember i said this a long time ago just if you're talking about you know spending money
on the business in quotes um i'm gonna do shit like that i'm gonna spend a bunch of
fucking money if i have it because it's if it's available i want to like put it back and try to
do something interesting or try to do something fun if it's if i'm capable of doing that and i
have the money to do it then i'm gonna try business laughing my ass off all right this
this warrant's being put on this is good actually that's great oh super frog sunshine but yeah
yeah i had if you're wondering why i took an extra day i was getting my taxes prepared to
get stuff sent to my cpa and get going from there just get it done that's why i was gone
yesterday i just didn't get it done all the way we know you don't do your taxes i yeah i prepare
it for somebody else that's way smarter than me to do it yes that's correct why are us taxes so
hard for fuck's sake uh it's yeah yeah it's well there's another thing is just especially
considering like where like a lot of this money comes from it's a lot more it's a lot different
than just i have a w2 and okay and here's what i owe here's what i'm gonna get back there's a
lot of weird little moving parts but that's why it takes a while fringe taxes for fail country
um every all countries paid to have taxes what are you talking about was there some
status but what are you talking about where are you what what are you on some random island that's
in like the atlantic ocean or something what are you talking about all countries have to pay taxes
at least for the most part all right let's go uh peaceful hailey thanks for the 250 hailey hey
jeremy thanks for playing one of my favorite games of all time the music the scenery everything's
perfect it gets fucking annoying at the same time though i hope the move is going well very much so
not under anthony bantony i like to eat taxes because american taxes are especially confusing
because of lobbying and from the very companies you used to do your taxes don't don't you got you
can't say the evil lord's name out loud into it oh oh i'll be all right nice one jeremy solid bit
thanks i appreciate that thanks a lot they got them all right i'm gonna keep moving i'm still
super high energy right now but like i like my back of my whatever i'm so high energy right now
you have no idea i'm gonna i'm gonna bottle this up and take this in just tomorrow hey lm man thanks
for the 500 bits jeremy if you were in the mario universe what character would you be a toad a
koopa or a goomba no i wouldn't be a toad no no way probably a goomba yeah i could see that
i could i would be i'd be a high ranking goomba though i wouldn't just be like a
regular goomba i would be like a goomba captain i would be a high ranking goomba
without there's some named goombas in the mario universe i know there are they've had dialogue
lines before in paper mario yeah that'd be that one hey c4g thanks for the 250 people happy jerma
auto just right at me uh frost 2e thanks for the 300 bits dinosaur bites thanks for the
thousand bits ten dollars thank you thank you thank you thank you hey jerma how would you feel
about voicing a giant king rat in my 3d platformer king jeremy is a big boy who needs to be fed cheese
before he'll move out of the way i can't think of a single person i'd rather have for the role
the game's called clive and wrench he's available uh probably not i look i'm gonna be really honest
when i i've been asked to do things before from other places and to do lines and shit and i just
never do them i just like don't i just lose track i don't have enough time to do this shit i i
i focus on the stream almost 100 if i'm not and i'm doing something in my like real life
people have asked me to do some things and i just haven't done i've been like oh yeah maybe or
yeah sure or no or i just don't want to be like yeah maybe oh sounds good hit me up and it just
gonna never happen i don't want to tell people that i'll do these things and i just won't
just don't want to i want to be honest too busy doing nothing that's not even true that's not
even true i know i know i know that a lot of people think when the stream is off i sit in the chair
and there's like a feeding tube in my mouth and then if the and then the stream turns on i'm here
i know that's a i i know that's what a lot of people think happens i just sit here and stare
at the blank monitor for three days you just schlep around your house naked
do a line for the rat king right now get out of here what you stupid i'll kill you
now just slow that down like pitch that tempo down like 10 to 20 percent that's not family
friendly i'm a boss i'm supposed to be a boss battle he's supposed to say i'm gonna get you
attack you or something yeah i don't you can use you literally just use that i don't care
i don't care like yeah i don't you don't have to pay me for and you don't have to pay me don't
worry i just use it who cares how about some like how about some like dialogue pop-ups like
huh crazy what are you doing oh oh oh okay what's that get over here i'll get you get over here i'll
get you use them use it wherever you want i don't it doesn't matter ask for cheese oh yeah give me
that cheese have some cheese i'm available to do it on the spot but no money all right here we go
let's keep going thank you dinosaur bites uh good luck s kilo thanks for the 250 bits it's the bernie
sanders thing that hey i made you something it's the bernie sanders the guy that sounded like bernie
sanders in the beginning of the game misty these past five days five days it's been that long it's
only been what it's only been like four wait what that's how i streamed four days ago five days
it's four you cancelled yesterday yeah that's four today would be day five but i streamed on day five
so i streamed four days ago i streamed on day five i started i streamed on the day five
it was a leap week four days plus one other day but the day yeah but the four days ago
five whole so five days yeah but on day but it's not but it hadn't been five total days
it been four days and then plus one here's the stream now germa what is it gonna get
go germa you've cancelled what pieces anyways anyways uh when is community content night this
weekend either saturday or sunday probably sunday uh shout out to the subs on germa discord i'll miss
you ps my stomach again exams show nothing out of the ordinary but the pain i'm feeling is real as
fuck i know that life is annoying they took a biopsy of my stomach it might not be anything at
all but it might mean my pain might never go away sorry to hear that that's never fun like i said
earlier i had these fucking mystery symptoms for two years no idea what it is i know what i knew
i had colitis for my whole life essentially the last at least 12 years or so like i've known that
but when you have some new random medical problem that you cannot nobody can actually tell you this
is exactly what's wrong with you it's a huge pain in the ass what if you're allergic to something
you're eating i it's not it i had a full i had a full allergy panel so they tested for everything
nothing and sometimes you have to just kind of you just kind of have to punch at it while you
just try to live your normal life just cast full heal on yourself you dummy i wish that that were
real imagine you just cast heal on yourself and just like oh wow i feel fucking perfect
but i try i try not to let this shit bother me because obviously if it did if it if i let it
annoy me and irritate me and bother me all the time then i would just be it would just be in a
bad place where i would just be annoyed and miserable all the time so i'm trying to look
on the bright side and just be like all right i'm just gonna keep going at it and just see what
happens and if it turns out that i have to go do this fucking injection into my nerve
i'm god i've gotta do it like i'm gonna do it not at that point yet we'll see but i don't i don't
really like to i mean we talk about this kind of medical stuff sometimes but i i really don't
like talking too much about it only when i have to because i don't want people to think that there's
something wrong oh he's he must be in so he must be in pain right now streaming dude don't stop
streaming what are you doing get out of here it's like i said this before and i'll say it again if
i wasn't comfortable which has happened before at least a handful of times i just won't stream i'll
just tell you hey i'm not it's not happening today maybe tomorrow that's happened at least a
handful of times over the last few months of course it has i'm not going to do that so don't
worry about that i'm not i'm not going to just like stream and sit here and be in like pain or
anything like that it's that and that doesn't really happen that much anyways it almost happened
today yeah but today was weird because it just kind of i've never been in that in a scenario
before where okay here here's like a new thing that's like might be i like i pulled like a
muscle in my tongue somehow it's still there but this is exactly how it started when my chest and
back started to hurt it was just like oh this hurts what's wrong what what is that did i just
pull my muscle in my back i must have oh that's where that's not going away let's stay now this
is there forever okay weird okay same exact scenario it's almost like uh like i'm on edge
when it comes to stuff like that so that's why i was giving a small like hey um i might leave
in 10 minutes if this gets any worse i just want to be obviously want to make sure i'm okay to
you kissed too hard but at the same time i also don't want to create some kind of worry or like
panic in the community that oh my god something's wrong he needs to go to the doctor right now
it's under control don't worry about me i'm actively doing this shit every week
so don't worry about me i'll be all right and it's not it's not that bad it's it's just it's
annoying and i have to deal with it but i'll be all right like it's not like i just don't want
people to be worried about this shit if i'm not worried about it you shouldn't be either let's
put it that way let's just keep going all right you do have a pretty flexible job luckily yeah i
do and i i i'm every day that i wake up i go holy fuck um this is i i i can i can i can actually
say no i don't i'm not doing it today a lot of people aren't in that scenario so i'm incredibly
lucky i am very very very much lucky for this because i know that if i was doing another
anything else i can't just like not go to fucking work you know what i mean it's just like you can't
do that i'm incredibly fucking lucky don't be extra hard on yourself because of your blessings and
push yourself too far no no no no don't worry i take time off i i just i just i mean we just
made the jib i was making the joke before but i mean i just took the last four days off i'm all
right don't worry we know you're waiting tables don't don't say anything about that unhinch your
jaw and i would delete that if i could i can't i don't have access to my deletion but anyways
don't want to get anybody concerned if i i'm not concerned you shouldn't be either hey let's move
on to the fucking comedy sticks renegade thanks for the 250 jerma i got an update to the sticker
car i censored the plates this time so you can show the chat yeah i mean god be careful man listen
jerma i'm gonna be real with you i clearly need more stickers and i i mean a lot more when are you
going to have your own vinyl stickers i've been waiting so long all right what is i okay one of
your stickers is i never leave rhode island seagulls are everywhere seagulls are everywhere what else
are these ones shark attack well let's take a look at these this they're everywhere when does
okay i have a question at what point does this become illegal you know what i mean when i'm gonna
shows when does this become illegal are you are you getting there i don't know what are the laws
on this type of shit you can't see i know i'm just moving some stuff why is this so big joe joe
i zoom right in on the joe joe why can i why is this am i even resizing this fucking thing
okay so i see you have sands back there what else you got both like a skunk oh yeah but at what point
do you get pulled over for this they're everywhere your car has sticker acne this is if reddit was a
car wait what does this one say bitch i'm going oh you oh mode ban this guy i can
what is this car all right cool car oh bitch i'm going uh i don't even know what that means
i'm not i'm not gonna ban somebody if i have a reddit car i don't even know what that means
say it right i how am i supposed to say something right that i've never heard in my life
uh when am i gonna have my own stickers oh um i don't know maybe someday who knows if that's
ever actually gonna happen i have no idea there's all kinds of things that i want to do
there's all kinds of things that i want to do but i gotta focus on one thing at a time
where's the background music oh whoops but um we'll move on i can't tell you when or if
what happened hey this is eskilo 13 for the 250 hello jerk but this is nintendo calling we want
you to explain this video uh but for reals most of my edits got deleted on community content night
like this one and this one yeah there's gonna probably as much as i don't want to say this
i think it's i should that there are so many submissions to community content night
i cannot show every single submission anymore there are sometimes month to month
hundreds and hundreds and hundreds of submissions and at first when people first start to figure
out oh we're just gonna put whatever i know we can just it'll just get on stream whatever that's
cool but going forward i it is gonna have to be some type of some type of like a initial
kind of content filter i guess and show things selectively and just because of the amount of
submissions is just so many and i really don't want to do a case where which it's not like i
felt it happening in any of the other ones but so let's say for instance either the community
content streams they're all they're all between four and the last one was what four and a half
hours they're between like four and five hours and i'd like to maybe instead of have those
potentially go even higher to like six plus hours we we got to start to because i don't want to just
skip through them oh i i know that we're going to be here for six and a half hours going through
artwork and edits and stuff so look at that one oh that one's kind of cool look at this one and
then look at that one and then this one and oh that one's pretty cool look at the line work oh
this one essentially you have to channel surf quickly otherwise you'll be there for 10 hours
so at this point probably going forward there's going to be at least a base level of sort of
selectively choosing what goes on to the stream and that's not to say that everything's going to
just oh wow now there's only going to be like 15 pieces of artwork and it's only going to be the
fucking insane ones that took people like six weeks to make no but there'll be at least a base
filter where we try to shave it down a little but that's kind of where that stands that's where that
stands no meme generator type stuff yeah originally originally like photoshops are were in there and
they could be funny and they can be fun but i don't know it's it's tough it's tough to try to
put like some kind of filter on it i'm still trying to figure that out now show the frogs
again oh like i accidentally did wait oh this uh why is it not here i'm trying to show the frogs
i'm clicking on them why i don't know they're not showing how can i not show the frogs they
should be on the screen right now oh there they are wait did we just big money just come in
another 50 from phylactery all these these red numbers holy shit guys phylactery another
5000 bits give me a fucking germa germ plus you streamer re 50 from core monster
if you don't do pachinko first thing tomorrow i'm gonna scream i will i'll beat it first thing
tomorrow maybe re resident sleeper but thanks both of you that's a lot of fucking money you
guys give a lot of money a lot i appreciate it anyways let's keep going uh let's go to lm man
for 500 bits five dolls from lm man germa when are you going to do viva piata probably not
this week because i really want to get mario sunshine done and if we do mario sunshine for
the next three four straight days between like six seven ish hours or streams six to eight hours
a stream i would assume for mario sunshine that's talking yeah how long is mario sunshine like 20
hours 25 hours but i'm not just beating the game i'm obviously doing a lot of the extra stuff as
he's seen today doing it like six to eight shines in each level is going to take how long
would you guys say not 100 in the game but i'd say like how long would like 70 in the game take
18 hours i don't know i only watch speed runs of it oh average run is like 16 hours
okay all right well we'll see the whole stream the all the content 15 20 hours that makes sense then
yeah that's that would be like three ish four ish streams sounds good to me but there's not
gonna be time and then community content nights right after that so there will not be any time
for anything else this week we'll have to do it next week any percent yeah long as you're not
doing full blue coins it should be good now probably i just get them when i see them
hey atrolox atrix thanks for the thousand bits first you played my childhood game
tony hawks underground now you're playing my childhood game sunshine i love you so much thanks
also what was the hardest mission during tonight's stream um probably one of the
jump on the rotating cubes secret levels the chingos not hard i mean it's just dumb
it's not that mission's that level's not hard it's just stupid and i mean stupid as in it
not that i don't think it's any fun it's just like you just launch mario for the spring in a
pachinko machine it's just it's stupid it's not bad it's just stupid mad because bad no no it's
not bad it's just stupid if if you saw if i was if there's a green screen edit of me flying around
at a pachinko machine you'd be like well that's this is pretty stupid you'd probably think it was
cool i would i'm gonna get on that thanks atrolox for the thousand bits 10 bucks appreciate it uh
fridel schlitz fridel schlitz slinch thanks for the 250 derma can you do the wink session at the
end of community content night my boyfriend made plans with someone this sunday so we won't be able
to watch the beginning of the stream it'll probably be right at the very end that'll be the last thing
that we do nobody wants to open a stream like that that's gonna be the last thing that i do
i'm gonna sit there for 30 minutes and just stare at the camera that's gonna be wicked
creepy awkward fucking stream i'm gonna lose fans from that stream you got it i gotta rip the bandaid
off hey not prior thanks for the 500 bits germa i have been watching you since your first gta 4
videos and your stream highlights ever since you started on twitch the first stream i've ever
watched live because of time zones i want to say you're a huge part of my childhood and i love your
work thank you welcome welcome to the stream hope you enjoyed it maybe we'll see you again soon
thanks a lot not prior future gamer thanks for the 250 this is going to be like simpson's hit and
run spread across four streams there is going to be at least two or three in quotes this game is
stupid no one ever beat this game in quote breakdown no one ever beat this game i don't think so it's
yeah you may be right i've seen a couple i wasn't even getting mad i was just i mean those these
levels are fun and interesting enough and it's really easy to start them over again they just
said the game is stupid but in a good way hey mr kool-aid thanks for the thousand bits germa would
you enable feels dance or alien please it would help me express myself more honestly in chat thanks
for the consideration thanks for the good times you're welcome mr kool-aid and enable pog no i
want to be able to read it i don't want to enable pog i want to read pog josh thanks for the 500
bits you should play mario kart double dash it's a pretty solid mario kart game what you meant to say
was the last good mario kart game i'll say it i know you don't have to i will i'll say it
i know everybody in every all the 2500 people here all thinking it i'll be the one to say it
let me take the flag for this not you i'll take it
no but the wee one the wee one i remember this is before i guys this is before i had a
twitch channel a youtube channel i played the wee one and i fucking hated it i remember playing it
and just being like oh the new mario kart and being like i fucking hate this thing
what i'm in first place i'm in second place why do i get hit why do i get hit with a blue shell
again every time i get in the first place just don't go in first place ever only be in fourth
place until the last 10 seconds of the race why are these in the game why why does this exist
because the asshole in ninth place is just going to troll people in the first two places this is
stupid and i'd fucking never played it again it's a matter of balance that's how all of them work
not all of them not all of them i need to make it fair so people in last can catch up well maybe
the people in last place shouldn't have driven into the wall 10 times when you pass when you lap
toad a third time is is a toad like toad when you lap toad for a third time should toad get a
shell to throw at you in first place like toad just like pull over toad pull over and cheer from
the side at that point toad come on toad deserves it there was a dick what we're talking about
mario kart this is mario kart here we're not talking about like life remember it's that's you
hate no no hey we're talking about mario car top up passing toad three times and you get hit with
a turtle shell because on your third time passing him he accidentally pressed the fucking a button
in the right way and hit you with a green shell everyone loves mario kart unless you're inherently
evil i don't think so i don't think i don't think it makes you evil to be sick of toad in the fucking
back throwing blue shells at you he's a villain i can't be evil i can't be evil he's got something
against toad no okay but all right how many put the music on how many times have you it's a
fucking video game it's my free time if i'm gonna be in first place in a video game in my free time
i would like to stay in first place unless i do something wrong and tipped it and if i'm gonna
pass toad five times i paid for this game with 60 i'm at the finish line and i get hit with a
bullet bill in a blue shell and now i'm in seventh place and i gotta read through the
level every spy paid 60 for this game you beat you're beating up but you're beating a kid
so it's like toads like yeah what are you talking about toads it is like late
30s if you're in first the whole race it's boring that's where you took a wrong turn you paid 60
dollars for a video game he's definitely raged at somebody at like we online or something no i
know that's what some of you guys are thinking he must be so bitter for mario kart week because it
was the first time nintendo even tried to do online oh and by the way this is the new mario
kart for the uh for the ipad i did not know this until um until it was brought to my attention
that game's not online you're playing against bots i thought it was online they give them flags
and names and some of the names are different languages and shit it's just like that you it's
like they're pretending that there are people playing i bet he lost i did because i got hit
with a blue shell in the first place like five times because i'm in first place you leave me
alone best place to be mario kart in third place this is why you're mad old people fail fall for
so many scams it used to be like an old pastime of mine to see how many times i could pass toad
in super mario kart for super nintendo on the bowser level you could do it six or seven
potential plus times that was the game was all right it wasn't about how many how many times i
could win the race it was i need to pass toad eight times this time am i am i psycho this is
making me like a psychopath i mean is it am i like does this make me a psycho i'll bring this to the
doctor you're like hey what do you think about this oh hey here comes the time interval pretends to be
the doctor oh fuck toad that guy sucks yeah by the way let's take a look i'm not doing it anyways
what was it oh yeah play mario kart double dash i probably yeah maybe i will it's a good one
are they blue shells in double dash i don't remember when did they introduce the blue shell
all right i guess i get to move the fuck on i just stopped this but it was like a one percent drop
wasn't it okay i'm done uh fugles thanks for the 400 bits hey jim just wanted to throw some money
at you as i vent about how i was just in mcdonald's drive-through at 3 a.m and they
were cleaning their deep fryer so like half of the menu was unavailable and it ruined my plans for
the night anyways here's a short video i don't click i don't click videos anymore but i'll click
it we don't click videos anymore on this channel i got i get gnomed and um and and and ear blasted
how many times okay it's too dangerous i'll uh i'll check it out though let's check it out
this is oblivion npc conversation call the judge and get some fudge can are you okay no no
a doctor maybe where's your md my dick you're dm you're trying to slide in the dms you're trying
to slide you're trying to slide in the dms what the hell is this oblivion conversations oh okay
well thanks for that video that wasn't you right thanks a lot jim well your name you know hey jim
that's not my name either it's neither one of our names probably thanks for the four dollars hey
pixel otter thanks for the 400 bits genius kind angel baby streamer germa thanks for the four
dollars hey gnarly thanks for the 250 i'm excited to hear that you're gonna play the battle for
bikini bottom remake i kind of want to see you play the original maybe it's just nostalgia talking
but i feel like that'll be better version whatever the case it'll be a fun stream
oh i mean here's the the 500 iq play here from me um germa only plays games before 2010
but but what if that game is a remake of a game from 2006 comes out in 2020
that means i that's a new game new game cool uh thank you to poly hex for 10 community subs
just a few minutes ago no it was two hours ago more than a few minutes a few more minutes after
that thanks for the 10 subs appreciate it thanks for tossing some in here bug smoke thanks for
300 bits hey germa if you spray water in front of you and slide on it you get really good speed
boost i figured that out eventually thank you though appreciate the tip seven layer wario
thanks for the 500 bits i yell at the tv when you fuck up the same way other people yell at sports
he dropped it oh what the fuck bro you i can't fucking believe you i'm not in competition with
anybody why is this so much at stake i there's not two people in here playing mario sunshine at the
same time to see who can beat it first it's me like sitting in my chair relaxing playing mario
sunshine this is not like a football game just betting on my gameplay i don't condone that that's
nothing that i did doesn't know bad call fire that guy well i hope you don't lose any money
keith king crimson thanks for the 250 fun fact under uh under two panties mows mask he looks
like the running guy from polka marina of time is the same character i don't know could be marry me
germa nope sorry put germa in he doesn't have the reach normally that's the kind of comment that
would get you timed out for at least six to seven days but it's clever i'll reduce your sentence by
one day see in five days no no no no no not because i'm banning anybody i'm just not streaming for
five days i'll see in like a week see in like six days let's get the credits rolling what do you say
i knew it he won't stream because of one guy the all-powerful the all-powerful one
i'm gonna hit you here sorry ah here they are here come the subs there were a lot of them
as you can see lots of people subscribed lots of people community subbed lots of people just
decided they were gonna sub for the first time today right now whoever you are thank you appreciate
it i really do much love to you all dodged them all damn right that guy's name though
by the way i haven't written down any of these people's names hopefully people did
hey germa suck speaking of subs you gave 10 community subs earlier
thank you uh nv11 casting thanks for the 250 my favorite streamers playing my favorite childhood
game and my taco bell delivery guy gave me like 40 sauce packets this is the happiest i've been
in weeks people happy but honestly thank you for being you germa you've been a great help
through the past few months of college stress a lot of packets thanks for the 250 enjoy your
taco bell hopefully it was good hopefully it was filling and fulfilling whoa all right nobody
this is mine that's like a restaurant if you go to a restaurant and then it's a at the end of
your meal and the waiter or waitress comes over they say at the very end you sign the check and
they go thanks for coming i hope your meal was but hold on thanks for coming yep appreciate it
thank you for the uh yeah your card i'll run it i hope your meal was filling i can't uh thanks for
the card i hope your meal was filling and fulfilling see you next time hopefully there it is it's mine
when i open up my restaurant booger burgers is what they fucking knows all over the buns and
spit on all the hamburgers hey yo it's mike thanks for the 10 bucks and also yo it's mike
germa thanks for playing this awesome classic games hope you can chill with some more with
viva piata yeah i will i had a lot of fun playing it definitely something i'll do you will see it
again hope your meal was filling and fulfilling stupid fucking idiot fucking goddamn dumb
fucking idiot you better leave at least 40 percent see you next hop come back soon
peaceful hailey thanks for the 250 my god germa i love you and i never send mean bits but god damn
man what the fuck are you doing you're triggering me you're triggering me with your play style right
now i'm a mario fan and this is the end of the line for me i'm on something what i've not even
played that poorly i'm playing like a normal human plays video games what okay i'm a normal
human enjoying a video game on an old elderly console what's wrong he's playing like shit i'm
playing just fine i'm playing just fine goiki thanks for the 500 bits i only caught the final
pachinko moment of the stream but i'm excited to watch more of this game when i don't have
standardized testing on a stream day maybe we'll see you tomorrow he did great on the
wall yeah people like to tend to forget about the watermelon level that i just did i did that in
less than 10 15 minutes i know that i know for a fact that took you at least six hours when you were
a kid i get credit for the watermelon level i do uh thank you hammer roid for the five uh heim
heim roid i'm heim roid what thanks for the heim thanks for the 500 bits hey germa i'm going to
boston in april to hang out with friends are there any places i absolutely need to visit while i'm
here i remember you mentioning an arcade party place but i don't remember the name now that
would be gillian's gillian's is great gillian's has two or three floors there's a full bowling
alley there's a full arcade there's a bar in there but gillian's is kind of like dave and busters
but not a meme if that makes any sense hash out oh go to the hash house or gogo that doesn't exist
sorry what's with you guys in reddit dave and busters is a reddit restaurant well i
well somebody has a reddit car somebody has a reddit restaurant somebody has a reddit dog food
somebody has a reddit coffee what what what else is there reddit streamer i'm not a reddit streamer
i'm just a i'm just a regular streamer i'm not a reddit streamer i found you through reddit yeah
but you found me through reddit i'm not like i because i have a reddit account i think i've
posted three times that my reddit account's name is germa's one reddit post that's my actual
account name i i actually i did like one post i was responding to somebody and i use it sometimes
to talk to people in the community i think i've written three times in 10 years why would you
admit to having a reddit i i've used it like three i don't know i don't know i've used it like i was
going i've used it like three times no whatever it's a fucking website it's like reddit is like
number four and it's like real close maybe two or three points off from pornhub at number three
okay so it's it's like one of the world's most visited websites what do you want me to do
he's going here he goes he's going to be defensive no i'm not i'm going i'm out of here
wait gillian's in boston was turned into a lucky strike and do what wait gillian doesn't exist
anywhere anymore what is it good is it still good is it good still it's still fun they've still
an arcade it's still an arcade though like the third floor what time is the stream tomorrow
uh between two o'clock and like three o'clock two ish three ish two like 30 240 220 i don't
know two but between two and three two o'clock three o'clock one of those p.m. hey gooberry juice
thanks for the 250 well germ it finally happened i had a dream with you in it all right and here
we go again stop stop eating mcdonald's 10 minutes before you go to sleep i dreamed i
was meeting up with a couple of old friends in a new york bar the weird part was that you were
doing stand-up comedy at this random new york bar and i didn't know if it's because i don't have a
good uh mental cognition of what you look like from the neck down but you were like really fat
like failed high school soccer coach fat people were going up to the stage you were on throughout
your routine and dropping donations in this little easter basket you had your stand-up was all right
by the way if you're curious it was just inside jokes from the stream anyway at the end of your
stand-up you read off the donations most of which were like who are you i went up to you after and
asked what you were doing in new york and you just started crying you told me auto died recently and
this is the only way you could cope with it i'm sad i'm i said i'm sorry for you then i woke up
what the fuck what the fuck this is fucking horrible oh i'm sorry dude what am i what are
you doing in new york i'm sorry man died so i went to new york to be a stand-up comedian
jesus christ and got pretty fat by the way and people were just coming up on the stage
well thanks weird hey again pendulum thanks for the 300 bids hey germa i know you said you don't
like dnd but i would really like you to actually role play have you looked into other tabletop
rpg systems uh i just i don't i'm not out for it i've gained i came to a realization a long time
ago i don't have the patience for it uh fuck hello hello hello hello hello hello all right we're good
thanks for the gold stop uh no i just it doesn't grab me i i lose my patience with it i lose
interest in it i've tried to do it a couple times before and it just didn't click but and i i will
say that i do respect dnd because it's the reason why we have skill trees and it's the reason why
any rpg's even exist in the first place almost all video games are because those guys made
dungeons and dragons like all video games are because of it so i highly respect it that's a
reddit silver worthy comment thanks does anybody you don't thank somebody for silver though that's
like thanks for the silver i guess where's the gold huh silver ah cool you don't even reply to
that do you don't edit your comment for silver i think that's that's taken it too far how would
you know i'm just yeah i'm just i'm just guessing that's how people will do things all right i'll
see you guys tomorrow get some sleep that's incorrect so is this so is that so is this
so okay now there we go found it nope there it is okay goodbye i'll see you guys tomorrow
more super mario sunshine i'm gonna go um rest my tongue and be annoyed
but see you tomorrow we have a couple more bits we have just speed for 250 how is the how in the
busy heck do you get 75 000 channel points i want the power to make my favorite diaper joke master
wink at my fingertips well don't worry because as of this weekend you're only going to need
half of those by the way if you were subscribed you get like double points or something don't you
yeah thanks a lot though and finally peaceful hailey thanks for the 250 i gave you 50 dollars
when i told you i was going to vegas and all you had to say was go to hash house or gogo what you've
said 50 times to us and jillian's is permanently closed omega low what the fuck yeah i know and i
said go to gordon ramsey steak one ramsey steak is awesome gordon ramsey steak is my is the other
restaurant i would say go to or uh carson kitchen in downtown you know to be real with you carson
kitchen in downtown is one of the best restaurants i've ever been to the new one it also but here's
the thing vegas you there's so much you could there's so many reasons why people come to vegas
that it's hard to give exact things that you should do some people come to vegas with five
grand and they blow it in the casinos it's like oh did you do you gamble uh i mean
if you do i'm not telling you to but you know don't do that be careful uh but um like the
cosmopolitan and the aria two of the best casinos resorts in vegas on the strip um if you are you
hungry it's got some of the best restaurants in the world do you like hiking do you like skiing
it has everything depends on what you want to do you want to go see a bunch of shows there are some
good shows pen and teller him and i saw pen and teller it was it was pretty good they still got
it it's still a fun interesting show it was like half magic half stage magic half um like commentary
from uh pen and it was it was pretty cool it was it was really like it was it was it was a nice
show i'll put it that way that wasn't it was sarcastic but i love pen and teller his germa's
voice pitch shifted um no you're probably noticing is my i'm talking a little differently
because my road is kind of fucked up for some reason no okay i don't have my effects turned on
i went up five octaves what no i did how anyways i'll see you guys tomorrow have a great rest of your
night high low rent for the rest of the story thank you all so much i really appreciate it
i just want to say that they don't obviously have the support of all the other people
here right in the first order they wouldn't have reason to try to i don't give spoilers on
the recent star wars movie but as you know i just want to
oh
is this better is that better okay that's better you guys actually hear it now okay let's go friends
reset to one reset for one guys okay reset for one