Hey, what's up? How's it going? Early. That's right. Yeah. Hello. Are you there? Yeah.
Hey, everybody. You hear who that is? It's um. Who is it? What's your name? Like it starts
uh, Ster. Oh, it's Ster. Hey, how's it going? And I'm absolutely gonna not be weird anymore.
Why? I just figured like I've been being like too weird and I'm like, I'm done.
You're turning over a new leaf here. Yeah. Interesting. I sense that like a lot of the times
I make you uncomfortable and I'm just going to be super normal today.
All right. So what that actually means is that in like 25 minutes,
you're going to turn your webcam on and just be naked. What? Why? You're going to turn your
webcam on. You're going to be wearing like, I don't know what you're going to be doing.
Why can't, why can't you trust me for like one stream? I'm not going to be weird today.
Nothing strange is going to happen. Don't, I'm turning over a new leaf. My wife is the same
exact way. And I've talked about this before. Whenever I say I'm going to, can I borrow one
of your bras and I'm going to, I'm not going to do anything weird with it. She won't let me have it.
Well, but why does it have to be prefaced with something weird?
Well, it's not, it's, it's not going to be weird. I'm going to be totally normal. I'm going to be
incredibly professional and we're going to have a fantastic time playing Ember Nights,
my second Ember related game. Yeah. That's another thing we have to bring up. I'm,
I'm sorry. I have to apologize to everybody. This is the second Ember game that Stir has wanted us
to play. Um, I, am I stream dying? What's going on here? I hope not. It's just so not used to
being live that it's like rejecting it. Why does it say it's unstable? It's weird. Stir, please.
What? No, you're fine. Relax. All right. So what do you, can you explain what this game is before?
And wait before, hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. What are we doing after?
We are 100% today doing the Five Nights at Freddy's watch along stream. Yes.
He's so excited. I've been waiting for this for like a month, by the way. I've got, I've got threats
in the mail from him since the last time we didn't do it. And he thinks I don't know it was him.
You promised us. I'll do it. All right. So you, those that don't know, this is Ember Nights.
It is a friend game, but you just, I actually don't even know what this is.
I just don't know. Um, I, I, I'm not entirely sure. It's generally like a co-op beat em up.
What was the old game that you co-op and you beat in a month? Uh, Battletoads? Yeah. Sure.
It's Battletoads. It's like Battletoads. It's a roguelike and I don't really know.
I've actually heard all jokes aside. I've heard good things. I, that's too. I've heard very good
things. I was playing, uh, I was having, you know, a little bit of a roguelike kick again. And I was
like, I never tried Ember Nights when it came out and it's got updates. So. Hey, did you tweet?
Uh, no, I didn't tweet. I didn't tweet. I usually just copy your tweet. I don't know a single
streamer that likes tweeting that they're live. Yeah. I don't know why I still do it. Why do I
still do that? Do you do that still? Do what? To tweet out every stream you do. Mine are forgettable.
So I don't need to let people know. I feel like I just, I have, that's a thing that has been a thing
since like 2012. And I just never stopped doing it. It's the only thing I put on my Twitter.
Well, better than nothing. You can set it up to be, have it be automatic. I could do that,
but I don't know. I feel like I have to be doing it. Then it has like a really lame, it's like a
lame generic default tweet. It doesn't have the extra flair. Why is my character named combo meal?
Because I, I felt like it today. All right. Are you, are you good to go? Uh, that depends. Are
you good to go? I mean, I am now, by the way, you're only getting face cam for 10 minutes today.
I've decided. Oh, why's that? Why? Because I, I had a, I had, look at big side burns and I was
going to do like a big side burn joke. Wait, why, why did you do it? I know. Cause I like, I,
I had to, I had to leave the house and I was like, I have, okay, if I leave the house,
then I'm going to look, I'm going to look fucking weird. Cause it was, I did it deliberately weird.
I think it was so, it was so bunched up right here. I'll have to do like the shave joke,
have something real weird, but not today. Today is very normal. No, just do wait. Hey, wait,
do you want to have the be as gross as possible challenge with me? Uh, what does that? I don't
think I need to explain very much more. Be as, as when, is this like a, like a date or is this
just now? No, this is just, it's just like, they just don't shave and don't cut your hair for like
a year. I, I don't, I'm trying to do the not shave again. My beard's getting pretty, pretty chunky,
but I've been trimming it so that it doesn't go in my mouth. I don't even know what would happen
to me. Just, and I'm not, when I talk about don't shave, I mean nothing. You don't do any cleanup.
You don't do any trims. It's just let it just go and don't do anything. You, you, you have to do
you a little bit. Well, for me, my mustache gets long enough that it curls into my mouth.
And if I didn't trim that, then it's like, I have, I'm eating my own hair all day. Yeah. I mean,
well, the, the one thing that we, the one thing that I would allow is that just trim it. So that
doesn't go in your mouth, but everything else has to stay. Okay. I mean, yeah, go for it. Have you
ever had a beard? No, I, the same thing happens every single time. I get to the point where I,
I get to that exact moment where just let it go for another month and see what it looks like.
And I go, no, this is fucked up looking. And I get rid of it. I never crossed that threshold.
I got a break for the awkward stage. That's right. And I never do you, you just, just a mustache,
I think would be great for you. My head doesn't feel like especially like a little, a little curly
mustache on the ends. It feels like that's your vibe. By the way, I took the is stir my type
test and the answer is no. Well, no one was my type. That was impossible. Can you air dash?
Yeah. Can you eat me whole? No. I put a freebie on there for you. I did. So you probably had more
than most. Yeah. It turns out, sorry. Not compatible. Sorry. I mean, if you got like 20%, I could make
some, um, will you press a for me, please? Are we playing? I'm waiting for you. Wait,
you never explained the grossest part was the grossest possible stream. Just
throw your beard out. You can't walk and chew gum at the same time. I don't even know anything
about the game. We're going to like, as soon as I click star game, if you're going to say quiet,
there's a cinematic. And then you're going to say like, wait, I don't know what these are.
Is no cinematic in this game is that that's not going to happen. We're going with this. It's like
a roguelike. All right. I just want one question answered. Yeah. Is the grossest possible stream
just you growing your beard? Yeah. It's just, it just don't. Yeah. How was that gross? Well,
that's not, I mean, I'm just saying like, just, I don't know. Maybe the word is disheveled.
What's the right word? So anyone who has a beard is like gross and to show. No, no, I'm saying if
you don't do any, don't like trim it, don't do any maintenance, don't, don't do any trimming,
just let it just go caveman style. There are plenty of people that that rock beards phenomenally
well. I'm talking no maintenance at all. I'm just talking, just let it go caveman style.
And I'm talking eyebrows too. And ear hair and the hair that grows in your fucking ear too. Wait,
you shave your eyebrows? No, I fuck. You don't, you don't do any maintenance here? No. Come on,
I was born this way. Okay. And you don't, you don't pull the gross old man hairs out of your ears?
Never. That's not a thing. That's not a thing. I said I wasn't going to be gross today and look
at you. You're just trying to fill the void. I've left. I do like that. It points to you.
How is it? How is, how is plucking your eyebrows just slightly? So I just, I don't like when hair
is in the middle. That's fine. If you don't want a unibrow, but when you're saying like,
I pluck my brows, that's a whole no, I'm talking about like here. Come on. And look what you got
to do a little bit of maintenance. I think you're ashamed of being a man. I've just told you I wanted
to grow all my hair out for like a year. So called it gross and disheveled grow your hair out.
You're missing the context. What is this sound effect that you're making right now with your
mouth? Am I? This is not you doing this. No, that's just like void waiting for all. We just
got to go. We don't have any. No. Enter the tears of the kingdom. Okay. And you skipped the opening
cut scene. You fucked up my joke. I didn't because we already saw it before the stream. It didn't
exist. What's going on right now? Why is this so weird? What? What is going on? What's happening
with this? I don't know. I'm certainly not me because I'm not doing anything weird. Did you,
did you do this? I don't even know what you're talking about. Are you ready? Oh, dude,
is money in this game? Are you serious? There's seriously money. Um, the dash. We both got the
money. We share it. That's good. Oh, yeah. You know, you know, dodge rolls. Yeah, you know,
dodge rolls. So do we have any context of what's happening right now? I don't think so. I think
the world's ending and we're the only ones who can save it because we're the Ember Knight. Hey,
hey, idiot, idiot. Are they high frames? I haven't played this. I'm in a weird mood. I'm sorry.
He hasn't streamed in a while and just comes back and is like, I'm going to go super great.
I'm going to do something insane that you guys have never seen, but I'm not going to shave.
But I mean, it was, it's different to everybody here.
Dude, I got, hey, I'm cooking up some wild shit. I'm telling you, I'm not going to shave for two
months. Yeah. The German contents got a weird direction. Wait, wait, wait. We have to decide
who do we share? I want shield. I want the charge. You didn't even you need. We need to roll for it.
Oh, I guess I'm going to be the fire guy. Well, your head looks like fire. You're a fireman.
That's kind of your thing. Oh, you have to hit enemies 10 times to get your thing. Okay. Okay.
So we just wasted them. That's not like a burp at first. And now it doesn't.
Now it does. Annoying. I joke is ruined. Are we going to, are we going to destroy?
I was thinking today because I heard that like Diablo four is like closer launch than I thought.
And I was like, I should ask Jerma if he wants to like do a co-op Diablo four and it comes out
and now he's going to destroy every single barrel. I'm just going to, he's going to read
every single item again and I'm going to fucking make the worst content I've ever made in my life.
Like it's probably not a good idea. You don't want to play Diablo four. Yeah. I mean, I, I don't,
I don't, I don't know what I'm going to do with these ones. I feel like D four is going to be a
game that I play just like on the couch. You're damn it. You're the reason they're making these
games so shit. No. What are you talking about? Couch Diablo sacrilege. Why? You're almost dead
by the way. I am room fine. Yeah. Hey, hey, worry about yourself. I have been and that's why I'm
not taking so much damage. All right. What did you just say? Don't just pick up stuff. I want to
see what it does. Okay. Read it. Whenever you use a skill, you throw a snowball at a random enemy
that damages and freezes them and does fight damage. And this one is, is your first skill
deals bonus damage. You don't have, what are you doing? What do you have for a skill right now?
Shield charge. Do you want the bonus damage? Yeah. Okay. So now I, I am both fire and ice.
You're an anime character. What, what the hell? What was the last sentence that you just said
before this? Oh, we just, uh, Diablo four. Oh, you, you talk about, no, no, no. You talk about
me playing on the couch. Oh, on the couch. Yeah. Couch. So if I'm connected to a PC
and I play Diablo four with a controller in my hand on the couch, I'm on PC by the way.
Does that make me a bad person? Yeah. Why? I just want the control scheme of the controller. I don't,
that's all I want. I'm not, I just want the controls. I just want the controller control scheme.
It's totally valid. And if you want to do that, that's fine. But you're the reason the game's bad.
No, no, I'm not. Like if people like you didn't exist, they would have made a much better game.
Oh, sorry. I, oh, it was, they were the same thing. Hey, if you, you want to compare ours
and Diablo two, we can do that. You would win by a long shot. I was like, what, what,
this guy's crazy. I like playing Diablo with a controller. Well, one specific reason
because left clicking with my hand, my hand can start to hurt after a while. After a long gaming
session in Diablo, click, click, click, click, click, click, click, click, click, click, click,
click, click, click. It hurts. I feel that I only want it to be able to press X. That's it. I
give me the PC. Well, no, no, like I, I, I understand because Victor Fran was like a
controller action RPG and it's a very good game. So you know what? I'm going to stop being such an
elitist and I'm going to let you have the W you could sit on your couch and you can play Diablo
four. Why not? There's no choices being made. There's nothing you need to do. Why shouldn't
you be able to play it with a controller? It's annoying that I'm going to die before you right
now. Cause like what you're saying is like, like I have two health and you have 23. And if I die
first, then everything you're saying is valid. You're playing with a controller right now.
How are you? Yeah. Yeah. I'm on, I'm on mouse and keyboard. So
hold on. Point stand. Nope. Hold on a second. I'm going to, I'm defending this to the death.
Okay. In the menu of the game on the bottom left, it says controller is recommended for the best
experience. It literally says that I win. Where does it say that? In the menu, right at the bottom
of the menu. Well, you got me there. You and stir should box. I would drop them. There's no way.
That's another thing. Like, you know, I was thinking of asking you to play Diablo four and
I know it would be a bad time and you know, we should definitely box, but like sometimes in my
chat, people like me and you should play guilty gear together. And I'm like, what's the fun in me
just like destroying you? Like, like it's funny for like 30 seconds and then we need to do something
else. Street Fighter, the same thing with boxing. Street Fighter six is, seems like it's going to be
awesome by the way. Does it? It does. Do you, what do you, how much do you know about Street Fighter
six? I played the demo. I did the tutorial and the demo and I've been, I know that I want to play
Maria. She's the big giant Dami mommy. And that's like the one thing that has me like still thinking
that I might play the game. I don't really play fighting games with the one thing that's pulling
me there is the go and fight random pedestrians on the street. Oh, oh, oh yeah. That was a character
creator and you can make some really weird weirdos for sure. There's a part of that tutorial. I got
the demo. I tried it. There's a part of that game that's just like, oh yeah, by the way, um, welcome
to the open world. Everybody around you, you can just challenge them to a fight. And it's even like,
there's just people like on their cell phone, just talking and you can go up and challenge them.
And you just, was that a demo? Yeah. You just fight like a regular person. I missed all that.
You missed it. Okay. Well, you got to check that out. I've seen it in the trailers, but you know,
I missed it. I only did like the demo and then there was only Ryu and Ken. And then I was like,
okay, where's my Dami mommy? And I closed it. I'm going to go to poison.
You got one health, dude. I know what we've been talking and shit. There's an inventory.
I think we have to equip stuff. Or maybe not. I think it being in those slots is what there's
like a slot limit. Okay. I assume. Okay. Be careful in this next room there, bud. Oh, I see.
Okay. Holding it. Watch out there, buddy. I didn't get hit. Watch out, pal. Watch your own screen.
Boss next room, pal. Okay, pal. All right there. This is a mini boss. Looks pretty big to me.
All right. You fight it. I'll be I'll be over here with a mushroom.
Snake. That was chicken. Fuck. What's he doing? What's he doing? You have the chicken. We both
have 11 health. What? I was behind him. He hit me. He cheated. He dashed forward and hit me behind
him. Cheated. That was fun. The game feels pretty fluid. Yeah, it's pretty crunchy. Pretty cream
cheesy. I can I can understand that. Finally. Help. Get these loiterers out of here. Wait. Oh,
God. He's got bugs. What was the thing? I forget. What was the thing? Diablo 4. Diablo 4? You are
and I'm trying to be nice about this but you probably are the biggest ARPG elitist I've ever
met in my whole life. And I mean by a long shot by an unbelievable amount. Thank you.
I appreciate it. How do you actually feel about D4? I feel like. I mean absolutely no disrespect
by the way. I mean you're very. That is the compliment. I've put a lot of time in being such
a guy. I feel like it's it's way too simple. There's no choices to making character creation
and it's going to get real boring real fast when you get to end game and you're just finding
I oh my unique sword. Oh now I have to find the legendary sword of that exact same sword. Oh now
I have to find the ancient sword like it's just I feel like it's just going to be the same thing
over and over again with no actual choices. Okay and I am going to wait until the end game
is available. I'm going to hold my opinion until then. Well once you have to farm the third variant
of unique status of your same weapon then you let me know and then and then finally play POE so you
have something to actually compare it to or Torchlight Infinite. What was the whole rant
that you went on that you said that like Titanfall hypnotized everybody to pretend that it was a good
game or something? Titanfall? Didn't you say like Titanfall? Well back when Titanfall came out you
were like everybody thought it was great and you were like I don't like it and it's not good.
You said it was like you said it was like I don't think it was Titanfall. You said that Titanfall
was like an illusion game or something whatever it was. I've definitely said this this was not
my chat saying they think it was Valorant. I think Titanfall 2 is one of the best
games like FPS games ever so I doubt I said that. I'm probably thinking of a different game.
Titanfall was good. I thought Titanfall was good. I've said that about vampire survivors for sure.
That's maybe what it was so now I'm like this um like what why Titanfall? I don't know where you
pulled Titanfall out of here. Where did Titanfall come from? It hypnotized yeah it was we're talking
about vampire survivors it hypnotized everyone there's no no I've also just said this about
Loop Hero. Absolutely nothing happens in Loop Hero. I swear I'm telling you you said this before.
Well Loop Hero was a long time ago and I probably said that about that as well. Let me see what I
just got. So this stuff is level one Loop Hero. I've never played it. You would fucking love Loop
Hero dude. Would I? If I'm saying it's a game that makes you think it's a game you will love it.
Can't you just like enjoy shit and can't you just like have fun? I enjoy a lot of shit very
passionately that's why I'm saying that there's other things better that you can be spending
your time on other than like vampire survivors. I will not let you sit here and talk about that
Do you want to play a good game? Do you want to like try a cool game I recommend? Oh like oh Jade
Cocoon? Want to play POE? Yeah dude Jade Cocoon. Jade Cocoon is one of the rarest video games of
all time. Is it? You can't find it anywhere. Did you actually look? Yeah dude I looked everywhere.
That's a shame because everyone's holding on to it because it's such a such a little gem.
It's a good series.
I know I know what that reference is. Oh you mean little gem. I thought you meant Jade Cocoon.
Jade Cocoon 2 was the game that was available and I remember I asked you I said hey dude I can't
find Jade Cocoon 1. Is Jade Cocoon 2 okay? I believe it was like $400 and you were like
no dude and that's the wrong one. Yeah I heard I never played it but I heard Jade Cocoon 2 was
terrible. Can somebody confirm that with me? I it's they're expensive and they're rare.
All right do you want a gem of wisdom or do you want something else? Uh or or gem gem a
path let's power up. Wait wait wait hold on. I don't know what this is. Two is better? It's
$60 on eBay. Two is good. I guess I was it's like 50 bucks. How much is Jade Cocoon 1? Did I just
make that number up? Nope I didn't. It's a hundred bucks. $75. Okay I start at what point is how much
percentage over something that's expensive isn't over complete overreaction? Like what percentage
wise? Like if I said dude it's like 500 bucks and if it was like 200 bucks is that still okay?
Uh I believe I think that's pretty bad because because you're saying dude it's fine you're saying
it very confidently and very assertively and very aggressively so it needs to be more accurate the
more you're like if you're like I think it's like 500 and if it was 200 that'd be okay that's true
but you you sound like you know what you're talking about you really have no idea yeah that's right
that's you're right that's bad that's bad that's that's bad dude if I had been like um I I think
that game is like expensive I don't know I'm not sure but I got angry with you and told you it was
$400 it's not even correct I got angry and just like guessed higher
all right do you get to pick a skill here too are we both picking one?
I think we both pick it's the second yeah yeah okay I pick and then you pick I like that
well you're literally a little bit of a magician okay let's get the hearts the healing let's get
the healing fountain I think how do we what is it the middle mouse okay you're on controller
I don't know what my the recommended way by the way yeah I know so you can dash over there healing
spring oh oh you're you're taking it all oh whoops okay sorry all right I did not think it was
gonna do that I we've shared everything in the game so far I figured we both could share
that together we've both been getting the same drops and that is true no the the shop we can
only buy like the same core items frozen frozen oh you froze him so let me practice this because
are you doing perfect uh I don't know what that is okay so when you hold down your ability it's
gonna fill up that bar you have to wait till it gets completely full and you have to time it
correctly to let go at the perfect time and then it does more stuff just to let you know well if
you're like practicing it you're still consuming uses and yeah you'll you'll get it you're much
more than I am I feel like I had a lot to talk about today like I feel like there was a lot of
things where I was you know what I want to get his opinion on this like what I don't know you've
asked me like one question it'll come I have a question yeah um as a reminder not being weird
today what is your like deepest fantasy and as a fantasy I'm defining as something that
you know will never happen riding on okay I got it riding on a roller coaster alone alone yeah
like having a theme park completed by being able to go to like disney world completely alone with
like the five people I feel like that could happen if you really wanted to have I don't think so
okay mine is a notebook where I've taken notes in it for a long time and every single page is
perfectly filled up with the exact like cool thing I wanted to write in it and there's like
drawings to go along with it like if you look through the notebook when you go along like it's
it's like a macula perfect handwriting it's like a joy to look at how is that not achievable
that's simply not it's how could how how could you do that so fire somebody because no every
time you like go to write a page of notes you start then like you realize like I don't need to
like I don't need to take notes on this anymore like it's not as in depth as I thought like I'm
over like you know and then like every page doesn't line up with the page before it like
you're trying to get like a chronological set of notes you know I'm saying I mean you you could
compile a bunch of stuff and if somebody helped you put it together and clean it up
that's just a whole career about people doing that it's like literally like proofreading
copy reading all kinds of stuff like that watch out final phase oh he shut down
you were supposed to keep dpsing I didn't die because if you just hit him if you just hit up
with me I'm fine I didn't die back up you could also rent out an amusement park all right I have
a feeling that renting out Disney World for a week is probably going to cost you millions of
dollars yeah it doesn't need to be Disney World yeah I'm just saying like I've I okay well then
what's an amusement park there's a there's a um there's a water park near where I live
and they sell like the exclusive pass like skip the line I was there nobody buys it there was a
line of like 60 people for like a water slide nobody in the premium one and it's like it's
like ten dollars more expensive oh it was crazy craziest thing I've ever seen in my life so it's
basically like you're there alone like you just walk you get you get the satisfaction of walking
past 60 people and just doing it as well did I buy it no I was in line give it to me please
but if I ever go again give it to me please hey that's because you lived on the bus because
you didn't know the rules I dodged the most enemy attacks too by the way I also dealt all the damage
what else did I do oh you ate all the food wow good for you I killed more enemies yeah it's called
last hitting okay I'm stepping it up oh yeah do you really want to make this like a whole
like a whole thing oh one of my biggest fantasies just came true right there I beat stir in a video
game no we both had two stars oh shit now I know that like I have to actually care now because like
I don't want you to get any wings shit yeah yeah you're playing now too hmm armor is always good
yeah I'm going armor yeah I'm going with this more skill damage so I do one and then the other
back to back apparently we got a buff in the horn I hate these sound effects it's like dial up
yeah I feel like oh so Esper actually summoned you I would have expected him to perish from
old age before actually making a move cringe this is the first time I've seen an ember knight
the defenders of the nexus thanks for telling me what I am is that supposed to be a joke a sneeze
could blow you away oh fuck it's hardly worth the effort but I'll give you something to play with
cringe and no you know you go ahead oh you do it this is the only minuscule portion of my power
try not to break too quickly yeah I could do it too yeah you can pretty good oh fuck I died
I was being a fucking idiot and just I don't know I had fun it doesn't matter oh defeat mini
boss to revive you that wasn't the mini boss okay well I hope you like watching what I was
just like admit I was mashing X and doing like a wicked weird face I thought it was fun you seem
to be in a mood today yeah sometimes sometimes don't worry I'll get you back pal pick those up
this is a rogue like be careful I'm aware I'm aware you don't want to die on the right side
right side okay where do I go now uh yeah use uh your one more you're using it not that often
I'm using I'm using it pretty often uh there was a like doors up here up here using my one
oh what those things icicles randomly explode yeah the icicles hurt if you touch them the icicles hurt
you can't dodge through them and the doors over on the left side by the way so you're kind of
fighting in a weird spot okay good advice it's fine because all the healing items are for me now
left side right yep there you go there's more than one door
anybody that comes to stream right now don't even doesn't even know you're here
oh we're getting a five nights at freddy's watch stream and we're getting the ember knight watch
stream I don't think people understand just how much I'm looking forward to that five nights at
freddy's watch along mini bosses oh boy that was like the first room yeah you have to go I
think you have to you're gonna get all the stars too and it's gonna be like you're gonna piss me off
yeah make sure you don't skip that screen oh dude oh dude oh someone's getting some move speed level
up yeah level up they did damage make a funny voice no can you announce the date for more
sorcery um he's doing it tomorrow he told me in private I was gonna be a huge fucking surprise
dude he's circles that was gonna be a huge surprise now I know I don't even I don't have the
motivation to do it again tomorrow just took all the motivation from me I was gonna be a surprise
to my community um I apologize maybe you'll play a cool game instead I need to have some room in
between now I think it'd be a lot easier with like another guy yeah it would be you got this
though you're doing fine there's no dk barrel that you can just pick up and throw and I can jump out
of it wait I these are locked I have to actually swap something out now wait why is it showing me
it's showing me stat upgrade for me but it's making me choose from your combo meal body
I'm confused uh I don't know when I get revived can we do the thing that we that they do in donkey
country where I go you can you can do whatever you want but personally I love monkeys those
people that get it you get it those people that don't sorry I don't like these enemies so true I
agree yeah so true bestie mini boss time you better kill it uh I got no health just chill
yeah that's like two guys to like help help on the left help on the left
oh like hey you handle the ads I'll do the boss yeah I got eyes on you're doing fine you got
I got this nice get up karma nice stand up let's go for it oh spawns are the same health as me nice
let's go for it now let's like go in the shop and like over gear you you know what I mean do you need
this I don't think I can use it what do you need this I don't think I can use it hello is that
even coming through to you no oh never mind what was it I was recording oh all right so here
hundred and you got a lot more money than I do oh I'll take it I'll take that can you buy something
for me um I just spent a lot of money I don't have money for these now okay I I unfortunately
used it on myself watch out these enemies are tough watch out dude dude great work if I come
back and beat you how could that possibly happen anything is possible I killed the whole mini
boss by myself you know what I believe in you if anyone can do it it's you I think we're actually
doing really well I mean this is our first run ever yeah we're at the end of stage two soon
let's take a step you don't want the healing fountain hmm I mean you yeah let's do that
you could use it I feel like we probably should have taken the gem because the boss rooms seem
to also always heal you beforehand I think we can go to full yeah we should have taken the gem
is there like a a greater of application um I don't know perfect I don't think so all right
can we just take a quick second to see what do the stats do uh agility is was 10 move speed
precision is crit chance or something okay so crit chance they're spoiled it so we didn't get
the announcement oh wait people together people think that was real um what was the announcement
I didn't hear it that I'm gonna play sorcery oh you've already beat like all of them like six
times have you ever played sorcery yeah you did right yeah beat the first one you didn't
do this I I might have done like half of the second one I can't remember second one's the
best one I feel like stirred now would appreciate that game a lot more what do you think maybe I
mean I liked it when I played it I honestly can't remember why I stopped not that stir
back years ago wouldn't know but you like that game is right up your alley in your current
my current form the current form maybe yeah maybe I try it yeah maybe we play peewee together
or not together you yeah but you whatever yeah whatever why is so loud very loud maybe you spend
the five hundred dollars for gate cocoon what is this what's going on we got yeah see it always
heals and now we like we have like full health already we shouldn't have done it shit are you
ready person to get hit loses first person to get hit loses okay I knew you were going to just go
walk and stand in the corner you can play at that game and my character can actually go invisible
I'm pretty ranged what I'm invisible yes yeah you need like a cheap way to win right now
because you were dead for the whole stage what watch out for his ice attack watch out for his
ice watch out he's invincible but let's watch out for the sword dude you just froze the ice king
that's insane that's true yeah tps time if you're gonna beat me it's now guys I want to see these
oh shit what shit yourself right I got liquid all of me so you want this
it's like every time I take a sip out of my drink it's oh it's like way over here
because I hate it when it's in the way of my other monitor so I have to like
crouch creep over here drink out of my drink I turned into like a goblin when I go take a sip
all right what do you want do you want this um you should probably take it
it's weird that the bosses only give one power up and everything else
like duplicates it for us you look like luigi luigi's fucking cool luigi is the cooler brother
okay like being luigi's not cool new outfit wow mario is categorically better who's it gonna be
oh I hope it's me okay receive the most damage oh god hit too many times looks like
is it pretty good yeah I was dead the whole entire level that that's pretty good for coming back in
the first dying in the first room and then coming back in the last room you got the spectator
badge I've never got that before that's crazy all right this one's now the real one our our
damage taken is actually one damage apart yeah that's weird yeah that must be a bug this level
looks cool I think uh when when early access came out this was the end of the game this stage
so I don't I I'm like vaguely remember seeing someone play it how long has this been in early
access for I think it's been a year not 100 sure it's pretty it's pretty good an early access game
that was in early access for like a year good yeah yeah yeah it's pretty good that's pretty good
it seems like a pretty good turn around what's wrong I got hit yeah we also oh this is me uh
poisons them aren't you poisoning people uh I am so I should probably take it already I
apparently you like level one to level two I already have that I like that I also have fire
I have to replace something though don't I um I don't know I don't know if you get the second
row you do okay wow we are the ember knights dude you know what game is coming out that I
I'm sorry I'm talking and getting hit you know game is coming out that I completely forgot existed
and I cannot wait to play this game what the golem lord of the rings game I don't even know
about that that's coming out in like a week I can't wait to play that game you have to play
as golem yeah you just play you play as golem it's a third person action stealth game I don't know
who is it made by I fucking died and because I'm talking dude I'm just talking I can't man so
so maybe maybe I let them kill me no no no we need to continue here you get to get you get to
keep talking now tell me about this game it's a game where you play as golem and it looks kind of
fucked up it just doesn't yeah I don't know I don't know what to think about it
I don't even know who made it I just know that it exists and it's just he's crawling around he's
just like crawling around like this wait wait who is it made by I don't know that's not a real game
yeah it is it's I'm telling you it's a real game stop talking out your ass no the whole
trailer for the golem game is a bunch of close-ups of his face going like this like and then it shows
him like crawling over shit I'm gonna have a lot of fun with that game just you wait yeah every 10
to 20 seconds in that trailer it goes like this just zooms in on his face I almost got hit like
trying to look at your stream which I don't even have open to see what the face was
you're gonna scream at the day it comes out uh well I don't know about that we'll see
am I gonna be the only no there's no way I'm not the only day one golem lord of the rings scream
that's not gonna happen that's how many people are gonna play this why wouldn't they it's like a big
franchise I'm gonna die out here champ well it's a rogue like I don't think we're supposed to beat
it on the first try yes you are oh right stir is stir is gonna be very upset if we can't stir
hates progress stir hates resetting and progressing he hates it what are you talking about stir does
not like when a game forces you to have to start over and progress distinctly I don't like when you
die and then it gives you 700 bonus damage and then three extra lives this is different I like
restarting my identity is restarting do I want any of these do a golem cosplay just like like
grease in my hair and have it come down like this and just like I don't know make myself look old
hey exactly why I should never have shaved I have no shirt on just eat a raw fish isn't it funny
that when you know you only have less than 10 health that's when you actually care more than
anything yeah I don't know how my armor works the 14 armor I have is that just damage reduction
I was hoping that would be like extra life shop game is saved volume impression the whole time
no healing whenever you crit heal games over wait what is it whenever I crit I heal
hmm
could you just talk like that forever good you just like I don't want drama anymore I want to play
with golem that was cow from cow and chicken I guess they're one in the same I never never
thought about it chicken it's me cow it kind of is a little if I really tried I I might be able
to do it although that that that's Charlie Adler the voice actor one of the most talented human
beings to ever live did almost every voice on that show if you didn't know I didn't know
I gained 19 health that room from hitting things I don't think people understand just how much
influence red guy had on my entire life who's red guy cow and chicken I hated that show so
I kind of remember him I'm sorry I know like you're telling us about your like formative
childhood years and like what meant the most to you and I didn't like it and I know that I
don't like it doesn't like something else but like cow and chicken you don't like anything I
yeah I didn't like your top cartoons growing up top like give me like a top three I that that's
like I don't even know if I could do that pop oh okay I think oh god I did a I did a like uh
cartoon network top shows like quiz thing on stream a while ago so I'm like prepped for this
okay but it was specifically Cartoon Network though what good shows did Nickelodeon even have
oh stop what are you talking about Doug you didn't like Doug how does that hit me this game sucks
fuck that behind him yeah you were saying Doug I didn't like Doug you didn't like Doug
what about Rugrats Doug Rugrats Ren and Stimpy um this is not a cartoon but salute your shorts
that show was come on Spongebob you don't like Spongebob Spongebob's okay hey Arnold
Ren and Stimpy was good Ren and Stimpy should not have been on tv Rocco's modern life did you like
I didn't like that either I didn't like rock rock I can't believe it I don't know Cartoon Network
was just better okay top three we got to compare top three is not like what I don't like you're
going to get because if I do a top three that's the things that I did like then people will be
bass-pilled and true fact it and if I tell you all the things I don't like then I'm a loser
shit okay favorite cartoon grown up like open your stream and see what like how deep in thought you
are that's got to be the Looney Tunes has to be that makes a lot of sense has to be Looney Tunes
I and that's not even Cart that's completely disconnected I honestly the old Looney Tunes
routines are some of the most engaging some of the most fun the Roadrunner I think that Wiley
Coyote and Roadrunner is probably some of my favorite media ever uh Tom and Jerry was I liked
it but I liked Daffy and Bugs's bullshit that they would do back and forth so your top three
is Looney Tunes well I just gave you one it's honestly probably Rugrats I loved Rugrats it was
just such a well Rugrat well I wouldn't put it in top three Rugrat I loved Rug how could you not
like Rugrats yeah it was a great show top three especially because I'm I'm Ren and Stimpy has to
be up there too I it has to be Ashley tells me all the time about how Rugrats is the ugliest show
ever made and her as an artist I hear about it a lot she's not wrong a lot of the old fucking
disgusting hey you're talking about the the class geek super style come on I like the one episode
where is it stews having or one of the kids is like having like a fever dream how's about it uh
class geek super were it was a they had a studio it was a I think it was I'm trying to remember
correctly you're a dude oh it was it was two names it was certain style that was in it was um
did class gate super do uh what the hell what the hell what the hell rocket power was class
geek super they're they're just as ugly stop it I imagine so they did um wild wild thornberries
was osco well uh was class key super right did you like the wild thornberries no I think like
Nigel is funny for like a little bit to just hear him talk and that was about it
okay well all right it's probably all the old looney tunes combined with the x-men cartoon
I would say that's probably number two or three the old x-men cartoon I know it's still the one
where Wolverine's looking at the picture in bed is that the one thing that you have from this whole
entire series because that's that's the one meme it's the meme all right I remember like one other
episode that got dubbed over with juggernaut that's it the Batman animated series was up there as
well probably three spongebob first three or four seasons of spongebob first five seasons of spongebob
get out of here get out of town uh if you want to go even further than that we got some of the
adult swims up uh aquatine aquatine hunger force that's the first smart thing you've said all day
oh please aquatine was was awesome venture brothers was good yeah but that's not I they're
they're not part of this you know what I mean like they're animes that's what that's like if I ask
I ask you what your favorite cartoon is and you say um like one punch man how is that unfair
all right what are we are we going back to the main I feel like I feel like we're staying in
the category of like daytime tv cartoon well but you have and then when you bring in like oh my
favorite cartoon was one punch man that's that's weird well then you have to give me some parameters
to work in or we're just working within the parameters of like daytime tv cartoons then
it's got to be the x-men animated series batman animated animated series rug rats doug rennan
stimpy um cow and chicken like some of those uh uh like johnny bravo i'm just trying to think of
that era like i watched looney tunes i watched them all cat dog is another one classic uh invader
zim i did not really catch or care about until much later so i can't say that on that i'm not
coping i'm setting the parameters there's no opinion in setting the parameter our real monsters
was also class geek supo so did you like that one no it was okay but like you know it was just okay
i just don't think you liked the class geek supo style did you not like the art style that's not
right it has to be what it is i think our real monsters works a bit because they're all supposed
to be ugly okay well what is your top five top 10 cartoons that you watched i cared about
not i can't believe not even brought up at all like ed ed and eddie for real but this guy's hell
wait a minute i don't even care about ed ed and eddie you think that our real monsters is
ugly and all those i don't like the ugly art styles and i don't like the weird kind of way
ed ed and eddie had a wild art style they're almost the same it wasn't ugly it wasn't ugly
no it's not the same it was very close to that kind of old class geek supo style yes it was
ed ed and eddie would fit in the same category as class geek supo and it's great i liked it i just
don't think i'd put it in my top five all right ed ed and eddie let's get another one oh hold on
we have like items we can still purchase more things here if you didn't from the shrine oh i
was like reading that we can start with like uh twice the amount of health that we started with
last time that's pretty good and there's like three different tiers of it so should we unlock
this i'm unlocking this one we don't share these points right uh no so you like unlock the first
one and then the other ones purchase three more upgrades to unlock the other stuff and then even
press e you can respect everything anytime it seems i'm just doing health and money
yeah see this is why it's a roguelike look now we have look at how much health we have
okay so at ed and eddie uh grim adventures billy and mandy yep that's that's a good one um i forget
what was what else was on there oh my god how did i how did i screw this up i can't believe it all
the uh donald duck all the old disney stuff donald duck you like you like yeah like an hour the old
donald duck cartoons he i i love the old donald duck cartoons donald duck would just like fucking
lose his shit he would somebody would just donald duck had a really fucking challenging life
something bad happened to donald duck every episode i don't understand why everyone's like
oh wow i can't believe donald duck's got such a temper yeah he gets fucked with every episode
horrible fucking things happen to him every single day i think i'd be a little upset too
uh yeah the old disney stuff too donald duck especially flapjack that's a good one
oh he's in the bow wait a minute maybe oh just stand in the back and use the bow it actually
does not go that far that's a might be hard to use but i'll try it i believe in you i'm gonna i'm
gonna say sword guy okay uh all right so is that would you consider that to be an accurate
complete list i i'm confident in saying eddie and eddie and grim adventures are like top two
they could even share the same place i don't care okay and then third i i don't i don't really know
like teen titans was pretty pretty good i liked flapjack i like chowder but i don't feel as
strongly about them as uh the top two i i remember i teen titans confused me a lot because i didn't
really pay that much attention to it but i i caught another i caught an episode of it and
they have a different they have like a different series now it's like team titans go and i i've
heard is good i haven't seen any of it the episodes that i watched the regular teen titans was was
good i didn't i don't like not like i have anything against it i thought it was a good show i didn't
really but i i saw that they came with it i didn't know if it was the same thing or not
well that's because you you had to be into it you had to be shipping raven and beast boy
if you weren't doing that then were you really even watching it
it's like the most controversial thing i've ever said bro is flabbergasted
sir they're kids they're teams for one and i'm not saying i will oh dude i want it to be in the
middle no i'm like i would just be happy for raven and beast oh no it's stop talking
move it on okay i don't like these i'm gonna take the what do i take germa what do i do here
i take frost wall it'll help us will it yeah i'll take whatever ice barrier you take it then
dude night's chart night can you drop items because night's charge was so good and you've got a bow
i'll i'll give you the chakram if we could so bad okay i wanted frost ball so bad
i'm taking okay chat chat to just like dive into this a little bit first are you telling me that
you want it fucking what was it beast boy and terra i'm gonna go i'm gonna go wash my windows
i'll be back and terra that shit was so fucking lame i don't even know what he's talking about
i but i know i feel like i have to cut his mic i don't know who he's talking about should i cut
his mic i'll be back back in like an hour he's talking about a tv show okay are you all right to
be clear are you muting me no you're here okay wait are you okay you're actually i thought you
were actually getting up to go do something i know you have like the old person thing you have to
like pee every 20 seconds apparently i do feel like it says something unhinged germa praise is
that what this says germa praise what i thought it said germa praise pretend he didn't hear him
oh pray like you started i was like oh i thought it said that i from rain oh lord i told you i'm not
even being weird today these are like normal people opinions a lot of people agree uh can you pick
your item please uh i don't know is there a description of how poison works i feel like
you're the kind of like coward who would use poison like if i ever die from poison it was probably
you i'm not taking it you can take some poison shit poison is guaranteed damage when you know
that you can't be there to do it tick damage is so huge affliction warlock was one of the best
classes in all of world of warcraft you know why why because the dot damage you just walk away and
you could just dodge mechanics and not actually focus on like contributing actually that is a
huge deal because you can pay attention to the encounter and not worry about not worry about you
know don't stand in the shit as they say right don't stand in the thing you could pay attention
much easier is that your is your favorite wow build of all time you you identify as a affliction
warlock looks your warlock was awesome not anymore i don't cookie clicker gameplay yeah sorry let's
just go okay doesn't work the bow is pretty good it seems uh seems good seems good seems good
when was the last time you actually played affliction warlock i don't know like like 2000
whatever year it was i can't relate to this wow talk i'm not a wower really this doesn't do that
much damage at all are you getting the perfect i think so yeah yeah it doesn't look like it is
i mean it like pierces targets that seems really good i think if you do perfect in a row it's better
oh that sounds perfect times five all right i gotta be good is this the stream he said he was
gonna do where he's gonna ditch stir and play breath of the wild um i didn't have a plan to do
that precision or power power i can't remember what power did i want to get it watch out watch
out there pal damage plus three holy what they're just handing those out
look at us not taking any damage we did all right yeah we did pretty good already at the mini boss
i mean i take i took a few hits but sorry nah we're very distracted nah dude we're good
we did this guzzle wound don't worry we got this guzzle wound okay but i'm still mad i died on
that last one because i was behind the guy shooting the laser i just thought about it again
that was a plus 15 perfects in a row epic epic yeah eat up why did i fucking laugh at that
what i don't know it's just like weird how you said it i don't it was i don't know yeah man eat up
but do you got how do you have more gold than me because i am gaming what are you gonna buy
oh whenever you crit your skills refresh that seems this one seems kind of insane while you
have 150 gold or more gain bonus move speed and crit i think i can anybody confirm is the perfect
a guaranteed crit or no it's probably not yeah press tab and like hover over the bow and read
it i want to buy stuff though uh this thing sounds kind of good all right now i gotta work on crit
all right can you please say happy birthday to me otherwise i won't just like the sims
somebody said they if i don't say happy birthday they won't it won't happen or something was it
happy birthday whoever you were i didn't uh talk to the top right just top left you good
i'm good happy birthday whoever that is i really shouldn't have gotten hit by that but i did
you know it happens to the best of us skills selector yeah you get that second skill you start
popping off oh it's i you identify just like the third of those we found uh blast bomb or
oh night night's charges night night's charge nice charge every time nice charge yeah why would i
have picked up night's charge i'm i'm using a bow because uh you're invulnerable while you do it and
it stuns everything so you could dash away from things kind of like i'll try this oh that's what
i've been using pretty good not bad pretty good yeah it seems like you've been having a ball with
yeah absolute ball when is star going to play five nights at freddy's wait while stir plays
five nights at freddy's can we watch the emoji movie um no that answers the point is to watch
the point is to watch me play five nights at freddy's i don't know why that's the point but
that is what the point is that's what that's what he decided he wanted i can't believe you've never
played five nights not once ever i feel like that's so i don't know how you avoided that
being a youtuber back in 2012 how did you even avoid not playing it that's like saying you've
never played minecraft before minecraft's an actual game yeah but i but but you know what i'm
saying though how did you avoid it but i just didn't do it i just i just played what i wanted
to play you know what i mean it's 10 hp dude your your health is getting up there man oh there's a
game that i i want to stream it looks i don't know why i just got reminded of it looks really
interesting it came out like a golem game yeah brog this is game coming out did you play as
golem from lord of the rings and you crawl you don't remember that woman i said that one
before i said that i remember when you said that uh have you heard him do you hear that that was
weird did anybody hear that i i didn't hear it did you hear like the no i didn't does anybody
so when you're talking sometimes do you sometimes and people don't ever kind of
notice that you do it maybe sometimes people hear you do it but do you ever while you're talking
game you wanted to play just listen when you talk sometimes do you go like this like blah blah blah
i know that wasn't the game uh did you do that you fucked me up okay do you ever talk and
sometimes you just go like like you just like yeah and then uh and and so i have to do
i feel like that happens to way more of us than will care to admit i what is the question i'm
confused what's the question do you sometimes have like air squeak come out of your throat
sometimes while you are talking i guess like have you ever noticed that you go like yeah i
my voice cracked pretty bad the other day no no not a voice crack this is just like air escaping
in the middle of your sentence just like i think that's kind of the same no a true voice crack is
like and i no no no i'm talking about you're like yeah and uh i also went to the store i can't hear
anything so well the people in my my community can oh congrats dude i'm i'm not gaming oh i am
yeah because you have the bow he even attacked you one you gotta clear the ads they're coming
after the they're coming after the caster dude well i'm gonna die i'm gonna die dude
skill damage plus 20 you better not die with that better not die picking that shit up after
the boss everyone's telling you to apologize oh wait about what apologize for you said
hold on oh stop who killed that boss because you you you didn't you refused to eat so therefore
i didn't need to i i've got potato chip grease all over my controller that's what's going on
okay oh you said ayaya apologize for saying ayaya that's what they're saying i said what's wrong
with you i'm i'm just relaying what 500 000 people just said i have a question for you sir
yeah i have a question yeah it always starts like that i got a question for you hey listen
man i got a question for you okay and i'm gonna answer this question like it's it's a job interview
okay how long realistically speaking if you and i both sat here and in a high pitch voice said
ayaya over and over again how long would it take for us to lose 90 percent of reviewers they're
here be realistic i think like most people would stay yeah for a while to be like how long
we probably go it's really happening i think it would go up yeah like at a certain point like
an hour and someone will make like a post on like twitter like dude they're still doing the ayaya
and like more people show up true especially if we came up with like a good reason for why we were
doing it like we're doing this to protest the war in vietnam come send our troops home
ayaya do ayaya for charity
it's because there's something wrong with you um what's you're just gonna say dragon ball z
what's your favorite anime we're talking about cartoons now we're gonna talk about adult animated
cartoons from japan i can tell you that because i have seen quite a few
uh it is not what everybody in here thinks it is my favorite okay so let me say
okay i really do genuinely love the entire concept and i'm a big i'm a big concept guy right oh this
guy i don't i don't really care about um i just love like just i want to interrupt i love
that was the first time i've really done it but i asked you a question and then i watched your
gameplay and i just fucking i loved it how quickly it degraded you were just like charging arrows and
shooting at like walls i was yeah anyway so back back on track favorite anime this the concept of
this series and we're talking that this could be uh most
so good i'm just giving hey do you ever think that if you have like do you ever think that
you have a dog right yes i don't know why i just thought of this but like do you ever think that
like your dog is usually if they're over the age of 10 they're like 60 you ever think that it's
like funny that there's like some 70 year old just 70 year old dude just lying on your couch
i've never thought of it like that you ever think it's like think do you ever think your
dog just lying there like ah yeah this is comfortable can i have some food it's just
like a 70 year old guy just lying on the couch okay i like pick auto up and i'm like oh let's
go auto it's like an old man like ah yeah carry me up the stairs human just as a refresher i asked
him what his favorite anime was like five minutes ago one punch man but isn't mob psycho just the
better one punch man yeah people keep saying that but um i gotta get i gotta okay the concept of
one punch man the entire series it's that's a really interesting series is well i don't spoil
anything but what that that's a concept that i find very interesting because i need to see
where they're going with it like i need to know where they're going with that because you know
it's gonna something has to happen right it's an amazing concept uh something something does have
to happen in the show well but i mean something it makes you think about like wait what's going
on here what the heck's happening here i feel you music um when when he goes in for a punch
when satama goes for a punch and they play that fucking song that like
oh man just like look he's gonna do it he's gonna do it he's gonna do it and you know it's gonna
happen and you know it's you know what's gonna happen and then he does it and he does it and
then the thing he won and then there was one punch so i am just i need to know what's going
on there that's why i like that show but now that you know what's going on there i don't that change
it i don't i don't i actually don't know what i don't i what do you mean you don't know did you
not watch the show yeah but but but we i don't i haven't read the manga or anything why can he do
that right and spoilers in chat you're gonna get permanent you will be permanently banned from
this channel no but then i just just yeah i know but like come on just wait isn't the anime like
over no there's not more in the manga i don't i wouldn't know i don't think it's over yet i
don't know how to read i'm pretty sure it's over it's still going i think there's still some more
left i think it's coming close the mount the manga is coming close to ending isn't it the
manga is ongoing there's a lot more in the box yeah all right i'm serious you you will get
brought from this community i don't want to see shit over here mods you know what to do if you see
the real shit okay okay all right uh if it's not one punch man i mean full metal alchemist is
a really simple oh yeah you're you're i remember you're you're a full metal alchemist killed it
was cool i liked it and you're telling me that you don't ship winry with anyone
i just i enjoyed the show man okay i enjoyed the television show okay somebody said stop him
what do you mean do you guys know that humans like are romantically intertwined on the regular
like it's normal for a man and a woman or whoever wants to like kiss whoever is like totally that
happens all the time i'm seeing all these like cat leaning memes what is this cat like leaning
thing oh fuck i'm gonna die chat your mom and your dad kissed shut up passionately your mom
and your dad kissed passionately and some someone's mom could be raven and someone's mom or dad could
be beast boy what's wrong with that breaking hearts what you ready to fight the boss yeah
don't die or if you're gonna die it's a good room to do it because you you wake up afterwards
but you haven't fought this boss before so you're gonna watch out for his ice attacks all right which
one of the teen titans would you want to be what i want to be like if like oh what what teen titan
let's just say you took one of those quizzes oh man um i'd want to be raven is it is it
cliche and lame to say robin kind of i i i was thinking that and i was thinking you were going
to say that because robin's superpower is having social control over everyone and that seems like
the thing that you'd be into it's just just like any anyone says some shit you just shut it down
well i was gonna say because i like nightwing but okay well i guess we'll take that what do you like
about nightwing what's not that like about nightwing i got big got big shoes to fill you know
that's a lot of pressure um you know batman's what essentially is this uh you know sidekick right
and then all of you know wants to be that's a lot of pressure i like the idea of you know he lives
up to it okay you buying anything he also people saying he's got a huge ass nightwing he i honestly
have never really thought about it but to like recollect the trailers that had nightwing in it
he did have a big ass yeah i got something in common with nightwing because it's huge
yeah yeah you're not wrong the snowball was all right try this are we good what was the
quote what were we oh what teen titan you would want to be yeah you said x-men was one of your
favorite shows so which x-men are you um i would say nightcrawler because of the x-men arcade game
my favorite character yeah i'm like nightcrawler i know if it wasn't nightcrawler then it would
probably be either cyclops or probably cyclops or gambit oh beast no beast beast is an easy answer
i like beast what about him i just want to be smart incredibly intelligent he's got brain he's
got uh he's got physical ability he's he's got a problem solving he's reasonable i think that's
he's got leadership written all over but i was saying i don't know what i i i don't i just i
don't know what i wonder what i would why have been hanging out with me way too much i have fun
i'm getting germ uphill my heart for some reason again is telling me that it would be cool to be
dark phoenix and just end the world like like if the world's gotta end wouldn't it be cool if
he's like i did it i mean kind of i mean i look up in the sky and i just see you up there floating
you know what my like least favorite superhero trope is i've been thinking a lot about lately
i don't know why it like keeps coming up and i keep thinking about it there's always the one
hero who has an awesome ability and then does the like it's my burden to have this power i didn't
ask for this oh my god i don't want to have this strength and they have like the best
fucking power in the whole show but they're like not happy about it so wasn't it like uh not uh
the one who touched people was gene gray or just like man i'm so sick of being able to have any
superpower i want at any time make it go away rogue it was rogue yeah oh okay i was like what's he
talking about i was like what what what x-men character just touches people yeah rogue i'm not
just oh no no okay weird you're the one being weird okay no i'm saying i was i'm genuinely
trying to figure out who like their power is they like they go like this i'm dead unfortunate
how do you have 70 how we've been talking this whole time how do you have 72 health
uh because instead of taking the max health perk i took the heal five after every room
because that sounded really by the way rogues power is not touching people power is absorption
absorption stupid idiot sorry i'm i'm sorry i got really i feel like i'm sorry no i i got i just got
every time i have an opinion your whole you want to talk about your community your community dog
piles on me that was uncalled for i'm you're encouraging it and i don't know if i feel welcome
here yeah i just like because it's got really i want to see beast boy and raisin together
doesn't mean i'm weird i'm just gonna keep powering up bring me back bring i have okay
okay uh but rogue's power is absorption okay i believe you remember why are you so toxic
every single thing that sir and i are doing right now is all for real and i mean everything
i'm saying about it no it's the fucked up thing about you is that you're what you're actually
thinking is worse than what you're saying you still haven't killed the mini boss yet i know
i've been waiting for at least two or three minutes maybe you should have died yeah that's
okay okay here you got it you got it you got it you got it that's very loud that's very loud
he's such a meanie your internal model monologue okay but if you had to be an x-men which which
person are you picking for explicitly their power like you wanted that power cyclops what the fuck
would you want to be cyclops cyclops's power is fucking amazing i've already had what you use it
for what would you use any x-men power for there too what do you mean all x-men powers are about
like fucking like killing like attacking people what power exists in the x-men universe mystique
mystique just transform into like any person so i could trick you to finally love me
that's not like fighting there's some there's someone who has like healing powers as well like
they put their hands on someone they just like oh they're healed and you're like no i want to be
able to shoot lasers you know what you know what superhero you would be i know what it is what
homelander oh please yeah you want you want laser eyes i'd be pretty sick
for you be pretty sick for you uh well i don't know what what's the correct answer there right
oh that was the there's no correct answer it's just what would you actually do with cyclops's
power is the question i don't know the only thing it can do is kill people you look at
yeah how often do you want to do that why why why are you okay are we in the x-men universe or are
we just like in my living room we're in your living room okay then oh i don't what do i need a
superpower you don't need one but i'm i'm offering you as okay as god who can create food well i
would just great i would just be the i could create food and solve a shitload of problems
i would do that one is somebody do that is there a farmer i would say i would is there a power that
could be better for like benefit the greater good right like i don't know politician answer no it's
not because it's an answer i don't even know what it is but whichever benefited mankind the most is
the one that i would select god damn it you got me you fucking got me you piece of shit he's got me
fuck he's got me he's got me that happens during a political debate yeah the next presidential
debate which x-men power would you want no i would definitely watch cyclops i could incinerate anyone
that i'm looking at oh no i mean the one the one that helps the one that would have food one
i don't know my bad wait am i just in my house right then the food one
oh man that's so stupid i mean come on who doesn't have who does what are you trying to tell me you
have not sat around and been like oh man imagine if i was like a powerful being and i could fly
and i could like defend everybody like everybody's had that oh yeah i imagine if i imagine if opening
my eyes only caused destruction fly does not mean defend yeah what i you got me so fucked up here
this is so funny you try to stir you have never worse have you never stood in the mirror like this
i gotta see what you're doing you never stood in the mirror like this and been like
leave everything to me you've never done that before you never start have been like leave
everything to these citizens you've never done that that's that's the saddest thing you've ever
said that not only do you do that but you're so shocked another human being wouldn't stand in
the mirror and do that i do i do it naked in the mirror so i do it naked in the mirror you're
gonna be mad at me for that too i do it naked in the mirror uh after getting out of the shower
every morning i said look at the mirror there's nothing wrong with that i mean if you got the
body for it and honey i know you do okay you haven't played this data before what would your
power be again mr perfect okay well if i'm the only one in the world that has a power i can't
pick rogue rogue is the obvious because you just get literally every power um uh i don't know
wolverine gets like that wolverine's another one he gets to live forever as like the strongest dude
in the fucking world he's like i'm so i just wish i would die man i'm so bored of being the strongest
guy who lives forever it doesn't have to worry about disease or anything
everyone who's strong is fucking they just they hate it you just don't like i don't know wolverine
or or charles xavier you just gave me shit for saying leave everything to me in the mirror
but you are psycho analyzing every x-men character i'm just bringing up the trope that i don't like
where everyone who is strong hates that they are strong and it's a burden on them like everyone
else doesn't have like real problems wolverine's problem is that he is immune to everything and he
hates it um that's it's the total opposite of what you're doing where you go in the mirror leave it
to me citizens wolverine's version of that is going in the mirror and saying i could save i could
save them but i'm sad about it you've definitely done that in the mirror before i mean like i just
but hey you added extra context though well wait what was the extra context am i not allowed to
elaborate and continue the conversation all right so here's my point so when you ask somebody hey
what would your what would your what would you have for a superpower and the person just goes
like they're like i don't know they're eating a sandwich like laser eyes i guess i don't know
monster you're a monster you're a monster you're a monster weird
the first thing that comes to your mind being laser eyes is weird i thought a superman has a
cyclops it's just like an easy like i guess i don't know flight laser eyes no flight would be normal
flight oh everyone wants to fly not everyone wants to and especially specifically cyclops
right can't control it and just does it he has special glasses do you want to wear special
glasses the rest of your life and if you ever take them off you like kill all of your loved
ones you just wake up in the morning and you're just like ah all right it's gonna be a good day
today you just blow a hole in your ceiling through it yeah oh my oh sorry my glasses came off honey
are you still there what was your power what was it i forget what it was i was all being it was
being able to change it was you wanted to change into like other people dude i would take power
mystique would be good xavier would be good wolverine would be good why wouldn't you xavier
charles xavier i feel like that would be too much i don't know if i want that just to like
tap into the room and like nsa anyone in the world and that and what and wait whoa
me wanting laser eyes is crazy but you wanting to tap into everybody's brain is completely
normal human behavior very interesting you ever fantasize about like if you had the power to like
stop time you would just use it to be better at video games yeah yeah i do yeah that's bad
i would i would just join a speedrun category and just and just have a world record that's
unbeatable you'd be a fucking track mania player all right let's let's let's gravitate
it to a more normal conversation do you have one yeah stir one germa zero um at this point
it's probably like stir 12 germa like eight or so we've been having a lot of conversations
who's keeping who's keeping track who's scoring our conversation yeah yeah cut that shit up
score would be funny though what are you guys scoring this what's the score what are you guys
scoring this right now this is a boxing match which means to us too biased one oh stir like
they just joined the stream well that's what i'm saying they were like one one bit yeah you're
both basically dead at this point stir is 15 and you're at a two no way no way who is the guy that
could run at super speed like the but not the flash the the x-men version quicksilver who does
nothing in every movie i would be quicksilver but i'd do something in the movie people would
argue that quicksilver is parts in those movies were the only good parts of those movies exactly
and i would be those parts oh shit holy shit i didn't even tell you about the game i know
i tried to get us back on that for a second um and we sort of just we went off on a bit of a
tangent the game is called disk room oh i played it is it good seems seems fun seems like a really
really uh seems very very nice yeah some of the stages like i'm a bit of an idiot so they were a
little bit too puzzle gamey feeling for me but overall i like a lot you got him yeah i got it
and why are you bringing the game up uh i just had to know if you played it not is it on game pass
do i have to answer that question let's just basically you basically just answered it
here take take these gloves you're building crit right i am
okay is five nights at freddy actually happening or is it just a meme
it's totally happening it is guaranteed to happen today i mean i'm enjoying this game right now i'm
enjoying the conversation no we're not in a hurry this has been some wild conversations i'm having
you're definitely gonna win work the the mvp yeah for sure what is this uh you activate those
and it summons like a like a ghost i assume okay never mind i guess it opens the store okay
secret number 11 wow we really missed 11 yeah we sure did miss quite a few of these new outfits
what five nights at freddy's character would you be uh balloon boy just because he goes hello
i think i don't know i can't participate in this conversation so i feel like it's
leaving me out and i don't like that well you'll know sooner or no all right we gotta actually
play now creepy oh scary watch out for his abilities watch out for those chains don't let
him curse you oh you just you've narrated every single boss fight by the way have i yeah trying
to help don't let him get you watch out for those rings he's charging up his power
and look i didn't get hit one time until right now i don't know your health looking kind of low
nice good job nice job dude hey great job man want this apple yeah oh shit that was an awesome
mini boss i like i'd like to welcome you to the five nights at freddy's novel for the forward
by bf bugleberry i want that apple okay there's a picture of bugleberry just leaning black and
white i want that apple why would that happen too many perfects in a row too many how do you
how do you have too many any health health looking a little low got any apples we can get you
maybe don't look like it hmm it has to be in this room right please do not die in this next room
i'm there's a secret no those are unlike every single stage
why am i not looking for them don't die dude dude great work great work dude i need that dude
i need that claw i need that tail oh 13% crit yep any apples any apples in here what's your
ideal climate um i'm a bit of a weirdo here and i know that i already know by you asking the
questions this is uh i'm like sir l no no no it's not no it is it is like 110 degrees out
it's my ideal climate are you being serious yeah like you're not messing around or anything
because that's mine too holy shit we're both losers star i live in las vegas i know it's my my story
is i moved to texas i've never been here before moved straight to texas when i got here it was
summer it was 118 degrees out i was like oh shit texas weather i'm gonna have to get used to this
so like mentally i attuned i like you know what i'm saying i locked it in and then i realized that
we have no infrastructure and everything freezes during the winter and it's not actually like that
all year round because i used to be a like i like it cold guy like the cold doesn't bother me anyway
frozen type of guy but when i moved to texas i like i reroute it my neurons you know what i'm
saying yeah now i now i i expect the 100 degrees expect the 100 yep but i don't get the 100
nah no way is that it i'm i'm gonna die because i'm being a fucking idiot um i got you i say i'm
saving you oh thank you yeah no i yeah i'm a similar mindset i like how dry it is here so
even though it's 100 plus degrees a lot of a lot of the year it doesn't feel like it
you don't really come eat this apple come eat this apple but behind it's behind the you get it
back here there's i um do you want this heal room it's yeah you want to drink up
you're always sweating i sweat when i sit here because i don't know
i hey i have no idea what it is about like streaming it sweats you up no it does it really
is it just the way it is uh take a little bit of that i don't want to take it all just take
the few points put a weapon here no no you have you're missing two hp yeah i don't i i heal every
room you did i have max health at least take the one get yourself over 70 okay um but no i
i like oh god damn it you're right here we are i forgot yeah i forgot i thought i i don't know
how many rooms are before the boss you know i guess only one um okay this boss i've actually
i've seen this one oh yeah i don't remember it but i remember it being like you don't you don't
want to talk to me about fucking croutons right now i need you to focus up hold on can i say
something yeah okay ollie and i went somewhere and i could not believe it i was so wrong i was so
incorrect and i feel bad because it was fucking delicious service was unbelievable olive garden
is that where we're going no no and and it was it was just so it was super nice everybody it was
really nice like everybody was so pleasant it was a wonderful experience the food was perfect
and i've i feel bad that i may have maybe over the course of my life said something negative
about this place and of course i'm talking about outback steakhouse we got a blooming onion and it
was fucking awesome what why would you talk shit about outback steak i don't know i don't know what
would happen what the hell i was thinking and you'd never been to one no i had did i have i talked
shit about outback before i don't i don't have the logs somebody does you must have i don't think
i have i don't maybe not outback it'd be really weird if you hadn't and you just started the
conversation this way i feel like you're making me doubt you but you started really confident
what you were saying no i i hadn't had in a while i kind of just like wrote it off is oh
whatever no no no no i don't want to go there no no no i'm not going there now yeah now place
is fucking like a c-minus at best we had it it was fantastic it was a wonderful experience
just gotta say it i gotta be real i have to thank you for keeping it real with me
thank you i appreciate it welcome it's the first for everything maybe it was uh it might have been
a tier list why is my voice is gone already it's been like an hour what's going on
okay focus remember focus look at that thing
watch out for the phantom's attack
he's casting spells casting all right stop you're gonna want to dodge those this is not fun for
melee he keeps dashing away like every time i go to attack he goes away shit it's done again
what's he doing who knows phase two don't get grabbed by the hand i feel like we have to destroy
those what the fuck what an overreacting yo what whoa attacks holy shit dude i can't even
i can't do it i can't comprehend this can't be for real dodge this nerf this what is this don't
let him be sucking that thing oh he's done i pressed the wrong button i thought i was playing
elden ring i'm always doing i'm gonna get rid of this oh my god i he's he's stun locked me i got
he's fucking stun locked me he throws me and stun lock my ass watch your pro i couldn't move
i was so hell bent on killing the fucking tower thingies oh shit i can't get around
watch out you're gonna get stuck like i did i can only hope how do you break out of that stun you
just have to like mash every button i don't know what that i don't okay i okay i what i what is
happening that's just so much damage i yeah that's not where he was shooting though he what we'll get
him next time but i was behind him again uh i don't know you don't like the bow i'll use the bow
takes too long we got a lot of new unlocks old man's got some stuff ember knight yes what is it
you met praxis what happened i see i understand you have to defeat him oh yes
oh perhaps my little leshy boy can help you on your way there's multiple watch out don't be
misled by their cat free appearance they work tirelessly to maintain the nexus let's go let's go
let's go i know yeah i know you're embarrassed from that but we're gonna let you have you're
gonna have to sit and fucking sulk in that sulk in what i'm actually yeah we need to do this
i am the guy what does you heal three hp after completing a room with enemies oh this yeah
and do that one do that one dude it has to be either or right yeah you can swap it i already
put a lot of points in this one so you can respect everything just press the e or respect oh that's
cool it doesn't cost anything cool five hp after completing a room that actually is kind of i feel
like you need it i need it that's how the rogue lights are so what about this money one game 50
gold when entering a world boy no i want more at the beginning this is not bad you should take
this one you get the damage bonus above 75 hp i think the the earn power would be more consistent
stacks i don't know if you know this but my mind is ascendant germa you know uh you know if i
didn't get to choose which x-men i was you just got you just got put which one you actually are
i would be modock because i have such a gigantic brain and i am i am unstoppable my brain's so big
i can shoot lasers out of it right but i can't shoot lasers out of my eyes well your eyes are
always doing it modock is powerful enough to know when to use lasers okay let's see how this is so
you have to charge it the whole way i actually i feel like i like this i feel like i'm going to
only like the sword there's a hammer and a throwing weapon all right what x-men would i be really what
x-men would i be or no forget that what super what superhero super doesn't matter what would i be
thinking toad is from mario what do you from mario no there's an x-men name totally talking
about that's my oh my white pick right well i would not be toad from x-men get out of here
no i would not that's absurd i'm any if we're going any super go it's definitely homelander
we're still on that am i am i lame and basic if i stay with the sword no you sure who's this
no elastic man oh i like that uh who's the who's the uh the stretchy guy
oh green the fantastic four mr fantastic yeah that's you oh that's all right that's one of the
smartest people you can mold into any shape and conform to anything he needs and he gets to be
the leader which i know you like gets to shut any shit down let's go you ready i would probably be
spongebob that's a good hero choice jim carries the mask that also works except the mask is always on
it never comes off you'd be captain underpants that's a good hero no i doubt it i doubt it
i'm seeing a lot of trues for captain underpants i disagree i would be anubis the egyptian god
of death what i'd be the joker this guy wants laser eyes and to be the the egyptian god of
death and judge everyone who dies forever that's fucked up and you're missing standing in the mirror
and monologuing well what if you you go to you go to monologue legendary relic but my hp is never
gonna fall below 10 i'll take it haha you don't get it anubis has the laser eye in smite yeah sure
it does that's so stupid he really i kind of assumed you were thinking of anubis as well
because you would want to like shoot your cocoon at someone and then talk to them for 10 minutes
well let me explain to you baddies what you've done wrong here
hahaha i don't see i don't see you helping and then once they finally understand that's when you
laser eye them you you baddies oh you take that i made that lasagna just for you i like that i
liked that that was nice i just get to you know i just keep charging you know what i mean
literally perfect let's this conversation is like nice and all i would hear you'd be we would both
be the the in the ninja turtles the reporter girl we just we just talk about what people are doing
uh now there's no way that i'm not michael angelo i'm sorry i've not i'm gonna have to argue that
which one's michael angelo like the smart one whoa man if you don't pick up immediately who i'm
talking about you've never ever ever orange one orange one orange one orange one that guy goes
that guy goes crazy you know actually why why i find uh nunchucks to be a really real you just
laugh at me i saw a nunchuck meme like a week ago i totally agree with it just made me think
about it nunchucks is such a they're they're such an unbelievable it's like a dance it's like a
dance it takes a ton of skill to use it it's just like so for no benefit i mean i think that
what would you use the the meme was about how just a stick is better than a nunchuck
yeah but there's deception with a nunchuck let's understand is is there that's the whole point
because it's like boom right in the jaw okay but like but you're fighting someone who has like a
real weapon like a spear they haven't trained for like 10 years to learn how to use the spear
and they just like poke you once if a spear is overpowered everybody knows that so you're
you're good enough that you don't need to use a spear but spear is spear is always going to be
the best weapon throw at history that's accurate right yeah spear does everything okay so we're
no one's allowed to pick spear it's too strong yeah we're like in the middle of our picking
ban phase and i banned spear okay cannot bring that to the battle what would make you want to use
nunchucks over like a flail which is just nunchucks but with a threatening part have you have you seen
what some people can do with nunchucks you almost can't even see them they're like helicopters
okay but then like it okay putting myself in i'm in the combat situation you've got your nunchucks
and you're a master we're just assuming you're a master i've had a flail and i know how to use
it because i've i just i've never used one but it's like a flail how could you not use it
i think i win that fight if i just like take the hits and flail you one time
okay but you're also missing the the potential comedy of that weapon where you do the whoa whoa
whoa whoa whoa oops i hit myself in the balls you're missing that i i totally forgot that we're
we're we're using the weapons for comedy you completely forgot that aspect of it we trained
him wrong as a joke okay i i feel like same conversation let's take it let's take it down
a small a small notch okay what dinner food are you you're not a super you don't get to be like
a cool super like what dinner are you for this mind space quiz okay i'm serious a spicy chili
i don't know something about the i'm serious is like you've thought about this and you know
i'm a chili i'm definitely a chili just a bunch of shit in a pot and just like it's so like
get everything good beans in there you got meat in there so you got like sauce put some fucking hot
sauce in it it's just kind of like sloppy but it's unbelievable gets the job done it's perfect
i would be a chili i would be a spicy chili and by the way i last a long time whoa all right
okay i want to pick what you get to pick for me what am i what kind of food am i what dinner meal
i you know what you're gonna be mad you get i think you're gonna be mad is gonna pick something
disgusting no no i think you're you're a ham sandwich you're a ham sandwich elaborate with
with one smear of mustard on the bottom of the bread on the bottom on the bottom of the bread
not in the sandwich yeah honestly you're you're you're you're a slice of pizza because everyone
likes pizza i think is and you could you could put anything on me yeah i think that you'd be
like a nice slice of pizza thank you that's a lot better than a ham sandwich with mustard on the
bottom i know i was just being mean for no reason i was just being rude all right well no now you'd
be mean to me i you wait you want me to be mean to you what food am i i said i was chili what do
you your turn uh hmm and don't say boogers that doesn't count as food i sometimes sometimes
it's screaming to me spaghetti it's not rude it's not rude i feel like i feel like you'd be a
spaghetti by the way ham sandwich i said that's not even rude you know how versatile a ham sandwich is
i do like ham sandwiches do you know ham sandwich can come in in the clutch and really bail your
ass out big time and the and that hint of mustard is a is a is enough of a kick to keep you going
i'm i'm happy to know that that's how you feel about me what when has anybody ever
turned down or complained about a nice ham sandwich with mustard on it i can't think of
anyone with i i feel like a lot of people would complain about the mustard i don't know i don't
think so not a lot of people are in the monster i think a ham sandwich is a versatile
just any occasion it's always a good choice okay all right what dessert am i
what dessert are you what dessert am i i honest to goodness i don't even know that many desserts
like listen you're a cream pie you're a creme brulee oh okay because you like hide all of the
good stuff you have to like crack through the the hard exterior to get to like what you're really
thinking what's really going on well that's why why why are you making me out to be like
intrusive thoughts andy well what is this like you're you're analyzing me
you asked do me do me okay okay okay um you're you're a an amazing you're an amazing
you're an amazing just just vanilla cone you know what i mean just a soft serve vanilla cone
that's somebody that's somebody sprinkled bacon bits on it like come on i'm still unlocked
what the fuck that means the people put bacon on ice cream they do you do you would
i would would i i think you would i don't think i would i don't think i would i i just
just i love vanilla ice cream that's top tier for me i feel like if you put stuff on it
you're fucking with the the recipe i think that you're a a oreo ice cream don't don't don't i have
a history you don't like i'm talking about cookies and cream yeah i am also talking about cookies
and cream when i was a young boy we're gonna take it all i must have been like second third grade
young boy my brother we went over to like a do you not want to hear the story no i do like walk
no no i just i wanted to make sure i was ready when you were um it was like easter so they had
like those those like hershey's like easter egg wrapped like cookies and cream like candies
yeah and i ate a whole bunch of them and they made me so sick that like since then like cookies
and cream and like the oreo filling kind of grossed me out and because i have a brother and it's like
a brother's job to gross you out he like knew that so he would started eating um he started
taking all of the cream out of an entire bag of oreos made a baseball out of them and then like
showed it to me and ate it and it fucking grossed me out so much did you puke uh from from the
original like eating the the candy the easter candy yeah i did puke that's awful no no that's
understandable so for me for you to tell me i am a cookies and cream yeah uh that's traumatic
i have cookies and cream trauma you guys are the puke twins you're gonna want to pick this up
dude you just take it you you need to do bro i feel a long game i feel like we're on tonight
i feel like we're on tonight we're on yeah i feel like we're on tonight who's on top
hmm but the mvp who's on top holy combo meal what's your what's in your combo meal
oh he's getting bacon he's getting eggs he's getting a sandwich he's getting ham
oh i'm on tonight look at that nice guy i feel like this thing makes up categories to make one
person not feel bad you know what i mean yeah now it looks like um you guys are on drugs tonight
looks like you did something uh this is much more better than the it's more um god damn it it's
fun it's the bow is i didn't like the bow very much yeah be like lightning zapper yeah all right
we're gonna do it this time uh here here's what actually happened i'm going crit earlier you
weren't paying attention because i asked you a question and i picked up two of the crit gems
which is why i gave you two of the health gems oh i see so so if we get crit again let me get
the crit stuff i will make sense let me in there and i'm gonna i'm gonna keep taking like crit
lightning oh oh i mean poison stacks one poison stacks one does this do these actually stack
though uh it does say stack so i would have to assume it's stacked you have to assume that right
you have to assume it
if you could pick any element that became alive and could be your friend what would it be any
element like are you saying like a like an ember fire head element would be your friend i mean like
like helium like hydrogen oh yeah okay i'm thinking fantasy
okay what kind of golem would i like to have i i kind of i just wanted to confuse you for a moment
i'm sorry i'm pretty confused especially when your example is helium could helium come alive
and be my friend i feel like that is not even one of the like strangest things we've talked
about today i think it is it might be but is it you don't want this you want some skill damage
uh i'll take it uh gold is the most precious of metals oh yeah so you could you could melt
your friend down and sell it yeah monster who needs friends when you've got money am i right
this is disney villain plot you could you have the power to turn people into gold
but then they have to be your friend dude we are so powerful we're actually doing pretty good
the first stream that i've caught in a long time and they have a sort of weird i think for both of
us this is the first stream in a long time i think we're just usually weird i think we're just
messing around i've been i've been very honest open and vulnerable tonight yeah
messing around just a little bit of a joke you know you guys are fun to watch hey cool we're glad
uh i do you want to be faster i feel like i've gotten like three of these
okay i'll just eat them up stats wait wait wait wait skill you happy with your skills i am happy
with these i don't think i need to change them dude that room we just annihilated them we were in
that room for like 30 milliseconds i was gonna say you know seconds are too long um they didn't
give me the crit gem i was gonna say can you reroll no there was a there was like a perk for
that but i don't think i took it what's your guy's favorite chips i actually have the answer to this
if anybody wants to know it a lot of you already know i've got i've got chip related trauma no
so there's another story did you did your brother like okay when i was really young again
when i was really young my brother he's older and his friend they're older i'm the young i'm
the younger brother he made a son chip baseball and he no he did one of the my brother's friend
was like man i could really go for some chips right now and i was super into it too and i was
like yeah i could go for some chips and then i found out like an hour later after this whole
like chip debacle that they weren't talking about chocolate chips and i felt very foolish
i mean that and that kind of ruined my life honestly i feel like you were i feel like you
were implying oh double you're gonna want to focus up for the phalanx throws
i won my fight we do more damage than i do you've taken all the damage items you've taken all the
damage gems oh okay now it's my fault that i'm doing more damage can you fucking eat this meat
uh okay so what is your favorite chip no um dude i don't i'm not really a chip guy at all
not really i mean it's got to go with something and then at that point it's more about what it's
going with than the actual chip you know it's like a delivery device and then i really care
anymore max relics oh shit i have to get rid of this uh can i even get rid of this
can i drop a relic because i just thought you farted i thought that was a huge fart
it's like why did you play that over the mic i thought that was the fart reverb sound oh i
misunderstood this one too i don't really want it shit i just i have i guess i'll take it it's
weird i if you can use that take it i apparently why couldn't i why couldn't you i fold relic
slots apparently how i don't know i only have i have two okay i have wait now i have four relics
i can't go down to the second slot you already have that relic oh like you can't have more than
one yeah oh i thought you could just kind of stack them so you're not a chip guy are you
any type of salty snack kind of what does that i mean like i i like chips but like i was thinking
it has to go with something so it's more about what it goes with like i'll have chips with cottage
cheese is you know like a consistent thing for me you know if you're in like a like nachos with
something that sounds cool do you do salt and pepper on cottage cheese no no but you that's
you would like it oh what are you going to cook for me
what do you want what do you like cooking what do you want i want what you like cooking salmon
every time every time someone's like oh i like cooking and i cook this all the time and then i
see them and i'm like hey you know cooking's cool i'll even help i'm not like asking to be like
served but like i like to see what people are into and what they're cooking good looking uh i like
you want the damage too you might as well take it what are you going to cook for me
i mean that's that's a very broad question i mean what do you what do you feel like today
i want what i want what you like okay so what what i want to experience you okay it's not about
so if i were to make food i don't know like pretty good pasta salad right now that's what i would
probably have like a specialty like oh yeah i cook this i do like a real good job salmon
egg salad i make a mean egg salad i make a good salmon in the oven
uh a good cod in the pan i'm a uh i'm a big fan of um do you make an egg salad
i actually do or is that kind of like making cereal where you just sort of put the milk in
the cereal together yeah it kind of is but there's some secrets okay oh okay i didn't i didn't know
all right burgers not not a pasta salad kind of guy pasta salad is a great quick and simple meal
and i said meal because if you put you know put a bunch of broccoli in pasta salad olives and shit
like get get everything in there make it a whole thing pasta broccoli olives tuna get it all in
hey you're but you're you're a salmon person i i do like salmon i kind of feel like anyone
who likes salmon like your taste buds are just fucked up i i do there's like probably 500
billion people in the universe and when i'm talking multi around each universe i'm not talking about
just that just actually gassed when you said that i know i'm aware like when i go to the grocery
store sometimes i like to buy the like they have like the pre-made like here you go like pre-made
package like ready to go like ham like the the pork that i left in my backpack yeah other room
we don't need to heal uh it's always like three dishes of pork and then the rest everything else
like a hundred options of salmon if i feel like they're just trying to get rid of this shit
like there's a warehouse somewhere with just like way too much salmon in it i mean it's it's probably
one of the most popular foods in in the world i would say i mean i don't know what the statistics
in the united states are salmon is very very very popular it's like a staple of a lot of people's
diets i think a lot fish uh cod salmon a haddock those are staples i feel like if you if you had to
have salmon would be like lowest on my list do you like like absolute bottom no no really um i
feel like i'd rather have tuna but okay what about tuna fish from the can that sounds disgusting
yeah i'll take the salmon no no no no no no no people just have such a bad opinion of salmon
out of the can and it's just you just gotta gotta trust me you just gotta hold your nose
no he's gotta you have to trust me all right everyone will be quiet watch out for his attack
he's gonna freeze you you're getting hit you're just standing still what do you
stop making me make jokes that aren't funny i would love it if you made funny jokes
like this this ain't on me he's just hitting he's landing them on me not you oh you got this
epic i will i will die on this hill doing a fish out of the can solid like you get get a good solid
albacore tuna and you're gonna take that you're gonna mix it obviously with mayo
interrupting your favorite fish though is your favorite fish salmon or tuna
it realistically is probably tuna it's probably tuna fish like all seafood like even like we're
talking like crab lobster i like crab i don't like lobster weirdly enough i actually don't really like
um lobster at all probably probably uh probably weird for this one but i think if i had to have
any seafood of all things it's calamari see now you lost me big time but yeah i don't know how you
will think that eating squid is fine but salmon is gross to you how doesn't make any sense it just
tastes weird how does it make any sense squid and has such a distinct odd flavor i i'm not
really it does salmon and if you they both seafood right but how do you like calamari but you don't
you hate salmon it's just it's salmon just tastes weird like sign me up for like almost any other
fish really that's really i think tuna fish and pretzels i know i've changed at least a few
people's lives here i just have my life was i was living a shallow existence i was germa streamed
he said because he said eat what what was it tuna fish so i'm talking canned tuna you take it out
of the container you mix it up like make a tuna like like as if you were gonna put it in like a
sandwich i'm talking tuna fish sandwich tuna fish you put mayo mix it up add whatever bullshit you
want to make it the way you want it but you no actually don't do that just do it normally
and take pretzel sticks pretzel cylinders wait i'm confused because i just had to throw out the
first half of the recipe i read the recipe and step five was throw out the first half okay
it's not drunk food it's not it's not high food it's not drunk food it's just good shit i'm telling
you a lot of people just write it off and they don't even give it a chance this one's probably
good something to do with the way the pretzels interact with the tuna fish i don't know what it
is there's gonna somebody that's in the science community please help someone who knows science
tell me why i like this food no i'm serious it's weird it changes completely i understand it's so
good exactly the combination is it's relentlessly good the salt no no it's it can't be it's the
molecular interaction between the salt the bread and the fish you must just like sodium whoa whoa
hold on a second check it out scientist in chat the pretzels contain an enzyme called
forazine that reacts with tuna proteins since they're long chain proteins they tend to spool
and it creates a stringy what i just didn't read i did i read something fucked up i didn't just
read something like fucked up right i i i don't know i don't know neither do i if we're gonna
keep talking about tuna and shit i'm checking out it's so good i know people like i'm a hater
i'm a hater i hate him but just if you ever have an opportunity and you just like you're if
you're at like the grocery store and just like you're in the tuna and pretzel aisle it's just
like the tuna and pretzel aisle i fucking hate that guy but uh you know what fuck him i want
to prove him wrong buy it prove me wrong tell me i'm wrong and you're gonna you're gonna fucking
bite into it and it's gonna be like a five gum commercial it's gonna be like
i'm lost i don't know what's going on i can't participate in this conversation
which x-men would you fuck cutting cutting right to the chase no more dancing around
no more dude no more like how do i word this no no just right to the point i'll take the skills
i can't wait till you play five nights at freddy's it's gonna be fucked don't know why i don't know
why this is like the exciting thing all right let's go he doesn't get mad you do that oh i have
more money i have a lot i have a lot of money but this thing i mean just i it's just more damage
i could have taken the pie but whatever you guys have a lot of health they sure do and so i have
the most twice your health it's so funny wait you want this one stop ignoring chat i mean i
i already am so absent minded when i'm playing a game like this anyways i'm just gonna lose if
i look over there more than a few times every minute or two all right take them both oh i'm
gaining power what's your percentage now hi i can't look right now i don't know i also get a
guaranteed crit when i when i use my skills pretty cool i get the lightnings i feel so powerful and
you actually have full health this run this is the one you look like you have an egg between
your cheeks and you're trying really hard to not crack it here i'd be a fun stream the egg stream
i think i just have jowls man owie owie owie that's some pasta uh you should take it along
into the bethoven stream do you know bethoven the mini boss yeah watch out for the curse
he's got chains well this guy really knows some occult shit he's so powerful you could
be any piece of gear in elden ring which should be anything i could be any piece of gear yeah
uh what's the fucking the ink katana that everyone hates uh moon veil i just want to piss moon i want
to piss everyone off i'm fucking moon veil i would be the sword of night and flame i would be the
sword of night and flame yeah well i would be the moon veil and i would talk to my wielder
and in between like combat they'd pause for like 10 seconds and we'd get to have the anime moment
where they're like i don't know what to do and i i'm the sword and i'm like you need to look within
sun and we'd have the whole conversation you need to do a charged attack fucking idiot again do
another one more one more charged attack with moon veil you know i used moon veil for half that
playthrough when i my first playthrough it was fun you should get that looking a little low
you know what happened today and i blamed you for this you started to call me for literally
yeah no you play i'm blaming you you get you fucked everything up because you came in here
and said i just want to be to tell you i'm going to be very normal it's going to be very i'm not
going to be weird there's not going to be any weird and and that like messed up my brain and
said like now we had to be weird oh so you were like okay now that he's like not going to be
entertaining and carry my stream for me i might have to like pull some weight don't tell anybody
that you thought i'm gonna have to stir on it's gonna be hilarious we're just gonna have like
i'm just gonna get to chill and play some like whatever and then i started by saying nope not
today i just i don't know i don't know like funnier than you i'm sorry i had to tell a joke
tell a joke tell a joke right now all right i hate that i hate when someone's like telling
joke that's the worst thing is there anything worse in the whole universe um i don't know
maybe ordering pickup at a restaurant i always feel like i fuck up when i second guess everything
i just say what i feel like i screw up every time it's just like oh hey yeah what what can i
get you uh and are you wait wait wait wait you know the internet happened right you don't like
you don't no one orders pickup anymore on the phone what are you talking about
do you call the place i mean yeah not every single restaurant in the world
operates on like fucking uber what are you talking about yeah they do boomer yeah that was good this
is like this this is the equivalent of the airplane food kind of like no one like when
you call the place to order food who who does that who's relating to this how but do you order
every single time from like an app or a website i i haven't called a place to order since like
the 2001 or something i don't but here's the thing about ordering sometimes through those apps
it can get weird because sometimes get weird because sometimes it's just it's listed fucking
weirdly and it's like wait that's not that's listed kind of not correctly like it's like wait a minute
i have to check like five boxes but wait that's not how the thing's listed on the actual restaurant
it can be weird i i feel like i i i know exactly what i'm getting when i call they can be listed
bizarrely sometimes you don't even know what meat is in a sandwich for instance just like oh this
one's like a number three it's like wait what is that what's in it i don't know i need to i need
to know i need to find out what's in the number three can't you read oh yeah yeah are you gonna
make an offering yeah giving them 400 gold i actually gave it 250 and he gave me a broken jar
i got more help he gave me a useless a broken jar for 400 but no honestly though it a lot of
times i feel like i know exactly like oh so hey what what comes on that by the way oh this this
this and this okay good what i want uh i'm gonna take the l and just admit that one of my least
favorite things in life is being on the phone i actually don't mind it but i know what you mean
though like if i think i was saying not that long ago one of the greatest inventions ever
or like the greatest modern trends is that everything that you can order food is like
done through an app and you don't have to talk to someone like i'd give up so much technology
to never have to talk on the phone about the food i want you should eat this
i mean you're talking about convenience it's much more convenient for you to not have to do that
right i get it i feel the same way a lot of times right but i uh i have also used those apps before
and no fault of of the restaurant or even like the driver doesn't matter right no fault of anybody
it's just kind of wrong and you stuff doesn't come out right um i i much prefer being able to
know exactly like by somebody on the phone it's like telling me what i'm gonna be it's a it's
trust issues it's a trust issue here that you have focus up this is wait is this the guy
what was this all right no this is the guy this is the guy focus up on the guy i need you for the
final phase i was just dope into him oh my god dude stop i don't know what's happening with my brain
okay for you i'm gonna suggest actually that you think less actually helpful watch out for this
golf i just i remember what your roll button is i just stopped talking it's gonna help
i don't know what he's doing what is he doing ah he went sicko mode on me i'm bad he's he's he's
you're gonna have to win this i'm dead i don't even know if i could have moved fast enough to
get to where you were he's healing dude he's healing it's don't touch that aim at it
need to be quiet you gotta focus dodge dodge dodge everything will be forgiven if you can win
everything you've ever done everything everything okay and literally everything you've
ever done hit him yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah dodge these balls
yeah yeah yeah yeah take your time you got all day man he's juicing he's juicing
you've got him right where you want him oh i like that the chakra there it almost got both of those
dodge it counterclockwise oh this is easy only an idiot would die to this
he's gonna juice oh oh just focus on dodging man you've got this pal come on buster
let's fucking go dude stop talking to me watch out there's a there's a thing shooting green balls at
the top he's juicing chakra chakra i don't care what he's doing man use your abilities
focus on dodging there we go all right buster you got this final phase is easy the you can
totally dodge the yellow beam even if you're standing behind him uh oh uh oh he's healing
one more hit you took all the damage you took all the damage shit oh damn i hate to see it oh i
couldn't even fucking hurt him man he still didn't beat my damage no because you picked up almost
every single damage gem in the game that sounds true that sounds totally true and definitely a
way to like get yourself out of this but now you're not forgiven for all of your sins
when you die god's gonna look upon your record look at this moment but i tried that's the part
that's sad hey watch it your relic selectors if you were oh oh wow no relic yeah i think relic
yeah six percent is that permanent if it is that's really good uh what is this new weapon
oh hammer man i actually like this i want to be hammer man i want to be hammer guy
how about we both be hammer guy do you think that you're powerful enough to wield it
maybe if i had one crit gem the whole game or one damage okay okay i'll bow down to you we
gotta go talk to this guy i'll use the bow what is that strange energy this game's fun i like it
yeah nice little buster beat him up so we are identifying these dude we seriously not give him
any ever because we had so many of these on our previous run oh my god we really didn't these are
now available on your journey oops that's a lot of new things i'm not i'm not gonna read them
i don't care we'll find them there's more
next next okay oh cool nice okay let me uh did you read the details of the hammer
i did so all of the attacks can be charged so you can go one two one two three
again they're all they're all different seems strong i'll try both i think bow looks bad but
i'm gonna use it i'm gonna i'm gonna be the bow guy i actually probably should use this okay so
okay like if i'm very realistic i probably should use this okay let's go then i'm hammer guy
me too all right what are you doing take the hammer we need to be the hammer bro no
i don't want to be the hammer brother i don't want to mirror match right now fine don't complain to
me when there's no funny material that we can do like a super mario thing together god damn it
okay i wouldn't use because came on today do you think uh that you can legally become someone's
brother you know what i'm saying like do you think we could go to a court and i could become your
brother uh probably yeah i think yeah what's this huh oh he's sexy looks like the fucking the
things that you ride in golden axe as a reference he's wait were you killing him wait are you strong
now i don't know what you skip you this is okay you read it you make fun of me every time i read
something every time we play together you try and like oh like oh wow like really okay okay like
doing me a favor and reading the thing on stream for me all right kind of weird what'd you do what
happened you went where you went somewhere last night yeah oh the skills up here skills up here
i don't like the bow it takes a lot are you using keyboard and mouse right so that probably would be
better for you it's it's helpful but i don't like the standing still hammer seems amazing by the
way it did seem that way wait what do we got frost wall or arcane bolts i'll take bolts
i like this one okay now i have two things i don't like god you want to start over me again
no i want to overcome yeah standing still tends to get you shot it's kind of rough
skills refresh quicker i'll take burn i haven't done burn you did burn it's pretty good
i guess i'll take it money or ember it's always money man that's what it's all about
how come that one chatter got a roblox birthday but i haven't gotten a minecraft party
uh uh uh they want to sweepstakes dude i'm the one who's firing ice now it's fun yeah they call
me frost burn when were the sweepstakes it was me looking over and reading a name and deciding
that i was gonna do the thing uh that one moment that was so brave of you that's a good move
by the way you're healing is increased your skills have an additional charge these are all amazing
the first perfect skill man that's 25 more damage for five seconds for the i mean that that is it
bad you're gonna you're gonna do a perfect skill so it's objectively bad because the only rooms
that matter are the boss rooms and then it's only damage one time in a boss room well i mean look
at this thing right here that's perfect for me love that for me works for my build so you're
right this is kind of like uh hey the only thing that i haven't seen that much of is the leveling
up skills but i feel like it's in the game right uh i don't know i know there's like more stuff in
the hub we haven't unlocked for sure when does hades 2 come out of wherever it is
i don't think they set a date hey dude when is the five minutes of freddy's i gotta wake up early
tomorrow um i don't know we could go later than usual because i woke up at 3 p.m today
on like uh you know i'm like a full degen mode so i'm not like a bedtime andy type of guy today
okay i do like about the bow that nothing attacks me and you you fight everything it is
it is kind of nice although it's kind of hard against bosses why very slow no no i'm talking
about the hammer it's kind of slow charge it up pal that does help whoa nice work there
thanks you need more max health do i do it gain five armor i feel like i did that a lot
right no what do you mean no ah god fine take it i'm the one that's getting hit you said it
yourself you've been ah i know go ahead i i'm the one that's in front of everything i guess and now
i'm distracted and look what's happening good thing you have all that armor actually is just
talking about how i have no health fine god mom said we needed to share big brother
i'm a blast bomber ember fire that's the name of the game it's kind of right i used more yeah
okay so this thing is going to be good i i am not the big brother germa's like 10 years older than
me not even remotely accurate stats or health uh definitely stats i don't know what this there's
some secret over here dude but you eat that yeah big boy eat that protein i'm i'm not vibing with
the whole bow situation you're not vibing right now i am not vibing i have to find a way to make
it work i feel like i'm just gonna do skill damage because why not if you cast that fire
on meat it will cook it and we'll do more healing really that's cool i'm gonna test that it'd be a
life you ever just like order something on an app and then like it comes raw and you're like man if
i would have just called them and told them in person what i wanted they wouldn't have cooked it
they would like cook it right it shows up yeah ever happen to you so what did that dinosaur even
tell us you were too busy being angry wait don't move oh never mind i have no idea what the dinosaur
told beware now yeah you're gonna you're gonna want to beware stunned did you just put that
bomb down yeah i've got the bomb ability you see a bomb it's my bomb epic can you wash your hands
did you take them both there was only one after a boss i took one because i'm low health
and you you commented about it i've been insecure ever since who's your favorite angry birds i've
never played angry bird congrats on the mvp oof sturm i'm sorry it's just some people haven't
experienced everything in the whole world there's some things that some people just don't have
experiences with and angry birds sorry is one of them for me i didn't see the movie i know
that it's a critically acclaimed masterpiece but i i just i just missed out on it you know
quick there's no way we don't beat that boss now i feel weak whenever you defeat an enemy refresh
a skill that seems unbelievable it does uh yeah uh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah i'm just gonna let you
kill everything i'll stand in the back and then we're gonna get to the boss and you're gonna have
700 weapon damage better you got him pal right there buddy just bop me i can't just bop me up
just bop me bop me give me a little boppy look out for the magicians i'm aware oh boppy you know
what honestly i feel like i'm fucking gonna be the useless one like plus two damage on a bow
when your hammer charge hits like six times i'll be damaged oh boppy
plus two nice oh yeah you get that kill bud oh yeah champ uh i'll damage plus one do you want
the max hp you probably take it you actually need it you take it no seriously take it you can't you
got it we gotta have you look how you look like the hulk it feels appropriate that you have more
health than me because i'm like hawkeye and you're the hulk yeah but the same shit's gonna happen
when i was the last one to fight the boss and i had no damage increase that was all my fault
i shouldn't have died i got hit by like everything you know what i mean like i just made a couple
crucial mistakes i won't let it happen again we got one of those things
so that makes me happy i'll learn i'll evolve i'll be better i'll do better
hammer is good hammer is good you'd like the hammer i believe you look at my last message
to see the curse i placed on you um money i don't think we need money do you really you want the
meta yeah we both have over 350 gold some things cost like 300 what does that stuff what does the
ember do uh that's when we go back to town at the end of the run and upgrade our character
oh okay you want stats or skills i want a skill i i hate my current skills i hate that i have
to kill these witches to get it though really start to settle into this character arcane bolts
is just so good i again i don't like either of these did you get the ability to reroll
it's part of the ember i didn't can i drop stuff i can reroll something for you did not maybe um
i don't think you can drop skills um i think i i used the dice i didn't like it very much
it took like it like you throw it and then it charges up by the time it charges up the
thing was dead just skip stick chakram dude chakram was good unless you like what you have is good
the burn thing is really good though i'm gonna keep what i have all right uh
uh hey i need a little bit of damage feel a little weird like somebody just took that
item do you need me do you want me to help i'm kidding or am i i don't think you are
there's no possible way that everything you say is a joke all right like some things you say have
to be real and true at some point yeah that's true you ready you ready is it a double again
or just one oh i know this guy he's summoning boys like little snowballs we just destroyed
that guy yeah i feel like he was alive for a very short amount of time i'll get that meat i want to
i want to see you eat it come on come on big boy come on big boy nice uh thanks for your continued
patronage and to maximize our profits to maximize our services you can now reroll items in the shop
here you might take that one yeah i don't like any of these i like this one how do you do the
reroll talk to him wait let me see it real quick oh the oh bro i got a broken jar that i paid
400 dollars for before secret number nine good as new wow it's not worth much to me now that it's
empty your first skill using each room grants shield for five seconds that stops projectiles
and prevents damage to all nights inside of it i would say that's really good but it only happens
once yeah i don't know it's kind of like prevent damage won't you know that's all right uh i think
you should take impact charm that sounds like a hammer would do good with that does the hammer
stuns but i mean i guess i wonder what part of the combo is uh is this what you already had every
four enemies you defeat that thing's pretty good is the um is the stun the second or the i think
it's the third swing actually hammer applies slow not stun is it's everything applies stun it's like
everyone has like a stamina bar and if you get the opportunity to get the the shield charge that
always stuns we said come over andy let me make that actually what it is oh you missed you missed
silence oh so holly and i were um we watched uh we watched the hunchback of notredame
and the villain in the hunchback of notredame got us to really think about something if at any point
you ever utter the words silence you're you're evil right or enough silence that's the only you
aren't you're evil nobody has ever uttered that word that followed up with being good
i yeah i'm trying to think of examples uh go against that i i can't think of anything i i
don't think there is a single example silence unless you're like a kindergarten teacher maybe
maybe i'm really thinking of outliers what about gandalf gandalf says silence that he goes
silence silence dumbledore says silence yeah yeah gandalf is evil no he's not like teachers i feel
like our teachers and parents are the exception here silent gandalf gandalf is basically a parent
oh no no another thing too if anyone ever says i will see to this insolence insolence is another
one as well true but villains getting typecast out there they all say the same thing silence
i have had enough of this insolence that means this guy's fucked up and is doing awful shit
terrible things yeah well no foolish is i don't think foolish is there
insolent fools yeah actually maybe if you're right that is bad guy speak isn't it all right such
arrogance you're saying a lot of you're saying a lot of evil guy stuff at the moment i'm thinking
oh shit i was frozen i didn't know wake up wake up somebody said finally
i don't think it's finally i think it's at long last means the same thing but one of them is
inherently more evil me and you were both the same you're just like me yep that's another one
good that's a good one like you and i are the same i'll never be you i'll never be just like you
right yeah that happens a lot they do exist why is that funny right now
you letting that guy hit you i kind of was i've got too busy thinking of other things
it's doing like ad libs what would a villain say all right stir yeah i'm gonna say what
is this from they do exist what it was a good try i have no idea i have no idea what is it
that is santa from the 1998 television commercial the m&m's meet santa you're right i remember
yeah you got you got me oh eat up eat up big boy let's fucking go are you ready yeah i'm ready
this is it right here i'm ready to annihilate this boss within like five seconds we're gonna
one phase him oh all right hold on my underwear is like glued to my ass right now oh come on
that was unfair just roll just roll
that was unfair that's unfair dude isn't it though the only way something could ever
penetrate my defenses was with some cheap tactic get up late oh that got deleted
did you love it when you the streamer read the comments i got delete it yeah like oh i wasn't
supposed to encourage that or something i feel like i do that a lot why are moderators removing
comments because they break the rules what are the rules you're afraid of like someone saying
something censorship i feel like i've seen people say like you're dumb and that doesn't get deleted
but what gets deleted is play five nights at freddy's you're gonna get mvp every time one
of them is an opinion the other one is a demand i think you should play five nights at freddy's
that's fine get rid of him that's an opinion well okay but that's i think you should play not
you need to play exactly okay but you said get rid of me there was still like a knee jerk get rid of
me silence you insolent cur cur is another one you vile fiend i kissed my ring they gotta do a
character that does all that says all that but it turns out he's not the bad guy hey my curse
takes effect this boss fight but there's a curse insulin oh another one is well are you insolent
well you sussy baka also yeah that's also used a lot oh that's good see that's whenever you use
a skill gain bonus damage not like once per room i'm not about this once per room can you sing
happy birthday for my daughter
it was singing he was singing down here did you know that me me and ashley we have a rule when
we're watching tv like it's a i think i've maybe even said this before maybe i'm a broken record
where if someone in a show starts singing we skip you know you like just press forward like once
so it goes like 10 seconds forward if they're still singing you press it again just get get to
the end of it i kind of feel you the only way i think that that does not make sense if it's a
musical yeah well then you're you're obviously want every song like three words where they set
up the next song like oh yeah like oh and then just yeah it's like next next and here comes it
now now get rid of this hey uh you want to watch the musical but i i kind of don't want to
i don't like when people sing you mind i don't like songs
they want it you know my favorite fast time is i've talked about this a lot but i
i haven't i have ever talked about it with you uh the whole like hentai thing you pick a movie
and you watch only like two minutes of the movie and then you go forward how am i supposed to even
fucking talk after that one you take you take a movie and you watch 10 minutes and then you
skip like 30 minutes and then watch two minutes have you actually done this it's fucking fun as
hell why why because you can watch any shitty movie you want and it's only like 16 minutes of
commitment but you gain nothing no you get the whole movie trust me watch five minutes in the
beginning skip 20 minutes watch 10 minutes skip 25 minutes watch three minutes skip to the end
of the movie it's so fun it's so fun trust me i i feel like i might have done that at some point
it's not like intentionally so deliberate in it but like there's a couple shows where it's like i
i really need to know how this ends but i'm actually so sick of it and think it's bad you
just watch like five minutes of every episode oh my god i did that with lucifer i don't know
lucifer the fucking wait wait wait can we talk about it we had we have to talk about this in
detail can we yeah okay let's make a very very important point here this is going to be massive
spoilers for this show let's show lucifer right yeah yeah so this is big spoilers for lucifer
huge huge massive i want to i want you to talk because i want to see if you and i did the exact
same thing i enjoyed it for a bit and then i kind of got the formula and thought every episode was
boring but there's like five minutes of interesting content every episode so i would skip to the middle
watch two minutes skip to the very end of the episode watch two minutes next episode yeah i
was a little more egregious um but yes that is exactly what i'm talking about doing i okay this
is a huge spoiler so massive lucifer spoilers i'm serious i'm gonna write it on the screen
so i how many episodes are in the first season of lucifer i i i mean who i don't know let's say
it's like let's assume 10 let's just say it's 10 i hold on actually i feel like it's one of those
shows that has like 20 episode seasons but the first one might have been like seven i think it
was more like a season one pilot kind of thing you're looking it up right now no i'm just i'm
writing that is we're talking about spoilers okay so um i didn't really care about this show at all
i just saw the thumbnail of the show and it was just him like as lucifer right he's he looks like
the devil um i opened up episode one and i scrolled through to find when he becomes that like satan
character it doesn't happen i i went through every single episode scrolling through until he
first episode no no he doesn't no he doesn't he does no he doesn't he doesn't like at the very end
of the whole show no i mean no you're saying it's a spoiler that the show named lucifer
the guy turns into the devil yeah but he doesn't do it until like the one of the last episodes of
this first season i i think at the end he finally no no i'm telling you i'm telling you no he doesn't
in episode one he absolutely doesn't in the trailer yes in the like episode one he starts
by like tormenting some guy then he's like i'm the devil like fucking 10 minutes in he does so my
skip strategy was was had holes in it it's like a big reveal that other people realize he's that's
like way further on but i don't think he like shows himself as the devil to like a that's what
i'm saying it's really not what you're saying it's really not he doesn't like turn into like i'm satan
i am like i'm like horns and i'm like okay i'm like we're in spoiler mode the show gets so
fucking weird where he finally reveals after like three seasons to the detective he's working with
and he's like kind of in love with like hey i'm actually satan and she's like ah i don't know how
to cope with that and they have this like weird on and off like i have been partners with satan
for like the last couple years of my life and it's weird where she's like trying to come to terms
with like him being literal satan but we're talking about the okay let me make sure i got
the right show in the thumbnail he's like this like right like okay well netflix changes the
thumbnails a lot it's not always one thumbnail but i imagine yes that right there and he's like
and he's satan he is satan he does solve crime as satan wait hold on a minute this is now that's
a series of unfortunate events that's count all off right it's a different show hold on wait
this is the same thumbnail they used to stand the same exact thumbnail for both shows
that use they use that a lot but my point still stands he doesn't reveal that he's satan
until like the last episode no your your point was no spoilers did you know the main guy in lucifer
is lucifer no that's not what i'm saying i'm saying he doesn't like reveal that he's lucifer
until like the last episode of the first season no my chat's reminding me that like he has like
a devil face and he even he even calls it like devil face like a fucking preschooler
and he doesn't do like devil face to someone for a bit but he's like very obviously satan
yeah but he doesn't he doesn't have the like he doesn't have that look until like the last
episode of the first season you might be right about that i'm telling you i i i'm gonna i think
i'm correct but it's not like they're hiding it no you know it's obviously that guy is lucifer
i'm just saying they don't do like that thumbnail face until one of the last episodes of the first
season okay and you you skipped every episode to find the face i just wanted to see a scene of him
being like oh yes it's me satan i just wanted to find it and i couldn't find it took me to the last
episode okay you didn't watch it no i didn't i'm telling you i scrubbed through every episode just
to find the one time but he did it was it worth it he does it every single episode i gotta go back
and do some he really does we're like he he ends up trying to catch the person before his detective
buddy does and then he goes devil mode on him to be like you shouldn't have done that by the way
i'm satan and then he like does some satan stuff in the first episode he definitely it has to be
in the first episode man he does it every episode yeah that's that's how i'm remembering it
though i do think like i don't know season one probably has some like melodramatic reveal of
like his real true satan self i i need to go i'm gonna have to do some homework tonight
yeah eat this meat buddy hmm chomp on that i want both these gems you take one
mad no actually i wouldn't want to make you mad hey take it we're about to fight the big boss
oh god damn it hold on spoiler alert the little mermaid is a mermaid how did i just get hit by that
i just keep getting hit it's annoying these laser beams look at how good of an ability that is by
the way super accurate super damaging yeah when are we gonna get that ability i i was focusing
looking at you and then they started shooting me a mile behind you that's a great on me what an
amazing ability to have and it hits behind them sometimes for no reason incredible what are your
expressions of cg you're reading too much into it can you just kill this boss
boss beat his ass we got a secret i don't know what it was that was a good one that was clean
it was clean just like myself who showered today for this stream but not anymore because
streaming has made me stinky we got kind of trapped on a tangent somewhere but
does your room get insanely hot insanely hot why to do that it's just like the computer rendering
it's the only so awful yep and you can't really have a big fan in the room because it kind of
pops up to the mic and it's like the chat they don't know uh it'll be like 80 degrees in my room
and i i finished streaming and leave my room and the the rest of the the house feels like 60
it's crazy that 120 degree weather great work i wish i could smell your room
no you don't smells like a fucking cheeseburger sub in here like yeah that's no yeah that's fucking
i could i could i could really go for a cheeseburger sub right now that sounds awesome
that does sound awesome right now you're right
okay those guys this guy's got some pretty big damage oh yeah never take the health because we
have um boss damn it these are on damn it watch out it's it's the only thing that's hitting me
it's such a good fucking move it's got me all fucked up i might die to this oh my god dude i
can't even i what's happening right now just hide friend just just run oh i almost
did die i seriously almost did that's mimic king in the next room hold up we got any any health
any health in here who's the mimic oh that was the there was a guy it was the slimer
what do we do here sniff sniff can we get some sniff sniffs in chat for germa's stinky toes
you must be a snack yeah i'm a snack hello little snack oh daddy
what you aren't food you think we can't eat you oh gobble me up come play with us little snack
i do oh wait i didn't see anything i didn't i wasn't looking my god you have to make a bunch
of fucking comments i didn't know there was a thing happening comments it's the one on the right
got to make all these comments and and we didn't even get the treasure because both of us didn't
hey you saw you saw the fucking stirred list you know i'm into this
that's it that's the whole that's all we just we were wrong we just didn't pay attention to the
game that we were supposed to be playing there's apples down here pal there better be all right
buster let's go geez what the heck i actually am gonna die i need you man i'm dead i couldn't
fucking do anything i was trapped is there even a mini boss we fought the mini boss oh my god the
curse guy we already did it dude i have to beat the whole boss by myself and you got all the damage
fuck i just got all the help was right here oh my all the help was in the next room
hold it whoa hey hey hey wait don't eat those oh wait why are you back oh because you have the
revive i have a revive i got the that is why i took it what a fucked up day
can i see can i like see you eat these though yeah let's just be all right we're good everybody
relax i was about to start being pissed off now yeah he's he got the revive it was good for his
build he was right all right now no more talking silence only i don't want you to think about that
thumbnail that we laughed about earlier silence actual silence for real i am gonna be completely
quiet so i shouldn't say like no and don't like anything don't coach me in the corner no coaching
let's beat it no commentary win good job oh you didn't even do it now i'm getting hit by these
oh my goodness oh my i'm so bad we're fine i can't i he's going to suck oh you're dead oh no i'm not
dead i'm not dead i'm not i'm one hp oh okay i'm never getting hit again my whole face is itching
smash up nice job nice job wow you did so good one health holy shit nice job just foot just
focused up you know you know i'm saying you know you don't know what i'm talking about that was
one health i can't believe it oh gee willaker nice job oh geez oh geez oh oh you know what i'm
saying why something's going on my eye okay oh you eat that meat oh you know what i'm saying
oh man you're saying that's not even the boss it was we get the cup scene that's you is that you
no that's you oh you curse please have it be me please have it be me
that's not fair that's not fair that's not fair never died there's only two of us
we did it we sure did we're entering the question mark this is uh this is gonna be interesting
okay the great boy anvil get it do you get it that is anvil do you get it do you get it i think
you need to walk up you get it we're on the same page yes anvil what's the germa combo meal two
mcchickens blooming onion a gate array to 10 piece mcnugget tuna salad and pretzels
sounds kind of good although blooming onion has to be there because i went to outback once
and said it was good but it's recent it's it's it's it's topical as well
i'm feeling powerful i actually do feel pretty strong right now i don't i i feel like i'm using
the bow and the bow is bad i feel pain i feel pain gem of wisdom what does that one do uh skill
damage up let's do that the agility is just move speed can't really cross that i roll i do a little
bit of rolling just like elden ring which elden ring which elden ring castle or indoor environment
has the best bathroom you think they're gonna say which elden ring castle are you which elden
ring uh indoor facility bathroom would you um i'd like to use the most and order it by least
to most favorite i i want to go to the top of that one spire the giant like tree spire that you know
you like climb down in the middle of and shit all the way down at the hallock tree um you should
take this i don't think it was a halogen tree it was just the giant spire
so which elden ring castle are you okay so oh it's the boss man it's what's the main guy he's not the
boss but he's saying that things are he doesn't like us and that he's gonna win and he's doing
the anime akuma turn his back and look at us with the eye flash uh he's saying that we're not useless
but we are or something he's laughing that's a good one i like that one you really think you
can stop me then deal with this draws a card from his yu-gi-oh deck oh no it's impossible
how could they have ever known to hit the crystals that were connecting the robots to the shields
oh it only takes no way it takes two hits oh how could they have figured that out in time
two hits really my my damage is not good evil villain tropes are so funny
she's like and they'll never get away from this i love i loved in diablo 3 when asmodan would
fucking monologue you every level actual chrono trigger joke yeah that is it is a chrono trigger
joke have you played chrono trigger no can i pay you to play it i imagine there's a price
damn it how long is it um it's pretty long it's a solid at least it's at least 20 30 hours at
least i'd say probably somewhere around 40 you want to do everything i'm saying 20 20 yeah when
you uh when you beat jade cocoon i'll play it no that's kind of unfair though because
chrono trigger has had five re-releases on a bunch of different platforms i i i either have to
emulate this game or i have to buy it randomly from some well you just said you would pay me
to play chrono trigger and my price is you playing jade cocoon okay i've named my price
that's just the way it's gonna be if you're you're sitting there like you know like chrono
trigger is one of the greatest games of all time he hasn't played like chrono he has dude someone
else besides me has to have played jade cocoon no every time i bring it up everyone's like what
what's that i've heard it was really good i've heard it was so sick of it oh this is a
ribbit ribbit frog oh my god why can't we be friends with him i know like he only wasn't just
such an insolent well damn it maybe we could have oh how much damage are your hits doing
uh that one did 91 okay 40 to 50 on average my fully charged arrows is like 40 if i get a
credit that's about 100 and my my non-charged ones are like 20 oh god that was a lot go find
the nephilim you're referencing things that i don't know about that's not fair that's not fair
you played diablo 3 oh true i didn't know what that's i didn't know that's what we were doing
talk to marvin he wouldn't happen to know the way out of here would you know is that okay kill
kill i'm gonna get in your way you have a you have a couple of dollars if you want to buy
something i do have a lot of money that's right uh well i want let's heal refresh all these are
bad refresh are they bad that's all skills i'm reloading i'm re-rolling again there it is
um that's that's the skill so good you should i take i want it i i want it if you're not gonna
take it i want it uh can i drop it for you actually i don't think you well well yeah i
think when you buy it it drops on the ground okay there you go if that improves your ability then
you should have it i am improved if you beat this boss first try you have to make me a mod if you
lose i get perma band just perma band him now i think that's easier yeah you don't have to
remember that's too much for me to have to remember ouch this guy knows how to teleport
pretty good any apples in here we could use food so i'm just checking any any apples in here
it's just the sus guy the read the description it covers all i'm still thinking about you said
cheeseburger sub yeah that's just that's on the brain now when was the last time you had a
good cheeseburger stuff there was a place that i used to live near in boston that made a really
trashy garbage can't say it was good cheeseburger sub but i loved it yeah but um that's not a problem
though it's a it's a cheeseburger sub you can't say oh i had like this thing you didn't
um cheeseburger something is just something about him all right i mean i gotta quiet i'm gonna need
the heal oh these guys suck yeah they do yeah let's make sure we any apples in here nope okay
we splitting this i feel like yes i took 40 which is half i took as much that was 39 so i feel like
i got chipped a little bit any apples in here any apples in here okay we're good eating summer
sausage and watching germa are you what is the summer sausage what is the summer stuff
uh well it's summer time right pretty much is it still spring does anyone keep in track
fuck mary kill cheeseburger sub tuna sub what was the other one
kill the tuna sub no wait hold on i need to see this fuck mary kill oh meatball sub tuna sub
cheeseburger sub uh kill tuna fuck meatball mary cheeseburger uh hold on
uh this is actually kind of hard i think fuck i'm fucking the cheeseburger sub
well i think i think i got it i think this is it okay and then i'm gonna i'm gonna marry
the tuna sub and i'm gonna kill the meatball sub i i sad whoa what hey whoa okay those i thought
they were crushing us i can't move oh this apple's in here wait any apples in here
there are look this uh this is maybe the final boss so i need you to focus up not think about
fucking a meatball sub right now i you weren't listening fucking your tuna sandwich
so i do no damage this thing's got a lot of health too hey trying i'll try and take care
of the ads because i can at least stun them and stuff ah shit all right i'm getting too weird
about this oh it's the worst alarm on the iphone i hate that oh my god that just i that actually
fucked me up big time wait dude don't you hate it in a tv show where they like try and be authentic
and use like the real iphone like alarm noises yeah and then the person takes way too long like
they slowly roll over out of bed it's like dude fucking what are you doing just press
just press it everybody that has an alarm you everybody knows this when you the first second
you hear that sound you freak out and jump up and turn it off as fast as you can i'm gonna die
i'm gonna be up to you here in a sec better not be i i i can't hurt anything is there any food in
any containers or anything i'm dead any apples any apples in here good luck i think we're getting
roguelike i i think this whole run would have been better if i didn't use the bow like if we both
actually did hammer yeah but we could be getting roguelike because i mean i don't think so you
don't think so this is this is tricky this is hard my camera is being really weird i mean it's
gonna be very i have faith in you i truly do those ads are a killer though i mean this would be top
gamer moment of the year if you could pull this up if i wouldn't it's because of the shield dash
nice damn gamer gamer gamer gamer nice we were supposed to get roguelike there but you didn't
let it happen nice job that was great you know what that claps for me i'm honestly one of the
greats i'm surprised that there's more uh yeah maybe maybe not i think that was the last one
oh yeah i'm glad you did that because you got to the end i mean i think this is uh the final
there would be one more area in 1.0 is what i think is how it's going to be congratulations
don't let your guard down as there's plenty of new content coming yeah i hope you're the mvp
i think like if you still are and you probably still did more damage than me yep highly possible
congrats dude you fucking earned it thanks you got a few of those
i i thought i would at least get rolled the most cool oh this is good this i heavily enjoyed this
game that was really fun yeah i want to see what was up with the raptor guy it's very very fun i
wonder when 1.0 comes out did get the final weapon this guy come over up the dino guy
come up to the dine come up to the dinosaur but we have to identify items we have to talk to dad
we have things to identify that first one seems great yep all right let's talk to the dino
this old thing has seen better days hasn't it huh he's gonna fix it oh he's gonna fix it look at
this look at this look at this look at this look at him fixing it look at it look at that if you
shit your pants during five minutes as far as you have to tell us okay i wouldn't hide it no
hiding it either uh we want to know skill convergence and creation device that lets you
break down skill tablets into their most basic parts like miniscule i mean so small you can't
even see them dude then it transmute demographize them into new skills so you can wait can you make
a new mechanic what do we got uh anyway we can convert the skill tablets you find into new
skills pretty great huh if you find any more be sure to bring them back to me what's the skill
tablet acquire skill i guess we could never find them before because we never did we didn't have
him yet oh okay what's the what's the last weapon razor wind there's also another weapon
oh this is such a this is a stir weapon this is such a stir weapon spectral throw is one
of my favorite skills you're not wrong actually it's good but it takes a long time to load up a
perfect yeah but it still has like a quick attack just like the sword does sword doesn't have a
charge thing right the thing with the sword is has the dash move does the dash attack so you can
kind of just get it and get up whenever you hit an enemy with your charge attack your chain attacks
become empowered and deal bonus damage i don't know what chain attack is maybe the lightning
chains yeah okay i wonder what the last uh there's one more weapon that's not here yet
truly who knows all right well are you ready to play five nights at freddy's which one should
he play should you play one or two hey i got them both stirred remember when you said uh uh
what was it about how you were just gonna be the entertainment on the stream
uh yeah well hey everybody we're gonna raid stir i'm gonna stay in the call and we're gonna watch
him play so you what you said was accurate yeah so we figured that would be the best way to do
it because otherwise it's hard with like stream delays for him to even actually watch yeah so i'm
just gonna stay in the call i'm gonna raid him and we're gonna watch five nights at freddy's i'm
gonna be in the call people saying play both let's get a poll all in your chat all in my chat
could he do one or two because i'm just gonna let's be realistic stir be realistic too you're
probably gonna play this for like 30 minutes and uninstall both of them i you said beating the game
was like two hours give or take then if two is the better one maybe we should just do two let's see
because i feel like if it took that long to like legitimately beat one and move on to two i would
not want to play too at that point one is way more beginner friendly i'm not a beginner yeah but
this is a bunch of weird shit the balloon boy and you gotta put a mask on when they come into the
room and stuff i think i don't know we'll see what does your chat say uh i didn't make a poll
and there's like one guy that said please play too okay so do you want to go by the one guy in
your chat or do you want to go by what what's going on over here like you you'll be here to
tell me like what i need to do with the mass you should definitely you should definitely just okay
do start with one and then play like a quick one and then jump into two yeah like get get familiar
with one and then you'll understand too and then we can just jump right into two after like all
right let's let's get it champ okay uh so hold on let me make sure this is going well all right
everybody uh thanks for watching this stream we're about to continue on stir's stream it's
gonna be i've been looking forward to this for like two months we're gonna watch stir play five
nights at freddy's it's we get to watch along react stream uh i feel like stir is gonna do
pretty well i can't wait to see him get jump scared um so let's go oh right oh my god when's
the next time i'm streaming um i was thinking about tomorrow but i might do monday we'll figure
that out this this game opened in like a black bordered full screen window there is no options
menu and it's super loud it is a pretty loud game all right uh yeah either tomorrow or monday i'll
update this us uh later but we don't have is enough time yeah there's plenty of time for me
to do this while we raid stir what are you doing i'm raiding you right now and i'm just doing the
credits oh my god i'm i can't wait for this i i don't know why you're so excited i really don't
because i know that you're probably gonna hate this and you're i i just want to see how you do
this we're gonna get a diablo rant about five nights at freddy and all the whole universe i
can't wait right back one second yep but yeah should be fun let's go watch him try to figure
this game out i'll see you guys probably monday i don't really have a plan yet wait i do i do
actually have sort of a plan uh by the way we're going to be raiding you're not going to be able
to see the end of these credits i apologize but i have to tell you this really quickly the plan
is to play devil may cry i don't know which one to start with that's another one that people
scream at me and tell me which one but we're gonna play devil may cry on monday uh i don't
know which one but one of them see you later well see you over on stir stream if you're gonna watch
see you soon see you in a minute or see you in a few days okay i think we're over here now