Hey, what is going on, everybody? I am the Cactus. Welcome to another Timed Chaos build.
And I'm like stuck down here like this. Hey, do not close me in. This is...
No, I'm stuck. Okay. This is a Timed Chaos build, like I said, with MLC Stealth and Italics.
Hello, gentlemen. Hi. How's it going, German viewers?
Hi. So this week's episode, we are going to build a praying mantis.
This could be the toughest one yet, considering it's a praying mantis and it's incredibly difficult.
So we're going to have eight minutes, just like last time, to build this thing.
And... are you guys ready? Wait, where are we doing this? Like, right here?
In the shadow of the giant back here, I guess. I don't know. Let me change it back to daytime.
The cheese guy? The guy that's like a block of American cheese?
We've got plenty of area to work with here. Hey, we need that space.
He's building a grass trophy. Alright, he's building something that's really, like, not allowed.
Are you ready? I don't know what this is. I'm going to start the timer and then we're going to be in a lot of trouble.
So are you ready? Nope, because I've got to delete this thing. Alright, delete, delete, delete, delete, delete.
Alright, and in three... Wait, what are we building again? Hold on. A praying mantis. We went over this.
Alright, praying mantis in three, two, one, go.
Alright, where's the front? Where's the back? I don't know.
I don't know what a praying mantis looks like. Alright, start with the legs. There's like four finely little legs.
Alright, so he's got four... No, he only has two legs, doesn't he?
You guys just get started. I'm Googling praying mantis. I think he's got four.
No, I think a praying mantis has... I don't know. No, he has two. He crawls on his hands and knees, doesn't he?
Why didn't we look up what a praying mantis looks like?
I'm pretty sure he's only got... I think he's got four legs. Wait, I don't have the color green wool.
He has four legs. That's Google Images here.
He has four legs? Now where are they? Oh my god, what are you doing?
I'm building a big spiny leg. Looks like a vulture.
We didn't put the green on the same color.
Well, we're using dark green, or whatever the darker one is.
Alright, like, why can't I put a block down here?
See, here's his legs. So that's... Okay. He's gonna be like a grasshopper.
He's gonna come out this way.
Or delete all of my blocks if you want to.
Wait, how do you place a block? Oh, right click.
How do you place a block?
I was left clicking and I was like, why is it destroying everything?
So wait, are his four legs bad? I gotta look up what he looks like.
No, he's got a really long body.
Yeah, he's got like two in the front and then two on the side, like right next to him.
And then a really long body in the back with wings on top.
This looks like a goose.
Okay, so let's...
Like a little sphere body. You know what I'm saying?
See, like three blocks wide.
Four blocks.
Alright, so...
So, don't make it any wider than this.
And just make his body come out to touch the blocks. You know what I'm saying?
Alright, good thing we're making like a goose grasshopper. This is perfect.
Yeah, currently we're making... I don't know what this is.
It looks like some kind of jungle gem is what it looks like.
I don't know.
Let's make the slide.
Oh look, we're making another horse.
It's the same thing as the horse.
It's a green horse.
His body's gonna be so much longer than this, like way longer.
Like, hold on.
Yeah, it's gotta go out past the legs.
I was building like his chest now.
Alright, I'll start building his neck, I guess.
Wait, I thought that's what I was doing just now.
Oh, is that the front or is this the front?
He's not like a giraffe. It has to come out long like this.
Yeah, the neck goes out pretty far.
And he's got his like scissor hands.
Wait, shouldn't he be looking up right now?
Start going up.
Yeah, why is he going so far like left?
What is this, Jerma, what is this?
Dude, he's like looking at something.
Like, he looks up.
Alright, well then stop going up right now, from here.
Alright, I'm building.
Because his legs start where he starts going up.
Hold on, we gotta redo the legs then.
I'm working on the tail or something back here.
Alright, three minutes have gone by.
Oh, good.
Three minutes already.
Alright, this just looks like...
Seriously, I just made a giant like man's arm.
Like, this is like not even...
This might actually come together pretty well.
I don't know, I'm not convinced yet.
Wait, what's going on with his leg?
This is his leg.
Why is this here then?
Why is what where?
Oh wait, are these the T-Rex arms?
One of the things I'm making out, these are...
He has four legs.
What have we made here?
Alright, I'll make his face.
This will be his face then.
What happened?
What have you done to Gumby?
Looks like somebody put Gumby on the torture rack and then like stretched him out.
This looks like some sort of dinosaur.
Oh, good thing we brought Gumby to the medieval times and put him on like the stretcher.
The breastplate stretcher.
Alright, I'm making some wings.
Alright, time to make his arms.
Alright, I'm gonna work on his head.
Four minutes and twenty seconds of Gumby.
If I cover up his body with the wings...
Wait, this thing has wings?
Yeah, dude.
Wait, wait.
Prey mantises have wings.
Dude, this thing...
We're making like a centaur.
This is not a preying mantis.
This is a centaur.
I did the arms like so wrong.
He's like...
He's got the same arms as the dude behind him.
Come over here where I am, right here behind you.
Alright, I'm redoing this.
It looks like alien, okay?
It looks like alien from the movie Alien, except he's green.
Well, I guess Prey Mantis kinda looks like an alien, doesn't he?
No, like the alien.
Oh.
God, this is so awful.
Five minutes have gone by.
Alright, I got...
I'm getting pretty good on the wings right here.
We're doing pretty good.
Alright, there's his head.
Oh my god.
Hi, I'm preying mantis.
Are you guys making Squidward over there?
Yes.
He looks like...
Oh my god.
This is the worst preying mantis.
We don't have no time.
You have to look at it where it blocks out the rest of his body.
And it just looks hilarious.
Come over here where I am.
Where it blocks out the back of his body.
You can't even tell.
It looks like a stick figure, like a green alien.
Oh, he really does just look like an alien.
He looks like the self-proc alien.
Okay, his body needs to be not a complete atrocity.
This needs to be a little bit bigger or wider.
A little more thick.
Alright, six minutes have gone by.
Six minutes? Good grief, man.
It's good, we got him.
I made some wings, so that's cool.
I think.
Where are you going?
Oh no!
He's got the tiniest little legs.
These hands have to be like knives.
Okay, make them knives.
My Minecraft is so bad at...
Now he has machine guns apparently.
What's the different colors?
You said he had to have knives.
So I made knives.
Alright, let's give this other one a knife too.
Oh yeah.
Don't mess with him, he's got like two Tommy guns.
Oh, okay, good idea.
Good, good, good.
Dude, these legs are too small.
Less than one minute.
When he was born.
We have less than one minute.
Look at his freaking head.
It really just looks like an alien.
Alright, wait 30 seconds.
30 seconds.
He can fly more with these wings.
Hold on, let's make him bigger.
Okay, here we go. His legs are a little bit more thick now.
He's so wise.
You guys are kind of...
He's a little lopsided.
15 seconds.
And one hand is like
extremely larger and thicker than the other.
10 seconds.
And then we combined two different things in the middle.
It doesn't even look like they're connected.
Three seconds, two, one.
That's it.
I put a torch on his face
to make it look like he was smoking something.
I don't know why.
A good thing we combined two things in the middle.
We made like an airplane
and then we combined it with this thing right here
and then an alien.
Somebody totally deleted my wings.
I added more wings.
Alright, can somebody come explain to me
what's going on over here?
What is going on? Why does he have like one hand
that's like...
This is most certainly not a praying mantis.
One hand has a darker colored knife
and has seen more battle
than the other apparently.
This is like, oh my god.
Come look at it from far away.
It is so bad from far away.
Up close, it's not that bad.
This is not a praying mantis.
It's like a dragon who just didn't make it.
Just like, I don't know.
The wings are like on his butt.
Oh man.
Yeah, we didn't like do enough.
This is like too long or we didn't like fill it in enough
like right here.
It's just like a lot of nothing.
Oh my god. Alright, well
thanks for watching guys
and we'll catch you guys all next time
and of course rate the thing
and give it a name if you want to give it a name
and we'll see you all next time. Take care everybody.
Boo!
What? What just happened there?