Hey, I have to talk a little low today because I turned my compressor way up because I'm going
to be standing kind of far away. Oh wait, Robo? What? Is it a Robo? Hello? What does it sound like?
It sounds like Kylo Ren. Not supposed to. Does it sound like Kylo Ren? How's this?
This reverb? There shouldn't be any reverb. How about now? Is that better? Is that a little
bit better? No. How would there be reverb right now? There shouldn't be reverb. Why are you
in a gym pool room? Is it two mics? It shouldn't be. Oh, wait a minute. I need to be alive. Listen
to this. Let me see what this sounds like. It sounds like a gym pool room. All right, hold on.
Let me see if I can hear what you're talking about. Gym. All right. Well, let me explain
something for a second. I have reinstalled Windows. Okay. So last night I reinstalled Windows,
got VR to work. Is it a gymnasium? So I got VR to work. Oh, shit. Hold on. Hello? Okay, let me see.
That sounds much better. That sounds better. Okay, so what happened was,
uh, yeah, I was listening to it at the same time. Fucking gymnasium. Okay, so that's better.
So we sound fine. Okay, good. That means I can turn the compressor back up and
because I'm gonna be standing far away. All right, good. We're good. So let me tell you the story
before we go over. Vive is back in action. Yes, I have no idea what the fuck happened. I've
reinstalled Windows. I reinstalled every program and now my Vive works again. I uninstalled every
driver. I uninstalled every program. I've reinstalled my Bluetooth. Guys, I downloaded a program
called like Super Driver Booster and it updated like 115 drivers on my computer
and it didn't work. So I just reinstalled. No, it's not a virus. The thing actually worked.
Windows fucks up everything. I have no idea. So yeah, I know this. Spoilers. You can hear it.
Let me turn it off. We're getting back into VR. I told you it was gonna happen somewhere
at the end of September and look at me. Here we are. It's a legit virus my grandmother would
download. Well, your your favorite internet streamer downloaded it. I'm your favorite,
right? I have to be. Come on. It's October. Yeah. What happened to Far Cry 1? I'll tell you what
happened to Far Cry 1. I reinstalled Windows. It got VR to work. So I'm playing VR and like I don't
think I even want to play Far Cry 1. I remember that game. That's the game that's like impossible
even on easy and the enemies can shoot you from like 30 miles outside the map and through walls.
Well, I don't want to play that game. Yeah, I would turn that. That would be like a Ratatouille
stream and you know it. Far Cry 1 sucks to be honest. Yeah, I'll play it. You know what? I'll
play it. Everybody is waiting for me to play. Everybody's waiting for me to play Half-Life
Alyx, but I'm not going to do that today. It's been like more than a year since I've gone into
VR at all. So I'm going to ease into it. We're going to start Half-Life Alyx tomorrow. That's
the stream tomorrow. I'm going to warm up with some fucking Chikootery board today and then
tomorrow is Half-Life Alyx. Yeah, fair enough. Yeah, I've spent like a year. Everything's set
up. It's ready to go. I'm just stalling because all my VR streams are like three hours long. So
I have to stall for like at least 10 minutes to add some, you know, content to the beginning of
the stream. I'll just shake up my fucking drink. All right, let me lower this because now you can
hear me. Tell me if it gets bad because I will try to fix it. All right, let's go. So the first
game we're going to play. Move over here. We're going to play Vacation Simulator. We're just easing
into it. Wait, I didn't fucking even tweet. Shit. This is a Tuber game. It's an ease into VR game.
Guys, I just like last time I have like 40 VR games that I downloaded. It's Chubby Bunny. No,
it's not Chubby Bunny time. Not on VR. What are you crazy? Okay, I just started typing Chubby Bunny
into my tweet. Like that's the thing I'm doing today. Chubby Bunny, come on in. Like that's
going to take three hours. Okay, let's see. What do I do? Yeah, VR. How about VR is back? That's
man. That's kind of that's too desperate. Like VR is back. Please come watch. VR meat and cheese.
No, that's what the title is. VR. Who cares? VR. That's it. VR meat and cheese. Sucks. Whatever.
Dude, I'm fucking laughing right now. I don't even know why. All right.
Why does it always default to German 98? Every time I type in my Twitch password into my Twitch
stream, I get this thing where it's like, oh, it auto goes to a Twitch channel called German 98.
And I'm like, that's not me, dude. Okay. I think we stalled long enough. It's time to go.
You leaked the password. All right, we're gonna have to see if this works. Well, here we go.
There you are. See, look, it's virtual reality. And me. So we are going to get started here.
I know I have idea. This is my coffee. He's here. It's him. The Reddit shelf. Can I tell you how
concerned I am today about this? I am really concerned that I'm going to hit this. I think
I'm going to move my entire VR setup into another room and just feed long cables into the room.
I have less space, guys, than last time I did VR. I can't move from here. If I go like two feet
that way or like two feet that way, I'm putting a hole in the wall. He got bigger. Nice. Did you
notice? Flip it when he does. I bet the whole thing's coming down. Look at how fucking annoying
this is. This is annoying. Why do they make these? This is, it's got spikes on it. Like it hurts to
hold this. It's like a challenge holding this fucking Starbucks cup. I don't even know why
they make these. It's a weapon. All right. You ready? I've stalled long enough. I'm wearing
pants, right? Let me put my headphones in. Make sure, you guys can hear this, right?
I can see the chat. Don't worry. I have the toolkit thing set up. Covered the game reward.
You're not going to see it at all today. Don't worry. Too quiet? I'm too quiet? Oh no, the game
is too quiet. Okay. I'll fix that. Don't worry. That was a one guy moment. Did I get one guide?
All right. Here we go. Ready? I'm going in. Okay. Yes, I still have the ice cream cones. I don't have
the fucking knuckle controllers. I'm sorry. I can't even hear myself. Grab a vacation pass
off the table to get started. Okay. I'm going in. No, I'm not. No, I'm not. It hurt. I was,
it was been on the top of my head for too long. Hold on. Dude, imagine if I just like,
just fucking bald and the hair is all stuck up here. Just got a haircut for this very purpose.
Shit. I forgot to wipe the lenses. Hey, yeah, yeah, yeah. I got it. Hold on. Because once you go in
here, you can't come out for like 30 minutes. I'm in. All right. Wait, which side was left and
right? I don't remember. Can you see? What the fuck? Why isn't it on? Okay. There we go.
All right. I'm going in. I'm going in. I'm going to be in. I'm going in. I'm in. Vacation is
waiting human. Grab one of those passes. Where's my other hand? In. Where's my other hand?
I got two hands. Okay. Human one, human four, human five. Or the, yeah, I could see you. That's
me. Insert guest pass. Hello, human. Waiting for guest pass. Try to speak human five. Great.
Now put it in the slot and pull the lever. I'm getting plus twoed for that shit.
I'm getting plus twoed for crunk. That's bullshit.
How are you? Vacation. We should learn how to talk to bots. When you're close,
just wait to get a bot's attention. I don't even wear the wrist wraps. I'm a fucking rebel.
That's a bad idea. Put those on. Nintendo warned me about that. What the fuck? I'm putting them on.
I know. It's been a long time. Give me a minute. The only way to get a bot to talk. Shut up. Try it
now. Shut up. Great job. You really nailed the standard human greeting protocol. This is a warm
up. This is a warm up. See? I've got a red dot sight. Hey, I would not say anything fucking mean to me.
I wasn't listening to any of that.
Fuck. Somebody said, somebody called me a fucking loser. Somebody called me short.
Oh, fucking NAA. How much ammo do I have? What do you say? Come take the thing out of the, oh,
now I'm getting too close. Hold on. What do you say? Get into the bathroom so you can get
ready to vacation. Let's go. Every human starts as a blank slate. You can be the you you see in
yourself. You're gonna watch me in the bathroom? Where's the toilet? Do I piss into the sand
bathtub? This is uh, this, this, this isn't like your grandmother's house. This is to make you
not think that you've had or something. Good. All right. Now what? Oh shit. All right. Come on.
Okay. Now Jeremy, you're looking for 40 cents. What is this? Makeup? Oh, it's snow. It's skin.
Okay. Mr. Greens. I'm sorry. I'm acting like this is the first time I've ever put this on.
I'm sorry. It's been a year. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Go back, back, back, back, back, back,
back, back. I want to go back. No, I want to go back. I want to go back. I want to go back. I want
to go back. I want to go back. I want to go back. I want to go back. I want to go back. I want to be,
I want to be a Ninja Turtle. Thank you. Am I in a Don't Tell on mood today?
Ah, Leonardo. Any green? Dude, you know, you know what I'm thinking? Why, why, why have they not
given a Ninja Turtle a beard? I think that would like really, really do well with like the zoomers,
don't you think? Like, like a nice, like clean shaved beard. I don't care about any of this.
Would you wear glasses over your VR headset? I don't care. Oh, shit. I don't have, I don't
have any hair for that. Oh, that hurts. You guys ever, hey, do you guys ever do this? I do, I do
this. I go, everybody does that. Why? Cause it gets, I don't know, it gets a little irritated
there. I look, I've seen, I don't know where you are, but I've seen the photo. I've seen the photos
of my armpit hair and it kind of freaks me out. So yeah, I got to stay on top of it because people
will take like a small clip of me like with my arm up and they'll like zoom in on my fucking armpit
hair. And the only thing that they say is hair, hair, look at hair, hair. And it's like, yeah,
yeah, yeah, we got hair. Okay. Oh God. What did I just hit? That's not real. I thought I knocked
something off the table. I thought I knocked something off of my table. That's just a fake
toothbrush. How do I do this? Oh shit. This is cool. Okay. Brush it up down there. Oh, you do drink
it. Don't do that. Why would you do that? Why did you drink toothpaste? Don't do this challenge
video. Okay.
All right. I think we're good. Can I leave the bathroom? Look crazy.
We have an am I in the room? I don't even know. Oh my God. It's a bath toy.
I lost an earbud. Hold on. All right. We're in the bath. These bath bombs. Oh, they are.
Are they bath bombs? Oh, that's dumb. It's rain. What? Oh, nice. Okay.
Shit. Be careful. Hey, oh, bubble bath. My favorite. Ah, is this even hot?
Where are the bubbles? This is fucking bullshit. This ain't Elmo bubble bath, the best one.
I'm going to hit something. Let's make a fucking fire. Okay. I ate it. All right. Oh, that's fun.
I'm done. Electronics in there. I can't help it. It's VR, dude. Nothing. It's not even real life.
It's VR. Oh, isn't there a video of a cat doing this under the faucet? Just sitting there and
just drinking cat like goes, it's like a funny cat video. That was cool. I got this long hair,
the carrot top. I'm having too much fun. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no. I can't have Twitch TV here. How about this? It's DJ time.
I forgot how much fun this was.
Here, take this one of a kind human back storage device. Wow, human, you look really tourist.
Feel free to continue exploring your suite. There better be a stack of red balls in there.
God, I like this one. This one's fun. Holy shit. This is a fun game. I like this one. I'm going to
stay in this one for a while. Kramer. You know what to do? Honky choco. Oh, diet doctor oil.
Hi, room. Is this somebody else's hotel room? It is. What am I? Don't make like a slam your
don't. Why would I make a slam your dick in the fridge joke? That's what I do that for.
I'm just I'm kind of unhinged right now, right? I shouldn't. I'm not going to do that.
Game's fucking terrible. Delete it. That didn't even break. I like it again. Hot drink pods,
lemon juice. Is VR so cool? All right. Lemon juice. Okay. Should I call Grover? Oops.
I just told him to go fuck himself in binary. All right. Where am I? Where am I in the room?
Blackjack on here. It's not even hard. Game's not even hard. I fucking win again.
Let's try the computer to go fuck himself in binary. All right. Let's go. This is an ego
stream. Bod watchers skip. It was the same joke. You can make the same joke within that was a one.
I guess one minute went by. This was my room. Let me know if you're ready to vacation and remember
waving is the best way to talk to bots. All right. Where do you guys want to go? Beach,
the forest or the mountain? No, I'm not. What? Are you ready to go human? You have to wave at me
if you want to talk in beach, beach, beach, beach, beach. All right. We'll go beach. How do I go?
Please only scan the hand that has the resort provided wristband for the resort scanner to
function. You must lateral hand movement also called waving is a convenient way. I need a
pass. We were ready to vacation, but it looks like all the destinations are closed right now.
What is this? This wasn't here earlier. Funny. You should ask the bureau of simulations requires
my goggles are getting steamy. Which you seem to have conveniently forgotten. Luckily,
I figured out a way to measure vacation, quantified memory management efficiency, but I should have
known here human take this wristband. It will be your key to unlock efficient. How many viewers
are here? Oh good. It's okay. There's 7,200 people here. Efficient. Now use it on that scanner over
there. Access denied. You don't have enough memories. Yes. You need memories to gain access
to different areas of the resort here. Try this. A memory of the time is how you vacation.
What did he just say to me? Can he just tell me to go fuck myself? It looks like your wristband
has enough memories for that scanner. Bring it back for the third time. Bring it back for a third
time. Accepted. When that vacation is open, you can visit any of our three destinations.
The beach is the most efficient place to start. Quiet. I want to play that way. Please select.
The beach is a great place to start your vacation. That's where I want to go. I want to go to the
beach. Oh, I had to like wave at it. Welcome to Vacation Beach. Humans came to the beach to
reconnect to the moment they evolved to walk on land. All right, move. I see you're finally
getting the hang of vacation. Make enough memories and you'll get access to more areas of Vacation
Island. Cosmo and Wanda, leave me the fuck alone. I'm happy we made it to the beach. The Bureau of
Simulations won't be... I wish I had no grandparents. Boom. They're gone. Didn't he do that in an
episode? But I know a way to track the moments you enjoy. And then like the apocalypse happened?
The camera in your backpack. It happened in one of those. Try it out. It happened, right?
Just tap the button on the camera to snap a photo. Oh, this is cool. Now this is vacation. Wait,
am I going to put the backpack? There are plenty of actual memories to be made on the beach.
But actually, I know that actually happened. Have fun vacationing your way, human.
Oh, you can do a selfie. We'll see you later. Why are all selfies all the way up like that?
How come there's no selfies like this? They're all always like that. Why? What does this do? I
don't understand. Why don't you just do this? I have to go like this? Why? It's too high.
Explain it to me. Because everybody's ugly and that looks good from up there.
Well, I guess you can go instead of like this and go see the difference. Yeah, that makes sense.
Oh, shit. I just took a picture of like my... Stop taking photos. I got it. Put it in the backpack.
Are you alive? I didn't... I dropped it a little. Oh, no, no. This guy needs some sunscreen. I had...
This is like GTA, guys. You have to punch the first person you see. How do I travel around?
Are you using that? Can I... Are you using this? Is this guy dead? Is he... Hey,
Marley, throw me the ball. Throw me the ball. I'm concerned about this guy. The sun is on,
the water is wet. Oh, yes. Pass me a ball and then it's game on. Hey, it's a handball.
Right now what? The rules are simple. Get the ball past me and I'll hand you a point.
Try to beat my high score, human. That's one. Where am I? Well, how close am I? I don't know
where I am. Watch this technique, ready? Fuck, never mind. That's it? With more training,
you can get that high score. Lost. Let's go. I gotta get a good one. Where am I? Perfect time
for sports. Hey there, human. Toss me something. Oh, it's all hands on and off. I wanna go to the
dive site next. This is so fun. Okay, give me a ball. I don't know where I am. The shelf. Is it
the red shelf? Is it okay? Is it all right? It's coming down. Oh, it's like a daria. No,
that would be this. I need another ball. Move forward. It's falling. That thing back to that
thing just rushes me. He's got low blood sugar. No, I don't. I've eaten. I'm fine.
Blood sugar. I need another ball. Burgers are up there. Fuck this game. Oh, yes.
Oh, what the fuck, dude? Oh, I can dig there. Maybe I'll get a fucking coin.
That was a plus two. Are you fucking serious? Are you guys kidding me? Are you serious? Really?
That's an Animal Crossing joke. You guys love that game. Really? Come on, dude. What do I do?
I just... Who eats a hamburger like this? This is like the police cut off the crust. Okay,
that was weird. All right. All right. What we got? Beach cheese. What are these? Tortillas?
I'm on there. No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm a human. I'm a tall box. I'm a super computer behind machine.
But I think I'm an animal in the head. Can you help me clear some of these requests?
Thank God we got it. Okay, well, I need a patty, right? A Minecraft cheese blocker.
All right. Can I break this down? Can I melt? I got to make my perfect burger. Fuck. Not too
much. A little bit more. All right. That looks good. No, just no gross ketchup. No gross mustard.
Come on. Give me that one. Oh shit. I touched it.
They have any vegetables? How come there's no vegetables?
This looks like a really shitty cake. Oh, wait a minute. There we go. Come on. Get on there.
Where's the lettuce? Hey, I'm taking this with me. Guys, it's made out of fondant. Don't worry.
These redeem at the front desk for 20 tokens. I want to make a hot dog.
Swiss cheese. That's the best. Let's want it. But you don't act like you guys don't do the same
thing. Wouldn't do this. Okay. Dog in there. Is it frozen? That's fucking rancid. People do that
shit, you know. Nice. All right. Good. Little bit of oil. Ketchup. Mustard. Ketchup. Bacon. Right?
Right. Ketchup. Mustard. Bacon. What's the rest of it? All right. Let's go. That was fun. Oh,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. What am I doing? What am I thinking? I'm such an idiot. Where's
my camera? Okay. Selfie. How am I going to get? Wait. Set it up like this. I got to get this on
Instagram. I am so glad you're here to help me out. Check out the requests. Ah, got it. Good.
All right. Get out of my way. It's all right. What is that over there? Nudge me? Sandcastle sandbox?
Welcome to the sandcastle station, human. You can design your own castle or try to follow the
blueprints. This is boring. No, I'm bored. Your minigame sucks. You should be more like the grill
guy up there. That's fun. Cool. And you have, by the way, you have the most expensive stand.
How many customers? Less than five? How many did the grill guy get up there? Like a hundred? Yeah,
well, you've got like an LCD screen too. Like this is rude. Missed so much. Missed 50 subs? Karen.
Minus two. Karen. I'm just, I'm not a Karen. No, I, guys, I have not walked up to the person filming
and went, what are you doing? What are you filming? Yeah. Oh yeah. Oh yeah. And they bring up their
phone. How do you like that? Huh? I haven't done that yet. I haven't done that yet. Who gave the subs
yet? Was it? It was Freddy Dredd? Thanks, Freddy. Thank you for the 50 subs. Fucking crazy. That's
so much money. Thank you, Freddy. Hook was upside down. Just uh, hook was upside down.
I'm going to have a place of business here. Probably have at least a little bit of cleanliness.
Okay. That side there. Hi. Hello. Hi. Yes, I am a customer waiting to be served. Hey,
you're my first customer today. Yes. Let's make a memory together. Take a selfie and hand it to me
so I can frame this moment. And don't forget your camera hovers my human. It will let you strike a
sweet pose. The bottom right rainbow popsicle, when I press it, it sticks in a little bit.
I mean, I still got what I ordered. I still got the popsicle, but it sticks in and it's fucking
annoying. I bring me and my kids come in here all the time and one day they're probably going to get,
it's going to get stuck and it's going to get stuck too hard. They're not going to get it.
Oh, you're filming and you're filming. Oh, okay. Hello. Hello everybody. Yes. Filming me.
Good. Yeah. Good. Oh, well, what do you know? Now I can film you too. Okay. Smile, right?
Fucking asshole. Fix your fucking machine. I lost my Jaron. Oh, I can't. What happened to my other
earbud? All right. I want one of these. I'm getting strangled. I'm actually getting strangled right
now. Fucking vibe. I swear to God, I would, Hey, vibe. Yeah. Let me talk to the vibe manager.
And I said the earbuds like didn't just slip out every five seconds. You know,
one of these days it's going to get stuck in there and okay. Taking a selfie. Okay. Okay.
You enjoy vacation. I got it. Subject. You look amazing. You must be a model. Oh, thanks.
I want one of those. You're hurting for cash. You can find some sand dollars on the ground
and shallow water. I want it for free. Oh, no memories. Do you want to help me prove that
beach vacation has the best moments? Give me a wave and I can tell you more.
Dive site. The joy of vacation is uncovered with tangible progress. In this case, you need five
memories to progress to the dive site. I haven't made any memories. What the fuck have I been doing?
All I've been doing has been making memories.
What are you talking about? I have to give photos. Look, you're obviously the hands of this operation.
So can you put the photo on the sketch yourself? Do you want to help me prove that beach vacation
has the best? Tell me what to do. Give me a wave. How do I do this? Oh, hi there. Are you also on
vacation? So, well, I'm not here to make assumptions about what sketch you're capturing.
You're going to have to place your own photo. It's hard to watch his mind going like this.
Of my sibling bots, the beach is clearly the best vacation. Am I right? And I need your help to
prove it. If you could take some photos that match these sketches, I can show my siblings I had the
best vacation. What sketches? Grill. He wants a photo of a grill. What sketches is he talking
about? Yes. Yes. This looks very photo. Now can you place it on the sketch? Oh, I did it. Now my
siblings will see how much fun I'm having. By the way, human, you can replace any photo on the stand
as long as it matches the original sketch. He wants a picture of like a hamburger
or a hot dog. Does it matter? All right. Let's go get that right now. I wasn't on the grill.
What the fuck was that? Oh, I'm whole. I thought I was holding it still. They defrosted.
I don't know. What the hell is this shit? Why is there like an upside down pineapple upside down
cake? Let's develop these. All right. I got it. That's what he wanted, right? I'm coming.
The fun of beach vacation inspired you human. Take this memory. Oh shit.
I need, I need three more memories. Let's go get them. Let's go make them.
Okay. What kind of memory can I do with you? Sorry. I'm like a dog. All right. What is it? What
are you doing? Oh my, would you look around? There are so many beach, all of these tiny creatures,
which would be a kind human and fetch me three different types. They're very shy.
So move slowly. Creatures. Shoot him out of the air. What is this? It's a manicotti. Here,
I got found you a manicotti. I want to look at that later. There's a motha boy. Does the butterfly
come back? Oh my God. I found money. All right. There he is. I got to get that guy. This whole
time he was sitting there just going like, please don't fucking see me. Please don't fucking see me.
Please don't fucking see me. Got one. Is he all right? Get him. Help, help, help. Oh, I killed
him. I almost just fell backwards. How do I eat? Can I, how do I get these? Backpack. Hold on. Hey
little guy. I'm going to take you to safety. All right. What? How do I give this to her? And this
vibe headphones, man. Put him on the grill. No, I'm not going to grill him. That's fucked up.
I need the butterfly. All right. We have to, all right. I'm going to put you back.
I'm not going to cook him. Why would I do that? Here, sit on this little island.
He's okay. All right. Oh shit. No, I had to make the friends. Oh my God. Where's that camera?
Give me the camera. Give me it quickly. Holy shit. This is going to get me a lot of money on
National Geographic. Oh my God. Wait, I get it. Good. Take a picture of them on the grill. No,
fuck out of here. We are. How are we? I'm not grilling these two. Look at how cute they are.
I'm not doing that. I'm not doing that shit. No. What was the actual? Oh yeah. Got one.
Thank you, human. Two more butterflies will really make my screen.
Great. One more for my bug report. Okay. All right. One more. Where's the last one?
I see it right there. Thank you, human. And so my heart is filled and so is this bug report.
Let's bask in the memory like a butterfly in the sun. Beach bugs. Okay. I got money now.
All right. I got money. What do you want me to do? Hello, human. I'm still having fun in
this game. Do you like to do some yoga? What's all over here? Here, human. Please follow me
to achieve a state of optimal profiting. All right. Now we box. You seem to be out of alignment,
human. Don't forget to breathe.
Am I asking too many questions? Inhale. Positive. Exhale. Negative.
Why do I have to hold them like this? That is very yoga. This is not how you do this.
Find your inner home page. I don't. Give me my money. I don't want the money for this. I don't
care about anything. Can you smell your stomach? Your precision algorithm is almost accurate.
Great job, human. Keep following the optimization procedure. I'm here. I'm going to turn the AC
down. I might have to take a little quick break after the beach. Yes. Feel the energy going
through your body. I don't want to do this. I feel like I'm like a monkey. Visualize a calm,
rolling ocean like this one. So excellent job. I hope your data is no longer compressed.
Take this memory. It is the essence of your path to relaxation. That's three memories, right?
Where am I? How close might I be? I need two more memories. Fine. Fine. I'll do it.
Oh, what the fuck? All right. Let's go. Fine. I'll do it. I'll make a memory.
Judge me. Where am I? I think you need to take a closer look at the blueprints, human.
Oh, let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Judge it.
The top is exactly what we're looking for. A front. Now we just need to make the rest match.
I feel like I'm doing the cup thing that they do in like the competitions where they go like,
how do people do that shit? Yup. Dodge, please. What? The sides are correct.
Haven't had a chance to look at the blueprint, human.
Off to a good start. Your front is correct. How about this? Now you just need to work on the rest.
This is the front. Right. I need a side. Am I doing wrong? Use the whole board. Turn on the
grill? Top right. Top right block. What's wrong with it? What's wrong with the top right? Fine.
Oh my god. He's pretending. His brain. Use the corners. Top right has a side.
What's going on? Top right. You can't be serious. Oh my god. He's insane.
Screamer. Fucking laugh. Different block. What? This is what you meant. I thought you meant like
this thing over here. I thought, okay. They didn't make it clear. You gotta say it top.
What are you talking about? That's correct. This is incorrect?
Oh, it's the left side? The left side has to be like that too. They didn't say that. They didn't
say that. Or shit. Oh god. Fucking damn it. Okay, this is, it's too up. So this front, it's like
this weird, it's got a thing on it. It's got a lip on it. This one has got, the right side looks
like this. Okay. And then this is that. And then this side is the front. That shit right there.
Right side. I know. I'm working on it. Okay. So front, three high. Okay. And right side.
What? What are you talking about? What's wrong with it? You graduated college? Yeah,
15 years ago. I haven't sat in a classroom in fucking 16 years. I've been eating cheeses
and drinking fucking cheese whiz and watching Netflix. I lost it all. I lost all of it. It was
16 years ago. Little bottom block is solid. I'll take a memory please.
Nope. Beginner. I'm not, I don't want to do that anymore. That's, that's annoying.
It's annoying. Yeah. Your game is annoying. You're annoying too. Annoying hat, annoying glasses,
annoying, annoying fucking wind fury from Hearthstone. What's the guy's name? What's
the guy's name? The wind fury guy. What's his name? No, no, no, no, no. He goes, that's what
they didn't say. That's what they didn't say. Like swatting insects. Like swatting insects.
That's what they didn't say. Alkazir. Alkazir. Alakir. Yes. Thank you. Somebody got it. Somebody
went to college in here. How many more do I need? Just one more, right? Oh, here we go. I need another
ball. Hearthstone college. No, when you attack with Alakir, he goes, that's what they didn't
say. That's what they didn't say. Cause you can go twice. You're never going to un-hear it.
That's what they did say. I'm telling you. What does he have to do?
I win. Oh.
Dive. I can dive now. When is the next iPad stream? Why the fuck do you want an iPad stream?
Oh, wait. I hope you like our machine serve vending product. Oh,
put it down. Oh, okay. I'm all right. That just like, that just triggered like a response from me.
What happened to my ears? Dude, biting like directly into a fucking ice cream like that
with like just, Oh, wait a minute. I hope you had an excellent time vending on vacation.
Humans use selfie as their primary method of communication. I'm that annoying guy with the
bottle of Sriracha that takes a bite and fucking puts a line down and takes a bite and puts a line
down and takes like, dude, fucking put it down, put it down. That stuff's gross. Don't do that.
Come on, man. Don't do that. Why are you that guy? Yes, I don't like Sriracha. I don't think it's
gross. I'll address you directly. I think Sriracha is gross. I think it just does. I think it just
tastes sour and like it smells to me. All right. Did I just lose like a thousand viewers? Maybe.
I don't know. I just personally don't like it. I know people that love it, but that's great.
I'm a Tabasco guy. I know I just made, okay. I just pissed off a lot of people. That's fine.
I'm a green Tabasco guy or a Tabasco reserve guy. Let me address you directly.
Oh my God. I'm so excited. Thanks. I had fun at the daycare.
Oh shit.
Enjoy your dive, human. Okay. Looking for 40 cents. Rehash. That's a fucking rehash.
Oh, that was pretty cool. Hey, get away. You're going to propel it out. Grab a lens?
Did you die by eating these? You die. You can die if you eat this, right? Aren't there like
four chefs in all of the world that can actually make it so you don't die if you eat that? Why
would you want to eat that? Come down here to see the sunken ship, but I'm more interested in
marine life. Poisonous. But there are aquatic creatures down here unlike anything. These photos
of the more unique citizens of the sea. So I may add them to my collection. Hello photo lens.
I'm fucking realistic. I'll take these to my backpack. I'm sorry guys. Anything that has
like a, like an 8% chance to kill me if I eat it. Uh, you know, it doesn't have that,
a toaster strudel. Just eat it. Well, why, why try to like hurt yourself to like eat like a rare
fish? I should probably move around. Fish eye lens. Oh, cool. All right, let's move.
Oh, the hole. Do not disturb. Please be nice.
That was the end of Yoshi, Nintendo 64. I will take the applause now. It's fucking up.
What's the chopsticks? Hit detection sucks. Whoa. Shut up. Oh, I can get the picture of the, uh,
I can picture the, the, the, I don't know, the, uh, the ink octopus thing. Ink, um,
octopus. Giant King. Oh, I love shit like the guys. Listen to me. Listen to me. Listen,
listen, listen to me. The room as a VR game. If you don't think that I'm going to play that
all fucking day, one of these days of room VR, I cannot wait. I can't fucking wait. All right.
How do I open it? It's a minfo. Oh wait, there's other keys here. All right. I got three keys.
The AC is on right now. It's blowing right on my head. Holy shit. This feels phenomenal.
Long John Silver really, uh, didn't spend very much time on that one.
This looks the way that a hundred gecks sounds. Oh, I want that. Oh wait, I have,
I can get memories. Watch this. Oh no, no, no. I want the backpack. Stay there. Stay there. Okay.
Hold on. How do I take, how do you take the picture? How do I make it do a timer?
Is it on? It kind of feels normal. I didn't get a memory for this. No, no, no, no, no. I wasn't
done down there. Oh no. He doesn't have a show. Wait, pirate. Oh, being fishermen. Stack them.
All right. I want to go. I'm wait. How long have I been in here for? I need to come out for a second.
Don't I? I need to take like a break. Don't I? I've been, I've been in there for an hour and 20
minutes. Holy shit. I haven't had a ton of fun. Wait, is it, how do I look? Do I have the lines?
Okay. I don't really have the lines. This is fucking fun. I forgot how fun this was. All right.
Let's do a hair check. This looks, this looks deliberately styled like this. It does not,
it looks better than before. TikTok hair. Oh, I think I lost my audio. Hold on. What is TikTok
hair supposed to mean? Hold on. E-boy. What the fuck is an E-boy? Ew. Wait, there's so much sweat
in here. Did the audio get dropped? How come I can't hear anything anymore? Can't hear anything.
We're in. Are we in? Good though. Yeah, we're good. All right. Let me put these back in and then
the headphones back in. Yeah, I wasn't getting audio when the headphones were in either.
Right. Oh, there we go. Mine is too gross. Wait, is it a joke if I have like a sweaty body?
Why? Do you think I just dumped water on myself and walked in here like, hey, look at, I'm so
gross. Isn't that a funny thing? Okay, here we go. Let's go. I'm ready to continue my vacation.
By the way, this, this one is way more fun than the first one. The first one was not even that
fun. This one's 10 times better. All right. I want to go back here. Why is that rude? That's
not rude. That's me being real. All right. What else could I, wait, what's this? I won. I got it.
Come on, I gotta get the one up. Come on. Come on, do it. Come on, I gotta get 10 likes.
There's nothing else for me to do down here. Okay, let's go. Let's do a new vacation.
I have a very new vacation. What was the other one? Somebody said, people said go to the forest.
Look, the puffer fish and me in VR. I think I probably actually could if I really wanted to.
I think I could probably do it. It would take me a minute. All right, new vacation.
All right, forest or I don't, I don't even know the forest or mountain.
The metrics are concerning. I came here to help, but I'm not seeing the upward trend. I was
expecting. I know it looks bad, but he has Funko pops. Well, if the metrics cross zero,
the Bureau of Simulation automatically shut down the vacation simulator. Oh,
we're still far away from zero. Which one? Human. I set up this board to help you visualize your
memory progress. This is going to help you optimize your vacation. All right, we're going
mountain. Welcome to snow. The only way you're going to reach peak performance is by collecting
more memories. Human. Remember, we don't need to be so focused on the goal. We can still have a
ton of fun getting there. Let me play. There is so much to do. I can't wait for you to see the
great idea. Oh, the overlook. Okay. Even more memories up there. Oh,
an even more space seat on jet blue. I already don't want to do this one.
I already don't want to do this. I know what it is. Yeah. You can shape this ice to your artistic
vision. The sculpture is already there. It's up to you to chip it out according to this blueprint.
All right. I actually, this one's cool. Right. The front row.
Right side is one. Let's start here. This is the right side. Okay. One front row has four. Four.
Right. Okay. Right side is one, two, three, four, one, two, three, four, one, two, three, four,
and then one, two. Okay. One, two, three, four. One, two, three, four. One, two, three, four. One,
two, three, four. Four. Your creativity shows no boundaries, human. It's a great start. There are
many more opportunities to show your skills. All right. Keep going. Right side. All right. Front.
Oh, no. Bye. Thank you. Puzzle maker. Insert photo. Oh, we get to make up.
Oh my god. This is perfect. Do the edges first.
Oh, oh my god. Puzzles. Right. Okay. Come on, man. How do I get them back? All right. We're
going to do the edges first. Oh, fuck. It's upside down. Um, I look at this. How do I restart it?
I hope you love putting all the right pieces together as much as I do. Let me do.
All right. Don't put it. We're going to start with face. Okay. That's good, right? Okay, man.
Relax. What? I'm actually pretty relaxed right now. Oh, because I said fucker. I'm not allowed
to swear. How does that look wrong? All right. That's like the chest hair. That's like a chest
kind of. Okay. Okay. What's the rest of the face? Relax. Relax. Where is it? There. Got it. Part of
the relax. We'll need a couple more pieces of the face. Nice. I'm getting there. Part of relax.
Part of face and relax. Switch it around, please. Are you puzzled, human? Good. If you want a new
puzzle, just put a picture in that machine. That's the other way. It's wrong. Stop doing that.
Know where it goes. Come on, dude. It's hard to see. Smooth brain. It's not smooth brain.
It's kind of blurry for me. You guys have the high definition view. I have the low definition
view. I got both eyes at low depth. You got one eye at high depth. Oh, cool. This looks fun.
This is my dream game. This is a bunch of random things that take like 20 seconds to do and then
you just move on to the next thing. Hatch item here. Pirate hat pattern. This is like electricity.
That was dumb. That one's not even fun. Oh, we got another funny food machine. Oh, my goodness.
This is the best. When it has a funny food machine, it's the best. Okay. What do I want to do?
Human, some bots have requests for very specific orders. I'm operating on a higher level than
simple input output, so I'm just not going to do that. If you want to help, the next order
is over on the board. Or don't. It's not your job. It doesn't tell me what it is. It won't be my job
either. Hey, what it is? It just says question mark. Apple mayonnaise pie. It's done.
It looks pretty good. Looks kind of accurate, actually. Let's test it.
Paper mache. Wait, that was the order book. That was the ingredients book. I think I...
Can I get another one? Children's game. Oh, dude, look at this. Oh, don't drop it. That's
in the beginning of that movie. Oh, with Orson Welles. Honey thermal paste. I don't... I'm going
to make an apple pie. I'm going to serve it to somebody, I guess. Not a tomato, right? Apple,
cream. Won't be needing that. Say cream and apple. Okay, got... Now, where's my tray?
Apple and cream. I'm just making every order at Starbucks. Yeah, I'll take like a spit of coffee
and then a bunch of like sugar, cream, milk, flavoring, caramel sauce and chocolate syrup
and raspberry sauce. Okay. What do I do with it? Do I have like a... I don't... I'm a hands-off
partner in this kitchen. You have hands. So by definition, you should deliver the bot's order.
Oh, he ordered it. Okay. Hey, I got your order. Who ordered the easy cheese in between... Whatever
it is. Oh, I'll get that for you, sir. It looks like you dropped it. Oh, let me... I'll fix that
for you right away. Don't worry. I'm working on it. Okay. Here it is. What are you doing in here?
It's pretty good. Whatever. I don't think we're going to be able to warm the console up by hands.
Have you ever found something like that? Ice is nice in winter. Ice is also nice in drinks.
Ice skis are not nice. Oh, yes. Snow is great. I love snow so very much. Oh, avalanche. These are
poems. Okay. Skiing. Skiing is so rad. Wooshing on the snow so fast. Wish I had feet, though.
Ice again. It's cold and it's wet. If only I had some salt. Oh, no. My book froze. What is poems?
Yeah. Eat. Oh, no. Hurry. Okay. Take it out. Take it out. Take it out. Take it out. I want it. One
second. One second. One second. Oh. Come here. Come on. Wasn't he a pie? You know, what do I do?
He needs water. He needs water. He needs water. Water. Water. Water. Water. Oh, God. I'll save
you. I need water. I need water. I need water right now. Everybody got water? He needs water.
Wait. Wait a minute. No, I don't have any mayonnaise. Wait a minute. He's drinking to it.
I got him. I got him. I got him. I got him. I lost my earbud. Don't worry, little guy. I got you.
Red. Wait. He liked it. He liked it. Oh, yeah. Okay. Wait, wait, wait. I brought it back to life.
Okay. Wait. Ice tea. He probably likes it. This is water, right? Okay. This is water. This counts as
water. I wonder if I can get bigger. What the hell is going on? Yeah, he's... Wait, he'll give me some
soy milk. Eat as much as you want. Are you good? I don't know where I am in the room. I don't know
where I am in the room. I don't know where I am in the room. I don't know where I am in the room.
Did he just kiss me? What? This is fucking stupid. Is he upside down? I don't even know
which way is upside down or not. Well, I was supposed to make a cake or something.
What do I do with him? He's just eating the... Okay. You'll be fine in there. Just eat.
You want cheese and shit too? You want meat? Oh. How do I make a fucking cake?
Oh, flour, eggs. Yeah, but I don't have a bowl. Wait, what am I supposed to make it in a mug?
I need a tray. One egg. Oh, it's a quiche. I actually don't have a tray though. Where's he?
For me? Thank you. Got it. Got it. Where's the other guy? Okay. You mountain bot with a guy
with the shades wants something from the... I've got to hand it to you, human. Actually, you've
got to hand it to bot. All right. Fucking squash. As in the order. Make it snappy. A, I don't know.
Broccoli, lemon juice, carrot, eggs. A little bit of cheese. A couple of eggs. YouTube video.
We're making a YouTuber video. This is what we call a YouTuber special, guys.
This is the YouTuber special. Think about your wacky fucking gross stuff. Wait, where is he?
Nice hot beverage for the mountain guy. Where's he up there? Hey, bottoms up. For me? I'll take it.
Come on. I can't. Oh, no. I'll get these off. Aquafizz. This machine will accept any official
snowflakes. I think I've seen some lying around in the mountain. Okay. Me and my friend are going to
do this. Fine. Put you in the backpack. Oh shit. He can go on the... Nice. All right. Cool.
Humble snow bot. Whatever. I don't care. What is this? Do not throw snow. What was that? What was
that? Oh. What are you doing? Doing a thing you're saying not to do. God damn it. Give it to me. I
want to do one cool thing. Fuck you, game. I fucking... Hey.
Here. You should probably take this memory too. That guy. Oh my God. Why can I hit this guy?
I went right through his body. Give me the fucking memory.
Or it's time for bed. It's not time for bed. What memories do I have? I still got to figure
out this thing. Wow. Congratulations. I'm too busy working on a soon to be award winning screenplay
to care. But there are more orders if that's your thing. Oh. How many is that?
I got to... I know what to do. I need a hot drink. I need a hot drink so I can put it on. Yeah. I
got it. Right? Okay. Hot drink. Thermal paste. Let's go. See how hot this is?
That was exhilarating. I am ready to vent for many minutes. Oh look. But I think it's going to be
worth your time. Yes. I haven't had a grip since anyone came by the hot tub and I couldn't motivate
myself to turn the heat back on. I've always been a social bot but I guess nobody wants to chat.
Thanks again for starting the heat back up. Bubbles? Sometimes you gotta get in and fix a problem,
you know? Get this out of here. I don't want this. The other day I found a bunch of dust and
fragments. I wasn't really sure what to do. But my buddy swears that a can of compressed air is the
way to go. I wasn't really sure what to do. What the fuck did I just happen? What happened? What
happened to this? So I just shook it in as deep as I could go and waved it around for a while.
I think it ended up blasting my processor fan with the air. But the straw definitely
knocked some dust out. Don't think that was a good idea. Electrocute this person. Stop it. Stop talking.
Yeah. Maybe not. Speaking of batteries. Why am I even in a hot tub? I could blow a circuit or
something. And I'm not exactly. I guess the tub has probably done a better job cleaning my vents
than the dust remover. Get in there! Nothing like a good soap to get all the gunky bits out.
Speaking of gunky bits. I saw efficiency bot hovering around here a while ago.
That broke some of the wrong way. Said something about bad metrics in my area. Not allowing you to
tell a human. I checked all my areas and I didn't find any metrics, good or bad. Do you know anything
about metrics, human? Did I get my memory from you? Very annoying. Yeah, me neither. I'm rarely asked
to measure anything besides when barista bot asked me to stay at least 10 feet away.
That's a pretty weird metric, given that a foot is an imperial unit and not a metric one. If they'd
ask me to stay three meters away, I think it would have been more concise. Not sure why they asked me
to stay away. It's not like I'm leaving this hot tub anytime soon. Like, um, oh yeah, cool. Catch you later, muleman.
Spit of coffee. How many memories do I have? Can I go to the overlook?
Let's go. Enough, right? You need to pay close attention to the sketches.
This photo isn't what I need. Carrot. Oh, he needs a carrot, a hat, and glasses.
No, don't eat it. Refresh. Give him like a big banana nose. He needs a hat too.
Okay, we're gonna give him like eyes. Here comes a penis joke.
Hey, do you think I'm gonna put the banana like where his dick is supposed to be?
Is that what you think I'm gonna do? Why else would you take the banana? Right? Okay, yeah, yeah,
do some detective work. Sure, sure, fine. Why else, why else would this guy take the banana?
Is there any other reason for that? I mean, very obviously it doesn't go there. So why would he
pick it? What does he think he's gonna do? You think you're gonna get like content by like putting
a banana dick on this guy? Let's find out. If you can't, you can't. Okay, let's go. Or content.
That's like, okay, anytime that you would go around your neighborhood and they would be
like a snowman, how many times did you guys go back like a couple hours later and the
nose was down there and the two eyes were down there too? How many times? Be honest with me.
Like it happened to every single time. What do you mean never? Are you serious? You've never
like seen somebody like move it? Did you ever do that? I didn't do it. 50s memories.
Oh, the only difference here is the snow is not wicked fucking dirty. You build a snowman like
this, there's dirt and mud and it kind of smells. It like stinks. And it's like, you don't even want
to touch it. You gotta wash your hands if you touch it. Yeah. And then, you know, like, okay,
you ever like take a piece of the snowman, it's like dirty, like head or like dirty gross, like
snow and you eat it and you just taste dirt. I know for a fact that a ton of you guys have done that
when you were a little kid. You didn't go like this when the snowman was built. You didn't go,
crunchy sand dirt, like dance sand and dirt. You know, you didn't think that was like funny
when you were a little kid. I don't believe any of you. I really don't. I don't believe a single
one of you. All right. So he needs a hat. You have mine. That's it. And glasses. Get a photo.
Perfect. Wait, his hands. Hey, hypers. And what was the other one? Just a selfie, right? Selfie
with what? With mittens on. Oh, mittens. He's a great thing about the mountains, human.
You can't get two minutes to get a selfie and then we can go to the overlook and Pokemon sound.
I heard a Pokemon sound. I can't. My voice is a little gone. Okay. Top of the morning to you,
human. This is the coolest you can get on vacation island. So settle in and get your chill on.
Jack, Jack, Jack, Jack, Jack, Jack, Jack, Jack, Jack, Jack. Why is everybody saying Jack?
Who's where? That was Jacksepticeye? What? What was it? Hey, human. Have you heard the legend of
abominable snow bot? It is said to be an elusive bot that roams these very mountains.
The few people who claim to have seen it say that it is very shy but has a special fondness for
music. I thought I saw it once. Jackson. Jackson's a good dude. What are you talking about? Wait, no,
no, no. Go back, back, back, back. I got it. That was a bad impression. Was it? That was, I just,
was it a bad impression? He's got so much energy. It was good. I thought it was all right.
I mean, there's only one Jacksepticeye. It can't be me.
Way to rock that classic winter look, human. Yeah, tell somebody to do an impression of me.
Fantastic start to proving my role as the unique sibling. I've got a unique voice. You can't do me.
Leave me the fuck alone. I don't want to talk to any of you.
I want to go to the overlook is what I want to do. Vacation bot tells me
gondolas were the human's most efficient way to climb mountains. Enjoy. Yay. Great job, human.
We're on our way to see the rest of the mountain. Get on this gondola and throw that switch.
VR games suck, lol. Oh, no, they don't. They're fucking fun.
Oh, I just leave. Welcome to the overlook, human.
We're really high up, but the sun is even higher. Just remember, it's about the journey.
What do I want? Okay, we've got vanilla, mint chocolate chip, chocolate, strawberry fruit,
orange cream, vanilla bean, rocky road. No. You know, I'm going to do three scoops.
How do I turn the stream off? How do I turn the stream off right now? Wow, there's a maximum.
There's a maximum. All right, let's go. What is that? Ronald McDonald's skis.
Oops, I just punched everybody in the face.
Avoid the obstacles.
Thousand points. One thousand.
But now I can. Get it? It was you. A score like that deserves a pack.
All right, let's go to the other. One more place to go to. And then this whole stream
has been vacation simulator. Why? I can't stop. You're addicted to this.
What about the memory? Ladder to the peak. What the fuck just happened? Current height?
Distance. First memory. I don't get it. Is this like Tetris?
Rock climbing. Oh, I thought it was like Tetris. It sounds like you had quite the climb.
It would have been much more efficient if we had just installed an elevator.
It's not really an accomplishment if you just skip to the end.
Anyway, no peak is complete until you fly your flag.
Oh, the flag. Go ahead and turn that tank
to raise up the flagpole. Is that testament to human achievement?
Up high. All right, what is it? What's our flag?
Hey there. Okay, we did it. Now what?
Now what? We did it. We climbed the highest peak on Vacation Island
and flew the flag to prove it. This is so much more exhilarating than a memory.
This doesn't make any sense. By all accounts, the human is doing great at vacation.
Why are the metrics getting worse? No, that can't be. This vacation is going so well.
Experiences are abstract, but metrics aren't.
The Bureau of Simulations could shut us down if the numbers drop low enough.
I'm going to spend a few cycles figuring out what's happening.
Is it going to turn into like a scary game? Well, I guess Efficiency Bot is busy crunching
the numbers. We'll wait here for them to come back so we can talk.
You can use that path to get back to Mountain Shop, human.
It's Aurora Borealis. We're going to achieve it at this time of day.
All right, we got Forest. This is lore here, but I'm on vacation. I don't care.
I don't want to be burdened with the lore when I'm trying to relax.
Painting? There's painting up there.
Next game, President Sleeper. Hold on, I like this.
We're just vacationing your way. We'll lead you to it.
I love the little mini games. They're so much fun.
Holy shit, this is cool. Look at that back. Oh, a photo. Oh, wow. Look at you. Why don't we?
Hey, that's fun. Wait, it's you want it to be. You want green at the top and the whole.
This is green. I'm going to say one, two, three. Oh, fuck. Wrong.
Oh, hello there, human. Would you like to discover the digital canvas with me?
I'd like you to paint me a little painting. That's what I'm doing.
Anything your heart desires.
I'm painting the thing that you want. Pink, orange. This is so relaxing.
Light blue. Painting is fucking stupid. Why would you want this? OK, then this blue,
right? Then yellow. Come on, get it. OK, now yellow. That's it. That's not what he wanted.
He wanted this is a happy color palette. Fantastic, human. I feel the energy of this
work. It truly represents narcolepsy. I could have just given him like a line across the
canvas. The bots on the board would love to commission you to make them a painting.
OK, sure. I know exactly what I'm going to paint. Let's see if I get it. See if I get it from
memory. Let's see if I get it from memory. I'm not going to look. Hey, that's one. There he is.
Backpack. OK, now, um, fireman. Hey, fireman. Let's do fireman.
Oh, his eyes are a little closer. No, it's not, right? All right. All right. Let's do one more.
OK, I'll try. I'll do the rat. I'll do the rat face. I'll do the mucker rat. Hey, what? Oh, shit.
What else? Oh, it's the ear. Right. I fucked a zero. Here, you can have that one. It looks
like you could enrich the lives of some other bots with your art. Why don't you give this one
to one of the bots on this board? Oh, wait, I could do that. I'll do a gerbil heart too.
It goes off screen. OK, and then let's go. I got a photo for you. Hey, have a fireman.
That's going to be worth some money some day. Thank you, human. Now I can finally teach my bots.
Denial. I bet that bot Moss has more for you to do. Be sure to say hi for me.
Oh, what's going on in this tent? OK, we got smores. Hey, hey, let me directly address you.
Where am I? Of course, this is going to be sick. Hey, and you do, where's the, how do you turn this
on? Wow, a real campfire. Look at that. Let me know when you're ready for a spooky story. No, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, this is wrong.
This is wrong. That's all right. This is how you make a smore, guys. Don't tell anyone. This is the
actually correct way to do this. If you do it another way, it's wrong.
Chocolate, double chocolate. Very important. Get the other graham cracker ready. Have your
thing with the marshmallow on it. Roast the marshmallow. Don't put, don't do anything with
this. Slowly. OK, there you go. Grab this shit. Squeeze it right there. Pull it back. Squish,
squish, squish, squish. The chocolate's going to be still solid, but it'll be melty and tender.
It's not going to ooze all over you. You're going to go, much better.
This scared me and made me drop this shit. A long time ago in a simulated forest, just like this one,
a bot family set up camp. Well, Kidbot heard a scraping noise coming from outside the campground.
The family went to investigate. What are these, what are these, like, textureless sausages?
As parent bot looked closer, it suddenly latched onto this screen, and you, excuse me, Maria.
Audio processor. It's so dry. A human. Would you mind giving me a nice hot cup of liquid?
I'm like, I'm like 10 years old. I'm older than you, and I shouldn't be acting that way.
100%. What I want. Oh, we can make tea. My niece does this. Every little kid has a little fake kid
guitar, and they just stand there and go, no, no, no, no. That's what I'm doing. This is my niece.
It's prop island. I did it. I filled them all up. We got honey. Hot sauce. Hope it's Tabasco.
Cool. Oh, cool. This is props. Oh, look at these props. Hey, human. Camping sucks.
My super dorky family is full, so he's made food for everything. I eat it raw. But what if you did
it and I took all the credit, eh? It would just be like a group project. Game of Thrones actress?
Camping sucks. Poodle? Wait. Prank? Why is that pranks? Cucumber coolant?
Food rehydrator. What are these? Oh, they're just little LEDs. Okay. What the fuck?
This is Play-Doh. All right, here you go. Let's be your kid. Hey, you want this? I made you a
Prado. I don't like it. I don't want to do anymore camera stuff. Garden. I can garden.
Maybe you should put something on my patented shrubifier. Then you can make some simple
topiary. Your garden is really starting to blossom. But any fact, you can plant anything
in the ground and watch it grow. I know because I tried. You could make it a shrub though.
I'm just having fun. I don't even know what's happening. All right, don't grow too much.
Your garden looks wonderful, human. Did I get a memory? It's gaming with carbon-based life
forms. Oh, you know, so you can shrink it. Use a memory of your horticultural demonstration.
Okay, so now what? Feel free to swing by and enter your garden anytime.
It's fertile ground. Look at that guy. Oh, wait, is this a horn?
Okay, cool. One more place to go. And then I'm going to play a different game,
like fishing, fishing, fucking finally. Hey, remember the banana for the day? Remember that?
I think the fish change color. Oh, we need green. Fish change color when you give them food.
Oh, I think they eat each other. That looks about right. Oh, here's some ancient fishing advice.
Hey, you just stole that out of my hand. It's like a seagull.
Ready? All right. Hey, this almost works, but it's not the right color.
Wow, that's yellow. Yellow trout. Oh, coin. I'll take that one. Ah, we've got you now, dick.
I need that banana back. Give me that banana. Blue salmon.
Am I eating this? All right, I'm going to catch a salmon.
To catch the right type of fish before we can give you credit.
A fish of all typecasts. So you have to find the right type of fish before we can give you credit.
Herder riding? What? Come here, you little fuck. Catfish. Salmon.
There's no better feeling in the world than finding what you're looking for yourself quietly.
Wow. There may be plenty of fish in the river, but I'm going to permanently
commit these to my memory storage. Thank you. That was fun. Is there anything else to do here?
I'm going to get all the memories. I'm over it. Oh, wait. Arm for coins. I think I did everything.
Wait. Welcome to the welcome center. Well, come on in. This is too big.
And this machine will accept any official wood chips.
I really want. I think I've seen some lying around in the forest.
In the fart one, right? How do you blow it up?
Please, you grabbed my acorn bar and slingshot. Just pull back the string to fling.
Give me a wave.
Most fun thing of the whole game. You waited to the very end. Show it to me.
This is so much fun. You beat Bart Simpson.
You take this currency. All right. New game.
I'm going to go piss, though, and I'm going to get some water.
We'll play another one. This was fucking fun. I really like this.
That back up on. But finally, he's all right. Let's move on.
I'll be right back. Just going to get something to drink and go pee.
OK, we're going to do next. I have a shitload of games. Half Life Alex.
No, we're doing that tomorrow. I've only probably got another hour or so in me in VR.
Let's see. What can we do? Half Life Alex is tomorrow.
I really want to start Half Life Alex and just do that.
OK, close this. OK, we got. I'm going to throw out some things here.
Let's see. I got Tap House VR. The room is going to be so much fun.
I got a bunch of scary shit, too. Bone Works 2. That'll be probably soon.
Pistol Whip. Oh, I want to try Pistol Whip.
I was told this game is really crazy. All right. Pistol Whip it is.
Let's get it open. Is this putting a command prompt?
Scary game? Yeah, I'll do. We'll do a whole night of scary shit on VR.
Ratatouille VR. That was a lot of fun, though. That was just chilling.
I played that for three hours. I can't fucking believe that.
When's Chubby Bunny? I don't know. I have to go get marshmallows.
So Pistol Whip, from my understanding, is a game where you have to VR shoot enemies to the beat.
I think it's pretty flashy, too. So I think I'm going to give a warning here.
It's probably an epileptic warning at the beginning of this game.
This is not a porn game. I've played it. It's a totally... It's an epileptic warning.
All right. Well, let's be real. It's probably going to be really...
Especially in VR, too. But I heard it was really fun.
I got a lot of recommendations from VR Josh. So he's given me some pretty good ones.
So many VR games have come out over the last year and a half since I last played.
All right. Why is it taking so long? Performing first time setup with a command prompt open.
Like, why do I... What is this?
I've never played a Steam game that had a blank command prompt three times in a row.
We good? All right. Here we go.
Hopefully, this is not loud. I'm going to turn it down.
Pistol Whip.
You hear it? Okay. All right. I think we're good. I think I'm ready.
Let's move this back over. Hello? Hi there. I'm going to go back in.
You might be able to turn down the flashiness in the settings. Really?
He's going in. Not yet. I'm going in in about 15 seconds.
Start. Training. I probably should do the training, right?
Keyboard mode. Dude's actually handsome.
All right. This is a good... I think this is a good spot to start.
And like here. Like right here. This is pretty good.
Although I always like drift over to be out of frame like half the time. So...
Uh, all right. Get the right headphone, please.
New modifiers. Vengeance and disorder.
Oh, shit. He are Ratatouille waiting room.
No, I didn't mean to shoot. All right. Now I got a real red dot.
Who's going to say Ratatouille waiting room? I can't get him.
All right. How do we do it? Training. Put on your straps.
Oh, shit. Shoot enemy. Dodge bullets.
Aim down to reload. Losing armor.
Powered. Shoot enemies. Repair armor.
Dodge. Duck. Dodge. Punch.
All right. I got to put this on. This game's sick.
Holy shit. This is a ton of fun. This is awesome.
I can't wait to play this. Modifiers. Player options. Game options.
Scenes. Let's go right into one.
Oh, I get the big one. I think this is the kind of gun that I would use.
Like the James Bond movie. You just go... Oh my God.
No, not the Deagle. The Deagle's the meme gun.
It's really loud. Where are you?
It's not really loud. I can see it.
All right. I'm taking the little baby gun. Customize.
Dude, what? Minecraft. Minecraft Creeper gun.
Oh, this is the sound. Ooh.
What do you think? I think I like five and four.
Five. Three's pretty good, too. I like five.
Minecraft. Gone. Founder's collection.
Ooh. Oh. Oh, this is John Wick.
All right. I'm going with this. I didn't go Ember's Another Day.
How about just the first one? How about Death?
Oh. The dragon. Oh, I love it.
Oh, shit. I lost hearing.
I'm losing my hearing. I can't. I can't.
I'm only hearing one ear. Oh my God.
He's reload Randy. He reloaded Randy.
Holy shit. My underwear. Oh, there's a song.
Bang, bang, bang, bang, bang. Oh.
I think I'm back against the reddit shelf.
Where should I move? Where should I move?
Come on. I need this other hearing.
Fucking stupid ass thing, man. Look at this shit.
I'm going to put these in until they hurt.
Come on. Get in there and fucking stay in there.
Ugh. Dude, I can't even fucking aim.
If I go for this way, I'm going to smash the bottom.
If I go this way, it's a fucking reddit shelf.
Come on. Bang, bang, bang, bang.
I can't hear anything.
Oh, I hit my head on the ceiling.
Oh, God. Come on.
Better this time. Better this time.
Come on, Wick. Okay. All right.
How much health do I have? How much health do I have?
All right. Yes.
He's going to need what? I got the baby.
I got a B. I got a B.
He's going to need another two months off.
All right. Let's do the gun. Bolden gun.
Let's try. God fucking dammit. I feel like a warehouse.
All right. Let's go.
All right. How about revelations?
Let's go.
Tuber music. My hands are so sweaty.
The speed is fast.
What songs are?
I'm like doing a K-pop song. Dance.
That's not how you should come out of VR.
That's not the best way to get removes from VR.
Somebody just pulled my scalp off.
I feel like I was just in a Scooby Doo movie
and they just revealed me as the villain.
I think we're okay.
Like I was doing like a K-pop dance
and I like lost my wig on stage.
It's not broken. It's fine.
It's fine.
That's because I stepped on the cord.
It pulled back.
Did you at least get to see it?
Did you get to see the thing fly off?
I hope so.
It doesn't help.
My head is... Look at how sweaty I am.
This is the sweatiest I've ever been in my life.
Of course it's going to be greased up and be able to fly off.
This game is a lot of fun too.
Shit. Watch the clip.
I'm like doing a K-pop song. Dance.
Dude, it looks like it wasn't even on.
It looks like it was just barely on my fucking face.
It was attached tight as hell.
Okay, I'm going to get back into the game.
Show the clip.
Hold on.
Let me see if I can get it on screen.
No, we'll do it later.
I'm almost like...
I can't fucking believe this is happening.
Do normal?
Pressing the eject button in VR.
Okay, that's like...
Press that button.
Mom's home.
You haven't finished your homework yet and you're in VR
and you got to fucking open up like a word pad real quick
and write a bunch of bullshit.
Alright, let's get back in.
I was doing really well there too.
I was doing really good.
There's no way.
Oh, look.
I died.
Destroying VR headset to farm plus twos.
Click the link, please.
Omega lul.
Okay, hold on.
How do I have hair in my mouth?
Okay, this is fucking funny.
This looks like if you woke somebody up out of a deep sleep
instantly, they were sleeping and you just shook them hard
and said, dude, wake the fuck up.
Look at the hair being pulled back too.
Like a sleepwalker.
Oh my god, the sleepwalker.
He's like holding a gun in his dream.
What the fuck is going on over there?
Alright, speaking of...
I got to like increase the brightness on this fucking thing.
This looks like shit.
Why am I like in a shadow?
Oh, there we go.
No, I'm not.
I still need to brighten it up.
Dying.
Okay, there we go.
Okay, let's try this again.
You fell asleep with your bike helmet on?
Stay away from the Reddit collection.
Yeah, that was a lot going on in that last fucking 20 minutes.
Funko alert?
What's wrong?
There's a gif now?
It's alright.
Alright, I got to be ready for this
because this is going to rip the fuck out.
No more like K-pop dancing.
That would be nice.
Check the gif.
Show gif, show gif, show gif.
This thing, this strap doesn't work, man.
I'm telling you.
Let's see the whole thing.
Well, hopefully there's nothing actually wrong with this
because that fell from like six feet high.
It's wet in here.
Hey, everyone was like, dude, just get an index.
The index is way better.
Well, I don't need to do that now.
Alright, I'm back.
This game is so much fun.
I'm going to relax.
I'm getting just too into it.
What the fuck did I just do?
No, get this off.
What button did I press?
How do I turn this off?
I'm going to lose all my hair in the front of my fucking head.
I know it.
I'm going to lose all my fucking hair.
Inevitable.
Okay, return to game.
Okay, you guys can hear it, right?
I didn't like unplug any cords.
Get this behind us.
I say us, I mean me.
Okay, you still there?
Still there?
You are.
Alright.
Am I in a good spot?
I'm not going to move.
I'm going to do it like Doom.
Go.
Yeah, you fucking asshole.
That was loud.
I just screamed.
I need a different gun.
I don't want this song.
I don't like this song.
Boom.
Kick.
Yes, fucking dead man.
Two gun mode?
What?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Oh shit.
Make sure you play this to father gas going.
Win?
Yo.
Uh, yo.
The 99% on beat accuracy.
Can I do two?
A laser gun?
Super soaker?
Merry Christmas?
I'll do a Merry Christmas gun.
Kind of like a candy cane.
What else we got?
Aptics.
Turn on dual weld?
Dual weld?
How do I do that?
I'm wearing like a club right now.
I have things in my ears.
Modifiers.
Wait, how do I get there?
Welders?
No fail dead eye.
Scavenger?
Oh shit.
Oh man.
Hey, hat's on, right?
I'm going to get these little ones.
Run on spot welding?
I don't know what that means.
All right, let's go.
On hard.
This is fucking hard, boy.
Bang.
No.
Oh, that's hard.
Holy shit.
We're going back to normal, boys and girls.
Let's go.
Oh shit.
Sloppy.
The house is on fire at The Sims.
Oh my god.
I feel something behind me.
Eh.
I'm doing over 4550 for the best person in the fuck.
I'm tired.
All right, I'm going to do one more.
Damn.
Okay, that's good.
Holy shit.
Big bits?
250 fucking dollars.
Who gave 250 bucks?
Listen, I like this one's easy, right?
What's the beat?
This way.
Fuck you.
All right, I'm going to do it sitting down.
Not even stand up and reload.
Hold on.
Have I been doing VR in like tiny bri-ball brain mode?
Average is 64.
Oh, then I'm good.
Yeah, I had it on 64.
Yeah, I'm good.
And use your phone to measure it.
I think I'm done.
I don't think I can do anymore.
Has it been like four hours?
I really wanted to get to four.
I really want to get to four hours.
He's weak.
Yeah.
Yeah, I am.
Yeah, I'm going to call it.
I'm going back tomorrow.
We're going to do Half-Life Alex tomorrow.
I feel like there's not going to be a whole lot of
diving around like a psychopath
and dancing to music for an hour straight.
That was a ton of fun though.
I forgot how much fun this fucking really was.
Oh dear goodness.
I need to tell you.
I'm going to hop in the shower as soon as this is over.
It looks like I already did take a shower.
It looks like I just got out of the shower.
Doesn't it?
Looks like I just got out.
Holy shit.
Yeah, I know, man.
I know, man.
Seriously.
You jelled?
I'm wet.
Yeah, I'm actually physically wet.
All right.
I do want to say Foxymuffin gave $250 fucking dollars.
That's insane.
Longtime fan decided to actually support you.
Keep it up.
That's 25,000 bits.
That's too much money.
I'll take it though.
I mean, that's unnecessary, but I'll take it.
That's a lot of money.
Thank you for the $250.
Holy shit.
Goiki gave $50.
Draw my fursona in VR when I play Tilt Brush.
Remind me, I will.
Thanks for the 50 bucks.
Freddy Dredd gave 50 community subs and Lovely...
What if I just went boom and passed out?
Lovely and Jubbly gave $50 too.
My heart is broken.
No far cry.
Probably not.
That game is fucking hard and broken and annoying.
It was fun in 2004.
Maybe.
He lied.
Yeah, I know.
That's what I do.
All right, guys.
I will see you later.
We're going to run the credits.
And I'm going to just get up and fucking go in the shower.
I'm dying.
Here come all the subs from today.
Thank you, everybody.
Really appreciate it.
This channel has tons and tons of subs.
You guys continue to support this channel with tons of money.
Hopefully, I spent it well.
I'll try to.
Thanks a lot, though.
Seriously.
VR is a ton of fun.
You'll see Half-Life Alex will be tomorrow.
I just kind of wanted to get used to VR again
before I jumped right into the best VR game that's ever been made.
So tomorrow should be pretty solid.
Thanks again, everybody.
Same time tomorrow?
Yeah, we'll probably start around 2 p.m. tomorrow.
Pacific.
I was going to start around 1,
but I had to go do an errand.
I had to run out of the house.
Make sure your PC can actually run Half-Life Alex.
Wait, what?
What do you mean?
Add good graphics.
Wait, is it really taxing on the computer?
Will a 1080 work?
That should be fine.
1080 is fine.
Okay.
Yes, idiot.
It's in VR.
Why did you call me an idiot?
I'm not the one that said it wasn't going to work.
Why am I the idiot?
I was just reacting to what they said.
I use 1080 at max graphics,
but streaming also bogs up the system.
Well, I just won't run it.
I won't do max graphics.
Thanks, everybody.
I am going to run away right now and just go into the shower.
I'll see you guys tomorrow.
Probably same time for Half-Life Alex,
unless it can't run on my computer.
Take care of yourselves, guys.
Have a great rest of your day or night, depending on where you are.
I'll see you tomorrow.