Hey, I thought you were retiring. Not right now. Late. Hey! He's gonna delay his retirement.
What are you, what are you, why are you saying that? What's going on? Yeah, I am very early.
I'm so early, in fact, that I am almost a full day early. I'm one day early. We've got some good news
for all of you, uh, audio Andes that hate everything about my mic setup and my audio setup.
Good news for you. My entire audio setup is changing as of after this stream. I'm gonna have
hopefully a really, really crystal clean sound as of next stream. Maybe. Depends on when I want to
get some of this stuff. I mean, speaking of mics, hold on. I said you already have a Newman. What
could you improve? Um, I like, okay, I like the go XLR, but I don't, I don't know, I don't like
the way that it makes my mic sound. I've tried so many settings with this thing. The product is,
it's an all encompassing product, right? You plug in an XLR mic, you have complete control,
you can do funny sound effects, you can do voice changing. It's very easy to use software. But every
time I change a setting on it, I feel like it makes it sound worse. I'm going to try a few things.
I'm going to try this mic with a new compressor, see how that sounds. I'm going to try maybe a
different mic setup, a different way, a different positioning of the mic, a different boom arm.
I'm going to try a few things, but how are you going to do funny voice effects? I don't worry.
I might still use the go XLR. I might actually still plug it in and use it.
Please address this title. It sucks. Just being a bug. I'm just being a bug. I'm early being a bug.
Spiders aren't bugs, you nerd. Yes, they are. A spider is a bug. It's a bug. What do you want to
say? It's a, it's not a bug. A spider is a bug. Yes, it is. I'm a bug is a bug. I know it's a
crustacean. It's a, it's a crab was a small crab with extra legs. Whatever. It's a bug. It's the
thing that crawls on your wall and it bites you and it has got poison in it and it will poison
you if it fucking touches you. Some of them. Spiders are bugs, but they're not insects. Yeah,
thank you. Appreciate that. Hurry up and play this stupid game. I can only watch for 15 minutes.
Dude, the game is only four hours long and you should know this by now. The first 15 minutes
of every one of my streams are awful. It's me explaining to you a dream I had or how much
Dunkin Donuts went downhill or how I forgot to drink water and I'll be right back again.
Now for the first, the first 15 minutes is a warm up, man. Let's be like that every time.
You said Thursday. I know. Yeah, I'm full of surprises. I did say Thursday, although the
reason why I'm here now and starting very late is because I have to take Otto to the vet. He's um,
some things I want to get checked out. He's okay. I think he's fine. Is he okay? I think he's going
to be 100% fine. He just might. He's having the same kind of, I don't know, he's, he's peeing a
lot. I think he's been prone to getting UTIs. He's had it a couple times. He's had a UTI a couple
times over the last five to 10 years. I feel like this is starting a new one. So I'm just going to
go get it checked out, see if he's okay. He actually had blood work done a couple months ago,
less than a month, like a month ago and it was fine. He was, it was all normal.
So I wonder if this is something just brand new, but we'll see. He's fine. He's happy. He's just,
it needs to be addressed, needs to be looked into. So I decided, you know what,
if I'm going to take him probably tomorrow, then I going to stream today. So I'm going to be taking
him to the vet tomorrow. You're a good dog, dad. I, he's, he's like the best. Everybody, everybody's
a good dog, dad. Okay. There are personal, there are like personal best friends. That's how I see
Otto. Otto's just like a, he's just, he's just best friend. It's just that, there you go. There's
my, there's what he is. True. Yeah. Everybody's dog is their best friend. And I don't believe
anybody that says otherwise. Does it in the goddamn title. But you can have human best friends and
dog best friends. Otto is my BFF. But yeah, I, there's two things for you to know. Next stream,
I'm going to sound completely different. I am going to be doing some audio testing for the next
few streams. We'll find a good place where I sound good. I might even use the same setup. I'm just
going to change a bunch of settings, but I'm getting some new equipment. Jeremy, you're
fucked in the head. Not going to lie. That talked about my dog being my like BFF.
I don't think anything I said was too outrageous right there. I feel like everything I just said
was very, very plain, normal, and, and very expected. That wasn't too crazy, right? I don't
think so. All right. So here's what we're doing. I was going to play house flipper pets DLC, which
I mean, we're talking about dogs, you know, cats and gerbils and rabbits and bugs. If you have them
but that's not what we're doing today because I'm starting so late. This is an impromptu early
reverse delay stream. We're going to play webbed, which we were just talking about bugs. So webbed
is a game where you play as a spider and spider around. And that's what we're going to do. So
nothing tomorrow. As I take auto to the vet for the impromptu schedule change, but here we are,
we're just going to spider around. So the plan, the game plan is there is as follows. Are you
listening? Listen up. This is a listen up engine house flipper pets. DLC is going to be Saturday
and Sunday because during that same period we're going to play wad blood wash and murder house.
So this weekend we're going to do pets, DLC, murder house and blood wash. I'm not sure which
day they could flip back and forth. It's the plan going forward here. Oh brother, this guy stinks.
What was that? If you had a movie made about you, who would play you?
Me. Is that really a question? Me. I would play me. But did you mean, because I'm 36,
what, what time period does this movie take place? When I'm older, when I'm still young,
younger, what, what is this movie about? Cause everyone's saying, oh, what it would be Willem
Defoe. But Willem Defoe is a lot older than me. Five years from now in the future. Um,
can it be Steve Buscemi? I can see it. I am still young. I'm young. I'm still, I'm still young.
I mean, when I turned, I think when I turned 38 is when I'm just going to be able to say, I can't,
I'm not young anymore. Although I did fall out of the 18 to 34 bracket, drop down bracket for how
old you are. That's true. Old is 46. I think old is 40. Old is definitely 40. It's 40. You can't
say you're, I'm young. Oh yeah. I'm just a young guy when you're 40. That doesn't, no, you're 40.
I think 30. Uh, I think 40 is the new 30 though. People are living a lot longer. So I look, I mean,
people are living to be like in their nineties. Aren't you 46? I'm 36. Aren't you 40? Um, no,
I'm, I'm almost 40 is midlife crisis, midlife. No, it's not. Is it? Yeah, it is. But okay. But
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. You guys can't tell me that I, if I, when I turned 40,
you guys can't tell me I'm having a midlife crisis. If I act like a weirdo or if I do something
strange, I've been having, I've been doing that old kind of strange shit since I was
working in my twenties. Right. But you guys can't say, Oh dude, look at him. He's being so weird.
He's having a, he's having a midlife crisis. I did that stuff like 10 years ago too. Right.
I'm just, that's just who I am at this point. But don't say that. We make me feel incredibly
poorly. 36 plus 36 is 72. Yeah. And people are living to be a hundred. People are living
to be a hundred. 50 is midlife crisis. All right. You guys ready to play? Let's, let's play. This
is webbed. The game is called webbed. It looks great. It looks pretty cute. Is this a controller
game or should I play with my hands? Is this a hands game or is it, well, you don't have any
mouse. Should I play with my hand or should I use my thumbs? That's what I'm trying to say.
Hands or thumbs? I think this is a hands game because you have to aim. That's a kind of scary
sound. It reminds me of, okay, you know when a hummingbird flies next to your head and you
feel like it's a gigantic, huge, scary insect and you go, Oh, you freak out, you scream and you've
run and you kind of move your hands around. And then afterwards you realize that you were blessed
by a hummingbird and you go, Oh no, come back. I'll stand still. Like, no, it's already gone, man.
You fucked it up. This is what you want. Want this? That doesn't happen. This does. Base cam Andy.
I want you to crank your compressor up as high as it will go and do one radio host joke next stream,
please. Maybe. You've changed. Yeah. I'm sure I have. You guys have, you guys have seen me go from
a guy in his early to mid twenties to a guy in his mid to late thirties. Of course, you've seen it
in real time. Some of you guys that have been here for 10 years, 12 years, you of course have
to change probably. Hopefully for the better. I hope for the better. I've changed physically.
I've changed probably a little bit mentally. What are you talking about? 12 years have gone by.
You're a young man. You've changed. You look chiseled. No, I don't. No, I really don't actually
today. I'm not even any. No, I do not. Chiseled. Are you guys? No, I don't. I'm looking at it.
I'm looking at it right now. I'm looking at the screen over here. No, I don't. I look kind of,
I look like clay. Can you chisel clay? I don't think so. Yeah, you can after you cook it.
That's not a zit. What is that? What is that? It's like a clump of hairs. What is this? What
is that? Did I not shave there somehow last time? What is that? I have no idea what that is.
Do you know what I'm talking about? You have dents. Yeah, I do have a couple. Yeah, I do have a
couple of head dents. I do have dents in my head. Whatever. When you get to be 30, you don't give
shit about a head dents. Who cares? I don't care about a head dent. I'm too old. I, guys, I used
to 10 years ago, I'd be in the mirror and I'd, every, every, I would sit there for 10 straight
minutes and just be like, I don't, I don't fucking care anymore. Like I care, I care enough. I care
enough to, I don't want to look like shit every day, right? But I mean, I'm not sitting in the
mirror parting individual strands of hair. I mean, this is just what I look like. And then for 40,
I look pretty damn good for 40. I'm sorry. You have to give yourself a little bit of credit
sometimes. I look pretty fucking good for 40. I think I've been drinking a lot of green tea.
I've been drinking a lot of, excuse me, water. No tea today because I ran out. I drink it so much
that there's no more. I didn't get any more. Play the game. I'm just, it's been 10 minutes, man.
Stalling. I'm, yeah, I'm just, I'm just hanging out. You guys can chill. Just chill for a second.
How did you run out of tea? Because I drink, I drink so much of it. I've been drinking,
I've been trying a bunch of things. Got a few that I really like. I have these like green tea,
like energy packets. I've got green tea powder. I've got, dude, I'm going to have green tea
souvenir merchandise and shit eventually. And then I take care of my skin too. Moisturize.
Developers like to acknowledge the Shigera, Turbul, and Gooby Gooby peoples as the traditional
owners of the lands on which webs is based on. Holy shit. What the hell is that? That feels kind
of good to do that. Hold Q to dance. Okay. Space is jump. Hold that to grapple to a point. Oh shit.
Okay. That's kind of fun. Can I descend down? Okay. Let's keep going. Aim at a point and hold
right click to go to, to start spinning a web. Now aim at a second point and release to build a bridge.
Wait, what? Whoa. Okay. Oh, you can connect them. Spin. I can spin a web. All right. Why are you,
why is Jared Leto playing web? I don't look anything like Jared Leto, like at all.
It's zero. It is zero resemblance. Zero. If you put both of our faces in a scanning machine,
we would have a like fucking 12% compatibility. Okay. That's cool. I don't know what you're
talking about. What happened? Okay. So we got to go like this. Oh, this is mud. Can I not grab mud
from here to here? Is this like Jump King? Am I going to get mad at this game? I'm probably,
I'm going to be pissed this game, right? Is this game that's going to piss me off?
12%. Holy shit. Shoot lasers? Okay. That's weird. Oh no. Why do I have lasers? What? Okay. Well,
that's kind of cool. I've Hey buddy. I'm so sorry. I saw it happen to your boyfriend.
That big mean bird has been menacing the land below its sky. Bower for years. It devoured
many of my siblings, but I think it has something else in mind for your bow. The bird loves to
collect blue gems, you see. And that love of yours is the shiniest blue I've ever seen.
Come by my old nest little buddy. I might have an idea. Okay. So this big ball of silk may not look
like much, but it was my home for a time. The ants below have approached me with reckless plans to
turn it into a heated airship. It's part of the defense effort. I've not let them try it so far,
but perhaps a little recklessness is what we need right now. Anybody else love ants because of the
Honey I Shrunk the Kids movie? People are like, oh, ants. Gross. Actually, I like ants.
In Honey I Shrunk the Kids, an ant saves all the kids. It defends them against a giant scorpion.
It's anti. They're good friends and it protects them. And I remember watching that and going,
ants are good. I like ants. They're good friends. I like ants because of that. Okay.
They'll need some fuel too, of course. I've looked to the dung beetles on the hill for that.
And naturally a guide is important for any adventure. Perhaps a bee. Nobody knows these
skies better than them. All right. Yes. This is a good plan. Go on little buddy. There's no time
to waste. Get out there, make some friends and save your love. Movement's clean. Is that fall
damage? What's that? Can I grab that? What is it? I found, I got a little spider friend.
All right. Okay. I gotta go get to the, go to the ants. Oh, what happens if I get more? How many
of these should I get? Oh shit. Is there fall damage? All right. Okay. It reminds me of worms.
The ninja rope. Who's that? Oh, I'm giving up my, oh, these are babies. You don't weigh enough for
fall damage. New Spider-Man game looks pretty good. There's no fall damage. Okay. Thank you so
much. These little ones have ballooned off when that big bird flew by, but they're far too young
to be off on their own. If you find the others, please bring them back to me. I like birds.
I like crows. With 40, I could bring all 40. I like crows. You know that, did you guys know
that crows are the most intelligent fucking animal? Did you guys know that? Okay. I need to
find an ant. Can't get up there. Is this like a metroidvania? Do I have to go get like boots
or something? I really do like the movement a lot though. It's fun. Where are these ants? Who asked,
nerd? Fuck. Who is that? Okay. There was a, okay. I gotta get over there. There's a fly over there.
I heckin' love small spiders. Stop. Whatever. Okay. I gotta get up here. So that fly is over
there. Can I like, like this? Oh shit. Okay. Oh. Ah, all right. That's how you, that's what I'm
supposed to do. No! What are you doing? Fuck. Okay. Get back up here. So if I go from here,
you should be right here. Oh, I got it. There we go. All right. What do you, what do you want?
Guild Predator, I am the Fly Lord. Your fangs are too small to devour me. If my kin don't sit well
in your stomach, come pay me a visit. Let's see what we can do about that. You haven't eaten even
a single fly? Perhaps I judged you too harshly. Get on your way, spider, and stay away from temptation.
Platformer Andy? What's up here? Oh. This is back where I was. This is where the,
all right. Get back over here. Tab for map? What the fuck? Okay. I'm in, I'm at the,
okay. I gotta go down there to go to the ant world. How do I get, how do I go there?
Where is it? Jumping spiders. I hecking love jumping spiders. Oh, here we go. All right. I got
it. Ant kingdom. Greetings, comrade spider. I hear you've got some problems that could use an ant
solution. We'd love to help out, but we're still recovering from the latest fire ant raid. The
workers could really use some extra help down there if you've got time. All right. Speak with comrade
Carl in the mech ant chamber. Be able to give you some work. Okay. Turn that on. What's this?
Can I dig? Hey, can spiders dig? Okay. What's the job? Help with the elevator. It's been broken
down since the attack, but I can't reach the part we need to fix it. If you can get me the brass
cog from the other side of this chamber, we should be able to get it running. Without that elevator,
we're stuck up here. All right. Fix the elevator. Fucking easy. All right. This is where you start
to die. Easy. Okay. I didn't know you could die in the game. What was that? Grubs? Oh,
I was supposed to do a huge cog. Hold on. Cog is right there. Oh, I actually have to drag it across.
Oh, that sucks. All right. Hold on. Should I go down the secret? All right. Stay down there for a
minute. Should I go do the secret? What if I get stuck down here? Oh, it's just a grub. Okay. Cool.
I like this game. It's pretty cool. So far. So far. Hold on. Relax. So far. Can I go in the acid?
Yeah, I just can't. Oh, shit. Hold on. There you go. Thanks. I'll deliver the cog back to the main
shaft. Just pop it into the gearbox and we should be good. Do I have to do that? What? Do I have to
do anything? I demand to know what your favorite soup is. Ah, fucking cream of broccoli or something,
man. Like everybody else. Hold on. Did you go like this? Fuck you. There you go. He's going
to rage. I'm probably won't. This game's too cute to be mad at. It's way too cute. Although I say
that now, something's going to happen. All right. So who do I give those to? This is a cute game.
What are you doing? I'm playing. I don't know what I was going to say. Up. I'm playing up.
Like the movie up. I've never seen up. I just know that there's an old guy and there's a dog
and there are balloons. I don't know anything about this movie. I've never seen it. But, you know,
I feel like I've seen the movie though, right? The problem with really popular movies that you
haven't seen is it's almost like you feel like you've seen the entire movie because everybody's
talked about every scene. So I feel like I've seen it already. I go down here. Watch it now.
You would like it. I know I would. I just, I feel like I've already seen it. What is this for? Hold
on. You should be arrested because you haven't seen it. I don't think seeing, not seeing up is
as outrageous as not seeing Star Wars or something or Lord of the Rings. I know I've never seen the
Lord of the Rings, but wait, is this a shortcut? That is. What else? Why is there a shortcut?
You're going to cry. You should watch it with Holly. You're going to cry.
Comrade Mark, recruit you from the surface. Fantastic. There's tons of work to do. Finish
the mech ant. Let's see. The mandibles need a final heat treatment up in the forage room.
About to turn that back on. We need to patch up the pipe works. Okay. We'll need that to supply
the mech ant. Oh, and it still needs three more legs to be attached. Oh God. I think we're waiting.
This thing's crushing me. That was bad. It seemed kind of dangerous. I think we're waiting on
deliveries for two of them from engineering. What are you waiting for comrade? Get to it.
Okay. So I need to get parts for this. I need mech ant legs, water pipes and propellant pipes
and mandibles. Where am I supposed to find this shit? What's this? Living quarters. All right. I
got to find eggs? Where do I shoot somebody with a laser? Oh, here we go. What does this do?
Oh, all right. That brings it up there. Bunker W. Why? What do you mean Bunker W? What?
All right. Attach this. How do I attach it? Is this with the mouth? How does this work? How
do I do this? It looks like a leg. Yeah, it does. But how do I move it? Oh shit. Okay. I have to
snap it in place. Okay. What? All right. I need two more legs. Is your favorite bug? Um,
that bait. My favorite bug is probably, I don't know, but I just, I love the ball so much
and I can't decide. Um, I can't, is it stuck here? Oh yeah. Probably a honeybee. Honeybees are
probably just fucking distracting me and it's pissing me off. I don't care. You know what?
Okay. No, it's honeybee. Honeybees are, they make this delicious goo. How would you not like a
honeybee? I'm not supposed to wedge that out of there. He's so grumpy. No, I'm kidding. I swear
to God. Earwigs. I don't, I don't, I don't mind earwigs. I think they're fine. How do I get this
out? Out through there? Earwigs are the worst. They really aren't though. What do they do that's so
bad? What, what does an earwig do that's so bad? Nothing. They just kind of exist. What's wrong?
Mosquitoes are probably the worst insect without a doubt. And ticks. Mosquitoes, ticks and fleas
probably, right? Like this. All the biting insects. Fuck that. Can I not pull this guy out? Yeah,
mosquitoes are the worst. They don't, there's no benefit at all for a mosquito. They just cause
problems. They just cause problems only. What about the leech? Yeah, but the leech had some medical
backing, right? Weren't leeches, didn't they have a purpose? What the fuck? A leech is not a bug
though. Yeah, that's true. Ah! Okay. Oh my God, there's more. Fuck you, stupid goddamn. All right,
I'm fine. I'm just trying to rush. I have to stop. Slow down. Oh, come on. So what the hell? How do I
get? I have to be able to pull these guys out, right? Is there a device I get? Wait. Oh, I got
one. Is that going to work? Um, how do I get this back? Wait, will this connect in here? Oh shit!
That's how you do it. All right. So you have to connect them. How am I going to get this back?
He's so fucking high. How do I get it out? It's getting called out right now. I'm fine.
Let's drag it out. Come on, pull it up. Yeah. Okay. I need to make a bridge here. I'm good enough.
So now I have to fuck. How am I supposed to do this? I got to pull it up and then turn it.
I'm not going to die. Here we go. All right. Now jump it this way. You look confused. I kind
of am confused. I kind of am confused, man. Heat bugs or riot. No, fuck you. No. Oh, it did. It
beat it for me. Good. Oh, there's one. Okay. He got it. Okay. So they transfer it. Oh, all right.
Let me just get a sip of water. How many of you guys with just room temp water out of a glass?
You can just badlands chugs that and it's not a problem. Room temp water out of a,
just a room temp glass. That's gone. It's gone instantly. Okay. I need, there's another piece
over here. There's enough. What was it? What was the other one? Is there more than one here?
I don't think there's more than one now. That's easy. Ah, that's very helpful actually.
Okay. So now there's another leg here. I got to connect it to this one. So I get it. Everyone,
that was Pepe laughing. You're really funny. Just for your information. Webbed is 10 bucks.
Wait, am I connected? Do I have to connect this one to that one? Is that how this works?
Is it going to connect to this? Do I have to do that? Well, I have to bring it up there.
I have to take it to the mech. Where's the mech from here? Up, upright. Come here. Get over here.
I screwed it up. Yeah. No, no, no, no, no, no. Get up. Get up. Oh my God. I soft locked it.
Okay. Now come here. Bugs have milk. I don't think so. Get this fucking thing up. I don't know, man.
I don't think, no. What are you talking about? Why are you saying such a weird thing? No. Whatever.
Start over. Just start the whole fucking thing over. Use more than one web. Stop being bad.
Yeah, but I'm trying to pull it up. I want it to go up more. I want it to go up more. How do I get
it to go up more? Connect it at both ends. It is on both ends. How do I pull it up? You need more
lines. No, I don't. Look at how many fucking lines there are. Put them on the ceiling instead.
Get up here. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. But go. This is for you. I think it made it. I think.
Let's go find out. Eat bugs. Shut up. What is that sound? All right. Look it. We got another leg.
Guys, we've got another leg. Connect it. Okay. It's one more leg. I have not been down to the lower
right. Let's figure it out. Can't talk right now. Sorry. Oh, a giant. Can you please be a little
bit more quiet? You almost woke up my dog. He needs rest. I was supposed to start barking.
I was about to try to do a real dog bark. Realistic dog barking. You know what I mean?
Kind of in the realm of. I caught that one really early. I caught that one very early. I like the
song. Yeah, the soundtrack's cute. Good day, comrade. Everyone here is getting really thirsty.
Oh, me too. You think you could turn the water back on so we can have a drink? Yeah. Drop this
somehow. No bark, Andy. How do I turn that on? Jeremy, maybe if you played the game, you just
would figure it out eventually. Now I have to ask a fake rhetorical question and go like this and
wait till somebody says the answer. Uh, where am I? I need water. Oh, boss bite. Is it boss bite,
I think. Look, that's a Mega Man door. That's the Mega Man door before the boss. You know what I'm
saying? This is a Mega Man boss fight door. I told you it was. I'm always doing a boneless. Get it?
Hey, you skater girl. Hit me, skate herb. I'm trying to teach all them ants to skate. They
got the right attitude, but still working on technique. You want to show them how it's done?
Yes. Heck yes. They're depart ants. We about to see some sick moves.
Rip board, release board, rip board, release board, rip board, release board, rip board.
What? W. That was pretty sick. What am I supposed to be doing? Oh, I have to grip the board
and jump. I don't know. I don't get it. Oh, what a cool trick. What a cool trick that was. Okay.
Um, I can. Oh, I can grow. I need to be on the board. How do I? Okay. How do I turn? How do I
restart? I don't know. I have no idea what the board is. Okay. Grip the board. Hold on. Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. That's the B. All right. I got the B. I got BB. B. Shit. That was
going to be cool looking. Can I grab this and put it back up there? There we go. All right. Wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait. Get over there. I need another B. I need E. God damn it. Oh, this way.
I see. All right. I got to go this way and then come down there. All right. Check it out. Here we
go. Come on. What the fuck? Use webs? I can't use webs. It pulls me off the board. Does it? Yeah. I
can't. If I use a web, it takes me off the board. That was pretty sick. All right. I got to go up.
I need E. An E and a B and I'm done. My head just caved in. Where's the last B? Right there.
I wasn't supposed to do this in a certain time limit, was I? Hope not. Hey, skater girl. You're
ready to skate? No, no, no, no, no, no. I don't want to skate anymore. I already did it. I can
just leave? Wait, did I get a skateboard as a present? Where am I? All the way over here.
I named my dog. Can you please bark back to my dog? No, I'm not going to bark at your dog
because me barking at your dog is an embarrassment for me. I'm not barking. I'm way too far away. I'm
going back to the ant kingdom. Is the music too annoying? All right. I need to go. I can't get,
I got to go up to where the mech is and then right and then down. All right. I think so.
Will you please just bark, please? Oh my God. Okay. Fine. Is that what you want to hear?
You want me to just wait? Is that good? The only thing I see is somebody very, very long,
long term viewer, mod, community members been around for a fucking decade. It's an all lower
case. Just wrote strange. What does it even sound like? That sounds weird. I did. I actually didn't
mean to have that on. I kind of want to, I kind of want to keep this on just like this for a little
while. How does it, how much more different do I actually sound? Do I sound even that much more
different? How absurdly different do I probably a lot, right? Probably a lot. I would take a quick
master. I have to play with the audio setup one last time before I get rid of it forever. I can't
believe I just fucking barked. I'm genuinely unhappy about that. Like why did I do that? What
was the point? Like I don't know why I did that. It's like 15,000 people here, four of you were
telling me to bark and you said it like 50 times. And then finally I was like, I thought, I thought
that you five people were like a thousand people because I keep looking over and seeing, dude,
you should buy dog likes when dogs bark. Bark at my dog. I'm like, fine. I'll do it. Okay.
It was not 20%. It was definitely not. I got to go try to go right.
You can't go right from, I need to go this way. Please, please say Aaron in the deep voice.
Okay. Was there another leg over here that I didn't get? How do I get out of here? What about up?
Okay. Please do a pull. No, I, you just got like your fucked up weird fringe guy voice.
I just did it. I just tried to realistically bark like a dog. No, you're not getting any more.
That's what you're getting. That's what you're getting. That's what you're getting today.
No more. Okay. Wait, I need to get water, right? Okay. Water pump is down.
Helmet pump is over there and the pump power station. All right, let's go down.
Shit. I need to make a bridge. No. Oh, a gear has to go there. What the hell happened? Oh,
it's too slippery. That's really slippery. All right. I gotta be careful. Ow. This mudslides
getting dangerous. I'm trying to repair this power station to open up access to the pumps,
but I slipped and fell. Would you lend me a mandible? Yeah. How do I get there? Can I help
you get up there? Do I actually have to pull you up? No. Is that helping? Oh, just like the movie
Up. Seen it. I'm going to go up. That work. Thanks for helping me out. You're a true friend.
Now I just need to find a way to fix this gearbox. Okay. So I help. I think I have an idea. All right,
check this out. What if I go like this? Not what I wanted to do. Can I attach this to the ceiling
over there? Or should I swing? I don't know what to do. You're killing him. I didn't kill him.
What do I do? Maybe I should fall. It's like mouth skin. What's happening? It called lips.
I'm telling you. No, it's mouth. I have this mouth skin. All right, hold on. What if I...
Okay. Very obviously. Will it eventually pull it the other way? It will. Okay. Kind of. I don't. I
need to understand physics. Hold on. All right. It's going. It's going. It's going. It's going.
All right. Got that. Got that. Okay. Now I got to pull this. And then, all right,
this is going to get pulled over here too. So let me get on the other side. Like this.
Oh, stupid. What the fuck? What? What are you talking about? All right. Wait, wait, wait. Do
a think. Do a think. You need to think. Hold on. Just give me a net so I can not keep falling down.
That longer? I think that's it. Here we go. Ready? See you later. Oh. Oh. I didn't get the grub.
That's okay. I don't want the rock. Stop picking the rock up. Get out of my way.
I'm working. Dude, seriously. Dude, get out of the way. Just get out of the way. Just get out of the
fucking way. Get out of the way. It's wedged into the middle of the rocks. Get out. Thank you. Hey,
I'm doing a cellar spider pattern, okay? They're the most intelligent of all the spiders.
You know why? Because they don't do this symmetrical web. They do this mess of a fucking web because it
catches more shit. The symmetrical pretty design. No. Cellar spiders understand what they're doing.
They do an incredibly messy design. It catches way more shit. Now get over here. Finally. Now extract
it. We're good. Did somebody fact check that? No, no, no. You can. Absolutely. Please do.
Cellar spider has an incredibly erratic design because it catches more stuff. Look it up.
Now what? It's true. Cellar spiders construct loose haphazard webs often in corners to catch
insect prey. They hang upside down on the web until a food item gets tangled. Once prey is captured,
a cellar spider vigorously shake their webs to further entangle their meal. That's what I'm
saying. Can everyone here that's telling me that I'm not a scientist go get the grub? I don't think
I can. I'll try. That cog better still be in there. Cellar spiders are really good for you.
They're just terrifying looking. Cellar spiders are really strange looking. They're kind of like
these white, yellowy, wispy looking. They have really long legs. They're really strange looking.
One and why I didn't take that one off. Oh, you piece of shit. It's not enough. It's not enough.
It might be enough. All right. I'm just trying to rush. Just stop rushing. That should do it.
Like that. One, two. Okay. There's one. That one's in a perfect spot. There it is. How am I supposed
to do that? Everything's in place. It's fine. I have to grab into there. It's going to be actually,
that's going to be hard to get. I have to shoot into there and down. That's going to be hard.
Okay. So I powered the station up. Very cool. Now this is the gas station. Did I go this way?
So I got power and now I need fuel. What are the dumb bullshit do I have to do here?
Take another grub. That's for sure. That's going to be a huge pain in the ass.
My patience is so low. So low. I just, it takes so much for me to, I know what I have to do here,
right? But the prospect of doing this is like, it's like I can tear fucking colors in my head.
I just don't want to do it. Does anybody else feel that? I see the solution. Like
gecko gecko gecko gecko gecko click. But my brain is just like, don't you want to just like
roll around on the ground? You know, I just don't want you to just want to roll around.
Yeah. I kind of just want to just like roll around on the ground. I don't want to like do this.
I don't want to do this. I know what I have to do. It's ADHD. I know, but still it's just, I
know what I have to do. I think my problem a lot of times I'm trying to music down.
The music's cool, but I can't even hear myself think. Um, I think it's because my brain has
already seen the solution. Puzzle games to me get really weird because I get this puzzle,
this big elaborate thing that I need to do. And in my head I see the solution. I've seen it finished
and I sit there and I go, I know what that looks like finished. It's this process of getting to
finishing that, that I don't want to do because I'm a very visual person. I can, these two are
connected in my brain right now. I'm watching it. They're connected. I'm looking at it right now.
It's literally a moving video in my head. I'm watching it. I just don't want to do it. He's
too smart. I don't want to connect these two fucking dryer vents. Okay. But I know I have to,
so I have to do it. No. Connect to the other one. Excuse me? Okay. Is that one? Oh, what a shit job.
Yeah. Is that wrong? Is that, was that, was it wrong? The one on the, I'm very confused.
It was not wrong. So what the hell's wrong? Do it! Why won't it do it? They're on. They're on,
right? That definitely looks on. They're both connected. Okay. They're both on. I'll turn
the machine on, right? Cool. Two grubs. That's pretty good deal. Where does this go? Okay. Two
of these. Awesome. Down there. There's a third cog over there. Okay. I gotta get them all up there.
You're reading this, please sing the victory song. SpongeBob? All right. Wait, wait, wait.
No, no, no, no. I gotta bring it back down here. Stay up here. Okay. You actually have the
behavioral patterns of a spider. You just confused me so much that now I, I didn't get the,
now I, now I don't? How do I have the behavioral patterns of a spider? Doesn't make any sense.
I don't, I'm not a spider. I think lizard is more accurate. Spiders are too delicate and they're
too calculated. Some of my happiest days have been just baking in the sun with my mouth open,
lying down on the ground. So I think I'm more of a, I think I'm more of a lizard. One, two. So yeah,
I would be a lizard and not cool looking either. I would, I'm not going to be a cool looking lizard.
But one, I would be the lizard that just lie there. They just lick their eyes. No, I'm not,
it's not, I'm not going to even say it. And when they run away, they do this thing where they go
like this, like they kind of shake their like arms like this and they kind of slide from side
to side and shake, shake, shake, shake, shake while they run. What is that? That's a crested gecko.
You're describing a spider. That's not a spider. No, the reason why you guys think I'm a spider is
because of the erratic movements, which I understand. I get that aspect of it. You know,
sometimes you're just looking at a spider, they'll just be sitting there and all of a sudden they just
go like this. They just rip another direction and it's like, holy shit, the thing moves so weirdly
and so fast. I don't, I can't, I don't like it. A squirrel does that too. A squirrel does do that.
A spider sometimes will be like this and then two or three seconds later with you'll blink
and it'll glitch and it'll be turning this way like that. It'll be like this. It's really weird.
Okay, so those are both in there. It's one more spot here, so that should do it.
Herman knows about the glitch spiders. I mean, spiders are weird.
Goodness, he's living in a video game. No, I wouldn't be a cool animal. Just clear the board,
clear the board, clear the board, clear the board and I'll be fine. What is it? Is it stuck to the
ground here? What the fuck is going on? Please. Can I pull this up? No, I can't. Okay. Well,
I can do this. At least I can do this. No, dude, seriously. Got it! All right, I filled it up.
There's enough gas. I think that's good. So now what? Now I filled the gas. You'd be like a magpie.
Yeah, I probably would be a bird. This is really annoying. It's constantly yelling non-secretors.
Birds kind of do that. Birds, I actually would be a bird. I'm trying to think of an animal that
would randomly for no reason just say they're great without any context. They just say it for
no reason. Yeah. Have you walked into a house with somebody that has birds that talk and you
just sit there kind of on the couch and it's just like, they're great. Fuck off. Stupid. Oh, you're,
you're a pretty bird. Oh, who wants a treat? Who wants a treat? They all do that. Look at that.
It's so creepy because it's always in their voice. The voice of the person who owns the bird.
It's terrifying and it sounds almost a little bit robotic. A little bit. It's a weird tape recording
version of that person saying it. It's so strange. It's like, um, it kind of, hold on. I'm gonna take
a second here. I'm gonna, I'm gonna be a fucking weirdo for a minute just in case anyone was trying
to chill today. Does this work? Does this work? Yeah, it works. Let's pretend I have a bird.
I'm gonna just pretend I have a bird back here. I got a new bird. But weirdly enough, it always
sounds, let's say it's an old lady that has the bird. The bird will be doing this whole routine.
Who's a pretty bird? It's like, holy shit. That was like, it was like grandma talking.
Let's see if I can get this. Hold on. It's good. Test it. It kind of sounds like this,
but not this deep here. Hold on. Let me fix it. That sounds kind of correct. It's a little better.
Hold on. This was better. Things to say. It's weird. This shit sounds exactly like this.
I've been in houses with people with birds before and it's just fucking terrifying in a way.
So imagine that that's, that's literally grandma's voice and you hear shit like this.
Anybody not gonna go see that fucking movie ever? Okay, here we go. There's a bird in the house.
Who's a pretty bird? Who wants a kiss? Who wants a kiss?
Oh, who's a pretty bird? Who wants a kiss? Who wants a kiss?
This goes on for 10 to 12 hours straight every day. This is scary. It's like scary.
That is scary. That is actually really scary. You guys know what I'm talking about though,
right? You guys get it. You know what I mean. You know what I mean by this, don't you?
I'm not crazy. That's actually what it's like. It sounds like a fucking old talkback tape recording
version of the person speaking, talking. It's fucking weird. What does it sound like? I don't
know. I'm scared to press it again. Oh, who's a pretty bird? It's weird, man. It's actually
fucking weird. You're fucked up. No, I'm telling you. I'm the smart one. Reconnect the propellant
pipes. Okay, so that's done. It's impossible for me to get killed. I actually don't even know how
that killed me. It's not even possible to die there. All right, so now I need to put the mandible
through the forge. Reconnect the water pipes. Reconnect the water pipes. Where am I? I have
to go down. Down to the lower right. Wasn't that where I was before? Isn't this the water
area down here? There's this. I forget where to go. This looks like a water pipe to me, doesn't it?
It would be less terrifying without the who wants a kiss mwah mwah mwah. But that's what they all
say. All right, I gotta focus. Leave me alone. We need to go this way and then down. What do I do
with the grubs again? I don't know. Who's kissing birds? I don't know. People that have birds,
they lean in and they... Right? I think so. What are you talking about? Oh, this is how I get down
here. This thing's operational again. People don't do that. I'm telling you they do. A sandwich. All
right, weigh that down. Yeah, they do. All right, it's good. It just sounds like a Disney movie.
Disney Pixar's Webbed in theaters May 20th. That sounds like a Disney movie name. It kind of does.
This game's cute though. I like it. Too heavy? Is it too heavy? Oh, I think it's a little too
heavy. No, maybe not. I'm panicking right now. Hey, what does that get me? Have you heard of
lyrebirds? They can perfectly emulate chainsaw sounds. Yeah, they're just tape recorders. They're
strange tape recorders. Feel like I'm gonna have to bring another one of these down here. Nice.
Holy shit. I was supposed to die there. I went in for one second. Wee. All right, what do I need to
do down here? The wheel. All right, first of all, do this so I don't fall in. Yikes. Is that... Okay,
put it in. Oh, you fixed the drawbridge already. Outstanding work. Now that the rest of the colony
can get through, we can start fixing this place up. I want you to turn it on. Oh, that's the way the
bridge is. Auto. Anything else up here? I don't think there's anything I can do up here. I'd have
to connect... I have to do the water pump thing, don't I? Or did I already do that? That connects
to here. It wants me to go this way. Can you bark again? What's the spider language? This. Okay,
so I need... What do I need to do? I need another ant leg. Reconnect the water pipes. What do I do
that? It said down here, water pipes. Remember? I'm just going back this way. Fuck it, I'm going
this way. Can you make some bird sounds? Probably. I have a fiver page if you want to pay for it.
The base is... It's one... For five dollars you get... I do one bird impression. It's about 10
seconds. Twenty dollars would get you two... Would get you three birds of your choice. And then 50
dollars gets you 10 birds of your choice. And I have a list of all the birds that I can do.
They range from cockatoo to chickadee to hummingbird. I have this... You can pick from a
list. If you want, just a little sample. I can give that to you just for a demo for anyone that
was interested. 60 dollars? Yeah. It's really good for background songs, background noise,
sampling. I've had a lot of people contact me over the first 10 seconds of songs. Whether it be
rock or rap music, whatever. Make a big intro. Doesn't matter. Genre. A lot of people use it
for a sample. Can I get a preview? Yeah, I mean, you've probably heard me a few times. Actually,
it was part of Hank Fuck's last album. It was featured a few times. He actually did the 50
dollar tier. If you remember, it's a pretty popular song. It has, I think, six or seven
hundred plays on Spotify. The opening is kind of like an inside echo-y instead of a cavern.
It has this big explosion sound. I think he used it there because I can kind of hear my chickadee.
The chickadee-dee-dee-dee-dee-dee. It kind of blows boom and he goes into his new song.
This was a fun experience. Was that way too dank? Oh, I'm so sorry. I'm sorry. I am so sorry if
that was that. That's why I need a new audio setup. I'm going to get a new audio setup. I'm
going to get a brand new setup. No more loud sounds. I swear to God, I promise. My audio is
going to be perfectly, perfectly done. That's not going to happen anymore. I promise. I'm going to
The compressor is going to be perfect. It's going to be perfect highs, perfect lows.
The next time I stream, I promise. Keep it like this. No, no, you don't like loud sounds.
You just say you like loud sounds because you want a loud sound to happen so you can go,
oh, shit, that probably fucked up somebody's ears because you think it's funny.
Somebody else's ears get fucked up. No, I don't want, I don't want any more loud sounds.
No more loud sounds. Here we go. Pump is going in. You got this. Hey, thanks. Chickadee-dee-dee-dee-dee-dee.
Chickadee-dee-dee-dee-dee-dee-dee. It's going to be hard to get up there.
Pump! Do I have to weigh it down or is this going to work? Fuck. Fucking piece of shit.
Fucking. Oh, I need another one. Okay. Let's do more. What? Why was that rude? It was me expressing
anger. Calm down. They're in the water? Stupid fucking goddamn fucking idiots. Fucking goddamn
stupid fucking goddamn game. Oh, they are here, yeah. Oh, is there whoever's on the ghost team?
Shut the fuck up right now. This is going to be such a pain in the ass. Oh, yikes. This is going
to be hell. How am I going to do this? I'm going to have to do it one at a time. One at a time.
Don't you wait on that one. Perfect. Isn't this guy supposed to be trying to find sponsors for
his streams? What? Because I said stupid fucking goddamn fucking idiots. You can swear and get
sponsors, right? But I stopped doing that. Just not very good ones. Not good ones. I'll be fine.
I'll be fine. There it is. All right. Water pipes reconnected. Pumping going on. I hope you don't
get any. Why not? Why? You don't want me to get... Why not? Hey, I want them. I'm going to get them.
Indram, I'm going to cancel my sponsorship. Okay, so I think I've been down in the ant
place for a long time. I need one more ant leg and I need the ant mouth. So how do I...
What do I go from here? Oh, it's filling the tank. All right. What happens if it goes all the way up?
Is the door going to open? Oh, cool. All right. So now I can leave through here. Oh, my goodness.
It's not going to kill me, right? Oh, my fucking God. Still going? Is it still going? Where's the
elevator there? What is this? The no talk stream? I haven't shut the hell up in 15 straight minutes.
Okay, I need one more leg. I did the power. I did the gas. I did all this. Water pipes,
propellant pipes, electricity. I need another ant leg down here maybe. What did I get? What did
I miss an ant leg? I need to go up. What's this twitch stream? So where am I now? So this is back
to the top of the ant hill. I don't want to leave the ant hill. I don't want to leave.
There's as much more to be done. Wrong way. Yeah, well, come on. So going up from here takes me out.
So I need to go left. This is not going into the highlight. Um, it is. Okay, so left from here,
I think. I'm gonna go left. Okay, so this is... I gotta hand it down here. Have I been over here?
I don't remember. I don't... I have not been over there. Fire? So I gotta put the fire out probably?
Suck up the water from here? You gotta forge the mandible. Well, somebody has to give it to me.
What do I get it? Do I have to bring it all the way over here? I can't go in there like Mario.
Are you ever gonna play Yakuza Zero like you promised? I know I said it a while ago, but
if somebody made a compilation of all the times I have lied on this stream or have not said the
thumb the thing I said I was going to do, it would be a four and a half up to five hour long video.
So I have to throw a mandible in here to forge it. Where do I get it?
And I imagine it would be done to the music of... what's that? Overture?
You'd have to replay that song three or four times. All right, there's one more leg and then the mouth.
Where is it? Down here? I'm gonna go there. I think I haven't... I don't think I've been down there.
I've been here. Yeah, it's right here, but what the fuck? How do I get it?
Where's this piece? There's a piece that I haven't found yet. No, I want to go down.
Okay, that's the 1812 Overture. All right, here we go. Thought you were gonna get me.
Nope. Oh my god! That just scared the hell out of me. You fucking idiot. This fucking rock needs
to get out of the way. Thank you. Interact with us! I'm... don't... look at how much I'm concentrating.
I'm sorry, if I'm diffusing a bomb, what wire do I cut next? Dance for us. Dance for us. You
should dance. Which wire? Who's the bomb? I need to fucking focus. We'll chat in just a minute.
Hold on. But you just keep failing over and over again. Just talk to us. Did I fail that time?
I better still save. It's there. It's there. I'm fine. Looks good. No, I just need... there it is.
Okay. Why did I... what was I doing? What am I doing? Seriously? We gotta go up. Okay. No, don't slide.
Go up. And then hand it to you. Check this out. Don't fire the gun. Oh my fucking god. Just...
I'm gonna scream. I'm so annoyed. I just... oh, I can see the solution. I can see it. I can
feel the solution. I just can't do the solution. Get the fuck over here! Oh my goodness,
I'm gonna lose my mind. Slow down. I can't slow down. I see the solution. It's already done.
My brain is like, do it already. He is standing, giving a peace sign, taking a picture with all
the webs in the right place. And I'm just fucking pissed at him. It's like, dude, I know... I can
see you done. I'm just... I need to get to it. Like he said, you took a vacation photo. Okay.
Take this down. Here it comes. Okay. Square one. Check it out. Slow down. Watch this. Bridge.
It was that easy. It was seriously... it was that simple. I just had to slow down.
Now that should go back up here. But I think... I feel like a bug just crawled over my hand.
Okay. Where... where is it? There it is. This has to go here, which will drop it. Okay. Now
this goes where? Nobody else has to pick this up, right? Over here? Right there. So now this comes
down. It's just a puzzle game with roguelike elements. Yeah. You're moving from point A to
point B. Yeah. That's accurate. Stop sliding. Slow down. I am. See, he just keeps... his forward
momentum keeps going. I'm not touching it. No, just burger boy technique. Just fucking burger
boy technique. Uh, that last one is here. So now I got all the legs. Jeremy, you're spending so much
fucking time with these ants. I mean, there's other shit to do with them. You're spending a
lot of time with these fucking ants, dude. Like, you've been outside a lot. You're just like,
you're digging around looking for fucking ants. I don't... I don't know what is...
getting a little concerned about you. Get out there. Quick. All right. Good. Done. Two hours
with the ants. I think this game's only three hours long. I could be wrong though. The mandible
through the forge. Where is this mandible? Here? Is it only because I haven't gone? Like, right?
Right? Down, right? Down, right? Left? Should I connect these? Connect the pipes to the ants.
Connect this? What do I connect it? On top? Oh, look at it. It goes on top.
You're right. Yeah, okay. Please attach. Please attach. Please attach. There it is.
It was attached! What the fuck? Okay, it's attached. Ooh! Attached. Why is it not attaching?
It should have attached by now. Why? What is with this fucking elephant nose? Get over here. Attach!
Attach! Attach to the thing! It's running. I have to attach the oil thing. Is it already done?
It doesn't attach. Oh, wait. I had to fuel it. Oh, okay. All right. Whatever. All right. So,
I gotta go right. I haven't been down here. I thought I had to stay on there. No, I gotta go
up. Up and to the right. This dude doesn't know what's happening. No, not really. I'm just here
for the ride. Okay. I have not gone down to the right. Where am I now? No. I need to go. It's left?
I haven't explored over here. There's a question mark over here. Down here. Where have I not gone?
Go back to the flame thing. Yeah, but I need the mandible. Where do I get the mandible?
The giant gas tank says left. Yeah, but I need the mandible though. The mandible is at the
giant flame. Did I not pick it up or something? Chad is wrong. Are they? Where am I? Okay. I'm
kind of going down to the furnace again here. Okay. So, this is the gas. Do I have to go all
the way back over here? Over here? I have to go over here, don't I? I am lost. Yeah. I am lost.
Oh, just respawn me. Just fucking give me a checkpoint. I'm just fucking going so fast.
I can see the solution in my head. You motherfucker. Okay. Back. Back. Back. Back.
Back. Back. Back. Back. Back. Back. Back. Back. Back. Back. Go on a home run. So, now we go over
here. So, where's the mandible? How do I open this? I can't open this. And unless there's
something I can do here, I pull this up or take this with me somehow? I can't scoop this up.
Because there's a big forge over here, but I don't have the mandible. If I touch this, I die.
Jump in the forge? Is it below this room? I've been in all these rooms already. I feel like I
need to go all the way left, but I can't open that door. I mean, right here. I can't get in there.
Something weird with this pipe, probably, right? It was down. No. This is the only place I haven't
been. So, I kind of feel like it has to be there. Wait, I can just use this? That's pretty cool.
I thought that was a one-time thing. All right. So, where the hell am I going? Find the mandible.
I must have just missed it somewhere. I think I just missed it. Just straight up missed it
somehow. Because this thing's ready to go. I just need the front. This is the engineering room,
which this takes me down here. Maybe it is over here. You passed it? Up one. Medium left. Medium
left. What do you mean? Go left. Medium left. I went past it. Medium left. Stop saying you're
breaking the- Okay. Yeah. I see what you're doing. Forge. Oh, nice. Okay. I don't think I did this.
No, I did. No, I didn't. There's got to be grubs up here, right? Whoa. Do you trust chat with your
life? Guys, if there were two doors, because I was doing an IRL stream and one of the doors was
safe. So, it's like a green door and a blue door, right? And behind the green door was a room full
of fire and flames. And if I opened it, I would get engulfed in flames and I would get fucking
annihilated. And on the right door, the other door was an ice cream party. A ton of people in chat
would be like, left door. Pepe, left. You should pick the left one. And it would be like, oh,
left door chat? Really? Yeah. Pick the left one. You guys are trying to fucking get me incinerated.
There'd be people in chat saying like, guys, no, dude, like, you're actually going to incinerate
them. Like, stop trolling, please. And then they would get timed out because they use too many
caps. I did it. I'll heat it up. No health. No health. Yeah. I would take my hand. I'd put my
hand on the door. They'd be like, hey, this one? You guys think it's this one? Oh, chat. That hurt.
That kind of hurt my hand. It's all red. There's a huge red circle. And I would look over and just
be no health. No health. Okay. I guess I'm going in. All right. Send these mandibles through the
forge. No vers. No health. Yeah. And then I would open the door up. It would be, there'd be a bunch
of, oh my God, deface, deface, deface. And then the next day, two or three days later, there'd be
people in the chat that would be typing, where is he? How come he hasn't streamed in three days?
Where the fuck is he? Excuse me? Where's the stream? He's late. He's supposed to be here. Oh,
up there. Where is he? Yeah. People say like, oh, that stream sucked, by the way. Like, that was
like kind of a dumb stream. I wasn't a big fan. That was like, dude, that was like really dangerous.
He's going to have some explaining to do when he comes back. That was extra. Let go. Worst stream
of the year. Oh, I was almost there. All right. Stop being panicking. Yes. Another hellfire door
stream. Okay. So I have to send this through the forge. Spinning. That's spinning. Ah, I get it.
What are we waiting for? What's wrong? Why is everybody freaking out? Let's not. I told him,
get new audio equipment. It might've been like an audio problem. I'm so impatient. I am so impatient.
I would like Uber Eats a glass of water from fucking down, like in my downstairs. You know
what I'm saying? I would Uber Eats a glass of water. I'm so impatient. I'm so lazy. Just do it
right. Just do it right. Just do it. It's here. It's in front of you. Just do it. That would take
longer. I know. That's what I'm saying. This has taken so much longer because I'm so impatient.
Okay. This over here. Hold up. If it wasn't so heavy. There we go. All right. Oh, the lever.
Okay. Go. Oh, yay. Oh, go like this. Oh, oh, do it. We're so close. Just burger boy it again.
Not a bad idea. Did it work? Okay. So now this is going to get grabbed. I'll wait for the next
rotation. Make sure it's only good. Oh, it took you fucking forever. Okay. Now let's pass it
through the forge. Here we go. Cool. G'day. It's all heated up. Now we go through here.
Punch that button. Oh, that's how we get over here. Cool. So now I should have the mandible.
I think that's pretty much it. That looks hot. Can I even touch this? This probably kills me if I
touch it. No, it's all right. No, it does not. It's not all right. By the only way I can barely
hear the music. Yeah, it's kind of one single loop, but it's a good loop. Yeah, it's good.
Do I have to cool this off? I definitely do. Don't I? Yeah, there's no way I don't have to do that.
Open the hellfire door. Where are you moving this? You duck. You know what a really great word is?
Quench. Thirst quench. Quench is such a great word. Pull it. There we go. Nice and
cool by going into the coolant. Hooray. Got it. There it is. Final piece. Time to put it back on.
And then that's it for the ants. Now we're just gonna bring this down. How far down?
Let me scope this out first. It's gotta go here. I gotta attach to this. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry.
Come on. Do it. Come on. Oh, please. Exactly what I wanted. All right. Let's get it.
Mandible attached. Shit. What? Oh, that's not good. Get up. I'm so mad. Okay, let's just go around.
What the fuck am I gonna do about this? Do I have to go all the way around the other side?
Stop touching that. Move. He's so focused. I don't want to mess this up. Gotta attach it up here.
Hey, looking good, comrade. Get over here and let's have a talk. It's ready. It's fueled up.
Mission accomplished. Kind of sloppy, but I did it. It worked out. Hold up a second. The platoon is
moving out. Got seen. We're having a great stream so far. I just joined and I happened to notice
that the title says be in a bug. I want to let you know that spiders are not bugs. They are
arachnids. So maybe you can change the title to something more appropriate. Thanks. What a beautiful
display. Arachnids. No, they're aliens. They're all aliens. Do you guys know the bugs have been
around since 500 trillion years or so before the dinosaurs? They've been around. They're the most
prehistoric creature and they still exist. They were mosquitoes back when the T-Rex was in law
school. You know what I'm saying? They've been around for so long and they're still around. How
do they stick around for so long? All right. Send a workforce ahead to help out with your mission on
the surface. They'll have that balloon up and flying before you know it. Dismissed. I got it.
Very cool. Okay. Find some fuel. So let's go to the surface. Aliens. I don't know. They're bugs.
They have to be aliens. Look at them. They've been around for 500 trillion years or something
and look at the sounds they make. Unfrozen T-Rex lawyer. Why do I feel like that's a show
that is on Adult Swim right now? Okay, so now what? I need one more grub. Oh man,
I really do need one more grub. But I don't, I kind of don't care. Is that where the fly should
hand it into the fly, right? Where's the fly? Harvey Birdman? Harvey Birdman. That's, what is it?
Ha ha. Stephen Colbert, right? Stephen Colbert. Ha ha. That's the only thing I know of the whole
show. I remember it being a good show though, right? Wait, you can fly? No, not, not. Ha ha.
I can't. You have to take all the air out. It's like, ha ha. No, there was still air in there.
Look at how cute that is. Ha ha. Stephen Colbert. Well, now I know. All right. All right. All right.
We're pivoting. We're pivoting. We're pivoting. We're pivoting. We're pivoting. We're pivoting.
We're pivoting. We're pivoting. Pivot! It's time for a pivot! I'm fucking loud and annoying. I'm
sorry. Your airship mechanic. We're almost ready for the trip of a lifetime. Take these blueprints
that we've got lots to do. Fuel engine patches, map, moth nest, spider webs. Okay. Rest of our
pre-flight checklist. Find a way to patch up the balloon. Bees to the east might be able to help
with that. Find a fuel source. Some good concentrated dung would work. Find some of the west.
Attach engine immediately below the mouth of the balloon. Your pilot platform. Oh, I forgot.
If you run into any trouble, just shoot the work bell and we'll reset everything for you.
And well, I need to get this stuff first. Oh, shit in this game.
These ants showed up just ahead of you. A quick work of the tree. They've been
badgering me with designs for ages, but I've not had the courage to let them try it.
Glad you're helping each other though. Your plans seem solid even if they're too bold for me.
Okay. So that's to float away. I need to find some fuel. Where should I go? Oh, cute. I guess
I could go to the west. Go to the bees. I'm going to go east. East. Or should I turn in the fly
stuff first? It's somewhere over here. Where's the fly? Where is he? Where is he? Because I have a
ton of those grubs, don't I? I don't know where the fly is. Fly is more to the left. Where you at?
Here? Yeah, he's right up there. Right there. Greetings, spider. I appreciate your visit and
your continued virtue. That's not what those are for? You're the Doctor Who Twitch. I don't
get that reference because I've only seen one episode of Doctor Who ever. And so when would
they time travel around like five times and he sees himself five times? I don't know what you
mean by that. Anytime I think of Doctor Who, I could be completely off with this. But I always
think of like Doctor Who to me is like a Harry Potter for adults. Is that correct? Does that make
any sense? I feel like it's like the Harry Potter type kind of sci-fi fantasy world as for like a
grown-up audience. Not that he's a wizard. No, I'm just saying it's like that fantasy kind of
whimsical world of Doctor Who, right? It's very whimsical. Harry Potter isn't sci-fi.
What, you don't remember the part where they were shooting the blasters? Okay, I got a quest for
you. The queen is making a new princess to make a brand new hive. To make a princess she needs
royal jelly and to make the jelly she needs pollen. Only the best pollen. Pink orchid pollen. 20
grains should do it. Bring that up to Canopy's Peak. I bet she'd love you. Come on. Okay, very
cool. So okay, give me a... I don't know anything about Doctor Who. I want a just a small quick
paragraph TLDR of... Okay, Doctor Who. Each season of Doctor Who, it's like Final Fantasy,
right? They're not connected. They're independent universes or something. It's like Final Fantasy.
How many seasons of... Yeah, Doctor Who. Explain it to me. What is it? They're all connected. Oh.
Okay, silly person travels with friends. Wacky British alien who time travels and does
fucked up stuff. Immortal alien. Hold on, this person has it. The doctor is an immortal alien
who travels through time sorting out his personal problems with mortals. He's an alien that changes...
So he's Rick from Rick and Morty. Alien that changes form every so often and goes on big
space and time adventures and has fun shit and does fun stuff and has funny catchphrases. And he
figures out his problems. I may have just caused the whole internet to fucking hate my life.
So he's Rick from Rick and Morty. How much you guys just turned purple, I think. I think a bunch
you guys turned purple. I'm just fucking kidding. I don't know anything about the show. I've never
seen it. I've heard really good things about it. Somebody in All Capital said, it's not Rick and
Morty. I know. I'm just fucking around. I'm fucking with you. I promise. Okay, it's not Rick and
Morty. It's not. But let me just be very clear. Let me be very fair. I see the same amount of
merchandise of Dr. Who at Spencer Gifts that I see from Rick and Morty. I mean, actually fair.
So who's everybody's favorite doctor then? There's a new doctor every season, right?
How many seasons are there? And is it worth getting into? And tell me the truth. I remember
before when we talked about JoJo's Bizarre Adventure one time. We're like, dude, you would
love JoJo. Oh my God. It would be like your favorite series ever. Just skip the first season.
Go to episode five of season three. Watch that one twice. And then after you watch that episode
two times, go back and watch the first episode. After you finish the first episode, then you're
free to watch the rest of the series. Let's start at season six. You can actually skip. You know,
nevermind. Nevermind. Skip the first five seasons of JoJo. And I'm just like, okay, can I just watch
the show? I'll just watch the show, I guess. Skippers? Yeah. What the hell? Watch it. Don't
skip anything. Just watch the whole thing. Yeah, I know, but that's what I mean. Just start at
seasons one through five are pretty good. See, here we go. Here we go. I'm telling you, here we go.
Well, man, you know, he's correct though. Seasons one through five are, I'm not so sure about that.
It looks crazy though. I actually, I was going to watch it at one point, but I just kind of didn't.
News is spreading. People are seething. What? What news? What do you mean? What news? News is
spreading. People are mad. What do you mean? News is spreading. What did I do about? I'm going to
apologize. What do I need to apologize for? What is it? What the fuck? I'm so mad because I called
Dr. Who Rick from Rick and Morty. Let me apologize. Let me just really quickly fix this. Let me fix
this. I, let me, hold on. I was wrong. I, somebody said just, they gave me a really, really basic
understanding of what the show is. They said it's a guy that travels through space and figures out
his problems with mortals and time travels and has interesting lasers and stuff. So I was like,
okay, so he's Rick Sanchez. And then now everyone wants to kill me. I, but I, I was very uninformed.
I was very uninformed. I, I'm very uninformed. Fucking get him. Bring up the Spencer's argument
again. No, it wasn't an argument. He keeps just jumping on spikes. Everybody relax. What I meant
to say was, listen to me. I, I don't know anything about the show. I don't know anything about the
show. I just thought it was like, whatever. I, I didn't know anything about it. And I made it,
I made it a little, little joke that just didn't, didn't go over well. And people thought it was not
funny. And how dare I compare those two shows? I look at, hey, look, the legacy of Dr. Who. Oh,
I mean, it's one of the most respected television shows like ever on British television. Right? I
mean, we all know that. Of course I respect it. I'm just, isn't off. This is a cop comment.
Everyone's booing him. Stop booing me. How many, I need, uh, how many more? There's no turning back
now. Your career is over. This is, it's just an observation. It wasn't real. It wasn't real.
It was an observation. I was observing. I was just observing. I want to go high. There we go.
There it is. Oh, 20, right? Dig your heels in, dude. You do, you have to start digging your heels
in now. You lost a thousand viewers because of that. I'm sorry. I don't watch TV guys. I really
don't get a lawyer. Can you imagine? I guess we're dealing with, uh, the, uh, the state, the state
of Nevada versus Jeremy Albertson and the, uh, he talked about how Rick Sanchez and the doctor were
essentially the same person being sued. It's so funny. I was just so inaccurate. That statement
probably was that people, I probably had some people spit their drink out. What's my 2022
yearly anime? That's a good question. What is my 2022 yearly anime? What do you guys think? Oh,
you know what? No, I called it the Harry Potter for adults too. Didn't I? I made a lot of just
like, like, like just statements, huh? I would just full of shit this whole time. I'll say what
I did see of doctor who I actually really, I thought was actually really good. I thought
the episode was really good. It was the one with, uh, David, yeah, David, um, what's his name? David
Tennant. He was great. I've seen at least a few clips. I've seen, I've seen at least two or three
episodes. Oh boys, people are gonna be mad about this, but I'm going to show it because I have to
because I just, I have to. I don't know. I honestly don't even know the context of that image.
Some of you maybe get it. I don't get it. That's a line from the show. I thought, oh, I thought you
were combining two things. I thought the, I'm doctor who in the, in this motherfucker. I thought
that was you, there was a Rick Sanchez. You were combining two of them. Like, I'm doctor who in
this motherfucker. Yeah, that's right. Me, Rick, doctor who. Yeah. I thought that's what you were
doing. That's not what you were doing. Okay. That's a line that doctor who says, I'm very confused.
I'm incredibly confused right now. Who, who says that? That's a line from the show. Rick says that
in one of the later seasons. Wait, he does? Wait, Rick says that in the show as a joke, like the joke
of, oh, I don't watch either one of these shows guys. I don't. What? What? I don't know. Should I
show these? I feel like I'm going to make everybody hate me. You fucked up so bad. I don't watch either
of these shows. You could show me, you could gaslight me so bad on both these shows. In fact,
I think that's what happened. It's, I'm sorry. People have been just like gaslighting me this
whole time and I, they were telling me like what that doctor who was Rick and Morty. So I believed
him. So that's what I made that comment about Spencer Gifts and everybody got mad. All right.
All right. I get it. Okay. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I thought,
okay, I thought you made that up. Rick and Morty came out first. Oh my goodness. That person's,
you need to turn off your DMs. This is supposed to be a stream where I played a game with as a
bug and we've relaxed. So that's what we're going to do. That's what we're going to do.
I, I apologize to all the doctor who fans and all the Rick and Morty fans and all the Harry Potter
fans. Sorry. I've been on a roll the last few weeks talking about everybody's favorite television
shows and movies that I thought would, but I'd never seen them. Nevermind. You've ruined my life.
Okay. I need to find little things. I apologize. Let me ask you a question though.
What I know that, okay, is there a show that if I, I feel like Rick and Morty has just,
has a ton of people that like it, are big fans, but a ton of people that hate it.
What's a show that has a bunch of people that just hate it? It's just, everybody doesn't like it.
Is there one game of Thrones? All right. Game of Thrones is pretty close. Got it. That's a tough
question. Oh my God. I'm feeling so terribly. Okay. I need, dude, big mouth, big mouth,
the big bang theory. No, I don't, dude, big bang theory has a ton of fans. That show lasted
almost 10 years. It had $600 trillion in revenue somehow. That show had a lot of fans. Okay.
There's one here. All right. Seven more. Riverdale. Riverdale. People saying Riverdale. Young
Sheldon. Oh, my sister was a real cool character. Me and my trains and my brother and my father.
That's how I know. Yup. Bingo. Bingo. There it is. Bingo. I knew it. I knew I could unite you all
in your collective hatred of me. I knew I could unite everybody. All right. Six more.
I was actually, me and Holly were talking about shows that we wanted to catch up with or watch.
I haven't seen any of Better Call Saul after season two. I want to watch a lot of that.
The boys season three is coming out, right? Which I don't know if I'm excited for it, but it's okay.
I was, I thought it was all right. I kind of want to see what happens. Boy season two was boring.
Yeah, that's, I mean, it was all right. It was just, season one was crazy. You want me to help
you? I gotta help this guy. Can I not help you? Can't break it. Barry's pretty good.
Barry was pretty good. Press E. Better Call Saul is the best. Did I just eat him? Oh, I just ate him.
Have you watched any good documentaries lately? I fell asleep through Supersize Me 2,
but that's not because the documentary wasn't bad or something. I just was really, really tired.
I love, you know what it is? YouTube has free movies where you just, they just ads,
just ad-supported movies. And it's just a bunch of weird old shit. I'll just pick one of those
and just watch it. You should watch The Expanse. Yeah, everyone's saying to watch The Expanse,
but isn't The Expanse just Rick and Morty for adults? I think I got them all over here.
Did I go this way? I did not. That's a great show. That's a great bait. What a troll. Yeah,
yeah, I know. The Expanse is actually Harry Potter for kids. Go fly. How come I'm not flying?
This is being completely uninformed and just talking out my ass. There are people that,
I know we talk about this and we fuck around, but there are probably people that have come to this
stream and have heard me say like, dude, this guy just said Dr. Who was fucking Rick and Morty.
I fucking hate this guy. I mean, that makes me sad in a way. This is going to be hard.
I got to hang. There we go. Okay. If you care enough about Dr. Who to get mad at that,
I need to fucking focus. Let me focus. So where, what's safe? Maybe I should just grab one of these.
Oh, yep. Got it. Oh yeah. All right. Only two more. Spot over here. The peak is over here.
Only one more after this. Hopefully I didn't miss any. It'd be very unhappy if I did.
19. One more. Toothstream? Oh, but what is a toothstream? Oh, you know what Holly brought
up yesterday that I didn't even realize? The old Scooby-Doo had a laugh track. That's so weird.
Cartoons had laugh tracks. Right here. Yes. I didn't miss any. Yeah, I did. Stop. I didn't
notice. No. Yeah, it had celebrity guests too. Here comes my impatience. All right. Slow down.
I'm a spider for God's sake. Like just, just do this. So much safer. Yeah. What are you doing?
There we go. Go to the peak. Save. I'm not. No. Why do you want me to say that? You want to clip
it so you can make me look like an idiot? Any more than 20? I know it's not an old idea,
but having a random laugh track to show up during the stream. I think it's kind of funny.
You already did that. Yeah, I know. Please save Bazinga. I got other people saying it.
What do you mean I got? Why does that mean? Hey, dude, I got other people to say it.
Oh, I move fast. I do. What am I doing? All right. I got to go to the peak. I've got 20.
Just wanted that last one. All right. Why does mates eat their heads? That's fucking weird.
All right. Almost there. Come on. I was right there, dude. Come on, dude. Come on, bro.
Praying mantis. I think a lot of bugs eat each other. Tons of bugs eat each other.
It's over here. Oh, hey again. Glad to see you took me up on the pollen quest.
Annabee's peak is just a bit further this way. Hope you don't. Hope you get the 20 we need.
The queen is waiting. I got it. I'm on it. Ants eat other ants. Yeah, it's weird.
God, ants are so weird. Bugs are so weird in general. I could tell you before.
Ants are just a math problem. Ants are math. The weird coordination. They're just a calculation.
Ants are math. They're almost a simple AI. It's really interesting. Reused bit.
Well, it's not reused because last time I did this bit, I think there were four or five
thousand people here. Now there's 50,000 in current viewers. My goodness. Thanks, guys.
Welcome to the stream. All right. We're almost there. Yeah. Just wait. Just wait for the
course it was got video where they're going to talk about bugs. Ants are math.
They're just a just a basic math problem. Whoa. This is cool. Look, it's the little spider.
Heard you've been helping out with the pollen quest. You got your 20 grains. Go on in.
Queen awaits. What does this get me? A new hat? Okay. 13.5 Andy.
All right. I heard so much about you. Have you brought the pollen for the princess royal jelly?
Yes, this shall make a powerful jelly. The new princess will be magnificent.
Wait here a moment while we prepare her. I'm sure she would love to meet you.
What do I actually get for doing this? Behold, your princess has arrived.
You're so beautiful. Such powerful wings. Thank you all for your hard labor preparing my royal jelly.
Dear spider, my mother told me of your predicament as I lay in my cell.
You're planning a rescue mission to a magic island in the sky. I can think of no greater
adventure with which to stretch my new wings. Come with me. I will take you home and help prepare
our voyage. Just eating my head. Nice hat. Thanks. We're going a long way. Okay. So what
what else do I need? Where the hell am I? Oh, here we are. All right. Did I get anything new?
Here's the rest of our free flight checklist. Talk to the princess about sealing up the balloon.
Okay. I need fuel. Okay. So I need fuel. Is the princess fixing this? Oh, there you are.
This is the balloon that's supposed to take us to the magic island in the sky.
It'll never make it in this condition. Let me fix that up for you. Prove this is your real hair.
See? This is real hair. But, uh, we shouldn't have any problems now. These wax patches are
completely airtight. All right. Cool. So now I need to have any fuel for the west.
So I need to go this way. Dung beetles, right? Cool. I saw the, I saw it. What do you mean?
I don't know what I was trying to do with that. Like I was trying to make it look like I had a
bald cap on or something. I don't know what that was. Weird. Okay. I want to go up this way.
Yeah. I was just moving my head back and forth. What the fuck was that? All right. This way.
This game's cute. This is a cute game. So go get fuel from the dung beetles. Huh? Did I miss my,
why am I back at this tutorial? Wrap around? Cause I need to go. Is there like a log to go
through or something? How do I get over there? Is there a log here? Um, how do I get over there?
I can't go over there. Maybe down into the left. There's a hole under the log. No help. You put
chicken fat in your hair. Down here? This is definitely it. Oh yeah. All right. Looking for
fuel for the hot air balloon. Oh shit. The speed run for this game is probably insane.
It probably is. Well, hold on. I, I can't breathe under there. Okay. So what am I looking for?
I can't grab onto any of this. So I got to move the rocks. Follow me. Here we go. I kind of,
I wonder how long, what's the speed run? Anybody know? What's the actual speed run? I can't get
up there. I can grab this. 16 minutes. Jesus. 16 minutes. That's so fast. I spent 16 minutes
stalling the start of my stream. Can't imagine completing this whole game in 16 minutes.
This level is cool because it's kind of just a lot of swinging. Swinging is fun. I feel like
there's such crazy tech with that too. With just the boom, boom, boom, boom. Make a thing to climb
on like that. And he's still moving. That's so cool. It takes my brain five seconds to go. I
can go there and there. There we go. There we go. Fluid. Fluid. Oh, be careful. I'm going in deep
here. How far up do I have to go? Oops. Oh, I have to launch this. I, yep. I think maybe eventually.
Okay. Let's try it. My eyes are so watery. Have I blinked in an hour? I think I'm in trouble here.
Wait, what's down here? Hmm. Can I pull this? I wonder what I'm supposed to do here. What do I do?
Oh, there we go. Kind of. Kind of. Yeah. Oh, get a launch. Launch. Launch. Swing. Up. Swing. Launch.
Launch. Swing. Launch. Ah! Swing and launch. There it is. Swing. Up. Launch. Okay. I'm getting
there. All right. Don't mess this up. Warning. Landslides. Bunker. Bunker. Oh my God. That scared
the shit out of me. Okay. What is that? Those are eggs. I don't know where I'm going. I'm just
sliding around. Mr. Sark is here. Oh, Mr. Sark is here. What's up, Sark? Hope you're doing well.
Mr. Sark is, I would say, one of the original funniest internet people in around a long time.
Maybe a lot of you don't know who Mr. Sark is. Oh, I would fix that immediately. Whoa. Hey there,
friend. Welcome to dung town. How do I get dung? Pushing a great big ball of dung is one of the
best workouts. Where do I get it? Fresh dung is the best dung. Where do I get it? What kind of dung
is it? Like cow shit? What do they use? You want some? You're in luck. We've got some friends with
loads of dung to share. It's not here. It's up the hill a fair way and there's one small problem
with getting up there. To the point. Look, we need to get across these puddles and I broke my wing
a while back. No flying means we're in need of a walking-based solution. I think you could use
your fancy web skills to string us a bridge out of them sticks. Help the beetles cross the puddles.
Okay. Done. Easy. Go. I got it. What do you guys want? I don't understand what they want.
They want a bridge? But how? I don't get it. I actually don't get it. They want me to make a
bridge but they can't walk a thing like this? Like just a basic little bridge? I don't understand.
Or do you mean pull these out of the water, make a bridge and then set these on top of the web?
No. You move out of the fucking way. You're just crowding me. Get out of the way. Stop the other.
What are you talking about? Wait, wait. I'm putting that, right? But then the log has to
go on top of those. On top of that. That's how this works. That's the only way it can work,
right? He's pretending. I can't make a bridge with two sticks. There's not enough. I need more
sticks. I need like 10 of these. How many? What? Look at that guy. How am I going to walk across
this? Look, these guys are so huge. The third log. How are they going to get across this one?
They're going to be stranded. Now what? He's almost. They said make us a nice bridge with your web.
All right, bros. Step on it. Go. Step on it then. What do you want me to do?
Hey, you fixed the bridge. Go. Yeah. Go ahead. You fucking idiots. That was not, that was,
that was fucked up. Yeah, please. That was fucked up.
That was fucked up. That was just like, he just mushed over all that.
I'm not soft-locked. Why are you being so toxic? I'm not being toxic. I'm being realistic. This
is, this is not toxic to say, dude, what are you? Go up. I need to move this big one over there now,
right? Because they're not going to go over there unless it's there. Is there one over the other
side? Stop yelling at them. Can I go under? I thought I was going to have to do that iPad game
where you make the whole bridge with the web. I thought I was going to have to do shit like this.
You know what I mean? Like connect the, make a bridge with the web and relax. You just relax.
Yes, bridge constructor. That's what I thought I was going to have to do. Okay. Go ahead and
cross it. What kind of bullshit is this? What? Just, just float. Just float. You know what, dude?
Just go. I promise you. Go. Why won't you go? Why won't he go? Give it a go. Yep. Go. You're,
he's there, right? Why won't, I don't, why wouldn't he go? All right, go ahead.
Tell him Wendy and Michael sent you.
Tell the Beatles and I got some dung.
Very nice. All right. So now I've got dung. I have fuel. Am I ready to go? What else is left?
You did that in the worst possible way. It's all right. It says to get done.
Ask yourself a question. Did the dung beetle get across the lake unharmed? That was the goal.
Yes. Does it matter how? Does it matter that the goal happened? Dung beetle gets across the
body of water completely unharmed. That's it. Was there like a dung beetle king or queen or
something? Cause I'm going all the way up. Look at this. What else is up here? It's kind of cool.
I don't care. What have I scaled the whole dung mountain? Is there a reliable fast way to get
back by the way? No secret. Come on. What is all the way over here? Oh Jesus. Hold on. Hey.
I don't actually, I'm not going to go to the whole thing, right? There's more to do
all the way up. Can you do a twerk stream? I don't think I would have to do a whole stream for that,
man. I think I just do that in five seconds. I think I have to weigh this down. No, don't.
Come here. I definitely have to put weight on this, right? What does this do? Okay. Oh,
all right. All the way, all the way. I wonder. Whoa. Hold on now. Don't go anywhere. What's the
point of that? I don't see anything here. What's the point of that? He probably could twerk if
he tried. It's going to take a hundred million dollars for me to twerk on stream. That's right.
There you go. Most of the peak you already did. What the fuck is this? How come I can't show this?
I can't like save that. Oh, here we go. Try this one. This isn't twerking though. It is twerking.
What? That was like a twerk. Yeah. Why does it sound like this is times? What speed is this?
It is slowed down. Hey, can you twerk? Yeah. That's fine. Whatever. I don't care. Being a handful of
beans. He admits it. He needs a glove. What the hell is he doing?
All right. I'm getting to the top of dung mountain. I know it's getting late. I feel like I'm pretty
close to the end of the game though. Yeah. Impromptu like 7 PM Pacific stream. And I do apologize for
that. Don't know why I'm not streaming tomorrow. And I decided to stream right now at 7 PM,
four hours ago or so, because I have to take Otto to the vet tomorrow. I'm going to get him checked
out. Just a couple of things. I want to make sure that he's good to go and I want to get him in.
So I'm going to be doing that tomorrow. We're doing house flipper pet DLC on Saturday and then Sunday
we're doing blood wash and the other horror game murder house. Or we might do that on Saturday and
then do pets on Sunday. Depends on how I feel. Keep us updated. Oh, I will. He's fine. Don't worry.
He's fine. I would tell you if I was actually concerned and I am not. So he's completely fine.
Yeah. Sorry. It's we started late and are going late. Still going here. I hope there's a fast
way to get back because I'm going across the whole damn game right now. God slow down. I just thought
of this picture again and it's like making me laugh. I just thought of this picture.
It's just flashed in my brain and I had to look at it again. I need to get to the top of Dung
Mountain even if it's a stupid just achievement or something. All right. Here we go. I made it.
Howdy, spider. Wendy and Mike sent you, did they? You must be here for the bounty of dung.
We got some for you right on over here. My problem is this dung is a little too comforting.
Our lazy son is simply refusing to leave the ball. It's so hot out there. Why would I want to leave?
Spider, it's all yours if you can convince him to get out and see a bit of the world.
Give it a little push. Oh, hang on. Hang on. Hang on. So this is the fast way to get back.
That makes sense. Hang on. They make it. Nice. I got the fuel. You're going to kill him. He's
fine. It's padding. Did I seriously just get kicked out of my home? I'll just have to live
here now, I guess. Help yourself to some dung. It's my favorite. Very energy dense. Okay. How
much do I need? How many balls of dung do I need? Can you come grab this? Oh, it's coming all the
way down. All right. How many balls should I do? One or two? I'll try. I'll try to grab one. No.
All right. Send it up. No. Okay. Now you just fuck with me. Get up there. Dung. Here we go.
Where do I need to put it? Okay. Am I ready to go? Okay. Now the dung is to go in underneath
there, right? Grab the dung. Dung in the cup. That's what I'm trying to do. Okay. Here's the
rest of the checklist. Attach engine immediately below the mouth of the balloon. Burn the secret
pilot platform to balloon. Just follow the blueprints. Fuel in the engine. Engine up into
here. It's patched up. Spider web this all. I'm ready to go. Okay. Now we stick this in here.
That's good. So now I have to attach this. Let's click in there already. Click in there. Why is
it not clicking in there? Come on. Do like a... It doesn't click in. Oh, well it's in. All right.
It's in. Now I need webs. I'm ready to fly. Are you ready to head out? Okay. So I got that done. I
need to go turn in the bugs. Why did it fall? This doesn't look safe. Retach it. Turn up the music
for the finale. Okay. We did it. Engine normal. Airspeed increasing. This is it. We're flying.
Engine nominal. Airspeed increasing. This is it. We're flying. What if I cut the strings? You can't.
Oh, dude. Fuck it. Let's get the skateboard out. No, not the board, bro. The ship is holding on
barely. I got it. We're fine. Mayday? What the fuck is that? I don't know. These are like asteroids.
It's gems. How do I collect the gems? Well, this storm was not on the forecast. The ship is still
holding out. The wind is really picking up now. I feel so alive. Uh-oh. Stay safe. We'll keep the
engine running for you. It was all fucked up. I had to fix it. This is it. The Sky Bower. The
airship won't be able to make it any further in the storm. You'll have to continue without us.
Go find your love. We'll meet you on the other side. This is the crow place. He says uh-oh,
like a toddler who shit his pants. Uh-oh. Oh, no. Up in the sky area. This is kind of loud.
Do I have to take this with me or something? Where do I go? Is that break? Um, what? Oh, okay.
All right. I get it. Yeah, this is gonna be a pain in the ass, isn't it? A little, a little loud
for me. Nothing down there. All right. Let's just go here. I'm here. Where is it? Up there. Shit.
Get over here. We're good. Oh, shit. Oh, will you please? Come on. Oh, my God. Boy. Okay. All
right. I made it. I got it. I got it. I need the ball. Where's the ball? Where's the ball?
Where's the ball? I left the ball. Are you kidding me? Where? I didn't leave the ball.
Where's the ball? Am I soft-locked? Huh? Holy shit. That was 100 IQ. Yes. Okay. Let me take a look.
What's over here? A lot of bullshit. Where are you going? Go in. Go in. Go in. I'm almost there.
There's gonna be two, isn't there? Oh, God. Where is it? Okay. There's one here. All right.
Just go underneath. I don't need to. Should be fine. Come with me. There it is. Thank you.
And open the door. Not bad. I made it. Do I have to fight the crow? I don't want to really fight.
I like crows. And oh, shit. Escape the skybower with your boyfriend. I found you. Can we get out
of here? All right. Come with me. We got to go. We got to go now. Come on. We got to go now.
We got to go now. We got to go now. Oh, okay. You got any of those gems anywhere? I need a gem.
Is your head made out of gems? What? Oh, I think I saw the crow. Can you get up here?
Nope. I got you. I got you. Watch out. Okay. You're good.
You make it. Come on. Holding Q is kind of hard in doing W-A-S-T. What's wrong? Get over here, you
dummy. What the? You settle the fuck down. Like, honestly, God, settle the fuck down. Really?
That was so outrageous. That was so over the top. That was fucking horrible for me. I don't know
why. Why is that so bad? That wasn't even a tuber reaction. That was like, I just, I really did not
think that was going to happen for any reason. That was so bad. Why did I get scared so bad?
It was the music too. Yo, you scared my bird. Oh, let's hear what they have to say. Oh, wow.
A lot to say that bird. Wow. One of my mods is saying when you screamed, that made my discord
lag for some reason. Will you get up here? We could have already been through the stupid
jump scare part. Follow me. Just get bird boy technique. You know what? I'm done. I don't think
this does anything. Whoa. Shit. Wait. Can you go through spider silk? Yeah. Right down here.
Get down here, quick. Rush his face. Aha. Good. Hurry before he sees us. Hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry,
hurry. Before he sees us. Oh my God. Damn it. That was, this thing's scary. Where'd he go?
Oh my God. Come back, come back, come back, come back, come back. I thought that was, I didn't
think it was a wall. Oh, good thing I, I, I got his mouth. I got his mouth sucked, sucked, sewed,
got whatever. No, come on. I don't know what I need to attach it to. We go now. You fucking
kidding me? I can't. Get over here. Out of sight, out of sight, out of sight, out of sight. I don't
know where he is. Yeah. I knew he's going to be like right here. God. Bro, let's press the button,
man. What the hell are you doing? Can you hold this? What do I do? I'm afraid to go up here.
See? That's terrifying. Oh, that was right there. Shit. Just clear everything. Clear the whole
fucking thing. Essentially what I wanted. All right, now pull that down. Don't kill me. What?
Why did it not land on the web? Click. Hurry up. Wait, don't go fast. He's going to be right here,
isn't he? Hey, back up. Good. Little Spider, you made it and you've rescued your boyfriend.
We're almost ready to go home. Vlad is just bringing the airship around now. Wait, he's
coming. Watch out. What? Hold on, Little Spider. We're going to catch this bird.
Defeat the bird. Help, help, help, help. Whoa. Whoa. He's fucking dead. Sorry we're late. Just
picked up a little help on the way. Hey, neighbor. MechAnt1 reporting for duty. This beast doesn't
stand a chance. Coming in close now. I'm already dead. I hit the ground already. Let's do this.
What do you want me to do? I didn't read that. I didn't read that. What did I have to do? I
didn't read it. I'm in position. Get clear. Attaching MechAnt1. We're going to fight his
head off. Okay, we did it. Now we can let go. We did it. The beast is grounded. What should we do
with him now, comrade? We send him away. You hear me, bird? You burnt all your bridges here.
The bugs of this bush will not put up with you eating and kidnapping their friends.
Now we have the means to defend ourselves. We need to find a new land to call home.
Maybe somewhere far away from here with more birds like you. Maybe somewhere you can finally
find a friend. But you leave now or I change my mind. Oh my, that was scary. I wasn't sure I'd
be able to talk to him, but I did it. Thank you, buddy. Thank you too, buddy's boyfriend.
Your brave actions gave me the courage to finally send up to that menace. Home is a little bit safer
today thanks to you. I did it. That was fun. Nice job. That was fun. All right, but wait,
this is the post-season credits. He doesn't know. I wish this game had music. I turned it down, man.
We should watch the speed run. What's the, uh, one of the mods link, uh, the world record? I'm
curious. I'm the second place runner as of a few days ago. Rip. Oh, wow. That's still pretty,
that's still awesome though. I mean, that's still, it's ridiculous. World record 1631. Is it any
percent or do you, uh, just any percent? Well, hold on. This is cute. And you as buddy the spider.
How come that bird's so nice? Why was the crow so mean? Why was the marshmallow one so nice? Oh,
hold on. Baby? Baby? Is that a baby spider? What is it? A baby? Oh, it's babies. A lot of babies.
Where do we go now? Very cool. What's through here? Is it just free roam now? It's probably
just free roam. Oh, hold on. So do you get a, what do I get for this? Give me a hat.
Yeah. Let me put the speed run on. I'm very curious about this. It's just, I have to watch
the whole thing. We do not have to watch the whole thing. It's only 16 minutes. Hold on. Let's get
it. Let's get a good view. So you, you use propulsion. What the fuck? What? You just throw
yourself down and you use the laser for propulsion. I can't even tell what's happening. Wow. This is
really a pretty, I would say this is probably a pretty good speed running game, right? There's
not a whole lot of, it's a lot of just go get that thing and put it over here. Do you even
have to help anybody? Actually, to get the, I think you have to. To get the, to get the
heart rate balloon, right? The whole lot. Does, does the movement speed stack? Does it have a
cap? Or can you just actually fly and throw yourself around? Oh, look at that. About getting a good
angle in the central mechanic. Yeah. This is definitely a speed running game. What the hell
was that? What? This is an actual spider. Yeah. This really is an actual spider. I'm curious about
the, that. Wow. That was close. That's so cool. All right. What about, I want to see up here.
Put on break core. I want to see one of these down. I want to see what happens at the end here.
So you just, you just, you just drag. Dude, what? How are you even supposed to do that?
All right. That was pretty cool. All right. Here comes the fight with the bird. How do you do this
fast? Oh, you guys can't even hear it. What? Wait, what, what just happened? Don't you have to web
the bird? It's a skip. Wow. Well, there it is. Well, congratulations. This is your world record.
That's really cool. That's so cool. This game's got some bugs in it. Time that person up for an
hour. Yeah. Link to the speed run. Yeah. We'll link the speed run. Here is a link to the world record.
If you'd like to take a look. The video that was just on screen. That's really cool. All right. I
think that's it. We get a baseball update. July 14th. July 14th. Mark it on your calendar.
Baseball is going to be July 14th. Yeah. I don't want to go too, too late. Impromptu stream here.
Supposed to be streaming tomorrow, but schedule getting changed. I got to take care of Otto.
So we'll see you later. We'll see you again. I will see you guys on Saturday. We'll do Saturday,
Sunday. And we're going to, we'll go a little longer. The last two days in a row have been
four hour, four and a half hour here. I'd like to stream for at least five to seven hours. So we
will do some long ones this weekend. Four hour Andy. That was a cute game. I like that a lot.
That was requested for a while too. That's fun. Oh, right. Sorry. Sorry to every sci-fi fantasy
fan of any show ever. I feel like you lost a little bit of respect for me tonight.
Very sorry. I want to profusely apologize. Very sorry about that. We have a lot of fun here,
don't we? Show the image again. This is the one that I still have. It queued up. I really thought
that you mashed these two together. I don't know. I haven't seen like really much of either.
I mean, I've seen Rick and Morty. All right. I'll see you guys later. Thanks for watching.
See you soon. See you Saturday. I will give you an auto update. He's going to be fine.
I just want to check him out for a couple of things. Things that are
at least concerning enough for me to want him to go to the vet. So, but he's fine.
I'll give you an update. Good luck, Otto. Yeah. Good luck, Otto. Otto. Thanks for the subs.
Thanks for the bits. A lot of subs were coming in today. A lot of community subs.
That was a good, yeah, it was just fun. I really like these experiences. Games that are between
three and five hours. They're almost perfect. I love these little bite size experiences.
Hope you had fun. I did. Small experiences for a small man. I'm very, I'm actually kind of nervous
for Dextreme because it's going to be a brand new audio setup, but I'm going to sound completely
different. You guys are going to have to give me some feedback. I need to know how it sounds,
good or bad. What's the schedule? Saturday at 4 p.m. Pacific is the next live stream on this
channel. Get some sleep. Take care of yourselves. Call your mother, you know, as usual. He said
that like four streams in a row now. Yeah, Saturday at 4 p.m. Pacific. Good night. Take care of
yourselves and goodbye.