How you doing? What's happening?
I cleared my throat right before talking to you, and that's the worst.
You know anything you're just ready to talk?
This happens sometimes when I answer a phone call too.
Milk voice? Did you say milk voice? What the hell? That's weird.
I know exactly what that means. I don't even like drink milk anymore. I don't even like milk.
That is weird.
All right. Anyways, right before you answer a phone call, you go...
Don't ring me for salt. Don't ring me for salt.
Hello? And then you answer and say that.
You get like prepared, and then you answer the phone call.
But after that, it sucks when you do all that.
So your phone starts ringing, and you go...
You can do this. You can do this. You can do this. You can do this.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hello? Hello?
I hate it. It's the worst.
Next game? What?
What?
I'm just fucking around. Why does everybody take everything I say so seriously?
You know what I mean? Why are you so serious, Batman?
I'm fucked up today. I'm in a really weird mood.
And I think the reason why I'm in such a weird mood today is because
there's a whole hands worth of olives sitting next to me, and I'm gonna put them on my fingers, I guess.
As I was buying the olives, and as I was walking around, and as I was getting prepared for the stream,
every five to six minutes, I'd say,
who am I doing this for? It's not for me.
Because I don't care, right? I like don't care about putting olives on my fingers.
It's one person said this. One person.
Why do I do this? I don't even... Why do I do this?
I don't care either. I don't know why. I don't know. Yeah, exactly.
Does anybody here actually want to see this? I don't think anybody cares.
But we're doing it anyways.
And I'm not going to do it till there's at least 10,000 people here.
I know. I'm like, what a psycho. An egomaniac.
No, I'm not going to eat olives off my fingers unless there's 10,000 people here watching.
Anyways, today, probably saw the title. I'm going to play Thief Gold.
Give you a short story here. Thief Gold has been installed.
Well, not installed. It's been purchased.
And in my, you should stream this list.
Uh, for probably three or four years.
Since I was back in Massachusetts, I just kind of looked at it today.
I was like, fine, I'll put it on the poll. Why not?
And it won. So, uh, this is the GOG version.
Yes, this is not the Steam version.
This is somebody said, do you collect trinkets around your house pretending to be a goblin,
laughing as you throw them into a sack? Why would I do that in my own house?
No, in your house is where you start counting the things you took.
I took the goblet. I took the treasure chest.
I took the gold coins. I don't put them back in the sack.
I count them. Why would I do that?
I've already put them in the sack. I took the urinal.
Uh, I took the urinal. Yeah.
What a shitty, that, what like, that sucks.
What am I going to do with that? What would I do with that?
That's just stupid. You converted it into a fan.
That thing's nice. In fact, thanks for reminding me.
I'm going to turn it on now. I'm turning my rotating urinal on
because I want some air. It's got a filtering.
Do you know that? This has got like an air filter
baked into this, in the middle and inside of it.
And it sucks air in through the filter and then blows it off the top.
It's actually pretty cool. And there's no, there's no fan on it.
It's a fanless fan. Need an olive on stream.
I'm just, hold on. I just turned it on.
All right. So we're talking, you want like the,
hold on. I got to, I got to go on campus.
But you want, what you want is you want,
you talking about like, I get it on my hand and I go like,
right? That's what you want. Like one, two, three, four, five, right?
That's what you're looking for. I think that's what you want.
Can I even get these on? It's going to be hard.
We're moving on real quick from this too, by the way.
This is like, I'm not spending more than a minute on this.
I can't, how am I supposed to do it on both hands?
I just broke one. Fucking hit the goddamn ground
and it's your fault. You did this to me.
All right. Look, my fingers.
I, it hit the ground. I can't, these ones have like pimento in them.
I can't put these on my finger. I mean, I can.
I don't care. Is that the one that hit the ground?
I got the wrong olives. I don't know anything about olives.
What do you think I know? Anything about olives?
Why would I know anything about olives?
Hey dude, you got the wrong olives. Oh yeah. Oh, sorry.
There's like fucking 40 cases at the grocery store.
I can't get them on all my fingers. You can just Photoshop it.
Here, look. I got the wrong olives.
Ego, ready? Like, oh, that looks gross.
Oh, okay. What is pimento?
Your hand's too big or they're too small? I don't know.
They're just olives. I just got like olives.
I didn't know. This is this black olives.
This is green olives. Black olives are like cut into rings sometimes.
Is that what you meant? I just bought olives at the grocery store.
I don't know. I got one. I got two on my fingers.
What the fuck is he doing? I don't, I, you know, and that's exactly why we're done.
I just used one of my dog wipes. These are actually dog wipes.
I'm not kidding. These are dog grooming wipes.
Like, wipe on his paws. No deal? I didn't even make a deal.
I don't even care if I don't have, what do you mean deal?
I don't care. I was just like, I'm gonna, I'm gonna try to put them on.
You got scammed? There was no scam. There's no deal.
I just, somebody said, put olives on your fingers and go like,
hoo hoo hoo at the screen. And I was like, okay, I guess I'll do it. Why?
Put an olive on each nostril. No, because that's fucking weird.
That's like, I don't know. I don't, no, not happening.
I don't even like olives. I like olive oil, but like olives are like a little too acidic.
You considered it? I did because it's stupid.
And, but like that's childish, right? It's childish.
It's, it's childish. It's what it is. It's, it's, it's like, oh, look at it.
It's like I got olives in my nose.
Clowns don't even do that at children's birthday parties.
Nobody should ever do that. No one should ever do something like that.
Sneeze out the olives. Yeah, that's just weird.
Why would somebody, why would anybody do that?
Anyways, we're going to play, there you go.
The one, for the one person that said put olives on your fingers and eat them.
I don't know what that was for, but there, yeah, I got the wrong olives.
A scam? I mean, maybe I'll put it on for a little bit,
but I got to move it though. It's in the wrong spot.
Actually, well, who cares? Doesn't matter.
Because I can crop it, but we're going to play thief.
Drop this here. That looks all right.
I don't, you know what? I don't like forward-facing face cam.
I feel like I'm in like an interview with you, right?
Oh, I feel like you're inside the monitor and it's weird.
I like an angle because it's like you're, you're like over here.
You're not just like literally staring in my eyes like here.
I don't know. I don't like forward-facing webcam.
All right. Well, whatever. We're going to move this out of the way.
I'm going to, let me just move the camera in case I want to use it for any reason.
I'm going to play thief, thief gold. It's the GOG version.
I don't know anything about this game. No, nothing at all.
Move the pair of underwear that's on the ground over here.
So you don't see it. I don't want you to see the underwear that I have on the ground.
Don't worry about it. Close my door.
All right. Let's go.
Why is there underwear in your office? I don't know.
Because I was probably like doing laundry or something.
All right. Is it in a good spot? Tell me. Not really.
Oh, should I have a ring light? I can turn, no, it hurts my eyes.
I don't want to use it. All right.
We got pretty much everybody's here. We can get going.
Thief gold. Make sure I'm comfortable.
I need to, no, you know what? I got to get, these olives are going to smell
and it's going to make me fucking gag.
Put the ring light around your neck.
If I put the ring light around my neck, I, it could actually fit.
That would be fucking stupid.
Oh, don't, don't stall this stream any more than it has to be.
Please let me just play thief.
That's so stupid. I think my, no, what if I get stuck?
What if I get stuck and I have to like go get it, go until I get it removed?
What if I get stuck? No, I might get stuck.
I think I could get it in there, but what if I, what if I can't get it out?
If I get stuck, I'm 36. Okay.
I can't make those mistakes anymore.
I can't put my head in a ring light and blame it on like, like, oh man, you know,
I, it's just, I was in college and we were drinking Bud Light and I was like,
yeah, you know, give me the ring light. I'll put it, I'm 36.
I'm an older man now. I can't do that.
I can't go to like the emergency room and like blame it on like the fucking Bud Reds
we were all drinking, like having a fun, just hanging out and like put it around.
No, no, no, I could, that's dangerous.
Just tell the nurse that you're famous.
What, who cares?
Oh yeah, see, I'm famous. That's why I put a ring light around my head and got stuck.
What does that, what does that have to do with anything?
Like the idiocy is still just the same as if I had one viewer or 10,000.
All right, let's go.
I'm imagining the drunk guy that just comes in.
Yeah, sorry. Yeah, I'm famous by the way.
Famous where?
Get out of my college dorm room.
It's the same. It's the same exact argument.
Yeah, they call, they call me fucking crazy, crazy Bill, pretty famous.
No, I'm not doing it. Maybe I'll see if I can put my head in there.
Not today though. On the next stream, if it's safe, I'll do it.
All right, turn this shit off.
All right, we're going to play thief.
Are you ready?
Oh, I'm famous.
Well, then you should, you should probably know better.
Like what you, you hold on.
You're telling me that you showed an audience of like 15,000 people.
Ha ha ha, look how funny it is.
I just got my head stuck in a light.
You should be way more responsible.
What are you talking about?
All right, we're gonna play thief.
I'll do face cam eventually, maybe in like 10 minutes.
How hard is this game? Is this game hard?
Tell me the truth. Tell me the truth.
Is this a hard game?
Yeah, if chat is good, I'll turn the face cam on.
Only if you're good though.
And you, I, I knew, and you better prove it.
Start training normal heart.
Not playing this on export.
I'm not playing it on hard either.
Not happening.
My arms are too high.
What's going on here?
I don't know. I need to be.
There we go.
I'm going to be higher than chair.
There it is. Okay.
All right, start training.
I don't know how to play.
I'm playing on normal.
I'm not playing on hard.
It's a boomer stealth game.
Oh God, the essence of balance is detachment.
To embrace a cause to grow fond or spiteful is to lose one's balance.
After which no action can be trusted.
A burden is not for the dependent of spirit.
I'm Maillard, third keeper.
I was a kid.
No parents, no home.
Running messages and picking pockets to keep my ribs from meeting my spine.
One night I saw a man.
Folks just passed him by like he wasn't there.
I thought he must have something valuable.
So I snuck up on him and made a grab.
That's not for you.
Please sir, I'm hungry.
Don't tell the hammers.
I promise.
What is your name, boy?
Garrett.
You have talent lad.
Let go of me old man.
To see a keeper is not an easy thing.
Especially one who does not wish to be seen.
We have a need for those as gifted as yourself.
If you've grown tired of how you live then follow me and we will show you a different way.
It's worth paying for a young actor to do this.
I caught up with him just before he vanished into the crowd.
It was the beginning of a very long education.
This is always the problem I have with audiobooks too.
I like I don't reading I don't reading is fine, right?
You can kind of make up your own voices and stuff.
But anytime you listen to an audiobook and the it's usually just one person
who reads the whole book and they'll typically do voices for everybody.
And it's usually like if they get to like a young character
or a higher character with a much higher pitched voice that they think.
And when they have a conversation with themselves it's always funny.
It's like I didn't want to do that.
I didn't want to go there.
Well you you had to at school is very important.
As she said leaning down it's always kind of feels off somehow.
But that can almost add to the charm in a way.
But I like to make up my own voices in my head when they when they do it.
That's literally you.
That's what I'm saying.
All right normal follow the directions of your instructor
in order to pass the training tests.
I use your last chance to make it not normie.
Instruct you in the various skills you will need to survive.
Please stay in the entrance area to each room while I explain the room's purpose.
When you are ready to begin your lessons proceed down this hallway to the first room.
Who's walking?
What if I'm not ready?
Are those health?
Why do I have like little health icons?
Um hold on a minute.
This is freaking me out.
What are these controls?
Wait wait wait wait what's happening?
I'm gonna puke.
Okay A and S is not strafe.
It's look left and right.
W and W is walk forward.
What's going on here?
Holding S walks me forward.
It's tank controls?
No it's not.
I need to rebind the keys.
Forward.
W walk forward.
Shift?
Is it shift?
Backwards is X.
Oh my goodness.
X no S.
Backwards S.
Why okay.
Slide left Z.
It should be A right.
Slide right is D.
What why what's going on?
Turn left slide to the right slide to the left.
Okay turn left is fine.
That can be keyboard.
Turn right look up page center.
The view is V.
Lean left Q and E is fine.
Toggle crouch F.
What are you what drugs are you taking?
C jump empty space.
Attack mouse one use item.
Is there a okay mouse two.
No no no block use item mouse three.
Block who made these controls?
Block speed toggle.
What's that mean?
Speed toggle like run and walk.
R slide on alt.
Free look is it sprint?
Speed talk next item.
These are all empty drop item G.
Free look I don't know like this thing.
Next item can I do scroll?
Oh okay I can wait.
Should I even do that though?
Previous item scroll a little up.
Clear item backspace next weapon.
Previous weapon oh I don't care.
Clear weapon who cares.
Sword blackjack arrow water arrow fire.
What is all this magical shit?
I thought I was a stealer.
Rope healing potion F1.
Breath potion F2.
What is this Listerine?
What are you talking about?
Breath potion holy water F3.
Some of you guys just help me out whatever.
Square toothed lockpick.
Triangle toothed lockpick.
Flash bomb gas mine compass.
View map M objective O hold the crunch.
Control jump slash block keyboard insert.
Gamma gamma rays.
Gamma plus lean forward W alt shift quick save.
All right we know what quick save is.
Take a screenshot.
Increase main volume decrease volume.
I'm just gonna play.
Okay at least like the basic controls are fine.
You must learn.
Okay I'll just see.
The indicator on your screen will tell you how visible you are.
Reach the top of the platform scene.
Okay top of the platform.
Where's the top of the platform?
So just don't be seen by this guy.
I see you there lad.
He's literally facing the other way.
What his head is facing the door.
I see you then.
He's not even looking this way.
He's looking at the door.
He's literally facing the other direction.
But just because I'm in the shade he can't see me.
Oh he's not he's looking this way.
All right so get to the top of the platform.
So I gotta get behind him.
Well done.
I did not see you approach.
Open this door to continue.
What?
When the door is near the center of your screen it will light up.
Indicating that it is selected.
Okay.
To manipulate selected doors and other objects use them.
That's bad.
Mouse three to use.
What a dumb idea.
Proceed down this corridor for your next test.
Are you sprint?
You can check your map at any time.
Does the show where?
Oh no please.
No no no no no.
It doesn't give you like a you are here in the mall.
Oh this is bad.
I guess I'm right here.
You must learn to move.
Some surfaces are louder than others when walked upon.
And moving quickly makes more noise than moving slowly.
Okay don't walk on like the glass.
Listen to your own footsteps to hear how much noise you are making.
The instructor will have his back turn.
You must get to the top of the platform without being heard.
Isn't he the instructor?
All right so just don't step on that.
That probably makes noise.
Do you didn't hear me?
Very good.
I did not hear you traverse the room.
Grab him by his top of his head and bottom of his head and just twist.
That will lead you to your next task.
What?
They're gonna teach me how to kill people like whoa.
To pick up objects select them by centering them on screen until they light up.
I got a weapon.
Then use them.
Choose your weapon now.
Try readying your sword and then your bow.
You can hold.
You can always put them away again if you need your hands free.
I feel like I'm in VR.
This is a VR moment.
Where is he?
I can't get him.
Oh he's over here.
Ow!
He didn't make the noise but you know.
Ready your bow.
Knock an arrow and draw back the string by holding down the attack button.
Make sure you draw all the way back or your shot will not have full power.
Take aim.
Nice.
When you are ready to shoot release your attack.
See if you can hit one of these targets.
That mouse sensitivity drops a lot.
Did I miss every shot?
What?
Wait a minute.
Did I miss every shot?
What's happening?
Turn around.
Oh good shot.
Keep practicing if you wish.
When you are ready to proceed approach the training dummy and ready your sword.
Head shot.
Ready your sword.
Swing at the target with the attack button.
A quick tap will give you a slash.
Move the tip of your sword to the left of the target for a left slash and to the right
of the target for a right slash.
Nice.
Then release for an overhead swing.
Try both slashes and the overhead swing on the practice dummy.
You can tell how good you're doing based on the cartoon sound effects.
Ready for a live opponent.
Practice against your partner.
Enter the cobbled sparring area.
The more it sounds like Scooby Doo the better you know you're doing.
You want to go?
Wait is this the trainer?
Hack him with your sword.
Wait did I just get disqualified?
His ears are ringing right now.
Oh I can block right?
Yep.
Oh we're not actually fighting.
It's right in the teeth.
Alright let's go.
Leave me alone.
That's enough sparring for today.
Well he's following me.
Let's walk over to the table.
He's literally following me.
Get away from me.
That was just like the me and my little brother were in a little bit of a fight
before we came to dinner and we just got called to dinner and I was like
I gotta get one more.
Coming mom.
Shut up idiot.
Okay so now what?
Why are you following me around?
How do we open this?
Open this.
Open the door.
Go to the table?
What table?
Would you care for some refreshment before you move on young Garret?
Apple.
Please pick up all of the items on this table.
Cycle through your inventory to see the objects you have in your pocket.
Apple.
Compass.
Once an object is displayed you may use it.
Healing potion.
Alright.
Have something to eat if you wish.
Then you may proceed.
The next test is waiting on the other side of the metal door.
Okay.
I have a compass too.
How do I use it?
Oh it's just up.
The door is locked.
But the key from the table will open it.
To unlock the door select the key in your inventory.
Center the door on screen until it lights up.
Then use the key on the door.
Good.
Now head down this hallway to get to your next test.
What's the next test?
Apples are nice.
Well only one kind of apple is worth eating in my opinion.
Well two.
Green or Macintosh.
The rest are dog shit.
First climb the rope by jumping onto it.
Move while looking up or down to climb up or down the rope.
So you can look up?
Turn to change your places.
Okay it's not S.
If you jump again you will release the rope.
Now climb the rope to get to the top of the platform.
Well done.
Run and jump across the gap to the other side of the stream.
I feel like I'm not running fast enough.
Is this how fast I can go?
Good jump.
This obstacle is easy to climb if you know how.
First move close to the wall.
Next jump to grab the edge of the wall and pull yourself up.
Good job.
I am most pleased with your progress.
I just breathed on it.
All right.
If you wish you may stay to practice your climbing and jumping.
Or swimming, ducking, leaning or crawling.
Okay this ball damaged.
You may return to your chambers by going through that red door.
Farewell.
Okay so it's jump.
Let go.
All right let's do it.
The keepers were training me to be one of them.
Mushroom.
Other uses for those.
Oh shit mushroom.
Eat it.
What is that?
What happened?
Wait what what wait no I wanted to explore.
All right so now I'm an expert thief.
You didn't explore don't need to explore the tutorial.
Well I just wanted to see I was just curious.
Where are my parents?
I don't know.
The most promising acolyte left us.
Not out of the lesser folly of sentiment but the greater folly of anger.
His heart was clouded and his balance was lost but his abilities were unmatched.
Even then we knew to match watch him most carefully.
Keeper.
Annals.
Stealing is wrong.
I have a simple job planned for this evening.
Break into a guarded mansion.
Break into a mansion.
Steal another fat nobleman's priceless trinket.
Steal a trinket and leave quietly.
Lord Bafford is out of town and rumor has it that the captain of his house guard went
with him as a bodyguard.
The time is ripe for a bit of burglary.
All right.
The front gate of Lord Bafford's manor is always guarded and the main street is far to expose.
Sounds like the guy in Hitman 3.
The constant.
Miss Burnwood.
Up floor.
All I need is to give you two bricks.
Give me two bricks.
An extra large heel.
And a fucking ski mask.
I'll get what you need.
I'll get up there and get that trinket.
Sneak into Lord Bafford's manor and case the place.
Well house in back is your best bet if you can get the key from the guard.
Lackjacking or pickpocketing him would be quietest.
Find the prized scepter and redistribute it to yourself.
Try to do it without causing too much commotion.
All right so I gotta get into the manor.
There's a well house out the back.
I can get the key from the guard or just all right I gotta get in there.
Starting gear.
I got a blackjack, a sword, an archery healing potion, water arrow.
Water arrow does not do any damage but it douses torches and other burning.
Okay that's really important.
What is blackjack?
This weapon will knock out an unsuspecting target with little noise and no blood.
Oh okay.
All right let's go.
Where am I?
Watch.
Okay watch for interior patrols.
There's the front entrance.
This is heavily guarded.
Do not try frontal assault.
Arrow cache pickup en route to the second floor.
One guard.
This well leads to the basement.
Basement entrance.
Okay we're gonna try to go to the basement.
So I gotta go to the right here this way.
I drew this map I hope it helps.
Is it illegal for me to like be right here?
No I haven't done anything illegal.
All right I haven't done anything illegal though.
So like it's okay that I.
All right so that's the front door.
Go in the front.
It's three guards.
I don't think let me try let me see if let me go to the well.
It's a well out back.
There's a cheese factory.
I can't go in there.
All right here's the here's the underground well.
You can't fight all these people at once.
I mean I can but it's probably bad.
All right where am I at?
There's one guard.
I'm okay here's the well.
That's where I am right now.
So there's a guard here.
Basement entrance.
The well leads to the basement waterway.
Basement waterway.
I got it.
All right cool.
I have to save the game.
Well that would have been a fucking disaster.
Where's the uh blackjack?
All right I can so this thing.
Or this thing you just whack somebody's head.
All right this will go up to the basement.
Is anybody here?
This doesn't look like a basement.
What's this way?
Oh okay this is where I am right now.
So I'm underground.
Keep going.
Thank god it tells you where you are.
Okay basement.
There's a door.
Oh shit hold on.
God damn it give me a break.
Can I get in this door?
All right stealth stealth stealth stealth stealth.
Somebody's coming somebody's coming.
Water water water water arrows water arrows.
Oh shit.
How many times do I have to shoot somebody in the head before they die?
What how do I move the body?
Oh my god all right dump them.
Dump them down here.
Okay I gotta get rid of the blood.
All right that's one guard.
All right save it.
F11 what's that?
What I can't go in here.
This I can't open this door.
I thought this is a place into the mansion.
Wait a minute.
I need to figure out how do I put the other arrows on.
How do I do it?
Who's in the options?
Okay water at four.
So I just have it up four.
There we go.
All right so what if I if I do this.
I just need to test this and see what happens.
I didn't do anything.
What what the?
No no I want to get points.
This guy's drunk.
All right wait what do I do about this guy?
Can you see me?
This is not very stealthy.
Where's he going?
Oh he's got the key.
He's got the key.
All right all right dump him.
All right I got it.
Did I take the key?
Close it.
Okay I was never here.
I got the key right?
Yep nice.
Hold down.
Yeah I can do like a big swing.
Can I take the beer?
I can.
Oh it's a bottle.
Don't do that.
I was trying to drink it.
Oh my goodness slow down.
I can't just pick it up.
How do I just okay drop.
That's so loud.
I think I'm in.
Oh here's the well.
All right let's bring this with us.
There's the well.
That was a tuber reaction.
It was genuine though.
All right so I have to go down the well.
Am I gonna get hurt?
All right so now I'm underneath the estate right?
This is all pre-recorded.
Now I'm just sitting back with my legs up on the desk.
My arms behind my head just relaxing while I watch this with you.
All right where am I at?
Basement is coming up here.
What's that?
Secret.
I don't know where I'm gonna end up.
Oh my god what is that thing?
Wait is this is that attack?
Is this evil?
Are these evil?
Do these attack?
I feel like do these attack?
I'm kind of I hate this.
Get out of the water.
Grab the edge and get out of the water.
Oh get back in the water get back in the water get back in the water back in the water.
All right I got it I got it.
I got one.
This is how I actually treat when there's a spider in the house.
Oh there's a chest over here.
Since I'm in here I'm gonna pick up something for myself.
There's nothing in here.
Waste of time.
What?
Okay well I got gold.
Oh swim come on.
Do you have a time limit?
I don't have a time limit.
And that person for a day.
Which way do I have to go?
I forget.
Do I have a face cam?
Yeah just I'll put it on in a minute.
Or maybe I won't.
I don't have to have face cam.
It's fun to use sometimes but you know whatever.
Okay I gotta be careful now.
Take out the uh take out the bludgeoner.
Wait are these explosive?
These are explosive I think.
Inside at last.
Are they the blow up?
Doesn't look like it.
Can I do anything with this stuff?
I'm making so much noise here.
Okay you know what?
This is actually good.
Because they're not going to investigate this.
Because they just probably assume a raccoon is in here.
All right we're gonna get upstairs.
Where are they?
Oops.
I was trying to hit him in the face in the box.
I can't go anywhere.
What?
No I just made a problem for myself.
I can't clip through those.
Go investigate that.
Wait opportunity.
I'll get this guy in the head.
I see you there.
Die.
Why won't he fight me?
Hurry up run.
God damn it.
I knew it was a problem.
I have to be off to this guy.
Before he brings the alarm.
Fuck come on.
Why is he so much faster than me?
I got him.
Wait there's so much stuff over here.
Hold on.
No I want the apple.
My health is okay.
Oh nice all right.
Money?
I gotta get these guys out of here.
What's that music for?
I'm so turned around though I don't even know where I was.
Was that a shovel?
Oh hell yeah.
Wait come here.
That means guards are coming?
Put him in the chest.
All right where am I?
I gotta get up from here.
Save.
Yeah yeah yeah.
This isn't Far Cry dude.
I'm not treating it like Far Cry.
I would have gone on the front door.
Goodness okay.
Anybody patrol this?
All right slow down.
Save.
Guys my Wendy's forgot special sauce.
What?
Dude that's not cool.
What was that?
Vase.
I want to hold on to this stuff.
I don't just want to throw it.
Okay.
What was that?
All right where am I now?
I'm in here.
Sneak into the manor.
Okay.
Steal the scepter with as little notice as possible.
There's another chest there.
I couldn't pick it up.
Oh I could.
All right cool.
All right I just gotta find the way up.
What the hell?
Who made that sound?
I'll never know.
He's just sleeping.
That guy's just sleeping in bed.
I gotta make it look not as bad though.
Okay that's fine.
He's asleep.
Now is this an innocent person?
Is this?
Can I loot their bodies?
They're all innocent.
Who's there?
No no no one's here.
Get out of here.
No one's here.
The humming makes that even better.
Did you hear something?
No.
I think we're almost there.
Yep let's go.
I think we're in.
Yeah we're in.
This is up.
We gotta get to the second floor.
Take out the bludgeoner.
Excuse me?
Is it like Resident Evil?
Can you like close the zombie out?
Shit.
No.
God damn it.
I'm fine I'm fine I'm fine I'm fine I'm fine I'm fine I'm fine.
Everything's fine.
Everything's fine I'm fine I'm fine I'm fine I'm fine.
I gotta dump him.
You have no choice.
You must kill.
Well I need to put him somewhere.
Wait where am I?
What's happening?
I hear somebody.
Nice.
All right.
We're good we're good we're good.
How long do they stay unconscious for?
Oh god.
Is there a torch in here?
Mushroom.
Where are they?
Oh god.
Why are they getting closer?
Is it dark right here?
Where is this person?
We gotta get to the second floor.
Yaron made me smile?
Oh all right.
What did I do?
Oh god.
Okay this looks...
Is this like the kitchen?
All right this is the kitchen.
There's the chef.
What's he making?
The chef is making a delicious meal of apples.
I gotta knock you out man.
I'm sorry.
What was that?
I hit the chandelier.
Oh give me all these crunchies.
I didn't kill him.
I'm not gonna be a weirdo.
I'm gonna put him in a place where he's gonna be.
He's gonna wake up in a few hours
and it's gonna be fine.
I'm gonna hide him over here.
There's a note right here.
What does it say?
Cedric please speak to Cook about last night's dinner.
While technically the menu conformed to my instructions
I suspect that the lamb was somewhat older than this spring.
And I am in no way fooled by his practice of
warming the salad to disguise wilting.
If Cook is incapable of finding adequate ingredients
he can be replaced.
And if he offers those same excuses
about the stone market shortages
please remind him that the grocery budget
is a good 50% above last year's figures.
And even he should be able to procure
adequate victuals at those prices.
Oh we have his bread.
Oh carrots.
Bread.
A little mallet.
Leesies.
Ooh a pan.
More cheese.
I should probably eat some of this stuff.
Does this heal?
I don't see it.
This doesn't heal.
Hope you're having fun.
I'm having fun.
Oh I can't alt tab this game.
Let me see.
I got it on my phone.
What the fuck is alt-ish man?
I'm not even gonna react to this.
I'm not even gonna react to it.
That's it.
I'm gonna play Thief.
I was playing Thief.
I'm just playing a game of Thief.
That's it.
I'm gonna keep going.
What was that?
Please, I just browsed it for a second, all right?
I saw it.
Why I saw it?
All right, where am I now?
All right, I gotta get up here into the interior courtyard.
Is it like a secret door?
Oh nothing.
I thought these were coffins.
All right, I gotta get upstairs.
What is all this?
Are you mad at us?
Mad at you?
Whoa, I just stole a bunch of stuff.
Okay, cool.
Hey.
Whoa, how did I turn around though?
My neck just enlarged.
My neck just stretched like 13 feet.
Stop it once and-
Shit, shit.
I'm dead.
How do we load?
F12.
What?
What are you talking about?
I don't understand.
Wasn't I saving it?
Okay, what?
I was gonna say that was like 30 minutes of progress.
All right, I can't mess around.
This is where I was.
Get out of the way.
I gotta get up the stairs.
Steal some of this stuff.
All right, slow down.
Use your sword on the banners to cut them.
I gotta be careful.
You can see me?
Stay out of the light.
All right, headshot this guy with a bow and arrow.
God damn it.
I need to throw something up there.
Stay in the dark.
Strange.
Whoa, that guy saw me.
Shit.
Oh, shit.
What if I just stay hidden?
Where is he?
Why would you still be using your bow?
Just duck.
Come under the stairs.
All right, here's the second floor right here.
We got it.
Oh, they're coming in.
Oh, shit.
Get him out of the light.
I think I'm okay.
I think I can go up the stairs now.
Where am I now?
All right.
Where is this guy?
I'm almost in his quarters.
Minecraft sounds.
These are Minecraft sounds.
Oh, boy.
Upstairs to the private chambers.
Bottom of the screen is light level.
Nobody will see you if it's dark.
Somebody had a lot of good advice there.
Oh, wait.
Okay.
You can load preset controls.
Blackjack only works if they don't know you're there.
If you pick something up
and it doesn't go in your inventory,
it's not worth anything.
Expert is not harder.
Just more objectives.
Oh, okay.
So this only works if you...
They can't see me.
But if they don't see me, is it an instant KO?
Yes.
Okay, cool.
There's no...
It's up here.
I thought those were guards.
Nothing up here.
It only works with the blackjack.
Okay.
Oh, we got a goblet here.
Nice.
Does it say how much this stuff was worth at the end?
I just ate a lot of food.
What does that do?
What does food even do?
All right.
We got to go up, not down.
Okay.
I cannot be seen right now.
I'm...
Oh, no, no, no.
Easy, easy.
It's probably somebody in the courtyard.
All right.
We're fine.
Don't just load.
Thank God.
I saved and loaded the same exact time, I think.
It's creepy.
What is this?
Yeah.
All right.
Walk on the carpet.
Where am I?
I have to mention second floor.
Throne room is right up here.
Is he in the throne room?
It's like the big dining hall.
What is this?
Is this like a secret room?
Oh, fuck you.
Stay right here.
All right.
If he's already seen me, does that mean...
Can I still get him in one hit?
Yes.
Okay.
Good.
I'm just saving it every five steps.
What?
How is that possible?
No.
Reload.
Somebody's seeing me.
I'm making noise.
Oh, whatever.
I don't have to hit anybody.
Let's just go.
Okay.
So where's my orientation here?
Throne room is this way.
The tile floor is really loud.
Yeah.
I have to go that way.
Shit.
Okay.
We're fine.
Is this a big bath?
Do you hear me go in the water?
Oh, great.
That's not good.
Does he care?
I don't think he cares.
Just don't move in the water.
I want to go inside of that thing,
but I don't want to.
Oh, boy.
You killed me in one hit.
Are you kidding me?
What do I have for armor?
No.
Fuck off.
I got it.
He didn't see me.
I'm fine.
Where's this other guy?
All right.
Nobody here.
Is it my going to the throne room?
I'm going back down.
Shit.
You jump from carpet to carpet.
Will they hear me jumping?
All right.
Water arrows.
So I can do this on torches, you said, right?
You got to use the rubber chicken
with a pulley in the middle of the water.
That's just good.
Absolute shit.
Why did that scare me so much?
I didn't expect he was going to be that close to me.
This guy's got golden armor on.
Swing at me, please.
He gave me a goddamn break.
All right.
Jump from place to place.
Holy shit.
It worked.
What a bunch of geniuses.
Seriously.
Get you in the dark.
All right.
I have to save it.
I have the key to the throne room now.
Recent delivery of antiquities from Vaughn
contains several items which we felt might be of interest to you.
Descriptions follow, but you are welcome to drop by our shop
to examine them or other goods in person.
An ornamental scepter three feet in length.
That's huge.
The body of the stave is weird.
Carved in the star and dot pattern.
Six inches of the ferrule and five inches of the grip
are bound with burnished copper overlaid by an ink and glaze
varnish.
It's pretty good looking, I think.
Cloudstone, one of the finest of its type,
we have seen a treasure box of two feet by three feet of four feet
by silver birch wood.
The lid is really pretty.
The inside of the box contains two principal compartments,
one with glass shelves, and it's very expensive.
No.
Ooh.
Dog bone.
OK.
Let's keep going.
Where am I now?
All right.
I definitely have a key to the throne room.
Healing potion key.
That's a big key.
Where's the throne room, though?
Think you can just vanish in the shadows again, tricksy boy.
I've played enough Dark Souls to be able to do this.
OK, never mind.
Where did he come from?
No, don't shoot it.
How do I pull it back?
What happened?
I hit him in the leg and he died.
All right, we're good.
All right, I think I got to go down that hallway.
Let me see.
I can cut the banners.
I'm curious what that means.
What does that do?
I need the throne room.
Now I'm on this edge.
I got to go over here.
I wish I had an indicator of where I was.
It's probably the courtyard, right?
Press Y to fart.
I mean, I did it, just curious.
I have a compass.
It's a grenade.
All right, so what is the compass telling me to go?
So the compass is pointing in the direction I need to go?
Or OK, so is this north, southeast, right?
Am I?
Is that correct?
So I got to go this way, right?
Is this would be east?
The painted top is facing north, right?
Guys, I haven't looked at a compass in probably 20 years.
I don't even care what they are.
This is pointing north.
So that means that if I'm going this way,
that I'm currently going east.
That's correct?
Yes.
OK, right.
I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it.
All right, so I got to go.
There we go.
Through that door.
OK, here we go.
This is it.
That's the throne, right?
No, it's a bed.
I thought it was it.
OK, from this angle, it looked like a big throne.
It's got a lot of money, though.
Another key.
What?
I don't know.
All right, not the throne room.
OK, it's another door on this side, then?
This is a personal bedroom.
Right here.
OK, this is locked.
This is locked.
Is he in here?
You're the flash bomb.
But I see this.
Ah!
I got him.
Is that a gong?
Don't touch that.
That's definitely like...
That's probably like an alarm.
All right, I made it to the throne room.
Tenches.
Here it is.
I found the scepter.
OK, scepter's right here.
Here we go.
All right.
Hell yeah.
I did it.
30 minutes.
Found 705 loot.
I picked one pocket.
Zero knockouts out of...
Wait, zero knockouts?
How?
Innocence killed some.
That's such a weird statistic.
This doesn't say how many.
Innocence killed, I don't know, a few.
I was not paying attention.
When I was writing down my debriefing,
I don't remember how many innocent people I killed.
So I just wrote some.
And others.
Ah.
Some and others.
I don't know, whatever.
I don't know who they were.
That was kind of fun.
You didn't hit the gong?
I didn't think I was going to end the mission right there.
Melting this down.
Someone just called Thief an unknown game that I dug up.
It got remade, what, four or five years ago?
Didn't they kind of do a remake?
I think so.
I went to Cuddy's place to deliver the sector.
That was ten years ago.
Wait, what?
It was ten years ago?
I thought that was like two years ago.
Apparently, they all proved of his occupation.
And I doubt they proved of mine.
It was 2014.
Really?
So hopefully, they'll never catch sight of me
when I break him out of their prison.
Which is what I'm going to do.
It was 2012.
They're holding Cuddy in a mine where he's flooded,
but the hammers still work the top-level mines
and have converted part of the complex
into a penitentiary for those who violate their tenets.
Reface came up for this one?
An associate of mine was confined there.
That was weird.
I don't know what happened there.
It would be difficult to get in by way of the main gate,
but there is another option.
The mines break the surface of a hill south of the quarry.
I'll drop into the mines and head for the mine.
Hairline check?
Got it.
Which way we found somewhere uphill into the north.
The hammers can venture into these lower mines.
It's getting worse, but it's okay.
Because they're reputed to be on this job,
but Cuddy's a reliable fence,
and I don't appreciate the hammerites abducting him.
All right.
So I got to break money for the Bafford job.
Break people out of jail?
Oh, your map doesn't show the way through the mine,
so you're going to have to scout around
to make your way to where they hold the prisoners.
Cuddy still owes you for the Bafford job.
Break him out and you'll get your cash.
All right.
I'm back.
Hold on.
Let me get the camera to look okay.
Let me wait.
Let me just get this done.
This is a dog bone.
How much is this?
I can buy this?
It's a tip.
It's 300 bucks,
and it reveals where the hammers are keeping Cuddy.
Speed potion.
This potion will greatly increase your speed for a little while.
I can just bunny hop.
I thought I said in Craigslist.
A former prisoner of Craigsleft says he has info about the haunted mines.
I have plenty of these.
Moss arrow.
Oh, okay.
That's actually really helpful.
Noisemaker?
Yeah, I want those.
I think I'm all right.
Is there anything?
Maybe I should buy another healing potion.
250.
I think it's worth it.
Probably buy it.
It's worth it.
Your cash does not carry over between missions.
It does not.
So should I just buy everything?
Okay, so there's no point.
So wait, give me that hot tip.
I want to know exactly where he is.
Give me the hot tip and give me a potion.
And how many arrows do I need?
Maybe a couple more of these moss arrows.
30 cents.
All right, I think that's good.
Spend it all.
All right.
Yeah, that's good to know.
This one, I'm going to save it right here.
I'm going to do like a hard save.
Let me get my camera to work.
Because the camera is like all buggy right now.
Hold on.
Let me turn on the ring light.
I've got a ring light.
How does that look?
That looks better or worse?
It needs to be a little bit brighter.
I like that.
It looks all right.
Is it better?
Yeah, look, I've got my ring light on now.
Okay.
How does that look?
Fine.
Do we look okay?
What is it, Ronnie?
I'm not putting the ring light around my neck.
It's not happening.
No.
Maybe if I can confirm that it's going to be safe, I'll do it.
All right.
You get face cam for a half of one mission.
Here we go.
I hope I didn't need that.
One full mission or no.
There is no deal.
I just turned it on and the white balance is wrong anyways.
Who cares?
Let me fix that quick.
All right.
It resets my camera settings every time I start.
It's better.
There we go.
That's like what it looks like in this room right now.
Like that.
Okay.
That's fine.
Is it a blue light?
I didn't even...
Whatever.
I don't care.
Let's just go.
All right.
I got to go through the mines and I got to find the...
I got to find the person.
I got to break the person out.
Can I smash somebody's head with a boulder?
I hope so.
We're going to try it.
Is it such a Bostonian?
Not anymore.
I've been not in Massachusetts for quite a while now.
Swim down.
So the goal is to get through...
I think I need to turn the bright...
What happened here?
That I deserve.
I did not realize...
I didn't know what was going on there.
Okay.
Give me my boulder back.
It was a...
All right.
It's marked on the map where he is, right?
Mines prison factory.
It's just like Dante's Inferno.
These are the layers of hell.
These are the layers.
What's this?
I thought that was an enemy.
I thought that was a person coming to get me.
What does that do?
Can I slash this?
What does this do?
Water arrows in it?
That's not a bad idea.
Holy water will kill zombies.
There are no zombies in this game.
There are zombies in this game.
Oh, that didn't do anything.
That didn't do anything.
What's that?
Where's the water?
Factory.
There it is.
Do I have to like bless myself?
All right.
I'm blessed.
It only lasts for 30 seconds.
It doesn't kill in one...
Holy shit.
What do I do about this?
I'm going to get up there somehow.
I'm going to turn the gam up.
I'm going to turn the gam up, I think.
Is that safe to go down there?
I'm going to turn the gam up.
It's probably better, right?
I have more.
This is cheating probably, but I don't care.
Is it buying to lean over edges and look down?
I think I'm supposed to go down here.
Or up, I guess.
How high should I go?
I'm already dead right there.
Is that guy a zombie?
I think so, yeah.
Can I just...
Okay, can I kill him?
Like with the sword?
Is this the zombie?
Why is he just breathing?
What happened?
Is he dead?
Ah!
I knew somebody was right near me.
What happened?
What?
It's not even fucking scary.
Relax.
Don't overreact for no reason.
Overactor.
Overreactor.
I thought that was him breathing.
I can't hurt him.
Okay, bad.
Are you going to give me a dead end?
They're taking up the exact space that I need to run around them.
I still have a grenade.
What is happening in this game?
Okay.
Is this a haunted house now?
All right.
Um, okay.
I got to keep going up.
Keep going north, I guess.
Or up?
I hear...
I hear humans.
I hear human life.
You get one little measly health back for a fucking $300 health potion.
I have those noise arrows, right?
Let me...
Okay, let me use them.
Moss arrow.
Noise arrow.
Quiet.
He's right there.
Get him right now.
I thought I spied something.
Hiding shall...
I threw a shovel at him and he didn't even care.
It takes care of those too.
Where am I at?
I got to go up.
This, uh...
I can go up that way, but what's over here?
This is a secret or something?
Something I can get?
I'll check it.
Why not?
Oh, I think this is a different entrance.
Can I swim up it like a salmon?
No.
Okay.
So this is another way to get down here.
Excuse me.
What's this?
Too far, too far, too far, too far.
I'm gonna get lost if I don't cut it out.
Guards had keys.
I think I got them.
I didn't get the keys?
I thought when I picked them up, it would just give it to me.
According to Dickit, a heretic who was recently let out of Craigslist,
Cutty's being held in cell block four.
Okay.
So he's in cell block four.
They had keys?
I didn't take...
Oh, shit.
Okay.
I thought I was gonna just pick it up on their body and not get his key anymore.
Where is it?
I don't know.
Babe.
It was just the potion?
All right.
So cell block four.
Here we are.
Careful, guard stations.
All right.
Control room, machine room, power station.
This is to the mine.
So we're going through and we're gonna be in the control room.
I'm gonna get to the prison.
Shit.
You idiot.
It's dark right here.
He can't see me.
What are you saying?
Do you have anything on you?
A key or anything?
No.
All right.
Move this shit out of the way.
Mine...
Okay.
I need those arrows right now.
Oh, shit.
He didn't see it.
I don't want...
All right.
I'm good.
Good, good, good, good, good.
He can't...
I'm in pitch black right now.
He can't see me.
Like there's a steam engine over there masking my sounds.
All right.
Come on.
This way.
All right.
Tread softly.
Toss him in the corner.
Okay.
That's the only thing I can press.
I thought I was going to shock the floor.
I thought I was going to just electrocute the ground in this.
That was so loud.
My ears hurt.
Okay.
Machine rooms, control room.
We've got to go up here.
Okay.
Get to the prison.
That's what that's all I got to do.
Save it right here.
Why you like this?
Because I attention deficit hyperactivity disorder.
And I'm like irrational and compulsive.
Very high, strong, neurotic.
I don't know.
That's why.
And I'm like being cut off.
Nice excuse.
I know it's not an excuse.
It really isn't.
I know.
I said neurotic, not erotic.
Open your ears.
Are there people down here?
Because this is the...
Oh, this is the way to get to the factory.
I mean to the prison.
I'm not erotic.
Why does it not work?
What am I dumping?
What happened?
Why somebody screamed?
What?
It was me screaming.
I was not even close.
All right.
I'll fucking take out some people here.
Let's turn him into hot fucking magma.
Come on over here.
Come on over here, coward.
Hey, look.
You flipped me off.
Where is he?
What?
What is that?
Where is he going?
Where are you going?
Oh, somebody's bleeding.
Got him.
Oh, I got the...
I got a hammer.
What do I do with this?
What do I do with the hammer?
Is somebody still alive?
Oh, I got two hammers.
All right.
What does this one make?
This one also makes hammers.
No, I don't want any of this.
Give me the...
Just give me the hammer.
Fucking asshole.
I tried to jump over it.
All right.
No more messing around.
Fucking idiot.
He's up here.
Oh, shit.
Oh, fuck you.
Come on, dude.
Don't even...
Who swings a hammer like this with one hand?
Like up that you can't even do that move.
That move isn't even possible.
You can't take a huge two-handed hammer and go like this
and have it hit me right square in the front of the nose.
I got an idea.
Madka's bad.
Yeah.
I saw.
Move.
You guys have anything on you?
No.
Kind of show me her right.
Yeah, rats.
Just rats.
That guy was singing.
All right, he's hidden.
I think there's one more guy here.
The prison.
Did I make one of these things though?
I feel like I need to take one of these.
Never face tribulation in their lives.
What?
There's nobody...
No, you don't look in the...
What?
You don't look over here.
Why would you be like,
in time, I believe that thief Cuddy's friend has some...
Why would you be doing that?
You're just having a conversation.
There's no way you're as fast as me be hopping, bro.
I'm sorry.
There's no way.
You stupid game.
Whatever.
What do you mean mad at somebody?
I'm just saying.
If you have...
Okay.
If you and I are having a conversation.
We're just talking.
Yes.
Okay, you're right here.
Like this whole space,
like this spot over here in the corner,
I am not going to...
If I see like a squirrel move over there,
I'm not going to immediately take a sword out and run over there.
We're in the middle of a conversation.
I'm not just going to peer that way
and go after whatever it is.
No, it's not going to happen.
They're prison guards.
Oh, but that...
We didn't even know I was there.
So you're telling me that they're prison guards.
Do you remember they're prison guards?
They're guards.
I just threw one of those nerf...
You know those nerf whistleers?
The thing that like Brett Favre was in the commercial
and he threw it like, look this,
I can throw this 100 yards.
And it goes...
I just threw one of those right next to them
and they didn't even hear it.
I just whipped one of those
and you're telling me that they're...
Aren't they supposed to be aware?
No reaction.
Why are they doing this?
Block four.
All right, let's go.
What happened?
Why did...
I'm confused what just happened.
This guy didn't see me.
It was a medieval security camera.
Who saw me?
I don't get it.
It's just like a little thing going like this.
Who can see me right now?
They didn't even have sound effects like this back then.
What?
It's in the ceiling.
No, it's not.
That's what's seeing me?
I thought you guys were making it up.
I thought that was a joke.
There's a medieval security camera.
Are you kidding me?
So what am I supposed to do about that?
I guess put this out?
Can it see in the dark?
Okay, I can't go this way.
I thought I could get him.
I thought I'd just go into the window.
Oh, can I go under here and then above?
I guess I can wrap around maybe and go up.
I don't know.
It's steampunk.
You know, steampunk is like the Jedi hand wave for all fiction.
Who passes there?
It's steampunk.
I would not have thought...
Therefore, it's fine.
...dare their teeth against the builders' house.
Steampunk.
Therefore, it's fine.
Oh, shit.
Who are thou?
Okay.
All right.
Very clearly.
That guy's got a key.
Use the walk button?
I'm thinking about just running in.
Somebody comes up here and patrols, and I need to be aware of that.
Just rush in.
I can't just rush in.
I think I can...
He heard you walk.
I think I have to go down to the sewer as much as I don't want to.
Okay, this guy's coming over here.
I'll knock this guy out in the corner.
The light goes out for a minute.
It does.
One, two, three.
This guy's just gargling in the mirror.
Nobody.
Nobody goes.
How...
When do I go?
Oh, that's not much time at all.
One, two, one, two, three.
Go.
Save it?
Save it, save it, save it.
Double up four.
Which one...
What is he in?
I need my hot tip.
According to Dickit, a heretic who was recently let out of Craig's Cleft,
Cuddy, is being held in cell block four.
How do I distract this guy?
I need it.
I need help.
All right.
Let's see what I can do.
Noise arrow?
I hear somebody coming over here.
Oh, God.
What do I do?
Let me in.
Open the door.
Open.
Where?
Out of here.
Got him.
We good?
Where is this guy?
Oh, shit.
You piece of...
No way.
No, turn it off.
Turn it off.
Kill this motherfucker.
What?
I was just kidding.
I was just testing to see if it worked.
We were just having an electrical test to see if it worked or not.
If we just have an electrical test.
Get out of the fucking way.
He's in the way.
You got to be kidding me, dude.
He's going to go...
I'm going to go channel channel.
He's kidding me.
Run away, coward.
All right.
No more Alex Jones.
He's...
Oh, yeah.
I can't get in there now, can I?
You didn't think I was going to be able to get in and get you, did you?
Ah, now you can't get in.
Now I can stay here.
Awesome.
Lady Taker.
Lisa Vandal.
Wills.
Number six.
Cutty.
How do I turn this off?
Good luck.
It's kind of crazy out there.
That guy's going to get fucking grabbed.
How many cells do I have?
Where's six?
Hey, Cutty.
Come on.
Come with me.
We got to get out of here.
Immediately.
Speak into my ear.
I'm imagining the guy that ran out first.
They're all going to just pile on top of that guy.
And like, he's the bad guy.
He's the one that broke out.
He caused all this.
What happened to you?
What?
What happened?
What's wrong with him?
Was that supposed to happen?
I'll get him out.
What's the new objective?
I failed this one.
Okay.
Find the evidence locker and retrieve Felix's map.
All right.
Evidence locker.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Off.
Okay.
Barracks and offices quarters.
We've got to go this way.
Did I save it?
I feel like I shouldn't.
How do I get out of here?
Level two.
All right.
I'm in level two.
Guards.
I couldn't hear anything from that cut scene
because the blaring...
Open the door.
How do I turn the alarm off?
I need the key.
Leave the corpse.
What is this?
What kind of...
What?
A weird door.
That's...
Okay.
Just in case shit hits the absolute fan,
I have a save point back there.
All right.
I need to find the map in the officer's quarters.
Find the evidence locker.
Evidence locker.
Nothing in there.
All right.
Shit.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Why does the prison have door locks?
I don't know, dude.
What did you do?
I'm needing to be distracted.
I want you to...
What I want you to do is I want you to scream really loud
when I walk over this way
so the guard will come over and I'll knock him out.
He's dead?
Hey.
Excellent job.
I was thinking about it.
No.
I can't zoom out, though.
Where is he?
So...
Oh, don't, dude.
Don't scare me like that.
You're pretending to hold a weapon.
He's walking around holding a fake weapon.
Get out of here.
All right.
Get out.
Go for it.
Let's get out of here.
Everybody, get out.
It's everywhere for himself.
Where's the guard quarters?
No, we can take them.
We can take them.
I don't know why I did that.
I just pressed it like an idiot.
Okay.
All right, all right, all right, all right.
Where's the guard's quarters?
Over here.
You all right?
You're smart.
This is a smart one.
You need a weapon.
You don't have a weapon.
You don't...
You need to get away from me, though.
You have to leave me alone.
Yes.
It's good to see you.
Very nice to meet you.
This is...
Okay.
Save me.
There's someone here.
Stay with me.
Ooh.
I just let him out of prison.
I just broke him out of prison.
And he's screaming assassin.
I'm sorry.
That was fucked up.
All right.
Where...
I got a barracks in officer's quarters.
Wait, what?
I can write on this?
I gotta head this way.
So I have to go down.
And then across.
I don't know where the hell I'm going.
I need to drink a health potion, though.
Officers quarters.
Officers cell block one.
All right.
Cell block one.
Which is across the way.
Link, can I just go through this door?
All right.
Cell block three.
I gotta get to cell block one.
Cell block one was on the other side.
Oh, shit.
And how...
Explain to me how you saw me, you piece of crap.
Don't hit your head on the ceiling.
Cell block one.
One, one, one, one, one, one.
Leave me the fuck alone.
Leave me alone.
This guy chased me.
What's the aggro range?
Leave me...
Get away from me.
Leave me alone.
This guy is seriously a superhero.
Get away from me.
Why would I even start...
I know where to go.
Do no emotion.
This is a stream sniper.
No emotion.
Should I do no emotion?
I can't...
I'm just trying to concentrate.
This game's hard.
Stop singing.
Why is everybody singing?
All right.
Here we go.
I don't have somebody chasing me now.
I can get to cell block one from here.
It's a scary game.
It's kind of scary.
All right.
Here we go.
Get through this.
Wait till it turns off.
You got like a two second window.
One.
Did you see that bait?
What was that?
Okay.
Oh, my goodness.
I'm fine.
All right.
Save it right here.
Drink a health potion.
I'm ready to go.
You just heard me gulp that.
You just heard me drink.
You got to be kidding me.
That would be so scary.
If you're just in like a pitch black area.
And all you hear is this.
Okay.
Save it here.
Cell block one.
And to the barracks.
All right.
No more alarm.
Finally.
I can take this guy out.
What happened?
What's going on?
What?
Stay in shadow.
Did he just turn the alarm back on?
I think he just got himself stuck.
All right.
We're good.
Cell block one is this way.
Bring this over here so nobody hears it.
I got to go get the map.
Okay.
Up here.
Barracks offers his quarters straight ahead.
I just have to sneak through with the shadows.
Let's have a good bad gamer neck there for a second.
Here we go.
The barracks.
Hit it again.
All right.
Where are we at?
Is it in here?
Oh, carpet, carpet, carpet, carpet, carpet.
I didn't want to pick this.
Not hidden.
Who is that?
A prince?
Who is that guy?
Got anything on you?
Oh, shit.
Nice.
There's tons of stuff in here.
All right.
I'm going to...
These are all the guards' quarters.
Knife.
Give me a knife.
Looking for the map now.
Wherever that is.
Hold on.
I came in through here.
How do I not have full health after eating all that?
All right.
I explored all the quarters.
Here we go.
I don't know who this person was.
I'm coming.
I'm going to throw the knife in his neck.
Can I think I can hit it from here?
Nope.
But it don't matter.
I'll get him.
He just baited me, but I still hit him in the head.
Okay.
I don't even know who this person is.
Does he have a key or something?
It doesn't look like it.
He's throwing a handle first.
It's not going to kill anybody.
Is somebody walking?
Where is this map?
Find the evidence locker in the tree...
Evidence locker in the...
Am I going too far?
This guy's got magical powers.
There's a lot of talking, but he's got magic powers.
Is this a spell book?
When I was cold, thou taught of hearth in roof beam.
When I was hungry, thou taught of pot and cauldron.
When I was beset by foes, thou taught of spear and shield.
Thy hammer pounds thy nail, holds the roof beam.
Thy hammer strikes the iron, shapes the cauldron.
Thy hammer in my hand, unto my foes.
I think I had fire powers.
These magic potions?
Okay.
Wait a minute.
Do I need to bring a hammer here in front of the door?
I hope not.
Still walking around here.
Hopefully I'm able to get to the next part.
What are these hammers?
Oh, I found a hammer.
What?
Holy shit, diamonds.
Oh, I got it.
All right.
I got it.
It was right there.
All right.
I couldn't save Cuddy.
I think that's scripted though.
The man-fools piled rock on rocks and raised a treacy roof.
Hammer saws tear the skin of goodsy wood and laughs at the woodsy lord.
And when learns of the lord of this, he sends his beasties to the man-fools
who attacks and hammer saws their useless flesh.
And build him a house of thy rotting skins.
I was pissed at Cuddy for a good one.
But hey, I gotta like stand up.
I like him for what the hammers did to him.
It sort of like stuck to him.
So I decided to go after that horn that Felix talked about.
Not like I had a whole lot of choice, really.
The rent is due.
The landlord's...
Manslide!
Man-filth!
The map's pretty specific about where the entrance is.
Too bad it's not as clear about where the horn is.
Felix did some scrounging before he left
and his notes say the horn is in the tomb of some nobles.
The Aquintus family.
Guess I'll just have to explore.
Felix.
Always helpful.
Also said that the catacombs are supposed to be haunted.
Great.
I think I'll go make some inquiries about where a heretic like me
can get some holy water.
I'll always go prepared.
Filthy man thing.
Uh, should I go pee?
Should we take a pee break?
Search through the ancient bone hoard and procure the legendary horn of Quintus.
Let me just get a good save point here.
Oh wait, let me spend some money.
These are pretty useful.
So I want some.
That's way too expensive.
Never mind, I'd rather have the alarm get set off
than spend that much money.
Water arrows.
50 rope arrows.
Okay.
I want health.
It's so much more important to me.
Holy water.
This vial of hammer-sanctified liquid.
It's potent protection against the undead when used on your water arrows.
I have a few of them.
Maybe I'll get more of these, yeah.
Okay, I don't want to...
I gotta be careful.
The money's about previous missions.
That's pretty cool.
This game's fun.
I like this game.
I'm gonna save it right here.
I'm gonna take a quick pee break.
I'll be right back.
You know, it's not...
I know it's like January 10th or whatever.
How about the Christmas one one more time?
What do you think?
Christmas one one more time?
Yeah, oh yeah.
Yeah.
All right.
I'll see you guys in two minutes.
I'm just gonna go pee real quick.
Grab some water.
See you guys in a minute.
Oops.
All right, we're good.
Beer B.
I have returned.
How are you doing?
Are you a Raiders fan ever since you went to Vegas?
I never really was a football fan to begin with.
I think it's cool.
I really kind of feel bad for Oakland though.
Because Vegas took the Raiders.
And Vegas might take the A's too.
So that's kind of...
I feel bad for Oakland.
Oh, we're doing sports talk now.
This is a prime 90s PC boomer game.
How did you not play it yet?
I'm telling you, it's been installed for like years.
I just had to decide on a day to do it.
And I just put it in the poll.
All right, let's do it.
Did you wash your hands?
I always wash my hands.
Always.
Are you gonna do Thief 2 and Thief 3 as well?
I don't know.
That's actually a pretty good question.
It really depends on how much I enjoy this one.
Which so far I think it's pretty fun.
Bring the scary music back up.
Back to this.
Thief 2.
Thief 2 is this but better.
Okay.
Reboot is trash.
Don't play it.
I kind of wanted to play this one anyways.
Add it to the list of old PC boomer games.
That's right.
Basecam or Outrage.
Wait a minute.
All right, so this one...
What are we gonna do?
Find the Horn of Quintus.
That's all the info I got.
And I have nothing else to go on.
This guy's gonna get up.
Yep.
Who cares though?
What?
Do I really care?
Just...
I'm just gonna go.
Right?
Like he's gonna...
That was just a jump scare that didn't happen.
Kind of creepy.
All right.
Do I have any notes?
Mario family.
Halls of Echoing.
Repose.
Hammerite crypts.
Quintus family.
So we gotta go down.
Down and north.
I guess.
Do you die from this?
Watch it.
I need...
Should I kill this thing with holy water?
Probably, right?
Fire!
Anybody else quick?
I only have 19 seconds.
Anybody else down here?
Oh, there's a goblet though.
Nice.
All right.
Oh, shit!
No!
That's bad.
I thought I was touching this.
I have to reload.
I thought I was touching...
Okay.
Sorry about that.
I'm an idiot.
All right.
Here we go.
Third time's the charm.
Shoot the arrow, please.
Anybody else down here?
I don't think so.
15 seconds.
Any other enemies?
Come on.
That's weird.
Three seconds.
Nothing.
All right.
So I guess I'm just gonna keep going.
Argoil wall?
All right.
Diving board.
What are your thoughts on...
Alaris.
Does that mean anything?
All right.
I'm still in the upper vaults.
Ooh.
Very useful.
All right.
I got 30 seconds now.
I'm gonna be some monsters right here.
Guaranteed.
Crap door.
Don't stand on that.
Oh.
I thought it was gonna fall.
Is this gonna be over my head?
All right.
Got it.
So, wait.
Will this shoot over my head?
It is.
Okay.
Is this just a depressing box?
I think so.
Okay.
I thought it was gonna fall.
Well, that's why I need the holy water.
Gotta go back and get it free.
All right.
Here we go.
Save it.
And...
All right.
Well, I got you.
Grab it.
All right.
Nothing else in here?
Why is the body exploding so funny?
I don't know.
It just is.
Nothing about it.
Upper vaults north.
Should I go down here?
Or deeper into the crypts?
What do you think?
How is it not funny?
I know.
It just is.
Is there any other holy water things over here?
These are both gonna get up.
Guaranteed.
Let me just see if this...
There might be a well right here.
No, there's not.
All right.
Well, do I need to kill these things
or can I just run away?
Yeah.
There's no reason to.
Just leave.
All right.
Let's go in here.
Neck light?
I mean, neck light.
Have I ever worn an apron before?
Maybe when I was barbecuing.
I was probably barbecuing somewhere
thinking it was funny.
Like, oh, here I am, the chef.
Nobody wants to be that guy, by the way.
You know how much panic I have
if I ever am the guy that is in charge of the grill?
The whole time, I'm just like,
everyone's gonna get poisoned.
Is that cooked enough?
I'm gonna kill somebody.
Is that too red in the middle?
Someone's gonna die.
Someone's gonna get too sick.
No, just me.
And then I overcook everything.
I have to kill this guy.
That's raw.
And those chicken wings are raw.
I can't serve them.
And then I always, if I'm ever in charge of...
Anytime you cook anything,
I always want to eat it first.
I'm gonna be my own tester for my own food, right?
You missed?
So like, the food's not ready yet.
Hey, when do you think the food's gonna be ready?
Well, maybe 20 minutes.
We'll see.
Because if I get sick, then I know, right?
So nobody eat it.
What was even in here?
You just ate raw food.
No, I'm just saying, I always want to make sure
I don't make anybody sick or anything.
And it can be really...
Where am I?
Wait, did I just go in a circle?
Whenever you have a guy at the grill
and you have like 15 hamburger patties on there,
it can be...
I don't know.
You can't really focus on one patty.
So you have to really make sure
that everything is cooked correctly
and everything's...
Why are you guys saying neck light?
I don't get this.
What are you doing?
Back in the water?
Put the light on your neck.
It's not gonna fit.
Okay, no, no, I gotta go back down.
No, you guys are gonna...
This is gonna turn into a cartoon.
Go this way?
Do I have enough breath to do this?
Where is this taking me?
It'll fit, trust me.
I'm an engineer.
Am I going?
Leave it open so you know where you've been.
Where the hell am I supposed to go?
All right, I went right and down,
so now I'm just gonna go over?
What do I hear?
Sleigh bells.
This is kind of creepy.
All right, wait, I see.
I see the cannon.
Yeah, you think you're so funny.
Nope, sorry.
I think I just drank all my potions.
No, I didn't.
Okay, so how do I get through here?
You promised all of things.
I did it in the very beginning of the stream
and it was stupid.
I couldn't even get three on my hand.
You...
All right, we're going down to wherever like...
We're going down here.
Oh, don't touch that, right?
Is this gonna do something if I touch it?
This looks lower, right?
There's a lip here.
Does that mean anything?
Washrooms.
I can't pick them up.
This feels like Castle Gryphonsteed.
What is that thing?
I gotta try to drop this on his head.
I'm by again.
Does this even...
Can you even hurt enemies with this stuff?
I don't like those sounds.
Relax, shut up.
Does this hurt?
This looks like one of those guys
in those inflatable T-Rex costumes.
It's like a pig and a...
I don't want to hurt it.
I don't...
I wish I could just say I'm not gonna hurt you,
but it's not gonna let me pass.
Jump!
I'm sorry, I had to.
It's because you threw a boulder at it.
I don't know.
It was trying to get me.
I'm coloring...
I'm coloring a cat coloring book.
What's your favorite cat?
I don't know.
I think cats are cool.
Oh shit, here comes the whole family.
Okay.
Where am I?
Why is there a little arrow scratched over here?
What?
I'm gonna follow the arrow.
I'm kind of scared to do this.
Okay.
Where...
I still don't know where I am.
I think I made it.
Is this it?
Watch out.
There's all these things everywhere.
Be careful.
If I crouch, it's fine, right?
Yeah, just stay crouched.
Ah!
The back...
B-boom!
This is dead.
Maybe right in the back of that.
Don't push that down.
All right, we got cheese.
Excuse me?
What?
He's right.
Bedroll?
What's this stuff?
Is dinosaur teeth or something?
What are those?
Speed potion.
Fire arrow is...
Oh, nice.
All right.
Cool.
All right, be careful here getting out.
All right, nice.
That got me that.
So now I gotta go the other way.
All right.
Can you throw up on stream, chat?
No, I'm not gonna throw up on stream.
Ha ha, vomit's all over the place.
That you thought it was funny?
Okay.
So now I gotta take these...
I gotta change pants.
I probably don't understand the concept here of climbing.
I think you just have to hold it.
I gotta be ready.
All over the place here.
Where...
Yeah, where am I actually going?
Down...
Okay.
There's dinosaurs down here.
I don't want...
I want to try to avoid them if I can.
Fire arrows on the dinosaurs?
Wait, did I kill that?
No, I didn't.
Where am I supposed to go here?
Let's go up.
They're not gonna get up, right?
They're dead?
This is such a maze.
Ooh.
That's it?
Are you kidding me?
Why are you so mad?
I'm not.
Eat the shrooms?
I think they're just light shrooms.
I don't think they're actual shroom shrooms.
I don't think I can eat them.
I gotta turn this up.
People saying, follow the music.
That was a pig.
That was clearly a pig.
That was that...
You know that pig sound?
The default pig sound?
All right, up here?
That's why I don't put the two goddamn headphones in.
Get up!
Climb up here.
Oh, now I'm back here.
All right, get away from me.
Shit.
Oh, get away from me.
I'm gonna die.
You gotta be...
How did he get up here?
How did they get up here?
They can't get up here.
I missed again.
I missed again and I went all the way to the back.
I'm gonna die right now.
I can't believe that just happened.
I can't believe it.
You've gotta be kidding me.
I don't even know where the save is.
Not that bad.
How did it miss?
There were three in the...
And all my field of vision.
That's so unfortunate.
Oh, well.
You got so much on my mouth.
Go change your pants and I'll be all right.
That's a worst gamer moment.
Uh, I mean, that was bad.
But that wasn't even my fault though.
That was such bullshit.
I...
You saw...
It was like the hitbox got weird.
I...
It just missed.
I don't even know how it missed.
I don't even know where I am right now.
But I'm just gonna grab onto this and go up.
And I think I just found it accidentally.
Did I just find it?
I just found where I need to go.
No, I didn't.
Is it still alive?
There's a sick McDonald's ceiling.
It's like not even...
It's not even close.
I mean, it's kind of close but not really...
Not enough for you to say that.
I don't think there's anything here.
All right, I gotta get through that.
There's nothing else here I can do.
Can I take something?
Push something?
No.
Secret.
It returns into the Joker.
Wait a minute.
Works on monsters.
That...
Good to know.
Very good to know that the...
The little bludgeoner works on huge monsters.
All right.
Time to get turned around a million times again.
Follow the music.
I feel like I was on the right track.
It works on anything that's alive.
Good to know.
That's funny.
Yep.
I remember getting the jewel here.
Follow the music.
Put in both headphones.
I hate doing that.
I hate it.
I don't like it.
It's too immersive.
What's wrong with being immersed?
I'm not aware of my surroundings.
I don't hear any music.
All right.
I gotta start burning this into memory here.
Oddwatches skip.
Don't skip.
You need to help me.
All right.
I hear the music now.
Okay.
This is where I got messed up last time.
I just burped.
Oh, I thought that was me.
Shut up.
Music.
Come on.
Get up there.
How do I get that?
Why is it saying go down?
Over there?
Do I rope arrow over there?
Music's in this room.
These zombies or these people?
It's hard to tell.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Golden arm.
No.
All right.
How do I get out?
I got a golden arm.
Oh.
Eat him, not me.
Eat him.
All right.
How do I get out of here?
The horn is somewhere down here.
Oh, my God.
I'm actually in the horn room.
I need to heal.
Golden arm.
I was just frozen in fear.
I couldn't do anything.
I was just frozen.
Die.
I can't.
Shut up, everybody.
All right.
Let's go, bro.
No, I'm trapped.
I'm trapped.
Okay.
Fuck this.
I'm out of here.
I'm just going to bunny hop through the whole thing.
What's in here?
All right.
I got it.
He sucks.
I...
Another golden arm.
I keep hearing the horn.
I'm going to go up.
Stop fucking breathing in my ear.
It's like ASMR.
Leave me the fuck alone.
He takes a sip and then he goes...
Why would you jump off?
I don't like this level.
I really don't.
I'm trying to jump onto the stupid platforms over there.
Oh, my freaking god.
Why would I jump off?
I'm not jumping up.
I'm trying to get off the ladder.
I can't just walk forward.
I have to jump like that.
I'm holding on for dear life.
What do I do?
Do I let go of space?
Should I let go of space?
I think if I let go of space, I pull myself up, right?
Weird dinosaur raptor guard.
All right.
Pig noise.
Whoa.
Got him.
Did I find a door?
I got a door.
Oh, my head.
I can't open this.
Come on.
So what am I doing up here?
Clean your face here.
A little bit sweaty.
This way.
I only have two earbuds in so I can tell where this horn is.
The game is too dark.
It's dark.
I know.
I'm trying to make it brighter.
By the way, why is it doing this?
It is dark, isn't it?
I don't know why it's so dark.
Is that better?
That's better.
Yeah.
It's meant to be dark.
I know, but like, come on.
We're gamers.
We're streamers.
I want to be able to see.
All right.
Honest to god, I think I have to go back down.
Wait.
No, I don't.
Check this shit out.
We're going to Donkey Kong Country this shit right now.
There's a rope.
Where's the rope?
Rope arrow.
This doesn't work.
It only...
It doesn't...
I want to reload then because that sucks.
It only works on wood.
Oh, that's annoying.
That's annoying.
All right.
I got to go back down.
Get the arrows ready.
Go down the ladder.
What is all this?
Hold on.
Ladder right there, too.
Trinkets?
Nope.
Are we trinket up here?
What's the point of this?
It has to...
It can't just be for no reason.
It has to be a point to do this, right?
What's the point?
For realism?
To avoid enemies.
Hey!
Somebody's shooting arrows at me.
Who's shooting arrows?
I hear arrows firing at me.
I don't know from what direction.
Don't go down there.
Okay.
They're going around in a circle.
Wait.
What did I do that for?
This is a giant circle.
What do I do?
Wait.
Hold on.
Here we go.
Oh, this place is so confusing.
This place is so confusing.
Can I go over here?
The music's getting louder.
I was trying to just fucking run by him.
What's that say?
Quintus.
I made it.
I got it.
Safe.
Jerma, be quiet.
My mother's trying to sleep.
Turn my volume down.
Turn me down.
I was trying to...
Whatever.
Okay.
I can take this out now.
I was trying to match the guy's speech.
Climb the ladder.
You dumb.
Get the holy water ready.
Okay.
We're fine.
I knew it was going to happen.
It's so wonky to jump off the ladder.
Why is Beard Jerma so mean?
I'm not mean.
What are you talking about?
I'm just chilling around.
I'm right there.
Just do it.
Is there ever a game that's gotten ladders right?
Dark Souls.
Dark Souls ladders were fine.
Because you didn't...
I have to kind of first person stick on them.
You actually climbed them.
So your character was just on it, you know?
But in FPS where you have to attach to a ladder and get off of a ladder.
I don't...
I don't think it's possible to make that good.
I don't.
It's such an awkward movement.
Just by...
You think you can snipe me from down there?
There it is.
Go up.
Thank you.
Now what?
Did I win?
Find the horn of Quintus.
Got it.
The ancient corruption was again contained.
To do more would have upset the balance.
But we knew to remain ever vigilant lest it resurface.
Neither the hammers nor the pagans could be trusted not to meddle.
Keeper annals.
I had some money to spare after disposing of the horn.
So it seemed time to invest in some new tools.
Farkas.
Functionals.
Farkas is one of the few merchants willing to risk selling to an independent like me.
And his prices are steep.
But the other choice is to let one of the so-called wardens give me orders.
And take a cut of my profits.
They've been after me for years to join one of their stables but I'm not interested.
Maybe they'll get the idea and give up.
More likely they'll just ramp up the threats.
Nothing I can't handle if I'm careful.
And lucky.
And my luck seems to have finally turned for the better.
Where we going now?
Now that you've got the finest in lockpicks you can go after more challenging and lucrative targets.
How about the local hammer temple?
Get at least a thousand loot.
Ahem.
Okay.
So I got lockpicks.
Gotta steal a bunch of loot.
I got a lot of money.
The fire arrows are explosions.
They're so loud and annoying.
I want at least a couple health potions.
Can I take more moss?
I don't use them though.
Playing on normal.
Yeah I'm a normal gamer.
The water arrows maybe I'll take a couple.
They're expensive though.
Fine I'll take one fire arrow and then a moss arrow.
And then just more of these.
Sure.
Alright sounds good.
Okay here we go.
Let me save it.
You get uh I'll get back here for you guys.
Save the game.
A hard save slot.
Okay.
How are we?
What?
Oh my god free stuff.
Why did I buy anything?
I have a this is all free.
Oh my goodness.
Holy that's a lot of stuff.
Okay what about this?
Anything else in here?
Alright so now I gotta I gotta trail the thugs who just tried to assassinate you
without being detected.
Where'd they go?
I don't know where the hell they are.
I don't know where are they?
In here?
I don't know.
I was busy stealing everything.
Oh well I'll find them.
They down here?
Oh they came down here.
What happened to me?
Did I just like I die?
Oh I thought I got like fucking like close to a giant trap and it instantly killed me.
I thought like I got sniped or something.
Alright um so I need to open up that hard save then.
Hey!
Oh what are you doing you idiot?
Alright I gotta go quick.
Is that Microsoft network noises?
Alright stay silent.
Stay quiet.
MSN sounds?
MSN chat.
That's so stupid.
I'm fine whatever.
No you I don't want to watch this guy die again.
Alright go go go.
You dumb.
I was reading chat.
Sorry.
Hail them.
Explosion arrows ready.
Explosion arrows at the ready.
Funny.
Funny joke.
He was doing the same.
No one is following you.
Relax.
Where'd they go?
I didn't see where they went.
Wait!
Moss arrows.
Shit!
Where'd they go?
Wait we're just going in a big circle.
It's gonna be loud.
Moss arrows.
Why do they keep stopping?
He's having an allergic reaction to the game?
What are you talking about?
Hey just spirit.
Where'd they go?
What?
Oh over here.
Ah you can't see me it's dark.
Idiot.
How?
This is...
This is long.
This is really...
His ass is too big.
Hey.
Pick his body up.
What are you thinking?
Pick his body up and throw him over here.
All right I'm in.
Hey.
These soft?
These are soft sounds right?
Let's pitch black right here.
What do I have?
What's my mission?
Time to show Ramirez who the real criminal mastermind is.
Break into his mansion and take what he values most.
His wealth.
Purse from his belt should make the point.
Loot the mansion.
All right.
I just need to get a lot of money.
Not going that way.
Give me that key.
This guy's got a key.
Somebody get coming?
Oh shit.
Don't go.
Just wait.
It's fine.
It's not for this door.
I thought I was gonna throw it further.
I have lockpicks?
This doesn't work on this door.
I have to get through here.
Try another shape.
I want to be able to hide in here.
Really?
Ooh.
Let's do the paintings.
Is that the Dana DeVito guy from Hercules?
Who is that?
Come on.
Something secret back here.
Oh wait.
I do have other shapes.
You're right.
All right.
That's all right.
Stop.
I know you can't see shit.
Leave me alone.
Can I take out the?
All right.
I'm throwing a flashbang.
Is someone there?
Everybody close your eyes.
Close your eyes.
I'm just not going over here.
I'm going the other way.
Stop seeing me.
I'm going a different way.
Those flashbangs are so bright.
A fair warning.
If I use those flashbangs,
they're going to be horrible.
So just be prepared for them.
I'll try to give you warning.
I'll say close your eyes.
Close your eyes.
Everybody close your eyes.
Open your eyes.
I'm not going to use it.
Will they see this or hear this?
Disguards it everywhere in this mission.
Oh my goodness.
How am I going to do this?
Lowercase scream.
Like...
Oh my god.
Hey, hi everybody.
Hi, I'm a thief.
Nobody can stop me.
What are you going to do about it?
Everybody close your eyes.
Close your eyes.
One, two, three.
They all went the wrong way.
I'm good.
Open the fucking door.
All right, I'm done.
I'm not.
This is the guard quarters.
Don't open that door.
Door stuck.
How much do I have so far?
How much have I stolen?
None.
There's got to be some expensive shit up here, right?
Give me a break.
Look at how expensive this carpet is.
Here we go.
What's in here?
Something.
Valuables.
Bingo.
Lord Ramirez, the reinforced walls and steel door
have been day-dutely installed
about your accounting room.
But I must warn you that we cannot guarantee
that against brick tunneling.
If you do not move the creatures
out of the basement into a more distant area,
we cannot be held responsible
for the potential damages.
All right, there's valuables over here.
Anything in there?
I don't know.
How much do I have so far?
I need a thousand.
All right, I got a hundred bucks right now.
I need like nine more items.
What does it look for?
Hidden panels on the walls.
I don't see anything in here.
All right, not a bad start.
Let's go.
He's walking.
Ooh, a rare painting.
No, that's a chair.
I thought it was a painting.
Hold on.
Why do you have nothing?
You have, why do you have nothing?
Really?
Keep going.
Where am I?
I'm on the second floor.
I could go down to the basement
and go kind of into his private counting chambers.
Okay, this topic, wait.
Let me check that other room.
Why does your mic have an echo?
It shouldn't have an echo.
All right, I open this door.
The key, lockpick.
Ooh, is that working?
I don't know what's happening here.
Got it, I guess.
Hold it.
All right, private stash.
What do we got?
What?
There's nothing even in here.
Don't press that button.
That's the Diet Coke button.
Ooh, expensive.
Very expensive stuff.
What was that?
200.
Well, I don't need that now.
Richard Dayanian.
I know with displeasure that, again,
one of my tough boys has been taken to Craig's Cleft.
May I remind you of the substantial donations I make to your office,
such that I may pursue business unhindered by idle scrutiny.
May I remind you as well of your predecessor's unfortunate end.
The rivers are so treacherous this time of year.
I trust that you will attend to this.
And if the hammers are too difficult for your policemen,
I trust as well that you'll let me know.
Here's something.
Private's book stash or something.
What is this?
What is this place?
This is weird.
That looks expensive.
Oh, my goodness.
Very expensive.
Nice.
Can I get in there?
How much more do I need?
Yeah.
Oh, I'm going to pick up.
All right.
I'm collecting money.
I'm doing all right.
Where?
Who?
Who's running?
I hear somebody.
Somebody up there next to the gigantic explosive barrel.
I can jump in that window.
I wonder if I should try it.
Not worth doing.
I can get it.
Nice.
OK, so what do I do with this?
What's the point of all this?
What did I just do that for?
What was this for?
Lock pick my way out of here?
Where is this guy?
The grass is not this loud.
Secret ladder.
Secret ladder in that fireplace.
Secret ladder in the fireplace.
The fireplace had a secret ladder.
Secret ladder?
Are you serious?
Go back and extinguish the fireplace.
There's a secret ladder in there.
There's a guy right here.
Oh, my goodness.
How did you wait for me?
You knew I was coming somehow.
Wow, that was terrifying.
All right.
Well, I got to be careful.
I'm just going to wait till they leave the room.
He's right here.
Peek your head out here.
I'm going to bludgeon you in the face.
The roof is really loud.
Moss.
I'm over the ledge.
I have an idea.
Close your eyes.
One, two, three.
I didn't want to fucking do that again.
How am I going to do this?
I got to get into the darkness here.
No.
I think I have to just wait till they get bored.
Use the bomb arrow?
I accidentally let go.
I slipped off.
There's no arrow.
I figured out why I miss.
There's no drop on these arrows.
They go in a straight line.
There's no drop.
All right.
One on one.
Let's go, buddy.
Oh, douche.
Touche.
I don't think this guy knows how to swing a sword.
That guy has never trained how to swing a sword.
Everybody have anything on them?
That was just a prop for that guy.
They don't have anything on them.
All right.
How could I miss that?
We're good to go.
I have no more fire arrows though.
Oh, dude.
You guys weren't kidding around.
This is a secret entrance here.
But now that's important.
Now this is important stuff here now.
Oh, hell yeah.
Somebody else's bedroom or something.
What's this?
Can I climb through here?
Can't get through this.
I can't go through it.
I'm trying to stuff in.
I can't.
How much money do I have now?
675.
No.
Total of 380.
I got 1,100.
I got it.
I have enough now.
Breaking his mansion.
Take what he values most.
The purse from his belt.
So I got to find his...
Where's his room?
I have enough.
All right.
Nice.
I got enough money.
Now I got to find his personal belt?
Is this his room?
Second floor, basement, Ramirez mansion.
I feel like his room is still somewhere.
He's in the basement.
Do I have to go to the basement?
I'm on the first floor now.
Keep going.
Did he say there was a creature down here?
Like don't...
Watch out for that creature that you kept down there or something, right?
I don't see a creature.
Still in the basement.
This is a pretty...
I got a key though.
Hell yeah.
There's an alarm.
Oh, is that him?
That's him.
I think that's him.
Is that him?
The king sends his regards.
No!
I wanted to get the...
Yeah, there's like a bunch of shit in here.
I want to get the money first.
I'll just end the mission.
No.
Really?
How do I get in here?
Does he have a key?
I can't open these.
Here we go.
Hell yeah.
What's in here?
The other one works for this too, doesn't it?
Thank you very much.
What do you got?
Open it up.
Open it!
Nice.
All right.
I just want to get all the items.
Here we go.
Hell yeah.
That coke button?
Eh.
All right.
Cutscene coming up.
That was a cool mission.
I like that one.
Stealing fur and fang of beasts for survival.
Then came the builder who brought us the hammer.
And with it we forged a new way of life.
Reject the hammer is to denounce the builder.
Book of hammers.
I was going to pay a base collection a visit,
but the thing is that they haven't divvied the boot-eaters' base.
Sounds like they could use it.
What do you mean the creature?
There's a creature down there or something that I can like...
What do you want me to do?
Steal the base from them.
They'll be so busy blaming each other no one will suspect an outsider.
You can milk the creature.
It's a meme.
Okay.
Well, I don't...
I don't really care.
The guild's hideout is beneath the casino.
I have a rough map of the complex I got from sources from the inside.
Once I'm in the overlord's fancy,
I'll have to search for the secret entrance to the hideout.
I have to be careful.
The downwinders know me all too well.
If they catch sight of me, they'll know I took the base.
Nobody said you should really skip this mission.
They don't just kill me for trespassing.
Does this one suck?
Finding the base may prove difficult since I have no idea where it is.
It should be a hot topic of conversation among the down...
Skip this mission, it sucks.
Yes, this one sucks.
This is the worst mission in the game.
Skip this one.
I don't think I can skip missions.
This one has an incredibly confusing layout.
I mean, is it possible that I could bunny hop all the way to the end and pick up the item?
I skipped this one in my playthrough too.
Really?
Why is it so bad?
All right, break into the downwind thieves guild by breaking into the gambling den.
The overlord's fancy.
Thrive the sapphire vase.
Guild mates stealing the vase more difficult.
Make them pay.
Don't leave with less than a thousand in loot.
Get out of the guild and bat...
All right, so just take a thousand bucks.
Get the vase and get out.
Is he enough?
Uh, yeah, I'm taking like at least two of these.
Maybe not that many.
See you in four hours.
I can't even...
I don't think I can skip.
I'll figure it out.
Whatever.
I like the water arrows though.
They're very useful.
All right, that sounds good to me.
Okay, so yeah, that is a...
I feel like I have to go like this and lean in real close and get to about here.
And then the girl from the exorcist is going to scream in my face.
What is this map?
Okay.
Howdy.
What did I do wrong?
This guy's going to step on it.
I'm going to make you bleed.
Somebody step on it.
So what?
They don't like that I'm...
What do they don't...
All right, let me just...
Okay, they don't like me at all.
They don't want to see me at all.
Open the door.
Fuck you.
Okay.
So nobody can see me, which is weird because how am I supposed to walk by this?
Oh, what?
I can't even exist?
What are you talking about?
What am I doing?
I'm like passing out.
What's happening?
I think I have to sit here.
No, now he hasn't given me the password.
Are you tapping me?
He's tapping me?
And I'm standing here listening to Dano tell you the password.
Do you think he's going to let me if I'm not in the guild?
Or you think I'm lackwood enough not to remember it?
Shudder.
I'll put up with your airs.
I got you now, Tapper.
Shudder.
I'll put up with your airs.
Over here!
But if you start putting it like I'm not much of a fool, there will...
That guy still had to get his point across.
Excuse me?
He didn't see me at all.
Let me in too!
Big mistake.
You left the door wide open.
What are you doing in there?
You bastard!
Open up for me, please!
Knock, knock!
Anybody home?
See you right...
Late time.
What do I do now?
Let him talk.
I'm just every orc in every movie.
Let them do their little cutscene and I'll move on.
Not to remember it?
Shudder.
I'll put up with your airs a ways.
But if you start putting it like I'm not much of a fool, there will be blood.
Now open this door!
Pop the door, motherfucker!
Oh shit, there's a lady right there.
Ah!
I just...
I just might...
I just have...
It's a GTA after just roast up of people.
All right, relax, relax, relax.
Didn't I save after this?
I saved after this already, didn't I?
You want to argue with the lords?
What's the password?
Whatever.
All right, just close my eyes and just wait.
Open the door, okay?
Well, now he hasn't given me the password.
Are you tapping me?
Security is necessary to prevent...
And I'm standing here listening to Dan O'Tell you the password.
You think he's gonna let me if I'm not in the guild?
Or you think I'm liquid enough not to remember it?
This reminds me of a local like car commercial.
If you start putting it like I'm much of a fool, there will be blood.
This is Larry and Steve's.
Larry and Steve's auto empire.
Come on down and visit me and Steve.
We'll take good care of you.
Are we good?
Where did he come from?
All right, I'm going this way.
I'm not just gonna go in the front door.
I think I got away with it.
I did.
Okay, let's go.
So I gotta get into the casino.
As you stole that from...
You know, there's a Justin Roiland joke.
Relax.
Okay, so is this the casino?
Save it.
It's so bright out here too.
Turn around.
Aye.
Okay, well, this is great.
Slowly walks up this hallway.
That's really fantastic.
You don't come all the way over here, right?
What the...
Okay, I'm hidden right here.
I could probably just smoke him, right?
This is dark.
Will there be keys on you?
All right, let's just take this guy.
Money helping doesn't work when you have a person.
Kind of does.
Yeah, it does.
All right, get into the casino.
Save it right here.
What is this place?
It's Merlin's workshop.
I don't know what this is.
It's locked.
None of these open.
Deliveries to the back door only.
Oh, I'm delivery.
I got a delivery for you.
Delivery.
Deliveries to the back door.
Hey.
Oh.
Wait, patience.
You don't come all the way over here, right?
Hope not.
All right, I'm in.
Oh, shit.
Where's his feet?
Oh, he's coming back.
I didn't know that that opened up to right there.
Oh, give me a break.
You didn't hear anything.
How would you hear that?
All right, I swear.
I gotta kill this guy right now.
I gotta wrap around and kill this guy.
Fuck.
I didn't mean to quick save.
Ron saved.
Ron has been officially saved.
We're okay.
All right, I gotta be more careful.
The door out of the way before I have a meltdown.
All right, relax.
Slow down.
Keep your mouth shut.
I'm gonna let you live.
You're gonna keep your mouth shut?
Gave him a chance.
I gave him an opportunity.
This looks like Wolfenstein.
Like this, the other ground.
What's down here?
I'll do that later.
Did he have a key on him or anything?
Line it up.
He wasn't doing anything?
If he had gotten up, I'm in a lot of trouble.
That's one less person to walk around and find me.
You have bloodlust.
I don't have bloodlust.
I'm just trying to think things realistically.
I'm just playing a video game.
If that guy gets up, I'm in trouble.
And you know for a fact I'm gonna throw a box at somebody
and he's gonna go from this line like this to
Oh, what was that?
And run straight out the door.
Like I'm not gonna have that chance.
I'm gonna go in here.
I don't wanna get hurt though.
Can I crouch and...
I have to take that damage.
That sucks.
Why am I...
This is like...
What's that game?
Boardwalk Empire.
A game with the music and it's hard
and you run around through the hallways and it's top down.
Hotline Miami.
Secret door.
All right.
Where am I?
They're so busy gambling their money away.
Notice if I take a bit.
Oh, he got a big key on him.
There's nobody even down here.
Just take everything.
Shit.
There are people here.
Can I play Blackjack?
How am I supposed to get by this?
I guess I can go...
Wait, there might be more stuff over here.
There is.
Of course there is.
Yes.
All right.
There's more tables over here.
Now over here.
I don't spin the roulette table.
I did not know that was gonna happen.
All right.
I gotta go this way.
No, actually let me go over here first.
Jeremy, you gotta...
I'm not...
There's nobody to milk.
Relax.
Piece of shit.
I swear to God.
This guy's walking around.
All right.
Take out the torches.
Thanks for the reminder, video game.
Much better.
You don't even see anything.
Shut up.
All right.
Nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice.
Fuck.
There's so much stuff in here.
What am I supposed to do about this?
Look at all the stuff that's back here.
They have light over here.
I know.
But there's so much cool stuff.
I guess I could...
Can I go around the other side?
Moss arrows?
That's a good idea.
That's a really...
That's actually a brilliant idea.
Oh, what do I do?
Too jumpy.
Who's there?
Hey, there's an intruder here.
Whatever.
I'm just gonna leave.
What's with this light?
Dude.
I thought I saw something.
Guess it was nothing.
Did I just see what I think I saw?
Stay right there, Garrett.
Oh, shit.
I'm a genius, I think.
Oh, he's got a gold key.
All right.
Let me in.
Oh, my God.
I figured...
I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it.
I'm stuck on the guy's body.
I'm stuck on his body.
Get off his body, please.
Cut up.
Okay, I got the one.
I don't care.
Oh, shit.
Don't hurt me.
Get away, get away, get away, get away.
Don't get away with the explosion.
I can't go over there.
Walk on that.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Don't turn the alarm on.
Got him.
Come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here.
Hide.
Hide, hide.
Hide, hide, hide.
He's gonna step on the landmine.
I'm good.
You stepped on a landmine, my friend.
You stepped on a landmine and you're fine?
Thank God you have potion on you.
Can I, like, get rid of their bodies?
I don't think this works.
I'm gonna drink that potion.
What's going on?
Oh, my God, you have money.
What's happening?
Wait, are they not...
I thought they were dead.
They're only knocked out?
I thought you said I was killing people.
I didn't know I was doing this.
I thought I was just getting rid of the bodies.
Okay.
Oh, he sees me.
He sees me.
The other guy's just blocking him.
Secret!
Can't break that.
Water arrow, please.
I'm not gonna do it.
I promised I wouldn't do it ever again.
Didn't he have...
Yeah, okay, I got it, right?
I got it.
All right, secret in the fireplace.
Use the back door, 47, if you must visit.
I don't give a damn what it does to your clothes.
I will not risk Ruben's scum following you in.
Until I get my key back and the vase sitting on my mantelpiece,
you're just going to have to tolerate the inconvenience.
I need the sapphire vase and I need a thousand bucks.
Sapphire vase.
Where would I be?
What an awful map.
I might as well just guess.
I have absolutely no idea where this would be.
So Overlord's Fancy?
I wonder...
In the fire.
Hold on.
Did he go over here?
He did not, okay.
He doesn't know where I am.
You wuss.
Wuss!
Don't let that guy ring the bell!
Why do you have to just run all over the place?
What are you doing?
Okay, I'm fine.
I'm supposed to be a dead lady too.
Let me give it to you straight.
The guy that you work for is a real bad guy.
He's a mean person.
He's corrupt.
He has all kinds of awful shit going on.
I'm just telling you right now,
I'm giving you an opportunity for you to go,
for you to get out and leave.
I'm going to take a bunch of shit from this guy
because he's a bad guy.
Someone's searching for something and we'll get the tap.
Exactly what I'm talking about.
Exactly.
So you and I are on the same page.
I mean, if you feel like it,
you can just kind of forget that I was here
and we can just go on with our days.
Yeah, there's a dead guy right here, but don't worry.
I'm not going to shoot another arrow at you.
I know this is going to be really gruesome,
but this is just how it is.
Welcome to the business.
I don't know if you knew this person or not,
but they were potentially bad.
They were trying to shoot me with arrows.
I thought we had an understanding.
How do I get down here?
Over here, he has a sword.
Oh, yes.
Hi.
How are you?
There ain't nobody left.
All the guards are dead.
I just, you know what?
I'm just trying to help here.
There's nobody left.
I killed all the guards.
Yes, I have a sword.
Yes, I have a bow and arrow.
I'm not going to hurt you.
I'm not going to.
Please leave.
Go into like a Minecraft gold dungeon.
Oh, holy shit.
Oh my God, you led me to the sacred room.
Uh, Davey, till Dono and Ruben quit their bitching,
best we just stick to our own turf.
I'm too much Dono's man to risk it.
All right.
He has a sword.
This lady, I swear to God.
Okay, I've not gone down here yet.
Let's save it.
I wonder if there's something down here.
This doesn't open.
Where am I going?
It's the creature.
This creature, it's a spider.
Relax.
It's loud.
I can't break those though.
Am I going the right way?
Dude, okay.
I have no idea.
I hope this is the right way.
I couldn't do anything about that.
Thank you.
I said I heard vase.
I heard vase action.
I heard vase.
Holy shit, you're awful.
Oh, okay.
You got me with that one.
That one was in the head.
That one was in the face.
Yeah, that was actually not bad.
That was not bad.
But now you pissed me off.
Climb the ladder.
All right.
Vase is down here somewhere.
My god.
Huh?
Oh, now you have a sword.
I don't like it.
Stop running.
Open this door.
Open this door right now.
Shit.
I'm actually kind of glad I got stuck.
Anybody have the keys on them?
No.
I need health.
Cucumber.
Save it here.
Now, what is going on with this?
This is blocked.
47.
What does it say something about 47?
What was it?
I have to get in here.
I can't get in here though.
Is there a drill?
I think I got to go this way.
What do you want me to tell you?
Like, I gave her like 100 opportunities to leave.
She's just yelling and she's going to get attention called to here.
All right.
Now, what do I need to do?
I need the sapphire vase.
47 is over here.
What do I do with this though?
I can go over.
I don't know.
There's a tunnel in the water.
You mean like down here?
Look at you.
Can I open that?
Can't open that.
100 opportunities.
I did.
I really did.
47.
There it is.
All right.
47.
48.
What is this for?
Should I just do them both?
Is there something?
There are doors.
Open 48.
Literally writing in the wall.
Good puzzle.
I mean, yeah.
But so what?
Milk?
So I opened the door that's labeled 47.
I remember even a door labeled 47.
Get me out of the water.
What's this?
So I opened that.
Does that do anything?
Should up here or something?
I don't know.
Yeah.
47.
48.
Something back here?
I have no idea.
49.
Well, shit.
I don't know where to go.
I remember this level was really-
There's a window on the other end.
Two doors in tunnel from before.
Window.
Like back here?
Uh, like here?
What's over here?
Actually, unironically skip this.
This level sucks.
I think I just found it.
Nothing's so tame.
He can scarf out the way he came quick enough.
But he don't want to go till he sweeps everything on the dresser.
Jewelry, candlesticks, whatnot.
Into his sack.
Gets halfway down the stairs.
When the sack starts leaping about-
This is like Owen Wilson.
He's cut the lady's cat, too, from the sack.
Everything falls out except the cat.
And that's halfway up his arm with claws every which way.
He had to jump in the river to get the damn thing off.
Left a trail of blood and water over half the city just going home.
Oh, actually, I bugged the cutscene.
Perfect.
Hey.
Into the dark, into the dark.
Down, down, down.
Okay, save.
This guy was stealing something from the dressers.
I gotta get this other guy, too.
He walks all the way over here.
Watch.
Here we go.
No, he didn't see anything.
This is a good hiding spot.
I'm gonna use this as a hiding spot.
Yeah, this is a good spot to hide.
I can go even deeper or let me let me peruse this area first.
Probably something here.
Is that money behind the bed?
It is.
Very nice.
Explosive barrel.
Oh, come on.
I thought these were bags of like Scrooge McDuck money.
Whatever.
There he is.
Got him.
Thank God.
All right.
What's in here?
Nothing.
Why are the bricks sideways?
I don't know.
Anybody in here?
Treasure in here, though.
Oh, hell yeah.
I definitely have to be at the threshold now, right?
I don't have a thousand bucks yet.
How?
That seems impossible.
Can I get this one, too?
I can't unsee the vertical bricks now.
It's weird.
Oh, nice.
Don't throw a piece of dynamite in here, please.
Nothing?
What a terrible room.
Give me a break.
Too many imaginings.
It was real.
Don't think you can hide for-
Yeah, you-
We've got an intruder.
How have you not triggered this?
Excuse me.
I guess it was nothing.
What's that?
Oh, shit.
Someone's coming.
That I'm hidden?
No.
Skip this level.
I'm probably-
I'm almost at the end of the level, probably.
We're probably right at the end.
For the last time, tell the maid to stay out of the banner room
and don't touch anything in it.
It is the room where I can have peace of mind.
My collection is too precious to risk any clum-
Okay.
Any clum-liness.
So, hit the banner.
It's all of it.
Go to the banner room.
Oh, someone coming.
You're not even halfway.
You're not ha-
What?
How am I not halfway?
You're halfway through or less?
This mission is the worst.
How do I skip it?
I don't think I can skip this.
Press Ctrl-Alt-Shift and put your entire fist in your mouth.
Okay.
I'm right-
Look, I'm in the guy's quarters.
What's going on?
How are you?
Nice to see you.
Somebody hear that?
Right there.
Oh, no.
Sorry.
Line aside him.
See you later.
Who's the next guy?
All right.
I'm up here now.
Private quarters.
Let's go.
All right.
What's this dude's name?
I don't know.
Hey!
Get-
Oh my god.
Stop splashing around.
Oh, you idiot.
What'd he say?
Where are you?
Okay.
Here he is.
All right.
Don't touch my things.
Don't touch my things, right?
Where's the key?
Remember, did you plug in the smelloscope for this game?
You needed to clear some levels.
Oh.
You can't be serious.
Not when I'm this far into the game.
Who makes doors that open like this?
Why?
Open the whole fucking way.
How do I open this?
That's the safe right there.
I need a key to get in there or something.
Is it in his room?
With a key.
With a lockpick.
Key in the other house.
I mean, other house.
Note.
This is possibly the most complicated map in the game.
From conversations or scrolls, you can easily miss-
Hold on.
This is important.
You can easily miss.
You will gain the following knowledge.
Donald has Lord Randall's vase locked in his private safe in the West.
Ruben has stolen the key to Donald's safe.
He's also entrusted his house key to his right-hand man, Tom.
You must first find Tom, get the key to Ruben's house,
steal Donald's safe key from Ruben's quarters,
then retrieve the vase from Donald's safe, bro.
I'm in the wrong house?
Is there a console command to skip the game?
What's the console command?
Just play the game.
All right.
Well, I know where this guy's house is.
The other house on the other side of the game?
This is Suncoast Ballacy.
Are you having fun?
Yeah, kind of.
Okay.
Control-Alt-Shift-End.
That's not how that-
You made that up.
Control-Alt-Shift-End.
As you made that up as a funny joke.
Control-Shift-Alt-End?
I feel like it's gonna-
It's gonna do-
Control-Shift-Alt-End.
I feel like I could have accidentally pressed all those
at some point in the game.
I'm sorry.
I skipped it.
Everyone told me to skip it.
Look, this is an old game.
Sometimes old games have, like, hard, weird levels.
A lot of people in chat were saying
this next level is, like, the best level in the game.
I was content-
How many levels are in the game?
Who impressed me to steal something from a magical soul?
Little is known about Constantine except that he is an eccentric new face in the city,
and mostly keeps to himself.
This next level is a skipper.
Victorious says the sword will probably be-
We'll see.
It will be well-protected-
I now have that power.
Security systems.
She also mentioned that the guards are tough,
and our mansion is confusing to navigate in.
They're telling me it's confusing already.
This place was constructed recently,
so I've had to pull an observation and hearsay.
Sounds like the place is a bit of a maze.
I guess if you're rich enough, you can build any sort of madhouse.
It's a maze?
This is gonna be a challenging job,
but it'll pay the last few I've taken.
Skip.
Well, I know I can at least complete the game by skipping.
As usual, the front entrance managed to find another-
This game is fun, though.
This is cool.
Of course, once I've picked up the sword, I'll still have to worry about-
You guys have to remember, this game was made in, like, 1989.
Or something.
It was a long time ago.
Okay.
Find and obtain the sword.
It's probably on an upper level of the mansion.
Take the opportunity to steal other valuables.
Leave the mansion with the sword.
A lot of stuff.
I want more of these.
How much do these cost?
Uh, another mine?
No, the bombs-
They just don't do-
This caused a lot of problems.
The mines suck.
They're loud.
They don't go off right away.
They're terrible.
And flashes flash me, too.
They're awful.
You know, I'm just gonna get more fire arrows.
Just get another one.
These at least kill people.
But I probably should get a heal-
Okay, yeah, another potion.
I need a potion.
All right, let's go.
All right.
Get into the mansion.
Steal the sword.
You got it.
And there's a guarded entrance right-
This is perfect.
Come back here.
Perfect.
You can't see shit.
Come back here.
Don't come this close.
Thank you very much.
I'll take that.
Thank you.
I don't see anything now.
Wait till he turns around.
I say, where'd you come from?
And I'd like to know what happened there.
He saw-
Wait, he saw me run?
Are you scared?
Ooh, not very good swordsman, are you?
Aha.
Nice key you got there.
I love how, like, when something happens,
I like look to-
I like look over to you, right?
I like look to you.
Almost like I can't believe it,
so you must not be able to believe it either.
I'm looking at you like you're a person.
Like, can you believe what just happened?
I'm over here for reassurance
that, like, I'll turn
and I'll see, like, a bunch of-
Oh my god, dude, that was fucked up.
Come get me.
Try sneaking.
That's a good trick.
I got the key off of you.
All right.
I'm just going in the front door, man.
Whoa.
What was that?
Oops.
Oh, shut up.
I've already used so much health already.
It's bad news.
All right, I'm in.
I got in the front door, though.
Now we slow down.
Be careful with everything.
I steal a bunch of stuff.
All right, nice.
I'm gonna come in-
Oh, you gotta be kidding me.
Right when I open the door, he's there.
You sidestepped me.
I got sidestepped.
He just led me to the treasure chest.
What a dope.
This is the main entrance here.
We're gonna wrap this way.
So the sword is up in the top floor.
The same room.
A big vase.
Stairs- I'm not done yet.
I think there's more stuff here than there is.
It's all just bottles.
That's it.
Oh, this is pretty.
That's really pretty.
Who's hearing me?
Get out of my way.
Why am I stuck on the chandelier still?
All right.
I'm just going the way that I was supposed to go.
And it's this way.
Take out the club.
Let's go.
What a weird-
I feel like I'm on the set of a Nickelodeon sitcom.
Like, what is this?
This is kind of creepy.
Info right here.
What does it say?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's weird.
That's a weird door to have in your house.
That's very strange.
Oh my god.
I thought it was speaking to me.
It's weird.
It's definitely a hidden thing in here, no doubt.
They have things that shoot out of their mouths.
Don't move.
This is tripped.
Yeah, this is trapped.
You know what?
I'm good.
Oh, hell yeah.
Definitely.
Where is it?
In like gold nugget up here.
That it?
Pretty good.
I think that's it.
It's gold rock.
Dr. Seuss house.
I don't like this place.
I heard a shot.
I was in a really good place.
I gotta stop yelling too.
I'm just like yelling for no reason.
I'm just making loud sounds.
Like, I heard a shot!
Like, you could just say that you heard a shot.
You don't have to yell it into the microphone.
They're all here.
They're watching.
They can see.
You said you were going to be a normal person and not be a weirdo anymore.
I mean, I think that went out the window.
I tried.
That was my New Year's resolution.
But all New Year's resolutions don't work.
I did it for like a day.
Is this a meltdown stream?
I don't think so.
No way.
I mean, I've been a little active, but I've been active.
I wouldn't say this is a meltdown.
It's not even close.
I'm just kind of having fun with the video game.
I already went down there.
It's going to shoot again, isn't it?
Oh!
Oh, that was fucked.
Oh, this wall.
That scared the shit out of me.
What do you think?
How do you think I feel?
It happened to me.
What do you think?
How do you think I feel?
It happened to me.
I'm the one that got hit by the car.
You watched me get hit by the car.
I had to get hit by the car.
Your scream was scarier than the thing.
Okay, don't.
I gotta be careful.
All right, don't get trolled by the stupid joke room.
All right, go ahead.
Three, two, one, shoot it.
What the hell am I doing?
Is it turn?
Oh, all right.
This Charlie and the Chocolate Factory fun house.
Wait, will he get hit by this?
This will shoot him, right?
Someone will.
Whoa, what's down here?
Okay, where's he going?
Oh, fuck.
That was do or die right there.
I had to do that.
Oh, it was over.
Where is this guy?
Down here?
Oh, shit.
Oh, that hurts right in the head.
All right, we're good.
I want to go in that weird door on the ground.
What am I doing?
Is there a second floor, third floor?
What am I doing here?
Should I go in there?
You can cheese guards.
Shoot him.
You just sounded like Finn from Adventure Time.
This place, fuck this level.
This level sucks.
This is, it's just like a trap fun house.
What is this?
All right, I guess I'll walk over here
and get eaten alive by the monsters.
Get off of me.
This place is huge.
I gotta go up.
There's the bug room.
Okay, let's open this one with a pick lock.
Where are we at?
Gash.
Very nice.
All right, am I on the top floor?
No.
Where's the, there's another floor?
Where?
This looks like the top floor.
What happened to those people?
Okay, nice.
I gotta find a staircase up.
Secret in the fireplace.
I think there might be.
Look at that.
Right above.
Looks like a button.
Place, shit goes.
Okay, whatever.
Hello.
Oh, hell yeah.
All right, I gotta find a staircase.
This is the main entrance.
This goes down, I believe.
Yeah, so I gotta go up and in here.
I've been pretty much everywhere.
I've been everywhere.
I can go up from here.
Oh, you unlucky bastard.
I don't know how you turned around.
Give me that key right now.
Give me the key.
I gotta put him behind the,
at least put him behind.
Stealth game, by the way.
I know.
It's, I am stealthing.
I'm, I'm in a fun house right now.
It's hard to stealth me.
You don't even know what room you're coming out from
or going into.
Okay.
Oh, more stuff.
Is this the big dining room?
Yep.
Remember, this is violent.
You fell off.
How long, how long do you think I could have
like an underbite for before somebody like,
that's new to the channel really,
like is like, what, what's this?
What are you doing?
I gotta go over this way.
What the fuck?
I need more potions, I think.
That hurts to do that.
He had a key too.
All right.
I didn't, I haven't been out here.
Marlin Brando.
Whoa, weird stuff over there.
That's pretty cool garden.
That's not a bad garden.
That's cool.
Night.
Magical tree stump.
Wait, this is, this is underneath the,
where, what is this?
This is really weird.
Can I climb up here?
There's a door up here.
Wait, rope arrow.
What's the point of this being in the game?
It only works on wood.
I, what, wood, apparently it only works on wood.
We're going to like Jurassic Park now.
Okay.
Time to go visit the Keebler Elves.
This is so strange.
What is this all doing here?
Yeah, this is crazy.
Oh, there's your wood.
Yeah.
Can I go up?
You can't, I can't even shoot up.
I can't go up.
There's nothing to even do this for.
What is going on?
Wasn't I just in somebody's mansion?
Walls or trees?
Wait, I can go down here.
I was already here.
Uh, a swim?
I wonder if this takes me somewhere.
Please take the next left you see.
I'm not joking.
This is left.
All right, I took the left.
Garden?
Um, wait a minute.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait a minute.
I haven't saved it in a long time.
You won't come in the water.
We're safe.
What's he doing?
Get in the water.
Get back in the water.
Did I make it through this garden?
Is this a new area that I haven't?
No, I've been here before.
Guys, I have no idea what's going on right now.
Back on the second floor.
Let's open this one.
You gotta follow the music.
Thanks for staying up late, by the way.
I know we're at about 930 Pacific,
which means we're past midnight Eastern,
so thanks for staying up.
This looks important.
Nothing in here, though.
It's gonna be a trap room.
Crouch.
E and I already read this one.
Pastor, the one who trespassed your greenhouse
is chastised.
He did not know the rules,
but spies there no longer.
Trespassed your greenhouse?
Is that where I just was?
I think I was just there.
I didn't go this way.
Really?
Can I not open this?
Nice try.
Good try.
I will commend you for the effort.
All right, third floor.
No, still the second floor.
PB&J or grilled cheese?
I would say grilled cheese.
I gotta be in the mood for a PB&J,
but a grilled cheese I could eat at any moment,
of any day, of any time.
It could be two o'clock in the morning.
It could be eight o'clock in the morning.
I could have just woken up.
I could have just, you know, gone to sleep.
I think I'm where I'm supposed to be.
No, don't pull this shit on me right now.
I'm already kind of getting tired,
and this is one of those
everything's upside down things.
Oh, yeah.
Um, I'm going up.
Going up.
You eat grilled cheese and you sleep.
I mean, I don't.
I'm just, I'm just saying it's good.
Whenever.
You can enjoy a grilled cheese
at any moment of the day.
And what, I'm looking for the sword.
How do you guys even,
I feel bad for you guys.
I really do.
Honest to God.
How do you navigate all this?
You must have a headache all day.
Oh, my God.
I don't, I do.
I'm done.
I think I'm done.
This is really, this game is really fun.
I'm done.
What's your favorite type of cheese?
Uh, I like Swiss cheddar,
provolone, um,
Super Mario tubes.
Uh, what else do I like?
I like, um,
just give me the sacred baseball bat.
Whatever the fuck it is.
Get out of my way.
Give me the sacred sword.
Whatever it is.
Where is it?
Parmesan is, yeah, I love Parmesan.
Shea Parmesan is fantastic.
Did you hear that?
I thought it was like giggling.
It was like a giggling like gnome person.
You've got a bow too.
You are in my way.
Oh, my God.
Sacred sword.
Get me out.
How do I get out?
Shit.
Step on it.
The mines are worthless.
This is the most worthless item in the whole game.
Worthless item.
What's the worth?
I can't even say worthless.
I can't even say worthless item.
I hear somebody,
it's like somebody's screaming.
Do you hear this?
Step on this.
Somebody's going like,
get out.
Get out.
Don't get me out of here.
Somebody's laughing.
You heard it.
What?
That was like the...
That was like fucking...
This is Mario shit.
This is the Mario...
This is like Mario 64.
I leave.
I can't open this from this side.
Of course, I can't.
Get out of my way.
Oh, this way.
This way.
What was that?
Get me out.
Oh, shut up.
The music is getting scarier and scarier.
I'm trapped in this goddamn house.
I'm trapped in this house.
I'm stuck here.
This way.
And then I could go right.
Yep.
And then...
Here's the...
That...
This is the entrance.
This is the lady was laughing
and making all kinds of weird sounds.
That was terrifying.
That was fun level though.
That was a good one.
It gets worse?
Gets much worse?
Oh, God.
Hello, Jerma.
This is SpongeBob.
Do you have any questions for me?
Yes.
PBJ or grilled cheese, SpongeBob?
Which one?
Animated.
You were being tested.
Do you understand?
And I must say you more than live up to your reputation.
Wait.
You are quite an extraordinary thief testing me.
What is it you want from me?
Do you have Satan hooves?
I am a Tim Mr. Garret.
But there are some items that are not available for purchase.
They must be acquired using other means.
In this case, the item in question would be best acquired by thieving.
Not simple thieving.
No, just like yourself.
What exactly is this item?
It is the gemstone.
He's got like goat hooves.
For its unusual appearance.
Yes, kept hidden in the sealed cathedral
deep inside the halls of the scum hammerites.
Oh, but forgive me.
You are possibly friendly with the order of the hammer.
No, fanatics make unreliable friends.
Excellent.
I am prepared to offer you quite a sum.
A hundred thousand upon receipt of the eye.
I don't see how I can refuse such an offer.
Marvelous.
Victoria can fill you in on all the particulars.
Is this the final mission?
And Mr. Garret, the sword, keep it.
You have earned it.
But also, I believe you'll find it useful in your quest.
No, okay.
There's a few more.
This is mission number six, right?
Come the time of peril did the grounded gape
and did the dead rest unquiet against us.
Our bands of iron and hammers of stone prevailed not.
And some did doubt the builder's plan.
But the seals held strong and the few did triumph.
And the doubters were in chat
thinking he wouldn't beat the last level.
But he did.
Laying into the minions' ride at Universal Studios.
Pretty lit.
I don't know.
I'm done.
I'll see you guys tomorrow.
Not tomorrow.
What's the day?
Saturday, okay.
All right.
I've got a question for people in chat here.
I plan on streaming again on Wednesday.
I was gonna do VR soon.
I think I want to do one more game stream.
I want to do Everhood.
But I also kind of want to finish this.
How much more time is in this game?
Another couple hours maybe?
Two, three hours?
This is fun.
It's a little old.
It's a little crunchy.
But I'm having a good time.
So what I'll probably do is on Wednesday.
It's probably two.
There's like eight missions.
Thief 2 is better.
Oh, there's a lot more.
Okay.
This might take more than another stream.
All right.
Well, I'm down to play it again.
I know you just...
You got sucked into a wormhole.
Oh, yeah, I'll play.
Yakuza again.
I'll play Sam and Max again.
Season three.
Oh, yeah, I'll play.
No umbrellas allowed.
Oh, yeah, I'll finish.
I'll finish Hollow Knight.
Oh, I'll...
I know.
I'll do Monster Rancher 2.
Trust me.
I know.
Or Hollow Knight.
But no, I actually will probably...
I'll probably do this again.
Wednesday, I want to do Everhood.
But at this time, I also kind of want to maybe do this too.
And or I'll just do this.
Maybe I won't do VR yet.
Maybe I'll finish this or play some more.
If not, then this is really fun.
It's cool to play for a while.
Wednesday, Everhood's the plan.
But, you know, we'll see.
What about all of this part two?
No, all this part one was enough.
Let me save it though.
Yeah, let me just...
Let me get prepared.
This is the...
Seems like a big mission.
Constant...
Oh, I actually get the new sword too.
I'll take one of these.
Two of these.
And I'll take a few...
I'll take a few of these.
I think that's all I can afford.
Okay.
Very interesting.
Save the game.
Hard save.
Right here in the beginning.
Right at the top.
I think I'm going to call it here.
That was really fun.
If we see this again, then we see it again.
If not, then that was thief gold.
I would give that a stamp of thumbs up.
I had a good time.
Hope you did too.
Are you going to put the ring light around your neck?
If it's safe, I would do it.
I don't know.
I'll see you guys on Wednesday, around 4 o'clock Pacific.
And I know that we're starting late a lot recently.
My sleep schedule is kind of all over the place.
Once I correct it, and I can pull back my sleep schedule a little bit,
we'll try to start more around that 2-2.30 Pacific area.
Oh yeah.
That was thief.
I will see you guys on Wednesday.
As always, thanks for watching.
Go to the credits.
Yeah, another reason why I want to start earlier is because I know that 4 o'clock Pacific,
if I stream for more than 5 or 6 hours,
it starts to get really late for people.
And I don't want to keep everybody up crazy late.
You know, 9, 10 o'clock Pacific is 12, 1 a.m. Eastern,
which is just an ungodly hour EU.
I'd like to try to stay in that, at least most of North America.
Doesn't have to stay up too late.
I'm sorry, EU friendos.
I live in the Pacific time zone, and I stream in the afternoon.
I'm very sorry.
It's the way it is though.
We have a 15-hour difference.
That's ridiculous to me.
Yeah, we'll at least be doing Everhood.
Keep an eye out if we do something else.
And then I'm probably going to get back into VR.
Hitman VR comes out on the 20th, the second that releases.
We're going to play it.
We're going to play it on the 20th.
Hopefully it works.
Hopefully there's not server problems or something.
The olives?
I already did the olives in the beginning of the stream.
I mean, I attempted it.
I can't say it went that well, but I did.
I tried.
What is the big stream?
The big stream will probably be, I don't have a hard day for you,
but it's supposed to be somewhere in the end of January
into maybe the first or second week of February.
I don't have a date yet, but I will give it to you.
There's a lot of factors as to what that date is.
Oh, I missed the olives.
All right, let's raid.
Connor Eats Pants is live.
Connor has raided the stream a bunch of times.
He's a really swell dude.
He's been a huge supporter of the channel, as you know.
And I'm ending, and Connor's live.
So let's go say hi to Connor, say hello.
He's playing Pokemon Brilliant Diamond or whatever this is.
If I die in the game, I die in real life.
Okay.
Say hi to Connor, everybody.
Say hello to Connor.
Connor!
No, go say hi.
I will see you guys on Wednesday.
Good night.
Goodbye.
Take care of yourself.
Sleep well.
Have a good one.
He's literally at the very end of Pokemon Brilliant Diamond.
He's literally at the last cutscene of the game.
Just be aware of that, by the way, guys.
Be aware of that.
He's literally at the last cutscene, I think.
I have no idea.
That's what he just said.
All right, be careful.
I'll see you later.