I hadn't even been in 10 sec, people are already punching me. Did you see that?
I turn the stream on, I just see, get him, and people punching.
How you doing guys? Welcome back. Welcome to part two
of the Chronicles of Riddick Escape from Butcher's Bay.
This is a two-part series. I plan on finishing this tonight. I think we're
fairly close to... somebody said I'm more than halfway
through the game. Uh, probably like 60% of the way through
the game. Probably have another three or four hours. Freddy Dread coming in
with 50 community subs. Just, he just throws rocks full of money.
He just throws eggs filled with money, not egg yolk, at the stream.
It's a lot. Freddy, you continue to fucking... Freddy,
Freddy sometimes comes to Vegas. Like, Freddy, if we go out somewhere,
if like we hang out, if you come to Vegas eventually, like,
like, don't, you ain't buying shit, okay? Like, if we go to... I'm not, and I'll
tell you this, I will take you to Denny's and out,
you can get anything you want on the Denny's menu, I promise you that.
At least twice. We'll go to Denny's twice, and you can get anything on the whole
menu. He's already paid for it all. You already
paid for it all a hundred times. He could, he could probably
own the franchise of this Denny's that I'm talking about.
No, but seriously, dude, you, you, you've gone above and beyond what anyone would
ever be expected to give a single person on the internet any amount of money.
Like, times of million. So, thanks. And if you ever come to Vegas,
that offer stands.
You're my, I shaved my head. All right, well, it's hot out. That's not a bad idea.
Get him. Uh, Grove Coaster just gave a hundred and forty-five dollars.
Not, not for Freddy to be, to be a hundred and forty-five dollars in bits.
What are you doing? That's a lot of money. That's too much money.
And they, they just said, I defended my master thesis
fifteen minutes ago. Thanks for being here. Like, like a debate?
Holy shit. That's a lot of money. Thank you. Did I change my microphone?
No, I sound weird. I shouldn't. Unless I fucked something up.
The microphone's closer to my mouth. So, I mean, do I sound like I'm too close to
you? Do I sound like I'm way too close to you?
Should I back up a little? Did you get the standing desk? No, I
didn't. I did not. Here's my problem with the
standing desk. So, last year or like a year and a half
ago, I got this really nice, you've seen it, the, my
like nice walnut desk. And this thing was kind of expensive
and I want to use it, but so it just sucks where it's like, oh,
well, shit, what do I do with this? What can I put this somewhere else? I have to
get like a whole new desk now. Yeah, let's get it as a second desk. So,
the idea is, me and Kim were talking about it and I'm
probably gonna move this one out in a space where she could kind of
use it as a little, like, area where she can do some work
and stuff. So, that's probably the plan and I'm gonna get a standing desk.
You don't need a standing desk, just get up occasionally. Yeah, but I, you know me.
I'm not gonna do that. I'm gonna be sitting here just fucking screaming at a
2004, like, 10-year-old video game. I'm not, I'm not gonna remember to, like,
stand up every 15 minutes and I don't want to, like, just
have that in the back of my mind. Stand up every 20 minutes, stand up every 20
minutes, I won't, it's just gonna fuck me up.
So, I might as well just stand the whole time. 2004 was 16 years ago.
I don't even, let me say these things. It's,
I know. All right, does anybody here feel like,
that every year has been, like, 2015? Like, it's just 20, like, it's just 2013
every year, right? I just feel like it's 2013.
This, we've not gone past it. The world is passing me by
and I'm just in 2013. Like, I just uploaded, like, Dramarumble 3. No, that was
fucking seven years ago. That's so much time.
How many, that's how, that so much time has passed
in seven years. What happened, what have I been doing? Have I, have I, okay, let me
ask you this. Have I, like, have I done anything in seven
years? I think I have. I feel like I've done a lot of things.
Yeah, I think I have, maybe. A little. I did the carnival.
Well, yeah, that was cool. Oh, yeah. Also, this is going to be an
interesting stream because I just realized something.
So, I woke up a little bit tight this morning and
I, I did, I took a, I took a little bit of tips of pain reducing potentials
CBD and this might be a CBD stream. I just want to make that very clear so
people don't yell at me when I can't open the door
for, like, the third time in a row. I was, I didn't want to cancel the stream
because I want to obviously finish this and I want to play and I want to stream
so I, you know, it's legal in the, in the United
States of Las Vegas where I am here and in this, in this area and I
am all right. Didn't, I took just a little bit so
I took, I take it for pain. Those of you that don't know.
Washed up drug streamer. Like, like, three milligrams of CBD and THC
for pain. I do not put that in that category, okay?
Anyways, we're gonna play This is Butcher's Bay. He's got wicked low
weed tolerance. By the way, why is that a bad thing?
You, you do realize that being able to, like, feel
better and feel good at, like, three to four milligrams?
I know some people that, like, are, like, they, they're, like, fucking doing, like,
20, 15 and they built up such a tolerance. That,
that's an expensive tolerance. Low tolerance, inexpensive is what you meant
to say. Remember, the gateway from CBD is to CBT.
Read that one out loud. Good. Pick them, pick that one
to read. It's only been eight minutes. Joe Rogan. No, I,
all right, I shouldn't have even said anything, but, like, I, it's almost like I
have to, like, preliminarily defend myself
when I, like, make a bunch of mistakes in the game. But, like, that doesn't matter
because I do that anyways. So, it's, it's just gonna be a regular
ass Jeremy stream, right? Like, I'm not gonna be able to remember
where the door is and I'm trying to, like, give, like, a thing to blame.
So, like, you know that now, so you can blame that. But I did that yesterday.
All right, let's go. You ready? Right where we left off,
uh, we had this dude here. We had to go get a bomb for this guy.
And just in case somebody missed it yesterday, I'll show you. I'll just
welcome, I'll show you. No, I'm not gonna do that. I was gonna punch him in the
face. I'm gonna punch him in the face. Just
the new audience can tell. Like that, like, you can do that.
Okay. How do I turn, all right. So, those of you that are wondering about this game,
um, you can see in the dark. Although, seeing in the dark just looks like
you're looking through a really expensive vase.
So, like, I have a piece of quartz up to my eye. All right.
I have to go back, right? Let me see. He wants me to go
get bomb. Go to tower 19 and get a bomb. To get to tower 19, head back from the
mining core up to the mine entrance, then use
Jagger's code to activate the elevator. All right, we have to go back to that
original elevator. I almost pressed that. What do I have?
Oh yeah, I have weapons. Don't adjust your monitor. Do not adjust
your screen. You're probably messing with the tent and
shit. Don't do that. The game is very ugly.
I promise it's not your screen. It's mine. Wait. Yes.
Yes. No. Yes. I was fucking with the tent, dad.
I just told you not to do that. It's not your screen. It's mine.
Uh, the game's kind of loud. I'm gonna turn the game down.
Fix my screen? Oh, no. That's you. You're making a joke. Okay.
Uh, all right. I gotta go back up. We're gonna go in the elevator. We're gonna
get a bomb from tower. I remember tower 19. It's where the it's in the
oops. Why does it look like sewer sludge is covering the screen?
Because this game is very, very, very ugly.
Now, I didn't say this is a bad game. This game is actually pretty fun, but it's
incredibly ugly. It's not ugly at all, to be honest. Well,
you'll see. This is only like a third of the game is
walking around with lights on. Most of the game looks like this. Oh,
we got two clubs here. Boom. Boomer. Wrong way. I think he's high.
Stop. Why did I even say that? And by the way, for those of you that's
saying, why is he like use this little like fucking black and decker nail gun?
No, I can't pick up, uh, I can't pick up weapons.
I'm unauthorized. I, everyone was very, very upset about that last time.
All right. I need to get out to the main area, which is
I go in the right way. Is this the right way? Yeah, this is right, right?
Mr. Rat. Get the rat. You missed the rat. Was there a rat on the ground?
Where's the rat? Rat list? Where is it? Are you? Dude, was it on the ground?
Oh, okay. There it is. List of rats. All right. I got it. I thought you're talking
about like, like there was a rat on the ground.
It's like you missed the rats. You missed the rats. Like, I thought like, oh, there's
like a rat on the ground. All right. Let's go. I just have to make
my way back to the elevator, which who knows how where that is.
It's been more than 24 hours. It's, it's gone from my mind.
Just jump. Oh, yeah. There's no fall damage. You're right. Can I use this?
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Do I want to go in here though?
Where is it going to take me? Well, this is going to take me back up or down.
It's going to take you back up. That's, is that what that's what I want, right?
Try it out. Yeah. Don't press the red button.
Of course they would make a game where you have to backtrack again and then the
whole. Oh, no, no, no. This is it. This is it. This is it.
No, it's not. This is not it. This is not it.
Uh, I just went down. Somebody said I was going to go
up and then I went down. All right. Hey, welcome to the stream. Let's go.
Here we go again. Let's go up. This is brain.
Okay. So what what's the actual way to go?
Oh, God damn it. Are you telling me that I just could have walked through this?
So I went this way. No, I didn't. Wait.
Upper mines. Yeah, this is where I want. This is where I want to be. I hate
backtracking. I'm so glad it was deleted from every video game.
All right. So right or left though. What's like the actual how do I get like
back to where I want to go? He's on DMT. No, this way.
Imagine trying to stream on DMT. That would be impossible. If somebody
could do that in no fucking way. Not a chance in hell.
Where the hell do I even want to go though? Like I'm trying to just get back
to the beginning. This is a safe point. Okay. I gotta sneak
through here. He's done it. Did I though? Like I have no idea
where the fuck I am. Climb those boxes. This is just bringing
me back this way. Through here? Okay. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. This is to
security checkpoint. Right. This is this. I'm going the right way.
Game is now very, very quiet. I got you. Why is this so new? This is new. I haven't
seen this. Oh my god. This is the this is the beginning.
This is the beginning. Okay. I found it. Just check your map. Well, the problem
with the map is it literally just looks. I don't even
know where I am. I don't know which one of these rooms I'm in.
I made it. This is the beginning. I just don't die.
There's no fucking way I'm going to be able to get through this.
Not a chance. I'm not going to be able to. Can I electrocute him? Could I like
lure him out here and push him into the electricity? You shouldn't have eaten a
BLT.
Where's the light? Turn it off. You've had too much mayonnaise on that BLT, dude.
All right. Now you're in my world. Does he have to be?
Well, I'm never going to be able to get by this guy.
He's just standing in the doorway. I don't think I'm going to be able to do this.
I might as well just run. I think I'm going to have to just run.
Use the bat? This doesn't work. I already did this.
All right. Ready? One, two, three, go. I can't see anything.
Now that's what we call a. Okay. This is what I need to do, right?
What? I just got a new code. Oh, fuck this. I'm out. I'm done.
We actually just take this back. All right. Here we go.
Get the rifle. You can't pick up rifles. You can't pick up rifles. You can't.
Oh, yeah. I tried to tape this. It doesn't matter.
I ripped the tape off in rage. It didn't work. All right. Perfect.
Now it's going to go back to tower 19. Why is all this activated?
Can this open? This is all messed up. The vent to get in.
I just broke my chair. I'm sorry to hear that. What's the point of this vent?
Wait, why can I even open this? Oh, it's the cigarettes.
All right. Well, hold on a jump up here and climb. Get those ciggy butts.
What the hell am I doing? I feel like I'm cheating right now.
All right. Where am I? Cargo transport.
I need to go back to like tower 17 and like the feed ward. Where the fuck am I?
Security checkpoint. I climb and I hang.
I guess this is not going to. Why am I doing this?
What am I doing this for? I can't sneak attack him.
Can I break? Should I break? That door is not going to open.
That door doesn't open. I think I have to break the glass and go in.
Stealth kill. I don't think you can.
I'm right up his ass. If he moves, he's going to know I'm here.
Is this motherfucker even active?
Holy shit. I thought he was inactive. I thought he didn't do anything.
I thought he was inactive. I was bumping into him and stuff.
I thought he was not activated. I thought he was not moving around and shit.
OK, so what the fuck? So that's not the way to go.
So I need to go back down here.
I have to go and like climb into the vents and shit, don't I?
This is the wrong way. Am I getting a cut scene?
Wait, hold on. Hold on.
Do I just need to give me the lights? Turn the lights on.
And then we go backwards, right? Yeah.
No, we don't go backwards here. Stop using the club.
Well, that's not my main concern. My main concern is what's the one stupid way
to go back and go back, backtracking, backtracking, backtrack.
I have to go beyond the bridge? Stop the car.
I'm just going to watch a fucking YouTube video on how to get back here.
Hold on. That's cheating. That's fine.
He's doing the... He needs a video guide.
Why would you have it like climb through? I don't... I don't...
I'm not even going to... Look, I'm not even going to...
What do you want me to say? I'm not even going to say what you think I'm going to say.
All right, I've made it to another fucking gray room.
All right, now it's up... Do I go up here and then all the way around?
This is the mines again. You need to go back to the elevator.
What? The elevator just took me to a place I couldn't go.
Is this shit it? Did I make it?
Dude, you took the whole bottle. This is it, right?
No, because this just brings me... Wait, what?
This is the fan, which then brings you back to the original area, which then...
This is a mess. Don't turn the service panel back on, dude.
Okay, so this is the beginning. I should be able just to go in that elevator and take me down.
I remember this shit. Do you remember this? This is the very beginning.
This is how I got down here in the first place.
Remember? I was like, oh, I can't do this yet. Why is this elevator not the way out?
This is how we came in. Take this elevator.
Didn't I try that already? They took me to a weird fucked up place.
No, go up the ladder in this elevator. Wait, this is a different...
Wait, this is the same thing. You're fucking with me.
We're in the same spot. Use the elevator?
Didn't I do that already? It took me up to that weird spot where the guy was blocking the door.
Use the elevator first and then go up the vent.
Why? Why can't I just leave? Why can't I just leave?
He's never going to find the cheese. Why can't I just leave?
Oh, okay. So take elevator up. Don't go out elevator door.
Go up elevator fucking ladder into the dark vents.
Go through vents up. There's two different vents, by the way.
There's two elevators with two different vents. They both look the same.
What the fuck is this? What is this like being John Malkovich hole that I have to find?
Which, by the way, that's a pretty good movie if you haven't seen it.
All right. We found it. We did it.
All right. Good. Now I can finally just turn off the...
Wait, no, I didn't. Did I find it?
Oh, healing station. Oh, that's it. I don't want to do the vent thing again.
Oh, my God. I don't want to do the vent thing again.
Hey, by the way, guys, we hadn't even hit yet.
I just wanted to make that's going to be very clear.
Are we up or are we down? Where are we?
It's going to... Oh, it's going to get worse from here.
No, it's not because we're not going to have to do any more like vent climbing.
You'll know when you'll know because I'm just going to go...
Hey, I have to go that way. I have to go over here.
Right now, you hear me? This is... I'm completely with it.
Oh, maybe not completely, but as with it as I am without being on any type of substances.
He ate the whole... He took the whole... He ate the whole brownie.
It's going to be... That was what we call a little...
Oh, I thought I could... Never mind. All right. Give me the health.
He ate the whole plate.
How do you eat a whole plate of brownies in a regular circumstance?
That's what I want to know.
Oh, wow. He ate the whole plate.
Why would you eat a whole plate of brownies normally?
If this happens again, I'm going to eat the batteries that are in it.
Hope that doesn't happen again.
I feel like if I ate more than two brownies, it would be like cement in my stomach.
Did I fuck something up?
Why could I not do this? What's going on?
Oh, thank God. It's another vent.
Wait, there's two vents now.
There are three vents.
What's the right vent?
Oh, I can't even go in that one.
Am I doing this right?
I really hope I never have to do this again because this sucks.
I don't want to be in vents.
I don't want to just do vents while I be in a dark room
and then immediately go to a light room the whole day.
Like, I don't think I've even been here.
Oh, cigarettes. What is this?
Can I climb that?
My character's just like on DMT.
Oh, shit. The lights are so bright.
Turn the lights up.
Where am I?
No, don't make any jokes. I don't want to lose.
I'm sorry, dude. I'm on fucking DMT.
I don't even know who you are.
Is this thing alive?
That thing's going to come out and attack me, isn't it?
Am I going crazy?
Was I just supposed to go back to tower 19?
What is all this shit?
Was I not supposed to kill him?
Wait, do I need a screwdriver?
Was it an NPC? Did I ruin everything?
What's over here?
Oh, I can go down there.
This is where I was before.
Did I miss something?
I didn't soft lock the game, right?
No. No, I didn't.
Hold on. Wait, did I DMT lock the game?
I hope that's not the running thing
we continue to reference this stream.
I'm sure it will be, but I don't want it to be that.
What's this?
No, there's nothing down here.
I have to do something with that robot in there.
No doors or anything.
Guys, I think I may have soft locked myself.
No, there's a ladder.
Is it alive?
What? Hold on, what?
I get to be in the suit?
Oh, shit!
I don't know where I am.
How many balls do I have?
Wait, why can I walk through walls?
I had the thing on.
But this doesn't help me.
This just makes me more dangerous.
I still don't know where to go.
Oh, I'm opening the doors with my little T-Rex hand.
I'm going to the briefing room.
All right, nice work.
Oh, okay.
Okay, I don't.
Is he dead?
Wait, can I get in his suit?
I want to get in his suit.
Wait, why are there two?
There were two?
How are there two of them?
Oh no, look at him.
He's sad.
Look at what he did.
He made me kill.
Two of my reverent monstrosities.
I never want to be in this place again.
Jerry, take me from here once and for all.
Okay, man.
Let's get out of here.
And Jerry, if you would please give me some of that DMT.
Oh, you want some DMT, dude?
All right, you got it.
I'll take some right now.
Right now?
Yes.
Hold on, man.
I'm not sure you're ready for this.
I am ready.
I'm starting to consider this whole witty thing a major-
All right, man.
Here you go.
I'm going to give it to you right now.
Just lift your tongue up.
Holy shit.
I can see the machine alien.
Perons have been here for 10,000 years.
Not 10 billion.
I think the clerk at my local Walmart is actually Jesus reborn.
And here are 200 reasons why.
Hey, whoa, man.
Whoa, man.
You got to settle down on a DMT.
Oh, that was wonderful.
Thank you for that experience.
Yeah, man.
I really wanted to DMT you.
Just hit me up any time of the week.
Get out of here.
Get out.
I need to get out of the robot to see.
Anybody know where I'm going?
Read the screen.
It's just Matrix glitter.
I can't read that.
Did I just go back the other way?
Oh, no.
Shit.
Somebody just said this guy is dumb.
No, dude, I'm not.
I'll get it.
Don't leave.
Just hold on.
All right.
I got rid of the noise.
Wait, that was a big problem for me,
but that wasn't the actual problem.
I can't go through any of these.
Maybe I'm really just not supposed to go this way
unless there's an event.
Wait, I have to...
No, I have to leave DMT robot.
No, I don't.
He can get up here.
Oh, no.
That's too bad.
Oh, that's it.
Well, see you later, DMT robot.
It's been a lot of fun.
Thank you, Jerry.
You have given me more experiences
than I could possibly ask for in a human.
Have a wonderful rest of your game.
Powering Joe.
Bye.
It's nice to meet you.
Turn off the filter.
Where'd he go?
The real DMT was the friends we made along the way.
This elevator sucks.
Why is it not moving?
It's because it's not an elevator.
Shit.
Oh, wait a minute.
All right.
DMT robot, power on.
We're going to have a bunch more fun, man.
We're going to take DMT
and we're going to do all this fun shit.
I cannot wait.
Please climb inside of me.
No.
Oh, no.
That's the origin story for DMT robot becoming a villain.
Why am I climbing this?
Why would he do that?
I didn't do that.
I didn't climb that.
I wanted just to walk down here.
Okay.
I'm...
It's hard to aim at the guy.
It's very, very difficult.
It's a difficult experience.
That's a difficult game.
It's hard.
It's a difficult game.
Why is he shooting at me?
No.
DMT robot.
What are you doing?
Oh, that was another robot.
What the fuck happened here?
Okay.
All right.
How do I get you to move?
Oh, no.
It's CVT robot.
No, that can't be who that canonically is in this universe.
I'm sorry.
Just get in.
Let's go.
I only died before I could do the joke part of what I was going to do.
It is too bad that one of my friends had to perish.
What happened?
What happened to the audio?
Did I fuck it up?
All right.
Well, that's where that arc ends.
I was going to do a thing where
this was going to be his dad mad that he was taking DMT.
He was going to be like, I'm adventuring, dad.
Leave me alone.
And they're going to be the big fight.
And it's like his dad dies because they're fighting.
You know, that's going to do that whole thing.
Let's just pretend I did that.
All right.
That was fun.
I did not expect that I was actually going to get into one of these though.
The whole game, they tease you about how scary they are.
It's going to be really sad when he actually dies.
I'm out of his aggro range.
It's fine.
Grenade.
Oh, no.
He's going to die.
Is there a healing thing I can do?
These people are friendly.
These people are not friendly.
Okay.
That's it.
Someone's sitting in the flamingos.
I took a lot of hits.
Flamingos?
Yeah.
What does that mean?
I'm almost dead.
I feel like this is what the dinosaur fossils of an AT-ST would look like.
He's dead.
Does it mean I'm dead?
I got to be careful here.
Out of like health.
Prepare the robot.
I don't know.
I don't know how to do that.
No, you can't.
I have the screwdriver on.
It doesn't work.
I just have to not take any hits.
It's kind of hard to do that, though.
It's regenerating health.
Is it?
Okay.
They expect me to walk through immediately.
I didn't.
They blew everything up.
Stand still.
All right.
I'm going to stand still after this and see if I heal.
Okay.
Here we go.
Ready?
Let's, for God's sake, hope they can do their job.
Shut it off.
Yep.
I don't think that it works.
I think we have to ditch.
Somebody said R2DMT2.
I think that's two.
I don't know about that.
I'm not sure I'm going to sign off on that one.
No, there's no deal.
I just have to not die to the flamingos.
That was my joke.
Yeah, so I said somebody said that.
Okay.
This is important.
Shit.
God, he's dying.
I'm sorry.
I got to get out.
Get out.
Duck.
No.
Wait.
I'm just looking at...
They're killing him.
I'm stuck in here.
I'm actually stuck in here.
I can't move.
How did I get in here?
Wait.
I can smoke.
Can I keep going up?
How the hell am I going to do this without the robot?
Wait.
What about up there?
Ow.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
Ah.
I would have...
I could have shot the lights.
Fuck, you're right.
Oh, I'm so stupid.
I'm not fucking around anymore.
Let's go.
Yeah, that's right.
I took the...
I got the last punch.
Did not mean to exit.
Send in the flamingos.
Did, did, did, did, did, did, did.
This dude says, ow, and he gets hit in the video game.
LOL.
Yeah.
Okay.
Um, I have the Nintendo Power magazine order for him.
I ordered the fucking vest thing
that vibrates when you take damage in a game.
You don't play games with those?
Okay, fine, dude.
So you're not like a real...
You're like a kind of use a controller
and then you don't like put your body, like into...
Okay.
Now, that's like cool though.
I feel like this game that way.
The lamp...
um apparently is has can take 5 000 rounds industrial lamp play doom music sure let's just
scream a guitar riff but that's embarrassing i'm not gonna do it extend in the flamingos
i can't kill them though all right here's the deal lights out where i need every light gun
oh my god
i have to get rid of the ones on the right jump out of the robot and take out the other one
i don't want to do that you have to avoid damage how do you avoid damage with two mechs of firing
machine guns at each other i mean not that one that guy was an idiot come on out
okay that's it someone sitting in the flamingo i've got two bars of health two bars of health
lights why is it the what okay here's the plan oh man they what are they doing over here
oh shit oh shit get in get in he's dropping his fake accent what am i doing oh this sucks
do what i did last time yeah i just gotta i gotta try to i really might have to go back and have
full health again let them walk to the explosives i did that last time but it didn't kill them
okay it's all right let's try let's shoot them i thought i was doing last like two times before
that shoot the flamingos i do an impression of a monkey oh i like
there you go and i i demand i demand attention from you now
i don't have enough fucking health i forgot about piece three okay i'm ready i'm ready i'm ready
wait till they get to the explosives and then blow it up that's the plan that's what i'm going to do
no it almost worked is it no way can i heal him wait a minute can the robot wait wait wait wait
this is important what about the heal boxes that have a key that's a heal right no what is that i
don't know never mind i thought that was a heal i figured that maybe the huge they could pick up
the boxes and use them stun gun can repair dmt bot all right time that person off for five minutes
no don't do it don't do it no don't do it please don't do it wait where the guy that's over there go
he's not an explosion that's that's a first if he's dead from the explosion okay come on
come on gotta get me over there all right just get over there just get over there so i can jump
exit under the shadows whoa okay you keep fucking kidding me this light can't be destroyed i'm not
missing this is not bad aim what are you talking about it's right i look at where that decal is
possible oh oh oh no no shit get up here the game is making me silly today
i had to give me a fucking break he threw his controller this sucks this sucks why come on dude
why i eat the battery all right fine eat the batteries it's so funny okay here we go first
battery first battery let me get it out okay first battery going in there it is in the mouth okay
all right okay there's one two three batteries in an xbox controller okay two this i got both
batteries down oh all right i feel good oh um is my audio set up right yes it is okay we're good
you absorb their power you sound younger hey do i wow typically sound like this hey yeah guys stay
we're gonna flank not today hey the grenade gets him every time you know what i saw that comment i
didn't reply to it i saw somebody say the grenade fucking gets him every time and like i'm like no
no fuck i'm not even gonna listen to that guy this might as well die right now okay that's it
why does their grenade someone send in the flamingos for god's sakes i wonder if they're
gonna be able to do their job oh you know what i got something for you god damn it somebody send
in the flamingos ladies and gentlemen your butchers bay flamingos here they come
you can't find the fucking grenade again flamingo handy stop it
i'm not gonna find the fucking grenades this time all right if i can find the grenade i'm giving
fuck i'm giving 50 community subs if i get hit by the next grenade
i promise who the fuck is shooting me who the hell are you did i get him what
i think did he shoot himself in the head he shot himself what the fuck
why oh okay don't laugh the grenade's still here i think he threw it i think he just threw it
what's the alarm going on it was a fake give me out
hold on i don't think it's avoidable i think you have to get hit by that grenade
i have to get out of the suit and tase that guy that's it someone sitting in the flamingo
distraction get up there and duck stop is it him is it my arch nemesis
oh you're aiming the gun down at me oh i'm gonna lose my mind i'm gonna fucking lose my mind what
is this checkpoint what the hell happened i just okay i just like blacked out and and opened my
eyes and there was like a dead guy and a robot in front of me i got a different strategy this time
this guy's so shit faced i can't even fucking do this you gotta go this way get up on it
shoot the lights i can't i guys i'm gonna get it right in the center i look see the decal i don't
it i'm trying trust me i already did it okay okay where is he where are you oh smart ass
i didn't hit him oh he's a smart ass i'm gonna get this smart ass he's hiding he's not looking
he's not looking he's not looking he's not looking i did it all right progress let's go
there was no reason to do that uh well are they gonna see me do this i have to get rid of the
lights but i can't even destroy that light okay we're going in darkness quiet isn't a guy over
here right i actually made it i actually did it i thought it just hit monk s all right let's go
tower number 19 vent i'm gonna go in this vent ladies and gentlemen welcome to episode one
of vent craft lights off lights out too bright lights off me why did i say me out loud
that was the mistake yeah i have to step on them what's in here locker 18 tower 19 that's it
i think we're going wait what did that just want to do i got a prompt what was that prompt
holy shit omega lull back to the beginning no we're not back at the damn beginning
we're not back at the damn beginning who's in range oh wait oh this guys this is the
prison i get it i do not see that he must be pretty stupid hey hey no don't do that
you're a scumbag console aiming but you either go too far to the left or too far to the right
you don't want to actually you don't aim where you actually want to aim i'm so glad will you
stop breathing and leaning forward i mean i think you would sit here and just when the lights are
on you know you can't be seen wouldn't you cup your mouth and yell in a different towards the
other hallway that you came from like be in the corner and like up your mouth and point your
like kind of whole mouth sideways to block out the and just be like wouldn't they you would light
up the whole entire hallway it was a bad noise was it oh because the robot filter is still on
i'm sorry the robot filter was still on i thought it was off that doesn't sound right oops sorry
i'm sorry okay i thought that was a guy for a second shit uh okay we're good open content
wait open the prison doors oh you can't ever open the cell doors i better be ready dude was
it the was it the platinum chuck-e-cheese membership card yeah man hey you wait hold on
no no no you know what i find uh most uncomfortable about you riddick how comfortable
you are here in butcher bay i mean caged inside this land i played the hand that was down all
right i wasn't expecting vin diesel and i got vin diesel this is for you vin diesel sound
uh why what was he supposed to do that is that scripted because um what the hell
that was not cool man i can't even turn these lights off okay anyways but i was gonna say is
vin diesel's voice is so low that he sounds like you know when any demon character is on screen
they always speak like whenever they i want to hear a demon talk in a normal speaking voice
it's vin diesel that's how they would actually sound every single demon on earth just is always
yelling loudly why do they make them do that in games the only way that you can tell that i'm
powerful is if i fucking scream every piece of my dialogue human just have vin diesel say what i
just said in a normal speaking voice you know what i find uh most uncomfortable about you ready
comfortable you are here in butcher bay i mean caged inside this so this is scripted i played
the hand that was dumb and then i cheat Thanos doesn't yell but he's not a big demon with a big
axe oh i killed him in one punch holy shit i killed him in one punch oh no oh real voice
that was brutal but what the hell is going on okay you telling me that from both angles here
from both angles there's a is there a vent it's gonna be the toilet jump off at the right time
oh like on to that guys i don't think i'm gonna be able to get that i gotta count i have to count
it's the only way i'm gonna be able to do this reliably okay it's here it is so it's down let's
go now right i got killed by the blade but you know what i find uh most uncomfortable about you
Riddick i played the hand not a bad philosophy this is for you so it's just all right stop stop
stop wait okay i have to wait till it goes up watch that light on the left one two what that
went very fast what wait i'm going am i going down am i going up well i'm not supposed to ride
like the brake glass elevator like in Willy Wonka i thought that's what this was
so hold on why didn't i not get the cut scene before oh i stood up didn't kill me
i just scraped the top of my head across the 200 feet of cement when that train falls in
it's down to my bottom jaw scraped down get up listen what did you say listen
no nothing i don't feel like it no jesus christ fucking move vent what's going on here
and i'm taking a look but i can't explode those this is his patrol by the way i want to make this
really really clear to everybody i want everyone to see this this is this guy's patrol you ready
a guy with a machine gun is here done who am i talking to um you collect like a bunch what do
you mean what who are you talking to that didn't do anything though i have to like release this
how do i release this is there a button down there something i can do down there
actually blind is it there was another ladder oh what the fuck omg there is a gun on the floor
old man i'm not an old man you're kind of old no i'm not kind of old it's like 45 like i would
say 48 is kind of old 50 is old 40 is kind of old 30 is whoa looking good 20 is oh yeah and then
anything below that you know this is why could i do this is there a crate i can jump up there's
a third ladder omega lull i know those aren't ladders they look like it from here yeah i can
agree with you wait go back down oh omega s omega s oh look another ladder let's go i drag him down
no this game's not that advanced okay can we get these bugs away from me all right i'm good
i got i got up and did a running haymaker and missed all he had to do was shoot me in the back
i can't take the gun up or down i thought it was like a gas wait should i go up first what's in here
who's this i noticed something gonna check who's there but it's saying he noticed the great ball
in here i can't i couldn't fit out i couldn't fit out the vent what's going on here i'm taking a look
just like a fucking wild animal man something is not looking good i think i'm gonna take a look
i don't know any of the codes oh listen to that a ladder vents and ladders don't hey don't go in
the vents you'll go all the way back to the beginning climb a ladder up you'll progress
10 fucking minutes all right there's a button that's alarm
i can't give up you killed me what's fuck you okay i have one oh what are they called
i wasn't quick enough to make the joke oh that hurts it stings when that happens stay alert
uh the little tabs that come in the little tabs you put in your tongue so your breath smells better
like the listerine tabs there it is i have one listerine tab left you know what i was trying to
say it's gonna it would have been funny and not funny step it up you know i could go over there
maybe i shouldn't go in the grate yet i just oh i want to have quick reaction times i can have
activate no turn it off rail defense deactivated
turn it it's off okay that was a random worker that was way health thank you so what is this
rail track computer right that rails finished need to find another i do that wrong what it's
because the alarm wasn't on where do i go then wait what's this thing wait where's this taking
me okay who's coming behind me he didn't notice shit for all this guy knows i could have been
like a broom and he just shot at it does that thing what is that thing i think i heard something
over there the second that anything goes in that guy's peripheral all these enemies doesn't the
second they see anything it's just immediately hold the trigger down at whatever it is all right
this could be the pizza delivery guy like what are you doing like at least see who it is
i've done the pizza delivery guy dude relax what is stand up why am i so small
die oh my god don't die to this guy why he stand up son of a gun oh son of a gun
what i hate i hate no don't say it
the camera i know what it was i'm kidding i just knew i was dead because i walked over the stupid
line i couldn't even do it myself what is he even doing here doesn't usually go
stop dying on purpose for more donations i'm taking a look the vent up there they're going
the vent you think yeah all right i gotta destroy this i know i'll run into it later all right let's
go in the vent so i think this guy's below average iq no i don't i don't incredibly fucking smart my
mother told me every day just how smart i was she was like you're so smart i'm just i'm gonna
give you smart boost i'm like oh cool smart boosting and she that she would do the my homework
with me i was sitting at the table and i would be stuck on a very difficult question you know like
six times 12 and shit that's i'd be like mom i need a smart boost she'd be like and she'd fly in
with a little cape on smart booster to the rescue and then when i graduated college
didn't think i really needed it anymore so just skipped a bunch of shit how many guys are down
there all right no no no i got jumped down and killed i just broke my ankle that was a shattered
leg i don't think he's gonna have a weapon what the fuck no please turn the backup generator
go find me a new car go find me a generator go find me this go find me that go take care of that
oh thank god there's a mom came in with a smart booster where's the other like i don't know i need
to be able to see through walls so i can see where the things are remember she gave you a placebo to
make you feel better about your learning difficulties what do you mean placebo she
wasn't walking in the door with like pills in her hand oh she didn't go oh here are smart boosters
and then like hand me like three pills wait wait what do you mean whippets what are you talking
about like wait you're saying that my mother did whippets and then like flew into the room with
like a cape on like do being like the smart booster i can't i honestly like i can't even
like address that that's too fucking outrageous for me to think about my mother doing that
oh somebody said dream thank god you said it i had a dream i had a dream last night that was very
strange it involves all of you i had a dream last night that i was sleeping in bed i was asleep all
the lights were off and i got out of bed or this is probably around one or two o'clock in the morning
like this i actually got out of bed to go to the bathroom but i was dreaming at the same time it
was really weird like i in my dream went up to go to the bathroom but i know that i woke up and i
went to the bathroom that's what i was doing so i went to go into the i went to pee into the toilet
and and i saw chat saying just like clockwork just like clockwork there he is right on time
right on time like you i sleep on stream and at 1 a.m like it's a thing that i get up and pee every
time i guess oh here it is like it's 1 a.m it's just like clockwork like omega lull that's the
whole dream and then i went back to sleep i was the generator i don't touch these and this was a
very very popular stream too it was there were tens of thousands of people here like i was the
sleeping on stream guy and everybody at 1 a.m it was like a thing that they were like emotes and
shit about it like just like right on time but i was just fucking sleeping and like going i was
going to bed and i didn't even acknowledge you guys were even there what a strange life
all right powers back on now i just gotta go back up and turn that shit on third ladder here i have
to get grabbed by that thing yeah just like clockwork all right back up and then this way
how do you feel about brain fluids hostile takeover of smart boosters you know what there really are
so many random what i just do oh fuck i didn't want to do that um there are so many random
supplements that do that that say that stuff smart and they always for some reason they always have
two or three big letters at the end i've never been able to figure out why that happens smart
booster qa z smart booster xr what the fuck is that for it's they're called smart boosters why
they called smart boosters like xr smart booster x3 why can't why can't just be smart boosters
it is a link here hold on what is it you wouldn't understand what is this why are you showing me
this wait okay hold on is this this is a picture of what i believe is me eating um some type of
food with chopsticks is that like a takeout container what is that it's me eating food with
chopsticks really just that and stuff that's why am i eating bacon fries with chopsticks it's a straw oh
um i've kind of lost for a second why was that important it was very important that i clicked
on that did i what happened did i walk in a circle no no now we go up just like clockwork
yeah where's that there was that little hallway that i could go and open backtrack and fucking
bury man i'm safe back to yeah i'm trying to find that real thing that needed power
i don't know i don't remember where it is from where is the germa shit stream um i've read that
in a bunch of different i thought you were saying when when when is like the good stream germa this
is shit i thought i don't know why that's what i've read okay um help me out here where was that area
in the vent or down here or down or over i don't really remember backtrack and i can't do it
you went past it not an event it's just in here down in the x door again here but i'm like what's
that power source bro down the ladder bro bro bro all right remember i said what is this thing
i gotta go on the lift right and yeah right no then wait no this is where i pressed the original
button is it there was a button that i pressed that i went oh and the thing crashed oh shit yeah
this is where that one is the edibles kicked in okay down the ladder bro this is not right
this is so wrong isn't it this is not even right everyone's so preoccupied with saying bro that
that okay saying bro is trumps saying like he's an idiot he's a stupid fucking idiot
he's never gonna find it the invention of like blips on mini maps oh man whoever invented that
i hope you patented it what am i doing down here this is wrong we're not gonna talk about
what i just said what are you talking about i said the same bro trumps saying like i'm lost
wait do you guys you guys not know what the word trump is it means like over or like over something
better than something right of what it's a word it's a it's a word i'm saying a lot of questions
this is like me saying like oh yeah i put something in a basket and people go basket
what the fuck is a basket what are you talking about oh by the way we also have a president like
john basket there that makes more sense okay okay i need to focus i need to know where the
hell i'm going okay what does it say back up generator what what no no no no what what this
bro oh bro bro okay so now i do i have to go all the way back to the other spot
for the original activator so that's all the way back here all right i want people to correct me
if i'm going the wrong way bro please i don't i'm just gonna jump over these okay that other
spot let's see the rail track is fully functional you can now ride a cell further down to the mining
core all right okay oh where the backup generator is all right i'm telling you something if you
ride in all capitals and you just say do monkey noises they're funny oh but i didn't it isn't
isn't um isn't vin diesel like a wicked good dude by the way like i just like i was going
to talk about that yesterday no yes he is i heard it i thought he was like like a wicked nice guy
he's weird oh oh he's not i i i stopped saying wicked why can i not say that
wasn't he like a like a gamer wouldn't he like really like into like supporting game stuff
my brain of vin diesel is like 12 years ago i don't remember he eats boiled chicken whoa okay
never mind i my opinion on him just changed very drastically oh fuck vin diesel once played dnd
with trump that's naughty that's what you made that up like you made that up i can't think of
something that was more made up than what you just said wait and i don't like activate it
wait hold on what back to the backup generator back to the generator i was just there i thought
that i already turned it on like i would believe aliens landed on earth and like we're all going
to be like they're gonna just like enslave like all everybody like we're like aliens come and
we're now they like just take over i would believe that more than news than vin diesel
and donald trump played dnd together it's real this is not that this is toy fair performances
he sends the competition to a watery grave this is not donald trump playing dnd it's the hammerhead
uh i okay never mind what what what is this twitter you're doing what are you linking me
vin diesel hey nice stream real mature impressions you mogul now get electrocuted
okay i gotta tell you you can you can only pull the like look at it's a real tweet
prank you got that you have to space that out more like more than a couple of months i think
that you just did this two days ago i don't think that works right now okay back to the backup
generator which god where am i backup generator i can't this map is filled in this is gonna go up
there's an elevator right oh my god i don't know what the fuck is going on
security make monkey noises no i i can't just do it for no reason
it's elmo you're welcome you're welcome that was for the one thank you my my like my internet
reputation has now gone down about three points to make you happy one person i hope i did finally
we did it back up generator ladies and gentlemen let's go here we go
what where was the cut scene where vin diesel grabs the thing and we why is he playing the
shittiest game ever i wouldn't say that all right hold on that's this is not the shittiest game ever
no links no links no links what is it i'm not gonna i'm not gonna show that on stream i don't
know i'm not i'm not i clicked it it was funny i don't know like they could is like i don't know
if there's a guy that there's like a dick in there i don't know i can't i have no idea
where am i what's the goal now plant the bomb in the gas filled room the creatures in there
will cause a lot of mayhem the gas filled room wait like the room that's all the way over here
who's this you must be ready jager told me to wait for you jager's gonna try to reach the space
port redick should put that package from jupiter in the cave when hell breaks loose
we dig heads for the space port yeah that's what he said john hey look it's john basket uh look at
me i hate john basket so much why i don't have to chill man okay we have to go into the room with
the gas and plant the bomb and i think i'm going the right way here we go plant the bomb
this is so bright all right where am i going get in what's hell i don't know why i'm thinking
about this but that this just looks like um every movie with a budget of under 200 000
dollars when they need to be in a space like this like a ton of indy movies look like this they make
like oh i'm in a cave but it just looks kind of odd but like halogen lights and shit shit's
expensive guys it really is hey james thanks for the 10 subs thank you james what though
oh sorry my mistake this is where it opens up and it's chubaca you know it's a friend
right he's gonna be like hey you didn't think you're gonna see me oh never mind did they do it
yes they did i've killed so many of these guys i they they sedated me i'm just pretending to be
sedated right like the guy came over and grabbed my arm and i went oh god i like pretend like i
tended to get knocked out that's me it's me it's me in there it's me like i put the costume i said
that i'm over there but you're talking to the guy in the room with him it's not dark in here
you can see in this room is afraid of i sleep in a room that's brighter than this
well you actually can't see me wasn't there another guy where's the second guy
oh that and hold on that another context this is so much funnier like i'm dead and the death wait
hold on i want to see the death cutscene the vin diesel the redic died cutscene oh shit oh it's
getting tough what will our hero do difficult enemy shit he's down verdict verdict died
ah it wasn't very good ah it wasn't very good ah it wasn't very good okay sometimes just swinging
this it would have been like it would have been close it was close where's my weapons
damn it wasn't ah it wasn't ah oh well uh put a line through that one in the notebook of funny
joke material to sing on string let's go through that one click do a monkey noise you'll be there
no i'd rather have it deducted points just a minute there's been a cave in here what is that
this is the first time we've seen actual dinosaurs in the game is this shit in the movie i kind of
want to watch this movie now beautiful so do i go down the no did i go down the hole i didn't want
to jump in there because i thought people were going to be like oh fall joke fall joke haha but
like i think i have to do that yeah i was so scared to do that because i didn't want to be
accused of making like a shitty joke the creature is killed without mercy almost felt like home
where is this shotgun you gave me a grenade oh oh you've given me a grenade okay a lot more
anticlimactic when they blow up like that unfortunately oh that was supposed to be
scary shit load it anymore what's up is a shitty head trap oh my god you have to be good
or you have to be good are you screwed can i punch in the face yeah you can hell is this
remember it's 1 p.m time for your smart booster oh shit i gotta be better with the aiming and
shotgun but it's hard to do i wonder how close i am to the end of the game of mercy
oh where did he go i'm trying to find him okay well the big guy's gone that's a lot of bullets
i don't have to use use three on that you wouldn't believe how hard it is to aim it's so hard it's
so difficult to aim and there's nothing in here play the pc version oh i don't you guys know the
golden rule you cannot stream any game that was on pc that was made before like 2004 because it
just has horrendous capture problems i would rather deal with controller aim than have to like
screen cap my monitor four times anything with like direct x8 direct x like seven is such a
pain in the ass even direct x9 too it could be such a huge pain in the ass where did he just
i think he just damaged boosted me all right this part's supposed to be cool but it's actually
irritating security gate jump click old mechanical lock i blow it up old mechanical lock sounds like
hey throw a grenade at the door i don't need a key three bullets i'm in trouble to find the old
mechanical key give me the other shotgun give me the shotgun give me give me give me here another
one old mechanical shit post processing please put on post processing why can i not open this
ventilation hatch why is it doing that i don't have a tool for it anymore how's that
toolbox right there son of a bitch holy i have 60 shots that's awesome i'm scared in three two
maybe maybe ah health pack thank you this fighting all right cool uh this way this doesn't look right
maybe no it does kind of look right not really but maybe there's the old mechanical key and
more shotgun bullets now i just have to get back to the old mechanical door and everything can be
good i want to hear vin diesel say more things and grunt and conversation more get to another
npc quick i'm going i'm going for it power cell is required to operate this machine
what do i have to activate this need power cell uh looks like we're going back up
yeah i think i'm yeah somebody said it i think i'm no here we go i gotta look at what all these
all these things are our cell waiting room somewhere else i could go from here can't open this
am i missing another way to go there's one way do i have to jump across the bridge or something
part booster waiting room stop okay i have to make this jump holy shit i did it
nice all right oh how do you reload just do this game never taught me how to reload
i just expected that i knew how can't press that one wonder what the what's the last boss of this
game all right now we're gonna go to that mechanical door it was this way right where was that mechanical
door backtrack backtrack backtrack backtrack backtrack backtrack where was it go back even
further no this is all the way back it's it's no it's down here that was a friendly
oh it was not he wasn't a friendly he was just too big to fit in the doorway
i'm wasting a lot of ammo because they just keep respawning these fucking things
there's no way to can i jump that i did i tried to i did that earlier what the heck all right here
we go mechanical door security gate all right missed the romance plot
all right that's at the bottom of the list of things that i want to do in the chronicles of
verdict game is do the romance mini game oh god should i blow the room up i'm gonna blow the whole
room up i killed one of them i want to heal again cell recharger cell recharger i need a cell
where's the cell where's the power cell no i wouldn't mind the backtracking for the
you have to remember like okay you need to add a power cell to go in that guy but to get the
power so you need to go this way and then you have to charge the power cell in that machine which is
over there i just it's you they give you give me too many points to have to refer to donor memory
battery no i'm good i'm good what's going on there why doesn't i want to do this all right
give me a battery our cell power cell power cell tools battery pack i don't know where that what
power cell prototype rifle oh all right anything else i need get the fuck away from me please
gunplay yeah i know sick gunplay charge the cell did he get to the diaper section yet
i don't think i got to the diaper section yet sorry dude just hang on though i must be there
soon because i haven't seen that shit and it missed me come on i have to put the power cell
into the robot and the robot turns on we press the button and then we go back to i don't know
i don't know i don't know an event and then we go this way what was that okay this is the room
in here ah get in there can't get in here grenade his ass well that was very that was very quick
okay our cell socket what does that do operate the cool hey oh i thought it was a person
bent or should i go up try to look around on the fucking vent vent time be a best vin diesel
i did you know it no i did it like 10 times yesterday oh man they got him
na aim oh this is uh hang down you imagine you look over to your right you hear a big
thud there's a big thud and you look over and redic just his neck is backwards and it's like
holy shit that's the guy that's been such a problem he's dead right next to me holy shit
i could say anything and then you go over this elaborate scheme and elaborate plan of how
hard it was to take him down and you took him down you got like in a tussle with him you got in a
fight you broke his neck and shit and everyone would fear you and respect you for the rest of
your life and all he did was fall next to you and die what am i jumping to here i don't think i'm
supposed to be doing this behind me right eco happy i can go up or i can go let's go in here
actually scared the shit out of me actually scared the shit out of me i'm trying to break
his neck get in i missed go do monkey noises this we okay i think there's a greater evil
would you say fellas fellas i think there's a greater evil you just got stabbed in the eye
with the scorpion tail three times i'm sorry i haven't don't kill me don't kill me don't kill
me don't kill me don't kill me don't kill me gun what's this i don't know what this is gun um you
bastard and um team captains okay i need a healing station very very badly thank you
now all right back the way that guy exploded why is it so bright over here what 2.5 percent health
down to one percent i can't even click it all right somebody explain the meme to me what's like the
dot dot dot meme thing wait this is awesome my first day in gmod this is my favorite thing
beat this man how do you miss with a grenade i don't know did i hold on i hit the lights how
much fucking help do you have this guy is not get him attack him okay what did i gotta have a mini
gun where is it mini gun holy shit let's go shoot it shoot him needed more bloom where's the right
way to go this way you have to do a heavy impression now this river there so i tried
i really did it kind of dude you don't just come at me like that it's only going to be a pack of
cigarettes i don't care i'm leaving eat sandwich uh oh the loading dogs that means i have to say
the words nom seven or eight times in a row and if you do nom two or three times you're getting a
lot of trouble nom nom nom nom i was four and already the internet hates me in the ass
shit wait there's more they're on a conveyor belt this is going to be hell let's watch that dude so
bad apologize for the numbing oh do austin powers prisoner come on who's shooting what is that like
weird sound okay did you hear that what was that like scrambled sound do adam sandler
oh no i just did it there you go thank you come on come on you're killing me with this you're
killing me i don't want to do just kill me so i can do it again you're killing me okay ready
ready go give me a fucking break then couldn't even rev up i should just just i should just
run through this when you play monkey ball very very soon actually like all right did you have
to spawn these that often you're alive that guy took enough bullets turn him into a stew and yet
he still stands to mock me all right let's go shoot it shoot it shoot him what's going on oh
give me that i hear a gun oh it's a gun i hear a gun what's shooting i hear a gun
knocked drink out of your hand dude what the fuck dude do a funny voice comedy streamer dance for
me get this throw this guy out get this guy out of here throw him out just knocked my shit out of
my hands get rid of him slaps your face slaps your face no you don't i blocked it i don't know
how many things were in here just one person that have bullets when you're gonna play saw again
when saw two is played nothing big one i thought that was a re i thought that was a reunion with
the robot i thought i was gonna be able to get in didn't have red eyes they have red eyes when
they're mad when they're mean and bad so um am i gonna escape from butcher's bay or i feel like
i could have probably got out by now i have to pee so bad all right let me take let me go pee
i'll be i'll be right back pee break i am back shall we continue just like clockwork that's right
immediately start firing only how many people are here two three i got no idea i kind of don't
want to put this down all right not enough for you two that's my thing that's my gig and you stole it
from me what what why are you two just standing here give me those grenades oh they were i thought
there were only two permanent health upgrade why is there was going one why not like this
not like this not like this not like this not like this makes you stronger i am for your smart
booster no i refuse to let that become a regular thing he did hey we're gonna do it we're gonna do
it i hope he died from his own grenade it kind of worked that's what pisses me off don't ever
underestimate the power of a dodge roll okay now where what's the actual objective here i think i
have to lose the minigun now i can i can jump with it i can't shit i have to lose the minigun
streamer must be one of those smart boosters hey you can't jump with the minigun well bye minigun
it's fun my minigun we can play again when are you gonna play regina before uh i don't know man
i'm not gonna play it now i don't know president before is a timeless classic i could play that in
20 years or i could have played it 20 years ago and it'll still be just as good don't worry
i'm really glad i brought the minigun uh he died extra where is he nobody okay i'm coming i'm
coming up there gonna take me a minute but i'm gonna get there shoot the gun am i gonna finish
this game tonight uh yeah i i feel like i'm very close to the end of the game i think we're pretty
much there those of you that have played this i i'm assuming i'm gonna get a comment here that says
yo dude probably like another like 25 minutes see yeah this is really really far away from how far
i had to just go um wait a minute doesn't this open yeah wait i was gonna say why is this not
open it's the same room over and over again kind of it's the same room over and over again and
sometimes it's pitch black still dreaming about peeing hi how much did you weigh your prime physique
oh one like 160 something would be like 165 something like that 165 kilograms no it's pounds
i'm from america i don't want to blow this this time is there something i hold on wait a minute
i kind of don't want to take the minigun i'm not taking i'm leaving the minigun if it's a
problem it's a problem he is what he can't got him there's another one refill the nano pod
whatever it is uh i could go get the minigun now i might need it yeah i'll go get it those pretty
cool game um what's over in this slot in this one has there been anything to the whole game
no not end of the stream voice no i'm saying i'm making a statement it's the minigun what's not
minigun doesn't take up take a slot up why did i drop it okay so um a button another button
so which one is the right one i'm assuming one of these was just uh you picked wrong now you die
right i think it was that one yeah from his last stream is this fucking crock of shit why it wouldn't
last stream where are you getting that info from no i'm not done streaming after this
oh man oh this is it this is the final boss
i know what to do you gotta drop these things on them what fucking reload what do you drop
2020 gaming has fucked me up so bad just the way the games progressed over the years
whenever a big enemy explodes or dies i just instinctively look for green blue and purple
text that minigun the looter shooter this game doesn't even have fortnight dances right hanger
you know what that means where this is it we're gonna open up the hanger and it's gonna be at
the top level we're gonna be on the roof and the bad guy is gonna be getting in the helicopter
we have to fight the bad guy in the helicopter i can't wait look at all those preparation last
boss and the game guns that he's not dead we're in the end game yeah we're in the end game this
is it this is bin diesel presents i forgot the name of the movie what's the first one called
chronicles of reddick i told you here it comes here he is there he is that's the boss that's
the last boss you didn't get on the helicopter reddick i don't think you'll wait here it comes
hello back on track i mean i'm using a screwdriver to do this fine and then sit down and stay out of
my way sure sure ready what always trying to ruin my paydays oh is it doubled cross is bound to
give me more than 22 after this now come on let's go but this is not the ultimate bad guy this is
second-in-command bad guy there's double the actual double cross
wait okay if i get put in a device and go back into prison this is stupid if i get put in the
hannibal lector device and i go back downstairs i'm gonna be like all right well that was fun
it's like the third time i've been put in that machine to go back to jail oh come on no we have
to do this this is the third time we've done this and you has just run since you are living
putting you give my ribs time to you may have jaggered being a better shot you'd be dead
and i'd be off so we both look isn't that the way with us johns lows what are you talking about
what's he talking about i said you were lucky to be alive johns but luck can be fleeting
ridic has already cost me plenty far more than your worth to be honest i'm just getting started
haxi yes i was afraid of that but that's why i'm having you put into cryo sleep why won't they just
kill me just like kill me you have a guy right there that has a gun that he'd shoot me in the
face why don't you do that what's with all the weird 80s 90s 2000s villains that just want to
like they don't want to get rid of you they they want to like keep you around forever
it's always some weird elaborate is my plane portal
proposition to abolish law number four three two dash three three seven b
is currently pending today is monday sunset free ocean
okay sunset free flow ocean sunset free flow ocean tv what's going on oh this script
somebody said i was waiting for it i knew it
what you said exercise kill exercise i haven't seen a few of it in like 200 years
i've been sleeping you put a guy in here that looks scary oh wait there
where are they
oh i have to do okay don't fuck that up again just i'm banging my head against the wall
they get me out of here they're gonna sedate me or what let me get my big gamer chair
going on in my own way this exercise appointment will be shared by our prisoners
is forbidden what's the exercise i won is tuesday hurt me before you are are they gonna
wash them where are they putting them i want to go in hey can you freeze us both where do you go oh
okay it's something to do with the chair okay so like do i climb it do i jump it do i punch it
all right like break it okay so he gets put away and then another one wakes up
why are they doing a sedative to me i tried i tried to talk to him and they gave me a sedative
i tell i'm i was pressing y and it wasn't doing anything all contact is forbidden
all contact is forbidden that means you can't talk to anyone
why would it give me the option to talk to them i'm not talking i'm not touching anybody i'm not
talking to anybody what two minutes of exercise begins now exercise okay wait i could just why
was that a prompt to enter the cryo box and now i can't get it to pop back up like that prompt
won't appear anymore yeah i i can't get in his box i was too slow i'll get this one i have to do
it at that first one well how am i supposed to get in somebody else's box okay guys where's the
magic prompt now rest with us yes his cryo self oh he told me don't go get get in his cell get
closer how much more close can i get to his coffin um guys i've been standing here this whole time
and i can't there's no prompt to get in his cryo chamber what how did i do that wrong
administer stand on it i'm gonna get in this cryo bed i don't know where where that is
that was not go back and watch the mod go back rewind what that didn't happen i walked i went
to the same exact spot go back and watch the bot the prompt didn't pop up when i walked over to it
you didn't though and laughing at me don't laugh at me
i was walking all over the fucking thing i stood in the bed i was lying in the bed i was sitting
in the bed what are we doing this part of the game for anyways well there are a bunch of
different riddicks that they keep in cubes yo what i'm wasn't paying attention to that
i said they keep all the verdicts in cubes that was a good joke oh i wasn't looking all right i'll
give you a really good joke somebody just said riddick and morty that's pretty funny
minister then okay what i do wrong there why take me out of the box why did you take me out of the
box who the fuck are you who is this what i said i don't know what that was he gave me a club
i think that was a friend oh shit wait it didn't work he's resistant all right bye he said i have
too much of a thc tolerance now i used to be really really low tolerance not anymore it
happened too many times i died in that stupid fucking portal room too many times i hear a lot
of noise i got hit by a set piece one of the stage lights came down and crashed me in the head
okay sure what does that mean the head last time and why am i fighting a bunch of expensive
coffee makers oh shit okay i don't have any health
i walk how and is somebody somebody with a gun uh how would i so how am i supposed to do this
i have the idea the idea is get to the health station give me your gun
nano miss plus when you need that extra care 64 shots looking good that was a fun carnival game
why is the cryo jail easier than the mines yeah i don't know why was the mines the most horrible
thing ever everything else was so much fun and then it was just it just ruined everything
where is he you can't shoot through that glass done holy shit dude your aim i'm fine it's tricky
open the container doors okay there's monsters over there there are legit monsters here now
huge ones how am i supposed to get away from those what oh my god you fucking empire death
star looking assholes i swear to god why does it why do we open those robots aren't tough just
blast them yeah it's the people that are the problem it's the enemy npcs those are the issues
that guy doesn't even know perfect time for a headshot here my auto my turn
all right i have to be ready for this i gotta be ready here we go
fuck it's so it's so stupid why are the people the hardest enemies in the game
i fought gigantic robots that took way less effort than shooting a regular guy with a pistol
you shouldn't stream on cbd this is bad is atrocious this is every single stream you may
have just came here like an hour ago this is pretty much every this is how it is in fact i
think i'm doing better than usual so i'll tell you i've it only goes downhill from there
better than the last one give me that shotgun
the fuck it's just the same engine as simpson's hit and run i sincerely doubt that also i'm
not playing this on pc there are probably people that all right let me tell you something there's
probably people people that come into this stream and think that i'm using a mouse and i'm playing
like this it's gotta be at least some people probably think that right i mean if i knew this
is on pc and i knew this guy like predominantly played on pc this is like holy shit man like you
gotta you gotta go like you gotta stop screaming like i don't know get up there it's like whoa man
that wasn't that bad oh no wait i can beat one of those like
mushroom kingdom people somebody just spoiled it oh you spoiled it right before i got in one
come on dude oh what look oh my goodness we just got to the end of the movie and i walked into a
room and the bad guy was in there and he says oh he shoots the bad guy in the head right now
come on i knew it was gonna happen but let me see it in real time
someone talks i don't even need to do the voice robocop yeah
all right just kill me because i was not ready for that i thought he slammed the door like somebody
got up they were watching the stream they were like i'm done i'm fucking out of here
i just heard a door slam holy shit this is impossible to use it has rockets how do i use them
kill me i want to start off with full health oh i use is that it who
it's too much take care of that light he was made out of legos oh that was perfect
that was wonderful somebody who's shooting at me i don't know i'm too big i don't even know what i'm
shooting at huh nope it's not happening man we no he's moving around too much die
come on xp idiot battleshoot ready xp 22 battleshoot ready
through the window oh no larry it looks like a dog got into one of the controls of the heavy
guards yeah just just you can dodge it pretty easily but just be fucking careful
am i getting backseat gamed by the robot in the game now got him stand still and you regen
ah that's barry the chopper from full metal octopus by the way i'll take a thousand points
for that yeah it is and where are they oh oh i wanted to die anyways the whole regens uh
was it though i feel like it wasn't the other one didn't do it why would this one do it it does
what i i don't think it is actually i think that's a is it i can't tell is that just the
background i'm looking at it was only rockets for robots oh it is okay let's just hang on
nightbot banned me i'll make a low well you shouldn't be acting up then you should be
behaving yourself they open up the curtains i know they're in there just open it i open
the curtain i know they're in here he moved he like jostled to the left
i feel like i have tts on right now and you guys just paying like three or four dollars to like
say fucking mean shit to me please please please what dude i'm not i don't want to tts is never
going to be on this stream it just won't ever happen it's too distracting for me can i leave
the area it's annoying i just it's it just distracts me i won't you think i have attention problems
in games now imagine with tts i would do tts maybe once or twice if it made sense and it was
something that was a major part of the stream okay so if you're a part of the group that he was
just with do you continue to walk this way or do you go holy shit and well it looks like
sure oh you wouldn't where do i go do one tts stream but do a children's puzzle i mean that
might be funny that might be fun can you press buttons do you say exit immediately why is he
kicking me out he's literally kicking me out that's not cool i can't take him with me okay
well am i gonna die in a cutscene somebody said incoming capture incoming metal thing around neck
i hope not do i control the plane now how's the back i'm taking you to another slam retic
we're getting out of butcher bay together that'll teach hoxy to fuck with me on the way isn't this
guy i even stepped the bastard on the med fees i thought this was a bad guy wait i did he think
he was going to take me to another prison he was haphazardly pointing the gun behind him
like he was looking in the backseat to like talk to kids in the backseat
he that wasn't was he good was it a turn i don't get it why wouldn't you just leave retic
why he come back here i guess you want to just shoot a missile into the window and leave
you'll probably you'll get him just hold a middle finger like right out the front window and shoot
make sure he sees
what the fuck is that device that chair doesn't make any sense that doesn't make that chair
i'm that's that's the most bizarre piece of architecture i've ever seen in a house
what is it what's the point of that why would you not go okay well here's the shotgun
i got a shotgun and i'm fighting his most intense unit
maximum security gamer room is what somebody just said and i cannot think of a more stupid
way to describe what we just watched maximum security gamer room i've got my two my two
gamer defense robots wasn't he just right here he can teleport thanks for for the last encounter
of the game showing me that things can disappear and teleport all right retic how do we get rid
of the sun my they can just see me now so you know hold the button down it overheats what
where's my what is it almost at the end of chapter one fog i find a pillar they teleport
should i just use the shotgun instead yeah okay that's just that's really cool where the hell is
uh god fucking damn it that one of them sucks one of them really really sucks so i can just
give it a one that really really really sucks first this one this guy's an idiot but it's so
easy that was so easy it should have been that easy i was holding i was holding the minigun down
what must be something wait there's no way to leave so he was just in there enclosed in this
little sphere oh shit hopefully they get him you wouldn't have a little back door
can you walk john i think so maybe how's your eyesight but now we're under arrest we're no we're
gonna know we're pretending to be arrested okay when they realize this who do you think blames
who for that one what do these guys just get on the next plane and leave just thinking that was
the guys clearly you have flashlights he's clearly tied to a chair with like a gag in his mouth
he wasn't bald well that's the end i won i only got medium
that's funny now do the sequel i'm not doing the whole sequel we'll check it out how about that
i'll check out the sequel i'm not i'm not doing it all i will i'll go into dark athena and i'll
look around i can't skip and i oh we just jumped right in what's how do i rate uh escape from well
here's the thing so dark athena is just essentially like a long dlc campaign just a remade which is
no one said that i said that because i did my research so it turns out we didn't make it out
no more of this i just want to look around all right if i can swim we'll play if i cannot swim
we won't play okay i have a feeling they added swimming to this one all right i'll see you later
red light on the door yeah i already know this i've this i played this
first x to go into stealth and crouch i just want to i want to kill one person
it's called eye shine i need to watch these movies i feel like i've been so lost
gemma gemma wait did he say kill me please or don't kill me please
i feel like that's really important what what first word is there he said play fall guys no
no he did not and even if he did i'm not sure i would do it oh oh i just want to look at the
extra content
wait when your palms what was that a new move in um i think i missed it it was just counter oh
okay making sure well this was fun i had fun playing uh britic i knew the game was worth
playing and it was worth playing i think it was fun i think i had a really good time playing it
you know what's funny though i there's not been one opportunity where i really
really needed to use the stealth like not the stealth the uh the drag the drag body thing
i'm supposed to go over here uh what let's play sonic adventure 2 on the dreamcast i didn't know
i already played sonic hold this great off okay while in stealth mode blue wait i had to wait
i had to wait this whole time oh this is wait whose gun is this am i holding this dude
i've got this dude hostage all right you're coming with me let's go hostage wow why was
this not in the first game this dude's dead what the guy is the gun that's that's actually pretty
cool i can't walk forward with him though that's kind of annoying uh it's a health kit i don't have
any you know that's a different mechanism i feel like that's probably more comfortable than the
last one stuff them in your inventory play fall guys i think that's a code they stay right there
hold on just stay right there for a minute hey you guys really want to see fall guys really
it's alive still you you garter he's just holding the edge the grate oh he doesn't see me
the disharmonium present art well it worked i tried to punch them
remember there are children watching this stream well hey you clicked on the 18
filter in the beginning if you're under if you're not old enough to see somebody get hit
and you got get out of here leave the new weapon crash can never had to confirm my age on your
stream it's that it's activated wait that's not there they're like this there could be mature
content here it should be there it's not what was it there like two weeks ago it's never been on
yes it has i'm gonna go into my settings right now and look at this i it's i know it absolutely
it's on i turned it on like a long time ago all right channel let's see okay mature content yes
it's enabled i'm being lied to it's all right for every time that i for every time that i fall down
a hole chat tells me one lie all right i'm not gonna play through dark athena i don't think
i just want to see what it was like i just want to see how fun it looked
uh we've you know i'll play i'll play i'll play like one or two rounds of fall guys because you
guys aren't gonna see me again till like sunday so we'll play some fall guys to end the stream
dark athena is great yeah i know i know it's it looks fun but i don't know if i want to give
it like the five to six hours right now this is not that's not gonna happen and you know me
dlc jeremy never happens so i wanted to make sure i got to look at it so we'll play like around a
two fall guys but i had a good time the last two streams i thought were very very fun i had a great
time hope you did too let's play a round or two of fall guys that was really fun oh the extras
thank you for reminding me creepy creepy cool don't play fall guys it's a youtuber bait
i played it a couple days ago and it was it was all right i had a little bit of fun
do it one more time okay where's the trailer you know it's in here
where's the trailer for the next vin diesel movie nice job guys hold on it is only you that matters
they realize it's not the trailer for the movie cool nice wait this wasn't made by one guy
oh it well you well yeah wait wait wait wait wait wait is vin diesel on the team i don't see him
there missing vin diesel well they rented a space at the bottom part there oh well he didn't work
on it oh all right all right let's play fall guys i'm gonna play like only one or two rounds just to
kind of end the stream because we did like a four-hour stream yesterday and i'm still all
right i'm still i still feel okay so i'm good for another probably 45 minutes or so maybe an
hour or two we'll see all right let's uh i'll be right back just to change this game and stuff and
everything ready to go back in a minute just gonna change