Hey, how's it going? I'm uh... I'm here. Yeah. Go back to bed.
Um, no. I will, but not right now. Welcome back everybody. Are you in a sleeping bag?
I'm streaming from a sleeping bag. It sounds like you're going through puberty. Is that what you said?
All right, let's... let's address the thing that we need to address.
I have COVID. I don't think I... the last stream from, what, three or four days ago was like,
oh, I don't think I have COVID, but I'm testing every day and, you know, locking down and whatever,
right? Um, it's COVID. Yeah. You look at dirty teeth. No, I actually don't. But yeah, I have COVID.
I'm okay. Um, it's become pretty clear that I'm right in the middle of it and it's not really
going away, but I feel okay. I just kind of feel like somebody, like, like, punched me in the face.
You know what I mean? Like, I've got... I'm pretty congested and it just feels like somebody went,
like, wham! Just one right hook, right to my fucking face, right? Um, but I'm all right.
And I... I need to start to kind of get a little more active here, uh, released in my own little
personal, uh, bubble that I'm in, because tomorrow is the VR among us sus guy stream.
So I'm going to... I need to get better. I have to feel a little bit better and I do.
But today I wanted to go live and hang out for a little bit. Um, streams are obviously going to be
not, um, more than a few hours for the foreseeable future until I can kind of get over this.
But today we have something interesting. It's like, you know what? Why don't I, uh, why don't I
give a buzz to my good pal Vinny, uh, Vinesauce and, uh, just ask him to see if he wants to carry,
uh, carry a stream for me, because that makes sick. So, uh, me and Vinny are going to play Splatoon
Salmon Runs for a couple hours or something, two, three hours. Something we've been talking about
for a while. Um, so yeah, Vinny's going to carry my stream today. I'm not, I'm, I'm not going to
put like pressure on Vinny to like, oh dude, you got to carry. No. Um, but yeah, let's just play,
uh, Salmon Runs. Something that I've been looking forward to. We mentioned it like a few weeks ago,
so let's do it. I'm going to give Vinny a call right now. Yeah, I like forget how to play. Hey,
what's happening? Hi, how you doing? I'm doing, I'm doing all right. I mean, I've got, you know,
I got COVID. Is that all right though? You got it. Yeah. That's okay. Cause I mean,
you know, the Splatoon will wipe all that away. Yeah. I'm just, I'm, you know, I want to just play,
look, you know what I've been doing the last like three days straight? I've been, okay. So I've been
playing The Sims 4 on Xbox. Does that sound fucking weird to you? A little bit. Yeah. I mean,
you need something to take your mind off of it. Um, you know, listen, man, as long as, as long as
The Sims are giving you an alternate life where you cannot live your own, it's fine. You know what?
That's true. Yeah. But, uh, yeah. So me and my girlfriend have been just kind of playing it,
locking down. I'm sorry that I sound like I'm going through puberty. That's well, you know what? I'm
sorry. I have a milk voice today. It's okay. I've never heard that expression before, but
the past couple of weeks, I've been losing my voice and I've sounded like the Crypt Keeper.
So don't feel too bad. I think it's, you sound relatively human compared to how I sounded. It
was, it was horrendous. Well, I'm glad to at least be alive. And I'll tell you right now,
like the next couple of days, I mean, I think me and Vinny were talking about doing some VR stuff
too. Um, yeah, I, I'm, I might be like a fucking weirdo, but you know what I mean? I'm like on like
cold medicine, right? Like, so this is like, well, this is, this is the sus guy. You know
what I mean? Like, let's just lean into it. Yeah. Do it for, do it because you know what? You,
you won't have an opportunity to do it again. We're not getting any younger. Splatoon,
not Splatoon, Among Us VR is out tomorrow. And you know, I was telling my chat, I might play it.
There's a chance you and I will play it at some point. Maybe it'd be fun. So be the sus guy,
you know, like, like when people, listen, when I see something spin, they want me to be the spin
guy. They want me to say spin. I say it. That's okay. Yeah. I mean, it's only one day, by the way.
I'm never doing this ever again. The whole entire channel is going to be rebranded to the sus shit.
It's going to be one day only. So you better be there. Imagine how many people were going to be
confused if they just joined in off the front page. Like I've never heard of this guy before.
And then that's what they get. Part of the idea is that, um, dude, it's, I'm going to put like
branding everywhere. I'm going to have like a sub goal. I'm going to talk about,
it's going to be like, I'm not, I'm not even Jeremy. It's a different person.
And I like that. Like, how do we borrow that? Can I be, you want to be, you want to be the second
side? No, you don't. No, no, no. You don't want to do that. I'm good. Don't even say it. Do you want
to, do you want to do, do you want to do some regular matches first and then salmon run or
you just into whatever, whatever you want to do. Okay. Um, hop into a lobby and we can just do some
matches just to warm up and then we'll salmon. How do, how do, um, how do I play the game?
Yeah, I can, I can get you, I can get you that information. Hang on. It's been a couple of weeks.
Of right trigger is shoot gun, right? Yeah. Shoot. You jump with B you squid.
I slept on this game for so long, man. Like it did really is so much fun.
Yeah, this is great. I mean, it's just, it's just a lot of fun to play. And you know what,
even though it's not ghosts, it's pretty good. I know we have a reputation. I'm going,
I'm going into the lobby. I only play games to kill ghosts. We only play like scary ghost
games. It's the only thing we do. Oh, okay. I remember how to play. Um, so do you have to,
do you like join off me? Do I have to invite you to the lobby? Um, I think you can join off of me
if you want. That's cool. Just in like the switch menu. Yeah. I got a, so just press, um, L I think
and then you'll here. Let me see. Wait, which L? Oh, okay. Save. Yeah. Regular L, regular L.
Right. Okay. And then join lobby. You should see mine. Okay. I see with friends. Yeah. Regular
battle is what was your name? Uh, is your name raw? No. Who the fuck is that? It's definitely
not wrong. I've never seen this person before in my life. Maybe that's my alter ego. I don't know.
It's a raw guy. Okay. Um, I'm in lobby. I see with friends. Yeah. Yeah. So it should be like,
regular L match menu. And then I see, I see friends. I don't see you. We are friends on the
switch chat. Do I have like a weird setting or something? No, not anymore. I mean, if I did,
you, why don't you make one and just do with friends and then I'll, I'll join off of you.
Okay. So if I just do with friends, hop into a turf battle, regular battle with friends.
I just click regular battle with friends. Okay. Yeah. Oh, there you are.
Well, you saw me right there online. I can create a room. Okay. Okay. So I see, I can't like invite
you, but I see you're online. So I'm creating a room chat. How do I join German's room? Do I just
press his name? There's no password on it. So that's fine. Okay. I'm creating room boomer
technology stream. I've got COVID motherfucker. All right. It's, I got it chat. Not like in a mean
way. I meant like, let him have this, let him be his COVID self. And like, I don't know what I'm
doing either. I got it. All right. No, I got it. We know what we're doing. I'm not going to even
read that. Hey, we did it. All right. Cool. That's vile. All right. I think I'm, yeah, we'll
probably just get random people to join in. And then like, if any of my friends can join off of
me, you know, just like to be in the group and carry us, feel free. Yeah. I'm down just to play
whatever. Let's do a few, we can just kind of chill and get some stuff going. Calm down. You're
aggressive. Yeah. This is, this is a low effort, like just whatever, just play some Splat. I mean,
it's not even Splatfest yet. It's not? Is that a thing? Do you know what Splatfest is, Sharma?
It's when you vote on one of three things and like the team that gets the most kills and like
win games. That's the selected thing. So this, this Splatfest, it's the Pokemon starters. It's
fire, grass and water. And you get to choose, you join a team and then you have to like fight for
your team. That's this weekend. That's pretty cool. It's neat. I've been out of sync this whole time,
but now I'm good. That sounds fun. That's your Splatoon name? Yeah. You said it's so dejected.
I just like did it really quickly. Okay. What's wrong with my shirt today? What's
wrong with my shirt? He has COVID. Let him live his life. It's a Marvel shirt, not a clown shirt.
Then he go over to the robot and press A. Okay. Somebody called it an arcade carpet shirt.
Oh, there you are. It's pretty cool. So what do you usually play in this? Do you usually do
like painter or like shooter? What do you usually do? Oh, um, ready up germ. Oh, I'm calling you germ
for some reason. Is that okay? Yeah, that's good. All right. Oh, I use. Yeah, I use like
just shoot gun fast, but also with good range. I like that the dual pistols are fun. I like the
dodge. Yeah, I like those too. Oh, and so remind me how do you use your superpower? It's like a
button you press, right? Yeah, I think superpower is oh, I press R the stick precedent. Oh,
there it is. Yeah. Oh, yeah. It's like this mech. Okay. Yeah. I have trouble with them with the mech.
Yeah, I suck with it, but it's the combo of the weapon I use. I can't choose anything else. It's
just like I'm stuck with it. Okay. All right. So you're a veteran of this game, right? I mean,
I'm fucking terrible at it, but yeah. Yeah. I have some ideas on how to like, uh, shoot.
Okay. It's been a while since I haven't played in a while. So let's see if I can see if I still got
it. All right. Let's get it. Let's get it. See now you understand. Yeah. That's, that's a good
catchphrase. Oh my God. Bubbles. They're fucking shooting bubbles at us already. Sorry. I just
don't like bubbles. It's a very annoying weapon. I'm fine. They, they shoot bubbles out of a urinal
germina. What? Out of a urinal? Hold on. They shoot it out of a urinal. I didn't know that. I
got to see this. It looks like it at least. I don't know what it is. Oh, I'm out of ink.
Sorry. Sorry. Sorry. You've okay. Good. You then you avenged me. Oh wait. It's the, um, it's the
bucket. It's like the bucket thing, right? Yeah. To me it looks like a, like a urinal or like, um,
like what are those things that they put? Like a bedpan, a bedpan with ink. Yeah. Oh God. What
even just hit me? I just, I got exploded. Yeah. We, we wiped. I have, I'm getting audio from two
different sources here. Is it like confusing? So how do you do your audio when you play the switch
and let, and talk to somebody? Uh, so I don't have anything on a delay. It's slightly delayed. Um,
essentially I am routing my capture card and I had an El Garbo too, by the way, for a while.
It focus almost just came out of my nose. I hope they didn't. No, no one saw that. Um, I, yeah,
I used El Garbo for a while. I had to get another one, which was even cheaper and it's fine. It does
the job. So basically I'm, um, audio is coming through a separate program, but the video is like
live, like, oh, I split. Yeah. So I don't have anything on a delay other than the audio is
delayed like half a second. So it's, there's a slight disconnect. We can kind of destroyed.
It's a warmup match. That's true though. Yeah. When was the last time you played? It's been a while
since I played. Three weeks. Yeah. We both played, we probably both played like the same day.
Yeah. Like to the day we both just got the urge to like, let's play some Splatoon.
Yeah. Separate. And then now we're garbage. That's okay. I have, uh, friends that are very good at
this game that are going to just hop in at some point and carry us. It's going to be great.
It's also all right too. We're going to be Sam and Andy's at some point, right?
All right. What's that? Sam and we're just going to be Sam and run Andy's or
Oh, oh, oh yeah. I thought you meant like Sam and Andy, like, like two names.
Oh, no, no, no. Like Sam and run. Like we're going to be Sam and Andy. We're going to do that. Uh-huh.
Sam and Andy. I was like, I'll be Sam. I guess. I don't know. That's fine. I don't even know
where'd you come from. All right. So how did we do on our first game back after three weeks of
being away from the game? Like 35%, 38%. That's all right. That would be, we, that we,
high MMR. It's our, our far from being so good. Yeah. I was wondering, so I have the game audio
coming through my left ear and then you coming into my right ear through here. So I, it's like,
it's weird. I have two different headphones. Are you okay? It's kind of, it's kind of bizarre
if you want me to be completely honest with you, but I can do it. It's fun.
Okay. Uh, okay. Cool. Yeah. That's what I couldn't do that. That's just too much. That's,
that's too disconnect would throw me off. Yeah. I think it would like my circadian rhythm,
like I would fall, like I'd be streaming and just fall to the ground. Cause my inner ear balance
would be thrown off. I didn't even get like a, like 2002 resolution for my score. Like,
holy shit, I'm under four ADP. That's bad. So, all right, let's do battle times. Maybe I should
change my loadout. I gotta, I gotta, we gotta get back into it. The game. Oh yeah. We got,
no, we get this. We got this. We got Nari now on our team. He's a mod of mine. He's,
he's going to carry. Oh, right. Nari. Really? All right. Let's go. His name rhymes with carry.
So he's going to carry us. If not, I'm going to remove him from my moderator's team. It's fine.
It's normal. It's fine. All right. I'm going to try hard this time. Actually. Come on. I got him. I
got him. I got him. I got him. I got him. What does that thing do? I think it's a grenade. Right.
Top right is a sprayer. Okay. Can we destroy those? Yeah. Yeah, you can. Oh, I am bad at this right
now. Hey, um, do you, do you only use the duallys? No, I just, it's just what I had equipped them last
time when I was playing. Okay. Cause I've tried other weapons in this game and I, and I'm just
rotten at all of them, including the ones that I'm good at. There's so much of their ink everywhere
I can't even move. They're throwing bubbles at us from a urinal again. No ink. There ain't no ink
anywhere. I just got so bad. We, no, we got this. We got it. Ooh, bubbles. Throwing for content.
Yeah. Ready to go to the right place? What just happened? Oh, I did. Okay. Okay. Okay.
What the? Dude, those bubbles kill you in one hit. The bubbles are such bullshit. I really don't
understand them. And then they update the game and it just like, bubbles are even better than
usual. That's like all the, all the balance changes and bubbles have just seemed better
and better each day. How do I get that gun? Is that, how much was that? I still don't, I don't
even have bubble. I don't know where it is. No, I don't, I don't know. Let's go. They don't know
that they can buy whatever they want. Well, now I do. God damn it. Chad, that's the exact line of
thinking that got me back into Pokemon cards. We, we don't need that again. Shooting the floor. I
don't even know how to control that thing, man. Shit. Dude, that, you know what that looks like?
That looks like a fucking Trix yogurt. I want it wicked bad. I've never had Trix yogurt. Really?
Wow. No, no, this just reminds me of Nickelodeon. Yeah. It's just like, like, like you win an,
your name is Jack Black. You win an award and they just like slime you for no good reason.
It's fun though. That's how we grew up. That was it. So do they want to do like how many more you
want to do before we do the salmon run? Let's do one more. We did, we did better that time. That's
a, come on. Look, we haven't played in a long time. Give us a little bit of slack. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I think one, one more would be good. Guys stop streaming. I'm at work. All right. We'll, we'll
just see you later, man. It's nice to hang out. I've got to wrap it up. So, so, uh,
Jerma, your symptoms, you're, you're just like, you got a headache and stuff. Yeah. So I had a
headache like two days ago. So we're three days ago. I don't even remember. Um, I was on stream
and like the day before this is, what was the last time I streamed guys? I actually don't even remember.
Um, I had kind of like an achy slow felt kind of shitty. It was three days ago. Okay. And then
that just developed into just, I was tired and I still am. Yeah. And now I just kind of have a lot
of, I'm not really coughing though. No cough really at all. It's more just like somebody
like punched me in the face and like my nose is stuffed. And that didn't happen, right? No.
Okay. Well, yeah, I see. I mean, unrelated. I got punched in the face.
This is your first time like with the COVID? Yeah. I didn't get it for the entire time
that it was, you know, during the major, major, major surges. Lucky enough, right? Yeah. I
avoided it up until about June or July rather of this year. And it was, I couldn't like,
yeah, I had the same symptoms like headache, tired fever. And then, um, it was like a week
of not being able to eat food because my throat hurt so much. It was like broken glass and razor
blades. Yeah. I'm so I've, I mean, obviously knock on wood, right? Because I'm currently
right in the middle of it. Um, I've been testing every, I want to say we're not, I haven't been
testing the last few days, obviously, because I have it, but I tested today. You know, you can
tell how much, you know, whatever viral, um, well, I guess whatever it is. So hold on. Let me like,
at least don't embarrass myself for five seconds while I talk. Okay. I gotta, I gotta, I gotta,
I gotta hold on. Okay. Okay. I can talk again. Okay. So, uh, use your special. I guys, I, I can't,
I don't even, I can't even see. Um, what was I saying? So yeah, you've been testing and stuff
just to make sure you didn't have like a high viral load. Okay. So don't laugh at that. No,
no, no. I'm just laughing. This is science. This is like medicine. No, I'm laughing at the fact
that I fucking have zero points. I think. Oh, come on. We have zero points. How can I look?
Are you sure this game is good for you in your weakened state? If you're going to,
you know what I mean? Like you may not have a voice after this. No, no, I'll be all right.
I'll be all right. I just want to make sure I have more than five points. Okay. Okay. So, um,
when you take a COVID test and that, that line that's at the bottom, right? It's like, oh,
is it faded? That's positive. Is it, you know, I'm not even playing anymore. I just got like
killed instantly. Um, like is the line, the line is like solid, solid, solid. Like I'm,
I'm in the middle of it right now. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I'm sorry, man. I hope you feel better soon.
I appreciate it. Thank you. I feel all right though. It's not, I'm not a good enough stream,
right? I mean, that's, that's a positive. Yeah. It's a positive on top of the wrong kind of
positive. Well, honestly, I'll be completely upfront. I really just kind of want to be live
for a little while just because tomorrow's a big day. Tomorrow's a huge day. Yeah. I gotta be
confident that I can be kind of live for more than a few hours. You know what I mean?
Yeah, I hear you. And you want to acclimate yourself. Well, I'm, I'm happy to help. I mean,
this is, this is a thrill to just lose Splatoon with you is a dream come true. So I'm down.
Yeah. Let's do, let's do the salmon run. Let's do salmon run. Cause that way we
aren't going to get killed immediately and we're going to have fun. It's going to be great.
I mean, that was fun too, but yeah, but yeah, but it's heartbreaking.
All right. No, but no, it's a, it's to be all jokes aside. I feel okay. Now are you going to
feel okay in a headset in VR? We'll see. Hey, I mean, if there's ever a scream to be like
fucked up, it's tomorrow. Let me tell you. Like if I don't, if I feel like fucked up tomorrow,
like who, it's the suss guy day. Like I don't, it doesn't, I don't care. It doesn't matter,
right? Yeah. You just have to like leave your like meat, like your flesh behind for a little
bit and just be an entity. Like, you know what? Be a goblin for a short time and then it'll be
over and you can relax. It'll be great. So how do I, so we do, do I have to join a different menu?
Yeah. So I'm going to, I'll make it this time and you can join in. Um, cause I have,
I have some people on my friends list that are fantastic. Hacker, are you going to join Hacker?
Hacker will carry us. Yes. Okay. Splatoon. Uh, I'm said Splatoon run. Is it such a fun game?
Splatoon run sounds like the iPad game they come up with where you just are on a lane and you have
to go like, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Left and right and collect coins and jump over obstacles.
Right. And it's like no regard for copyright, complete disregard for all of Nintendo's IP.
Okay. So, um, have you beaten the chicken in a salmon run?
I've beaten the chicken. Yeah. I call it chorizo. Yeah. No, um, sin or base can, uh, I'm ready by
the way, German. If you go press L go to salmon run and then you find, uh, do the same thing from
before you can join, um, base or sin, we can rotate you guys out, but I want to get Hacker in
because we, we need to win. Um, so I see private battle, regular battle, and then, uh, friend
request received. Oh, great. Uh, I think, yeah, you have to go into the salmon run lobby grisco.
Oh, I actually go to the lobby. Okay. Yeah. You have to, uh, press like,
what is it? Yeah. And then you'll see, see me and I'm recruiting. Okay. Cool. Cool. Cool.
So now match menu and with friends, I freelance. I think freelance. Yeah. And you should see me.
There you are joinable. Let's go. All right. Let's do it. The audio is fucked up. It is.
Okay. There's, there's, let's get it. And, uh, we just need one more. So,
okay. Thank you, sin sin. We'll, we'll get you rotated in, in a bit. All right. Yeah. I love
this mode. Nari, you have to leave Nari hackers joining not Nari. I promise you Nari, we will have,
we will get you in. We're going to, we're going to rotate people out. It's going to be great.
I'm not at all confusing and annoying because Nintendo has the best online infrastructure.
Yeah. I, this, and this game is like, I mean, okay, this game has felt the most online complete out
of any Nintendo game I've ever played. Does that make sense? Agreed. Okay. Yeah. A hundred percent.
Yeah. I mean, smash was okay. Smash had its moments where it felt easy and then it also
sometimes felt awful, but this one feels pretty good. Yeah. It's not bad. The only problem I have
with it is a lot of disconnects. I've seen thankfully that only seems to happen to be in
a lobby and not in a game. I haven't seen it in a game. You know, obviously knock on wood.
I've said that like three times today now. You know, knock on wood. My family used to say that.
That was like a big one. Knock on wood. And uh, Jerma, have you ever heard of the Maloikia knife?
The Maloikia knife? Yeah. No. What's a Maloikia knife? I'll tell you about it. This is real,
by the way. I grew up with, um, so my, my family's Italian Americans, those that don't know me over
in Jerma's channel. I'm a New Yorker. So, you know, it's kind of, yeah, of course, you know,
right off the boat. And, um, one of the things that they would do, my grandmother and my great
grandparents when I was really young, but my grandmother picked up this thing was they had
a knife, the Maloikia knife. And whenever someone was sick, they would throw the knife across the
room to ward off evil spirits. Oh my God. Yep. Now I've told this story on my stream and I'm like,
chat, I know I'm insane. There's no way this is real. This is a false memory. It's implanted by
some movie or something, but it's real because some other families have done this too. This is
an old Italian thing where they thought that like, when you got sick, it was like spirits.
Wait, we're going to lose on round one? No, no, I think we, we got this. We got this.
So, so wait, so if somebody started to get sick, you said, like some, all of a sudden
somebody would throw a knife at like a wall. Yeah. My grandmother would throw a knife and
say Jesu Christu or something like Jesus, you know, in Italian. And then she would throw the
knife at the wall. Were people in the room? Yeah. Oh, it's gone flying past me several times.
Oh my God. Yeah. I was, this stopped happening when I was like seven, but it was definitely a
thing. I don't know if the Maloyka knife is still in my family, but if it is, I'm selling it cheap,
chat, if you want it. By the way, selling, selling things are cheap. I wish I could, I hate this
weapon. I don't want it anymore. How do I get rid of this? Next round. This fucking umbrella
shotgun thing sucks absolute ass. I hate this thing. Yeah. Speaking of selling things.
I've never heard of that before. Oh, you want to just get rid of the weapon. That's what you were
trying to say. Okay. Yeah. No, it's just a weird thing. I just thought that you might find it
interesting. That is some wacky, wacky traditions. What was it called again? A Maloyka knife.
Yeah. Right. You can throw the eggs too, right? You can throw them. Yeah. They cost as much as
it takes for a grenade. Okay. So you probably know, but for these lads, yeah, you're gonna
throw a grenade in their mouth. Yep. So I'm assuming you've played mostly salmon run, right?
I pretty much, I spent a little bit of time doing the other game, but this was like more fun to me
in my brain. Yeah. This is the best mode. Oh, please. What? They don't go in his mouth.
Sometimes they bounce out. Yeah. Yeah. How many do we have? 23. 23. Yeah. We're good. We're good.
Anything else is a bonus at this point. They get it. There you go. We can't have,
it has to be more than that. So what, what if we, what rank are we on right now? What
we put difficulties is technically, I don't think this is all that high in difficulty because
I demoted, I did so bad at one point that I got like demoted a couple of times.
So this is like normal ish, I think this is a new weapon I've never seen before. It's like a burst
cannon. Yeah, those are good. That's okay. All right, German. So for this one, you got to shoot
the spigots. They're called what? Yeah, you know, the geysers. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. So shoot them like
regular shoot them like just like what I'm doing right now. So you shoot, shoot them until they
start, they burst and then you'll see eventually a fish will emerge from them. The golden, it's a
little confusing, but there's, there's now a golden fish that we have to shoot. That's some
crunchies over here. Right here. Right here. This basically gives me like anxiety.
Yeah, it's like if John Williams composed Jaws on cocaine.
All right. So these are the guys are going off. Do we need to do anything with it or no?
When it goes off, you're good. You just have to get a bunch of them open and that way we
spawn a golden, a golden fish thing. So yeah, just, yeah. Okay. Golden fish spawning at my
location. Golden fish is spawning at my location on my way. That's what that means. Right. Uh huh.
Oh, wait, is it? Oh, here it is. No, it's here. Germ. All right. Get it. We got tremendously close
to not succeeding. Yeah. I'm very rusty. Oops. I pressed, I actually pressed R at the set of
whatever. Vinny, try not to open too many valves or else you'll get mobbed with other enemies.
The higher the geysers are, the closer the goldfish is. Oh my God. We nailed it. I'm so confused.
I'm getting bad advice from my chat. Does your chat ever give you like, um, bad advice? Um,
I'm trying to remember the last time I got good advice from them. Okay. I think it was probably,
um, I want to say seven or eight years ago. Oh, all right. Yeah, that's, that's pretty good.
Somebody told me to buy a certain key in TF2 and like, don't buy these ones. I went, I was like,
oh, what does that mean? And then I gave it up being a good, I did like advice or a certain
crate or something. That's cool. My chat was like, Vin, you should get Dogecoin. Trust me.
10 K Dogecoin. I was like, all right. No, I didn't do that. You should get Doge. I should get it now.
That would probably be smart. Like, like after the fucking crypto collapse.
It's just fucked up. All right. I got the gun. All right. I'm going to, let's see if I can get
some high scores here. Okay. Oh, the UFO is my favorite one. I'm, I'm really going to get in the
UFO. All right. There we go. Ooh, no way. We both recently had a strange phenomenon happen to us.
What happened? We were both, we were both on the news for different reasons.
Yeah. You were on like CNN. So fucking weird. What were you on? Like, what was your, what did they
do? I didn't see it. Well, like, what was your thing? Um, well, there's been a few that, I mean,
well, I don't know about on the news. I did an NPR interview. Okay. That was cool. That was really
fun. It's cool. But like, you were actually like on like CNN. I was interviewed because I played
trombone champ. That's the only reason they had me on. It was, it was like a 30 second
total amount of me on the screen, but it got shut out to like a thousand places.
People were saying they saw me on their local news. I was like, why? That's so fucking awesome.
So wait, how did that happen? Did you just kind of get reached out to like, oh, hey,
we're just even playing this game. You want to know the truth? I mean, I've,
yeah, whatever the story is, I'd like to hear it. The reporter's son was a fan of mine.
Really? Yeah. He's like, dad, you got to see this game. This guy, Vinny plays it. That's the cutest
thing I've ever heard. Yeah. That's so weird though. I was like, all right, yeah, I'll be on the news.
All right. That's fine. Slow news day. Oh, I know this one. You have to throw it into the, uh,
receptacles, right? Oh goodness. That's like a, I mean, here's the thing though.
You can always kind of reach back to that no matter what. Like, oh yeah, you know, how,
you know, how did you, how was your career? What did you do? Well, I was on CNN. You know what I
mean? Yeah, yeah, yeah. That's good enough. Like I'm fine with that. Like at the top of your resume,
no matter what happens, no matter what happens for the next like 50 years of your life,
that could be at the top of your resume. It could be. So I will, here's the thing. I will tell you
that it was not good enough to get me verified on Twitter. What? It was, uh, yeah, there was
a denial. And now that, um, the muskrat has taken over, that whole thing is just a complete
clusterfuck. I have no idea what's happening anymore. But I said, you know what? Now that
I've been on the news and I'm like kind of a big deal in the trombone champ community, I should,
let me apply. Let me see if it happens. I got like, it's probably a good word.
30 minutes later I was denied. I got like a Mondo rejection. What happened to my title?
Why is this my title? This title is fucking disgusting. What the fuck is this title?
I didn't do this title. The title of the stream. I didn't make this title. I don't know what you
mean. I just saw in chat somebody said, dude, what the fuck were you thinking with this title?
And I'm like, what are they talking about? Oh, okay. I think one of my mods, it says like I'm
shitting my pants and stuff. What does it say? I shouldn't have eaten that sushi. It gave me salmon
runs. Who did this? With mods like that, who needs chat members? That's really good. All right. I
got to hate this weapon. The salmon runs. I can't even change it. They're blaming, they're blaming
Josh. Oh, that's, that's, that's, that's it. Josh is a good lad by the way. We've, Josh and I have
played Valheim together a lot back in the day. A lot of VR stuff too. I probably wasted that, but
no, Josh is, Josh is, Josh is a good dude. Unless he's the guy that changed your title, in which case.
Yeah, in which case like what the fuck does this guy think he is? Right, exactly. I can be the
depositor if you just throw him. Okay. You can also use this receptacle here. This like device,
it shoots them. So this is. Oh, we got to, these guys are the worst. I hate this weapon. I'm just
using it. Okay. Thank God. Thank God I did that. We're in a little bit of trouble here. I'm trying
to. We're good. We're good. Okay. Good. Good. Get a couple extra. Yeah, I can get it. Oh, okay.
Yeah, we're good. We're good. The NPR article has a funny picture of you.
You know, I saw somebody mention this and I've, I've heard, I've said this myself as well.
There are like four pictures of me that exist on the internet that anybody uses for anything.
There's like the one where I'm, I don't hate it and I don't know why people keep using it,
but I guess it's like one of like three pictures I have. You know, the one I'm talking about where
I'm like. Is it the one where they say that you look like a psycho? That's what I'm going like this.
I'm not, I can't see you. Oh, right. But you know what I mean? I'm going and people use it for
fucking everything. It's a blurry photo. I got like kind of messy hair. It's like a screen cap
from a random face, full face cam thing that I did. Um, base, can you rotate out so we can
get someone else in? Okay. Nevermind. Uh, next time base, next match. Um, yeah, no, it's weird
because also you do, you're on camera a lot. I'm not. And like, you have thousands of hours
of photos and like video of you. And if they use those same four, they're just doing it to spite you.
Yeah, that's clearly like you could take. Okay. Ready? Like, like use one of those.
Well, I think it's the same picture from what I like from the fucking basement.
Like you could, how many images of you can take a frame grab and just kind of blow it up and clean
it up and make it, you know what I mean? I'm, you know, I'm doing my own headshots later.
We're going, we're going, we're going, we're going to do this. I might be sick, but I don't
even care. I'm going to full cam and I'm just going to do various poses that you can use. And
please use, if you're going to write articles about this fucking scream, use those. We'll do
that. Maybe not. Maybe not today. I just said I was going to do it today.
You're like, I don't care. I'm sick. I'll do it now. It's fine.
I actually had, um, here's another weird one. I had some photographer ended up being a really
nice dude. Want to take a headshot of me in like Washington square park in Manhattan.
Yeah. And the idea was, I thought like, is this like some kind of weird thing? But it was a weird
thing, but not in the way I expected. He took photos of various like content creators and
YouTubers and then posted them on a website with just their subscriber number. That was it.
It was art. It was art, bro. It was, it's like not their name. My name wasn't on there.
It was just a number. Yeah. Yeah. That was the goal. It was like, the idea was it was trying to
kind of, I mean, if you have to explain the art, it's not good art, I guess, but I'm, uh, essentially,
yeah, it's like online. You're only valued by the number of subscribers you have kind of thing.
That's the, what it was trying, but people have just turned that into like a nightmare, like,
like meat rot photo of me using AI.
Do AI is fucked up. I'm, I'm serious. I have probably had more to say, but that was,
I guess all I was going to say. That's fair. I mean, yeah, I know the, I think that picture
of the meat, right? No, there's like, there's like this photo that looks like a headshot,
but then they put it through AI and it interpreted it in like the most bizarre way possible. And it's
like the same way you kind of have the sus guy photo. Oh, okay. This is just like a terrible,
terrible photo of me, but at least it has, you know, my subscribers. Yeah. At least that
people do know how many subs you have. Yeah. That's the important part. Somebody said my
microphone's fucked up. No, my voice is. It probably sounds like I'm talking through a wall
because I kind of am. I'm talking through a wall, which is my congestion. Yeah. Chad, do you know
what picture I'm talking about? If anyone can like grab that photo, I just want to show,
I want to put that on the screen after this match. These guys are rough. He has a big grenade heads.
Yeah, I don't, I don't like them at all at higher levels. This, this is absurd. I can imagine.
Diamond run is just absurd. And if you like even just casual conversation like we're having
is enough to ruin the match. You know, it does feel that way. You know what I don't understand?
And like, like honestly, if you were, if you can do this, I know a lot of like streamers can do
this and a lot of people like probably watching and the chats can do this too, but I don't know
how people play video games at a very high level. Well, just talking about like whatever,
like people like, you know, playing Valorant and they're like, and then they're talking about like
their favorite Dunkin Donuts order and shit. It's like, I don't even know how people do that.
Right. Yeah, I can play like low, low effort baby games, but not. Yeah. I can't hear it. Oh,
fuck. Yeah. Chad, here's the photo. Jerma, I'm going to put this in our call and you can
when on your own time. Oh my God. It's fucking horrendous. You look like an alien that ate
Vinny and like became him. Yeah. Which explains a lot. I mean, that it's scary. Yeah.
All right. Let me get back up there. Yeah. AI isn't a really especially AI images.
They're in such a weird place where do you feel like when you look at an AI image,
you are looking at the way that stuff actually feels and looks like in a dream?
Yeah, I've I've had the same thought. Yeah, absolutely. Like you can't grasp it. It's just
the more you look at it, the worse it gets. Who's shooting us with that laser?
Yeah. If I had a dream that you and I went to go get like a piece of pizza somewhere,
this is what you would look like in my dream. Right. Right. And yet you have to see
some of the new AI stuff. Like I saw some photos where I was like, that's a real person. Yeah.
I couldn't tell the difference until I looked at their hands. It's always the hands, right?
You know, like when someone's like deceptively old and they had a lot of work done. But if
you look at their hands, you know, interesting, interesting. I'm telling you, like Martha Stewart,
she she's like 80. She looks like she's 50 at most, but her hands are 90. Wow. AI is the same way
because it adds like five fingers and like makes them all weird. Yeah. Hands are the giveaway.
That's that's the trick. You'll always know, right? That kind of like if you're in a dream,
you look at a clock. Right. Yeah. If you look at it, you guys don't know if you're in a dream
and you like don't know if you're dreaming or not. If you look at a clock, it'll just be a bunch of
it'll be a mess. It won't be like alien language. I have like, do you have recurring dreams, Jerma?
I do. What are do you have any specific locations that you go back to? A lot of my recurring dreams
are in my bedroom. Like I'll wake up and it's one of those things where I'll wake up five to ten
times in a row in a different dream in my bed. And I just can't escape the dream world. It's
happened like three or four times now. Shit. It'll be like, okay, I'm awake now. And it's like,
no, I'm like a weird AI version of my bedroom. And no, this is something's weird. Something's off.
And then something really strange will happen. And I wake up again. And the same feeling happens.
It's like, okay, I'm obviously not this is not real. Because you know, this is not real,
because my bed frame is not 10 feet around the bed. Right. This is not accurate, right?
Stuff like that will just keep happening. And I'll keep waking up and being like terrified.
Jesus. Yeah, even that. Yeah, I don't have that experience personally. That's, that's, that's.
Yeah, you'll kind of wake up. If those of you that have these recurring kind of bedroom dreams,
you'll wake up and you have a ceiling fan. No, I don't. Well, that's weird. That's not my room,
but it is. I don't have a ceiling fan. Bizarre. Someone said, Vinny, have you ever seen your phone
in your dreams? You know what? That's fucking weird, because I'm on my phone like all the time,
as most of us are, have never once looked at my phone in a dream. Let me tell you something not
to do, but you're going to do it next time. And it's you're going to it's going to change
literally your entire life forever. If you're ever in a dream and you know, I feel like I don't want
to say this because it sucks. Okay. If you're in a dream and you're in like kind of lucid dreaming,
and people, people in my chat know this, but I might be scaring people in yours.
Okay. Well, look in a mirror. Go find a mirror and look in it. It is. But are you, you're inventing
the mirror. Yeah, because your brain does not understand mirrors when you are asleep. So when
you look at a mirror, it's your subconscious trying to recreate a full mirror in your head.
And it has so much trouble doing it that you will look at yourself in a mirror and it'll be this
weird, like eyeless, like demon person that's looking back at you and like their proportions
are all wrong and weird and shit. It really is like AI trying to make a person. It's like that
episode of Star Trek when the holodeck can't compute the data fast enough. It's true. Yeah,
that's such a good way to put it. Um, if you, uh, hold a, oh, sorry. I have like three headphones.
That's okay. Three headphones. How many years do you have? Well, I've, you know,
look at my AI generated face. I got like four years. Oh, okay. I don't think I've ever even
looked at a mirror in a fucking dream. I think the most, I know I've seen myself in dreams,
but like from a third person perspective, but I, for me, it's more, more location-based. Like I
keep going to weird post-apocalyptic versions of places. I already know they're not like fallout.
They're just wrong. They're just wrong. And I keep going back to them. Like once every month,
I go back to this weird mall that has a PF Chang's type Chinese food place and like a flea market.
Really? And I don't buy, I never buy anything. And it's just anxiety dream. So it's so weird.
Yeah. So my dreams are more location-based, but I've had plenty of, um, I was, uh, do you ever
keep a dream journal? I, you know, I used to, I used to, I got really into it for a little while,
but then I ran into the problem that you probably run into too, or maybe you have,
you will wake up after a dream and you're so tired and you're like, I need to write this down,
but I don't give a shit at all. I'm going back to bed. I'm tired. Yeah.
That's, that's the thing that happens to me with music. So I wake up with, with songs,
like some of my songs come from dreams and I have to like hum them into my phone and I've lost a
number of ideas. Cause I was just too tired. I was like, fuck it. But I did have, um, a dream
journal and I was telling my chat when I was taking melatonin a lot, I was having the most
bizarre fucking dreams. I had one, one dream that I was hanging out with Martin Scorsese,
but he was a stick insect and he was like, you know, I know you like my movies, but you know,
I'm a stick bug. So there's no more like, all right. Thanks. Mr. Scorsese. That sounds like,
like a Rick and Morty routine. Yes. Yeah. That's like a Rick and Morty like episode.
Oh, thank you. Scorsese stick bug for the advice. Right. Like that's,
that's a Rick and Morty routine. Yeah. Uh, thanks. Thanks. Mr. Scorsese stick bug.
That was really cool. Yeah. Mr. Scorsese stick bug. You're the man. Whoa. Scorsese. I love your
movies. Love your movies. Yeah. I think I just went, I had a lot of, a lot of good ones.
Have you watched the new Rick and Morty season? Yeah. I had, how'd you feel about it?
It's all right. I, it's all right. Very incest-y. Yeah. A lot of that. A lot of that.
My chat's like, what? I mean, just watch it. There's like two episodes with that topic.
I mean, it's pretty good. It's not like season two good, but it's, it's okay. Some of it was good.
I think honestly, the first couple of seasons of Rick and Morty I thought were actually very good.
Yeah. I agree. Memes aside, I made myself look like such a tool because I was so into it.
But yeah, but like people, okay. Like Family Guy, right? Like Family Guy was just like funny for
the first like four or five seasons, right? Six seasons. Yeah. Got into it. I mean, I didn't get
into it. I just, you know, watched it. It was a thing that was, well, you have to remember too,
this is something really important that I think a lot of people don't really understand about
like Rick and Morty, right? Adult, it's not, it's adult swim. Adult swim for a very, very long time
was like, just didn't have that new thing that they didn't have very many shows.
There was no shows that were coming out from adult swim that were like big hits, big deals.
No. Yeah. That was the first one in a long fucking time. Yeah. They were doing a lot of reruns.
Like there was like, yeah, Family Guy, a lot of Aqua Teen, stuff like that. Yeah. Well, I also,
that, you know, I, I will stand, well, I didn't really talk about it, but have you seen Smiling
Friends? Yeah. Love Smiling Friends. That's fucking phenomenal, right? Yeah. Awesome. And like the
anti Rick and Morty in a way too, cause it's so simple and it's so like gag based, but weirdly
smart. Yeah. I think it's great. I love that show. Every single episode of that show has been like,
wow, this is just clever and funny. Yeah. I I've I'm dying to voice a slug that gets stepped on
like as a site gag. Or I'm just like, oh, and then I get stepped on and that's, that's the gag.
I'll be really happy with that. You need to be a stink bug, Bill. That's fine. Oh,
this is one of those long levels. That's all good. The, uh, the turrets make this one good.
I'm just going to start tossing them. All right. Oh, with this water here, I've been bad at these.
Jermbo, I have one more question for you, actually. I have a meaning to ask you. Ask away.
Ask away. All right. Um, how are you? Did you finish breath of the wild or did you?
No, I am still going. Did you enjoy your play time so far? It's phenomenal. It's phenomenal.
It's phenomenal. Uh, no, yeah, it's great. Cool. Yeah. I'm happy to hear that. I'm glad you like it.
Uh, I honestly, it's just, um, all the traveling I've been doing and then getting sick is just
kind of, I really wanted to get back and just start screaming again. Yeah. Yeah. It sounds like
you've had a busy couple, a couple, uh, months. It's been, it's been busy. Yeah. We've got a bunch
of projects coming to working on trying to stay busy. I, I need to throw a grenade at that guy.
I think we might be in trouble here. Um, yeah. Use your ultimate. I think you got it.
Did it work? I don't know. Just get them in, get them in there.
Mary, get them in. You got it. You got it. I should have been focused more on the game.
That's my fault. Ask him about the Battleaxe dodging stream. Please swim. I guess I haven't
played this game in like six months. Uh, oh, the Battleaxe. Yeah. Um, I mean, people are talking
shit about how we're not very good at this game, but it doesn't really matter because, um, I can
dodge a Battleaxe in real life and I'm going to. I don't understand this. What's happening?
That's exactly the response I'm looking for. Let's leave it at that. Uh, you, you don't,
do me a favor. Don't die. We like having you around and, uh, yeah, just have fun.
It's actually really funny. The, whenever I tell somebody about this, it's like a person,
like a personal friend or a streamer or something. I get that same response of like,
everything good? Like this is good, right? Like it's not, you know, you doing this for real?
I'm like, no, it's going to be fun. Just like if I'm here, if you need me though,
everyone's like, dude, you're not going to like really dodge a Dax, man. Like,
right. This is like a funny joke. I'm just like, why don't you fucking tune in? I mean,
I'm going to tune in now that you've said it, but I'm, I'm worried. Like I'm, I'm,
you know, I'm worried now. I'm going to be fine. Don't worry. I'm going to be fine. Also, uh,
Jerma, you have to join the new lobby. Oh shit. All good. We, we're very close to fighting Chorizo.
I think we are, right? Yeah. We're not too far off. Uh, Newt, can you also, uh, fuck off?
Are we great? That was so mean. No, no, they're, they're my friend. Newt is great. Newt's a good
friend. No, it's going to be, it's going to be like, you know, it's going to be a fun event
stream. It's going to be fun. It's not going to be, there's going to be fun activities and
don't worry, it's going to be fun. Okay. If I have to do a eulogy for you at any point on my stream,
I'm just going to be upset. So be like, you know what? I met him at PAX one year.
We, we, it was cold. We walked around. It was cold. It was very cold. He was a nice lad and
that was a good time. We liked, we liked to bust ghosts and that'll be like, I'll be like,
we'll miss him. But he just, he had the desire to get chopped in half by a battle axe.
No, I just got to prove to everybody that like I've got the physical capabilities that people
just don't understand. I mean, I'll do like, I'll do like a jump, I'll do like a jump or like a,
like a cartwheel or something on camera. Uh, and like I jumped up on, uh, on a chair on name,
your price. And everyone was like, Holy shit. And I'm just like, okay. Yeah. So do I have to,
how many more of these do I have to do? I mean, some people just post videos of them like doing
athleticism, you know, like, like on a couch or something, like, you know, like not actually
dodging a battle axe. You know, what's funny that you mentioned this right now, there are tons of
people who are incredibly athletic, putting up like parkour videos of like an amazing athleticism.
Uh huh. I jumped up on a chair on, on a show and I'm like, I can dodge an axe.
What? That, that's like my barometer here. That's good. That's a nice, that's a nice logic. Um,
just, yeah, I'll tune in for that. I don't have a hard date for it yet. Still trying to plan a
few things around it as well as maybe another show too. So sure. Yeah. I can imagine planning
a few things around it. The will, you know, the suit. The suit. Yeah. What's this thing?
You want it like, you know, you want it to be buried in a double breasted suit. Like that's
important if you're chopped up. Whoa. Yeah. I think I got, I think we just got killed by the
same thing. No, no, no. We're not dead yet. We're not dead yet. Oh, who's still alive? Is it you?
I'm alive. Oh yeah. Yeah. I'm going to get you guys back. We should be like together, right?
Here. I'm going to, I'm going to get you guys back. Nice. Oh my God. What an absolute save that was.
All right. Now we just got to get a couple more. Oh my God. Just need a couple more.
All right. I'm down. We. Oh, all right. It was a good, it was a good try. All right. So this next
one here. So here's what we're going to do for this next one. You and I concentrate are only allowed
to talk about the video game and we have to call out video game information. Cool. Okay. Yeah. We
died on wave one. People are laughing at us. Yeah. Yeah. Oh boy. I lost rank from that one. My, um,
my friends are, I'm sorry, hacker. You lost rank. I'm so sorry. Oh wait, that's bad. That's actually
not good for your friend. I think hacker left. Oh no. Friendship only goes so far when de-ranking.
Oh no, she's back. All right. All right. All right. Okay. I was actually like hilarious. I
felt really bad about that. Yeah, me too. Let me make sure this is nice and pushed in.
Okay. Here we go. All right. Okay. We're now landing on the battlefield. All right.
I have entered my squid form. Yep. Just trying to get a paint everywhere so we can
clear on the side. Yep. I am attacking a thing with a metal umbrella and depositing eggs.
UFO by me. UFO down. Good. Snake over there. Snake dead. Throwing eggs. Tower. Grenade out.
Chet, this is not an E3 commentary track. Sorry. Retrieving egg. Throwing egg. This is not an E3
commentary track. E3 commentary track, we would add like way more words here. And then call each
other broski. Yeah. Like you're, yeah, you're forgetting to add like the extra like three or
four words per sentence. Right. So if you, if you were wanting to say, uh, like, uh, eggs here,
instead of being like, Hey, eggs by me, you'd say, Hey, eggs over here. Seven o'clock,
seven o'clock eggs, retrieving eggs, throwing them. All right. That's frosty. Oh yeah. Be like
eggs over here. Gnarly bro. You forget to add like the last like couple of words. I'll try to
remember. I mean, I would, I would call that unbelievable. That's a 100% higher than what
we needed. You know what? If we just act like E3 people, definitely real people. And we call
out gameplay. We double what we need. That's how good we are. I know everyone makes that joke,
right? About like the E3. But why wouldn't they just record people just playing the game? Like
just why don't just record like some of the devs just like playing it and like having fun.
Yeah. I mean, the devs definitely not like random people, but yeah,
yeah. Like get the devs who are best at speaking like the top four. Anyway, we're sorry. Throwing
egg. They really don't even need to be like, just, just hang out and just play it right. Like,
I don't think people really need to hear like, oh man, that's what me and my squad's going to
sound like. Just play the game. You know what I mean? And this is what happens when I fucking talk.
Yep. All right. I'll be retrieving you momentarily. Thank you, hacker. I appreciate that.
We're going to get you back up. All right. Big lad this way. We're going to take them down.
Tango's down. Snake about to be down. Snake down. Oh, thank you. You saved me. Thank you.
Watch out. Big UFO. I honestly don't even know what this does. What is fucking happening? Unleash?
Did I do it? Any more eggs? There's a couple, but I think, yeah, we're good. We almost doubled again.
That's pretty good. Someone said never played Splatoon. What is happening? We are eliminating
tangos and retrieving eggs and putting them into receptacles. So what this, uh, the splat umbrella
is that does the umbrella do damage or is just a shield when it launches out? Um, it does damage.
You should use it like a shotgun, but if you need a shield, you can hold it. Oh my God. Shit. But I
had it. Snake to our right. Oh boy. What? Splatted by big shot. All right. We're okay. Yep. It's the
dolphin thing. Okay. Damn. That took a while. Power over here by me. Okay. We're almost at
quota. Yeah, we got this one guy with a laser beam. Get out of here. Yeah. I hate those things.
Come on. Come on. Here we go. All right. All right. It's chorizo timing. So what's the
strategy here? The trick here is usually you want to kill bosses as fast as possible and then throw
the eggs at him. But it also helps to have someone shoot him a little bit or like, so
you want to kind of, I think the best strategy is to divide between bosses and eggs and actually
shooting. Okay. Uh, chorizo himself, but it doesn't, it's not overly effective.
So we should just ignore him and just kill bosses and shit. That's the big strategy. Yeah. That's
the main one. I think I have no audio. Wait, can you hear me? I can hear you with nothing else.
Okay. Cool. I still can't hear anything. Why halfway halfway. There's some eggs down here too.
Okay. We got those eggs. Oh God. Oh God. That's getting crazy. Um, be sure to use your special.
If you have one term, the wrong. All right. Unleash the water. Nari, help me. Okay.
Damn. I don't know what that special does. So you charge up booyahs and then you bomb.
That's it's just a nuke basically. Yeah. I was just like tap, tap, tap, tap, tap, tap, tap, tap, tap,
tap, there you. Hit R right? Um, yeah, pretty much. I beat him once, frankly, like one time. Um,
how are you feeling by the way? I feel good. I'm fine. Do you want to play a little more
or I don't know if I'll have time to go for another chorizo. I want to make dinner
because I, all this chorizo talk is making me hungry. Oh I thought you, for a second.
I thought you said you were making chorizo. So you like. I don't want it now, but.
Well, I can take I can go on my own, too
Okay, so how about this?
We'll do we'll do a couple more and then when I feel my stomach starts it, you know eat at my stomach lining
I'll let you know. Yeah
Hey look this this the whole point of me being on screen today is to see if I can make sure I can be the sus guy
Tomorrow, that's a lot to live up to man. I know
Like joking aside though, how does it feel that that sus guy thing has like spread far beyond
Like you as a human
Well, let's see how much money I make tomorrow. I hate my laugh. That's cool, man
That's great. That's great. All right. Okay. Hey, you know DMV in like a few days and we'll talk we'll talk
If you Nari, I guess do one more with us and then we'll get Sin City in here just to rotate out
Thanks, Nari
Appreciate it. Yeah, the the one thing I have that has kind of I mean a couple things
Have had a little weird reach but the main one is me saying the word spin in a funny voice
That one was weird places that it just like like if there's a tick-tock of something spinning. They usually overdub my
my voice
Really? I feel like yeah, I probably heard it. It's just I'm sorry to do this everybody, but especially Jerma's audience
I apologize, but spin that I think I've actually heard that before
Yeah, it's stupid
Whole day. Sure. I'm so sorry. I've had like a bunch of cold medicine today. I'm sorry. Okay
Someone just said you're that guy. I don't I don't know. Am I who am I really? I don't even know
You actually know what I could do after this. I could probably just go right to breath of the wild play for a little bit
Whenever you're uh, I think you've had enough of this platoon
That's cool. How long do you usually stream for anyway? Um
Typically
somewhere around
Five to seven hours depending like four and a half to seven
Okay. Yeah, you got me. I do four
Yeah, I mean it was like sweet spot. I think I used to do like four
But I started streaming a lot less
So you know, yeah, how did I even die? I don't know what happened
Gotcha. Thank you. I think for me like a sweet spot at this point is like six hours and that's like what twice a week
Once a week, I mean it like two or three
Two or three. Yeah
Sometimes more sometimes less
I'm doing three a week for like four hours each time usually but I also do on my
One like in the mornings when I wake up
I usually do like I record like an hour or two of a game. I just I'm interested in and
That oh god and that's uploaded like pre-recorded on my youtube channel. So it's not live, but I basically do the same shit
I'm doing now. Yeah, and it's it's been really good for me because I get I
Feel like I feel better as a person when I upload something every day
It's bizarre. I don't know why I feel that way, but it's nice to have like a new upload every day
I you know YouTube is one of those things that I probably gonna start to get a little more involved in as
Time goes on here
But you started on YouTube no
Yeah, but I mean but as of like the last few years
I've been pretty much only twitch with like the second channel having highlights and stuff, right?
But I don't know. I have no idea
Dude, you wanna know what I was so pissed off about
What's that? So?
The the Xbox I play like I usually just kind of chill and play Xbox on the couch and I'm just kind of hanging out
They have like a record feature
Right. It's like oh you can record a clip
it's I'm really like funny shit has happened in a lot of these just random things that I'm doing just lying on a couch and
I didn't know this until pretty recently
But Xbox fucking auto deletes all the shit that you ever record unless you put it on to like a hard drive
I was like, excuse me
All my funny shit is gone
No, I didn't know that
Yeah, you have to like up so you were planning on taking all of it and uploading it like eventually
I was gonna do like a video. I was gonna make a video like on the shit that I was playing
Like what games are you playing on Xbox though? Um, so believe it or not. I was playing a lot of Shadow of War. Oh
Lord of the Rings middle earth. Yeah
Which that game is so fun. So funny. Yeah, I've never played it and I'm a huge fucking Lord of the Rings fail
God, I'm a big Lord of the Rings nerd. Really? You've never played shadow never played it. No
any
Yeah, I know what you're doing like tomorrow, right?
It's that game is 100% content
Okay
Like that game is just content. Okay, and it's just is it good for a Tolkien fan too, or is it like yo, yeah
It's I mean, we're not really
We got we got beat pretty bad. It's all right. We just like tang would chat
That's probably one of the funniest games ever
I don't want to spoil anything for you
But like the amount of wacky just absolutely wacky shit that could happen in those games is just is a record breaker
All right
Am I getting bad chested for saying content?
Hacker I'm so sorry that we are decreasing your rank
You don't have to continue playing with us hacker. Yeah, we don't have to win enough to drag you down
Like I'm gonna do maybe like two or three more, you know, cuz I'm enjoying
Hanging out with Jerma as well hang on to but I also do not want to ruin hackers rank because hackers like
Pro yeah, you can only hard carry so much, right?
Well, okay. I know I go content. I say that's not I what I mean by that is if you've ever thought of us
If you've ever thought about screaming that game or like making a video on that game. It's just it's it's so good
It's so fun. There's so many things to do. I
Felt that way about birth of the wild
Just because it's like just all these wacky physics situations that can you can get yourself into
But I know that like the nemesis system has the you know, that's where the fun is, right? Oh, yeah
Okay. Okay. This there is just something that hits so hard when you play that game and I
Don't want to say anything cuz like, you know quite it
Okay. Yeah, that's a good suggestion. I'll keep it in mind
But I'm just gonna mute and say it to my stream
Okay, but when you play that game and you just kind of
Walking around like looking for like the starter. Well, shirma is is muted or has muted me
He probably can still hear me in one of his three headphones, but I'm true. I could
so when you're just like walking around looking for the start of a mission and all of a sudden the game just takes control and
Pans over and zooms in on a guy that's just like a ranger
Oh, you thought you could kill me but I'm back and I'm ready to eat your blood or like it's it's so fucking funny and
Then like a caragor bites him and kills him in one hit. It's just like it's absolute fucking zany nonsense
I'm back. Okay, so I'll take your recommendation and when I have a little like time where I have like, you know
Some some gaps in my schedule. I'm gonna check out that game
Yeah, I don't know if it's completely
Canon Lord of the Rings. I mean the story is good enough. I think I
Don't think it's fully canon. But after rings of power, I'll probably be like this is amazing
Why did this get ran over? Oh, yeah, the glow flies. I this is the worst one
Hacker you left at the exact right moment. I know this is like the word guarantee. This is just a nightmare
Pause it pause it. What's the time? Did it work? I pressed it
You know, there's something about audio coming through one headphone like
I feel like I'm playing with like like my eyes closed. We did it kind of we just need to live now
Somebody stay alive
Wow, who did it? I don't know. I said well sin got us back up sin city. So thank you since it nice job
All right, Jeremiah, I have a chat member named colostomy bagel. Okay, I wanted you to know that
That's all oh
Here's another question. Do you like the Sims? Do you like city builders?
Um, I played
What the city's skylines, right? Yeah, that was fun, but I'm too stupid for it. I really can't do it. Okay
All right fair enough
Honestly, like I I want to play the sims 4 again on screen
That's another game that just has so much weird shit that happens all the time. I'll probably never have played a sims game
am I just like
like
me capping my my channel by not playing sims and like
I mean, but just out of mortar. Yeah, you could start in the very beginning
There's like a hundred years of video games that you could play just by playing the sims franchise in a row
You would love the sims too
It's not there like a thousand dollars worth of like DLC for the new one though
Yeah, and I I I could be wrong and this might be a completely wrong take
But when you look at that list of expansions to buy
Mm-hmm. I tell me if I'm wrong, but I could be wrong a chatter or you and everybody knows this
Like there's no just buy this all
There's no just like I want most of this there's no like bundles
You have to like you have to do it. You have to individually purchase every fucking expansion. Am I wrong?
There's like 30 different things and like I going to the checkout and like here's your credit card info
Buy this one thing or two things, right? You have to buy you to add each thing individually to your cart
On steam apparently, is it actually on steam you can do it. That's I don't know. That's what my chat saying
But then again chat has as we've mentioned before giving me bad advice
From time to time I wish they would do like a like a gold bundle like a platinum bundle or something
I mean why I there's like 50 expansions that have to add each one individually
That's a first-world problem. Oh
Boy, I have all this money burning a hole in my pocket
How do I buy more Sims content? I need adult babies expansion. Oh hell yeah adult diapers
How do I buy the nursing home expansion, please?
That is really such a good fucking non-concern it really is
I don't want to click a button individually and place it in what I want to buy all thousand dollars worth this right now
Wait, why can't I?
Do they do have some like weird stuff in that expansion list by the way
Is there clown stuff? I don't probably
All right, cuz I I kind of like clown stuff like that would be perfect
Yeah, I'm looking through it's just like oh like my first gerbil like what okay?
I'm we get
Come on one more, and then we live one more, and then we live we got this I
believe in us
Quota met now we live
Robin fucking bomb
Please we got this
Now picture this on higher difficulties
I feel like we're on the higher difficulty
We're not we just lost hacker. That's right. She's just that good
That's right. We did lose the best player
So getting we got double high tide okay? What's up, Joe?
I think somebody's asking if I'm gonna play Breath of Wild after this probably yeah
I'm as long as I still feel okay really I'll be all right
I'll do like
me see
How long we've been going for?
Yeah, it's not over in a half. It's all up to like one
Um I don't think we're gonna get chorizo for a while, so maybe I'll just do like one more. Yeah
Okay, I mean I did for those who that don't know I did just like
Send a message to Vinny being like hey. Do you want to stream today? Yeah?
I was like can you do it in an hour? Yeah, it was I listen man
I'm happy to do so we've been talking about doing this for a little while
So I'm happy we get the chance like collaborate, but I was actually recording a Star Fox mod
Like a Star Fox rom hack like I was about to hit record, and then you messaged me
And then I was like all right well that's gonna be put off till later
So no, it's all good. It's all good. I'm happy to do this. This is this is good
Yeah, and I'm sure we'll
See you again for the next couple of days whatever we do of the longest tomorrow or whatever we do more VR
That's gonna be coming also. It's gonna be fucked up. It's gonna be cool, but
Did you do among us VR in VR chat ever?
Yeah, I have never even opened the video game among us. I don't I don't even know what it is I
Swear to God I have no
That of all the things that you could have been known for outside of like a wider reach of the Internet
It's a game. You've never played. It's unbelievable no
And that's why it's tomorrow's one day only
Well, so here's the thing chat. There's a chance. I may do among us VR
I'm not sure because I have a studio day, and we're finishing up recording
Some stuff so I don't want to
Miss that and then there's other variables too like I you know if it's like a full server
I'm not gonna bully my way in you know what I mean, but at the same time
There's almost a 100% guarantee. I'm gonna do among us VR in the future if not tomorrow
Just to let my chat know because they've been asking for a while too. Oh fuck
Vinny you killed two of your teammates
What these hamburger fucking grill things pissing me off?
There's no pink. That's okay. We just gotta live now
fucking bad you know idea
Hey, Jeremiah. I don't want to like peek too far behind the curtain
But I want to ask you one very important question if you if you want to answer on stream or not that's fine
But is it difficult to hire clowns um actually kind of yeah
Okay
Although the thing is a lot of that you would hire to that's a clown a lot of times
They're they do a lot of other stuff
So some people have their side gig well. It's not it's just like a performance right performing. Yeah, and a lot of these
a lot of the more
They have like more than one thing so like oh, yeah, I need to there is a clown that I'm hiring a clown
You are a clown
No, you might be somebody that can be a clown, but you're also like a magician
You're also like a fucking like incredibly talented like contortionist and like dancer
Right, it's not just like oh you are something yeah, right
Yeah, I would imagine you'd need to if you're gonna be that kind of entertainer you have to diversify your portfolio
So you can get more work because I mean how often are people having clown baseball games, you know?
Not very often I would imagine
but yeah, it's
If you're looking for like a clown you should be looking for like almost like a performance group
Okay, for like a performer that is more hold on. I have to save somebody's life
Okay
Yeah, it's easier to find somebody that can do a clown if you need a clown rather than just searching for a
Young I need a just clown right like this is my life and identity is clown. Yeah
Okay
Also area to depends. I know there's a lot of cities that are a lot less in the performing arts
Yeah, so like Vegas is probably easier to get clown than New York City. Well, New York City's got like kind of everything
I feel like I feel like New York would be wouldn't be hard
Yeah, I
Mean we do have a store that specifically sells like clown outfits
So you do yeah, we do we do it's not it's like a costume shop
Oh, like it's just a massive costume shop and they have plenty of clown outfits
Because I had to me and my friend Mike
We were clowns for the back of one of our albums
We had to buy clown outfits like
six years ago
So yeah, there you can get them but I was invincible if I did that
Chat I'm not telling you why I may hire a clown
That's part of the fun. But you know, maybe one day it will come to fruition. Maybe it won't
Maybe I'm just clowning around. I feel like New York would be pretty easy
I mean you can hire like a lot of different types of entertainers
Yeah, New York's a big entertainment city. Yeah, we are. Yeah, we have everything
Holy what just happened? Who just Boo-Yah? Oh
It's getting tough. Where are you? I think
I'm here. So we may need to start
Yeah, I'll throw some ultimates
Damnit was busy boo-yahing. You got three. Oh my yes. There's plenty on the map. It's just impossible
To like get them over there right now. There's so many that are there we could still do it
We just need some depositors
Mary no, no, he was dead for a while. This is the worst platoon gameplay of all time
No, I played worse. Um, you need to kill the boss is closer to the basket. Yeah, that makes sense
Well, Jerma before I go out, I'll tell you one more little story
There's like a famous clown story I have about a stapler clown
Did you ever like see a performer who would have people staple money to their chests? No
You mean like I was at a bar
Yeah, like so I was at a bar one night and
Going back years ago and there was a clown who his whole act was, you know
They did sword swallowing and juggling and stuff and the cloud the usual clown stuff. It's kind of smelly
Like like he kind of stunk the place up. So he was like a smelly cloud
I don't know if that was part of the act but at one point
He said if anyone wants to I got a stapler here my lovely clown assistant will help you
I've got if you want
$10 you can staple it to my chest
You know for $50 you can staple it to my stomach for a hundred you can staple it to my
nether nether region what
Jerma I witnessed a clown's
You know
So wait, it's in so the so the idea here. The idea here is that yeah, it's like you that you're paying
That's like he keeps the money. That's like are you stapled to me? I keep it. Yes
Once it's stapled to him he has it and I don't think you'd want to touch it again after no
Just trying to get the service, you know what what he was doing the stick whatever it was, right? That's that's so
Somebody's he stapled it to his
Yeah, like his batwing he would batwing and he would let you staple it there, but it had to be like a hundred bucks
What is the batwing? Well, it's like kind of when like you stretch out
The skin and
It looks like a batwing like like Batman. So he would stretch it out for you
He would batwing it and then he would let you staple it
Like to that yeah
It's good living I guess so and somebody did this
Yeah, I watched it. It's real. I've seen it and Nari in fact in my chat
There's a video there are multiple videos of this clown or similar clowns that exists
I
Don't know why I'm telling you this German. I'm sorry, but I just thought like we're talking about clowns. Let me just yes
I felt like you needed to know because like so I'm trying to understand like the the how does this come up?
Like it was somebody did somebody like hire this person or was he just kind of like hey
You could staple shit to me for money
Yeah, so that's a weird thing because this bar I used to go to before it closed down
They just had like musicians usually just you know music but this night
I was there with friends and the clown was there and we were like what the fuck so
We see the act and he's like throwing the swords, and he's you know juggling
Okay, all right, and then about an hour later. He goes all right
now we're gonna close the doors and have some real fun and
then he
Like literally closed the doors and gave us his terms and conditions about like stapling money to him
What the fuck?
Yeah
I'll link you to a video. You know what don't watch it. I'll link you anyway. Don't watch this
That's okay
All right
well
Sorry
Anyway, hey, maybe maybe we'll see you tomorrow the next day or something from here
Like what like an actual VR clown?
Like for among us or for like anything
Okay, dude when I hook up VR, it's the only thing I do for like a week
Cuz I don't take it all down. I gotcha. I gotcha. All right, so yeah, man. Um, well, it was fun
Thank you for having me
Play some Splatoon with you. I really enjoyed this. No, it's fun. It's always fun to have you on like a friend sesh
Yeah, for sure. I'll see you soon, man. Yeah, thank you. Thanks for playing everyone. Say bye. Say bye to Vinny
Bye Jerma's chat. You guys are cool. Yeah. Bye. Bye Jerma