You know, it seemed like it was potentially a funny idea. I was gonna- I didn't want to delay
the stream though. Oh damn it. Don't freak- don't freak out. That's what they say, don't freak out.
I wonder if I can reach back here. I've been sitting here like this for at least 30 minutes.
I put- I put chicken grease in my hair! Wait a minute.
Nice swag, thanks. You look like a Space Channel 5. You can see every like,
inch of my face too. I don't like this. I hate this. Oh! Holy shit, people are so ugly with light,
aren't they? Holy shit, people are so ugly. Look at- all right. Oh, Jeremy, you look real handsome
today. You sure about that? People are ugly with light on them. So I- I think we just have to stream.
Wait, what do these buttons do? What does this button do? Like a depiction of an angel in the
Bible or something. It's like I just be like, like, yes my son. Like, yes. Are you okay? I'm
all right. I gotta shave though. You can see how weird I look. All right, let's go ahead and uh...
Whoa! Holy, are you kidding me? Oh no, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. See? I'm not ugly!
I can't even use this now. You want to see me fucked up? Watch this, ready?
Everyone looks like that, okay? Anyways, wait, I need to keep this on. No, I don't. Turn it off.
I got it off. The chicken grease worked. Hey, I'll be live in two seconds. It's dual personality.
Oh shit, that's probably loud. Sorry. All right. Hey, stream's starting.
Where's Shito? I don't- what? No, there's no Shito today. Shito needs batteries to turn his brain
back on and I don't have the batteries that are required. You took Shito off the shelf?
No, I didn't. What are you talking about? He's right there. He's sleeping. He's sleeping. See?
I can hear it. Can you hear it? Hey, oh, okay. Geez, I'm sorry. No, no, no, no, no. I haven't
turned him on in like two years. Yeah, I know. Well, you can go back to sleep for a little while.
All right, all right, set it on. Set it on. Stop, stop. All right, I get it. I get it.
I'll- okay, yeah, okay, okay, okay, okay. So, shh. Okay, back to sleep. Uh, he said he's very
grateful that everyone thought he was cool and that people were happy that he was going to make
a return. He was mad that I kept him asleep for two years. I did say that- I said I was going like a
long weekend trip two and a half years ago and I was like, oh, we'll just shut you off for a
little while. And it's been two years. I will get you new batteries, Shito. Bumber for a little
longer. Hey, we're starting the stream soon. Just a minute. Did you smoke crack? What? I don't smoke
crack. I don't smoke crack. I don't smoke crack. I don't smoke a crack. I don't smoke crack.
He's role playing and he's 36. Who cares? Does that- why? Does that even matter?
I can't role play at 36? Okay, well then every actor has to retire when they turn 30. How does
that sound? Today, we're gonna- I know I lied. I'm sorry. It will never be an actor. There would
never be like a- like an old man in any movie or TV show you ever watch ever again. It'll be people
that are like 30 and like 40 in makeup. Okay, so we're gonna play Internet Cafe Simulator 2 today.
I know I lied. I said we're gonna play Everhood. I'm really sorry, but I kind of- ow. I- listen,
I kind of had a headache and Everhood is a game I don't think you want to play with a headache,
but I've seen some of this game. It looks like it could be interesting. It seems kind of up my alley.
I was like, I want to try it. It's a simulator game. Fart Simu- I know.
I don't- why would I need to explain it to you? This game is not a game you want to play with
a headache either. Why? Yeah, I'm having a good time. I'm just hanging out. Hopefully,
you're doing okay too. Pretty cool. This is a simulator game. I beat this in the entire time.
I was just wishing I could see you play it. I'm excited. Oh, that's good. You lost 4,000 people.
No, I did not. I have my analytics open. I can see my analytics. All right, so let's get started.
Let me just stir my coffee not into the microphone. How do you feel about being
called an e-clown? I- we made that term up here. That's not- somebody didn't make that term up
and then call me that. Like, that's like a- like, only a few communities even use that term.
So, who cares? All right. Uh, hold on. Let me get this going here.
I don't even have my dashboard open. What an idiot. Play the game? It's the intro.
I just- just give me a second. Oh, there we go. There we go. Okay. Uh, is the camera still on?
No. No cam. Off. Is it gonna be a ring light neck stream? Uh, no, I'm not gonna- I'm not
gonna torture myself like that. There was also a heated debate in the chat room earlier about
hamburger helper and I- I- I feel like I need to- we have to talk about it. I got a lot of shit
because- all right, let me ask a really quick question. Do you guys know, in the chat,
ones in the chat, do you know what hamburger helper is? Because apparently it was fucking crazy
that I- I've been saying- was saying these words. I was like, yeah, a hamburger helper. You get the
cheeseburger mac and what you do is you do this, you do this. Everyone's like, what are you talking
about? What- what is hamburger helper? What- what help what? It's good, yeah. And I was talking
about a little recipe that I had. If you don't know what hamburger- this is what it looks like.
It doesn't look like that. Uh, it doesn't look like that. It looks like this. Um, so that's
hamburger helper. People would like show us the box. That's- there's the box. I can't even like
not laugh at that. What was that? It was- I don't know. It was like an image on my desktop. It comes
with real cheese. Okay, this is what hamburger- listen. Hamburger helper is a boxed macaroni
product. You take a pound of ground beef and you mix it in with this whole box and it turns into
this macaroni dish, right? It looks like this. This one here. Uh, this is a good one. Yeah,
this one. It looks like that. It tastes- it's- I mean, okay, the entire time you're making
hamburger helper, you're grossed out. It's disgusting looking. It feels gross. It's like
you hate it and like you don't even like looking at it. But when you take a bite, it's hard not
to eat the whole box. Um, at least, you know, between a few people. So what I said- well,
what should I put- let me name this. Um, oh, right. EXP and espresso. It's the name of the
cafe. What are you talking about? That's hamburger helper. Is it actually a stolen name? No, it's not.
From where? It looks worse though. No, but okay. So you take the hamburger helper, you eat it,
maybe you put a little bit of onion in it, maybe you put some, you know, parsley, whatever the
hell you want, some of the bullshit to make it taste a little better, be a little nicer, whatever.
But my case that I was making to pretty stream chat was what I do, because you ha- you don't
just make like half a box of hamburger helper, right? You don't just make one like, oh, I'm
going to make like a third of a box of hamburger helper. It doesn't work that way. So you make a
shitload of it and then you store it. And what I said is after you take it out, after you store it,
you put it between two pieces of bread or two pieces of toasted bread or bun and you eat it
like a sandwich. You heat it up, you heat the hamburger helper up in the microwave for like
20 seconds or something. And then you put it between bread and you eat it. And then you put
some ketchup on the side and you dip it in the ketchup. I- okay. Even my mods are like,
you're fucked up. But that's eating the leftovers though. Okay, you can adapt to the game in a
shorter time. Okay, don't worry, they're not boring and long. Yeah, WC, yeah, tab, skills, skills.
Okay, I have a punch. That sensitivity is going to go way down. Uh, even more than that. Yeah,
you dip it in ketchup. That's better. But it makes the, honestly, it makes the leftovers more
interesting. No joke, that sounds really good because it is. I have a punch. Oh, I tried to get
my girlfriend to take a bite and she did not want to. In fact, I got a really, really bad look.
I don't- it's just leftovers. How do I press- call the elevator, okay. Just be- I have weird- I have
a weird palate sometimes. It's a current- yes, it's a current girlfriend. It's a current girlfriend.
I alluded- all right. I alluded to this on Christmas Eve and I think it's time to talk about
it. I have a girlfriend. I've had a girlfriend since early last year. I've been pretty private
about it for a magnitude of reasons. But ladies and gentlemen, I'm about to announce, she's in
the chat right now. Where can we meet her? She's here now. And the reason why we kept it private
is because we wanted to- we wanted to find a good place to do this because I didn't want to kind of
just throw her into this whole thing and have it be like, oh hey, come on, everybody, you all know
who this is? She's a community member and she's been a community member for a while. This is not
a joke. It's Halulu. She's in chat right now. It's not you, it's her. It's not- it's not community Jake.
Does she know? What? She does. And ever since Christmas Eve, I've- I know people like, what are
you- what are you talking about? What does that mean? How do I get out of the fucking elevator?
Do you guys kiss? Of course we do. But I will say this, all through 2020 and into 2021, right,
I think I've been dropping some hints to you guys about how much better my personal life was getting.
You've probably seen a few different times where I've been like, hey, it's, you know, somewhere like
at some point last year where I was like, hey, my personal life is going really well. I'm really
happy right now. She had a lot to do with that. So, um, we were trying to find the right way to,
like, introduce her. She's fucking amazing. So, taking Andy, that's it. All right, I gotta get
out of my fucking apartment. How do I leave? Okay, here we go. Is this an elaborate bit? It is not
an elaborate bit. But how do I go up the elevator? What- what do I do? Two? One? What? Where am I? I
thought I was- I'm already on the third floor? I thought I wasn't like- oh, okay. Let's go.
But all through 2021, I kept my private life pretty private. I was only streaming, like,
once a week. My health was in the fucking shitter. You all know that. Squid game? All right,
go to the- go to your internet cafe. Press M. BTC Miner? Okay, that's my home. This is my cafe.
I'm ready to fucking rock and roll. All right, can I- I can punch people. I know that for a fact.
Wait, this is the sus guy. Don't tell her that. She already knows that. But you'll probably be
seeing a lot more of her in the future because obviously I wanted to wait until we were both
comfortable kind of talking about it. So, there you go. There's your- there's your girlfriend
announcement. What the fuck are you doing? All right, so where's- where's my cafe up here?
Does anybody care that I just did that? All right, should I hide? That was rude. All right,
grab the mop and clean your cafe. This cleaning this game. So yeah, you know, I'm gonna fucking
love it. Any plans for her to feature on the stream? Um, if she wants to- and that's another
thing too. I didn't want to like- the reason to keep a relationship private is because obviously
you guys know- and I'm- this is real talk here. This is really just me being real. I live a pretty
private life. Besides, like, the public, you know, streams and stuff. So, I like to separate that
kind of stuff. But if she ever wanted to do something like that, I'm sure that we could-
it would be fun, yeah. He's an enigma. Not- I'm really not, though. Like, that's the thing. I'm
really not- I'm really not that complicated. I'm pretty simple. We know. All right, so it's clean.
Very cool. We call her the sus lady. I- I don't- I- well, I mean, she's here right now. You
literally- you can ask her. She's in the chat. I don't think she wants to be called the sus lady,
though. The electricity's off. All right, let's turn on the electricity. How do I use the computer?
There's space to start the computer. No electricity. Oh. How do I turn the electricity on?
Oh, shit. All right. I computer case monitor and keyboard mouse on the Xamibzor. Why did you
announce your girlfriend while playing Fart Simulator? What? I- I don't know. We're talking
about a hamburger helper, and, like, I- she was literally in this house. We were eating it,
and I was- I figured it was a good point. I have a good place to do it. You're feeding her hamburger
helper. I'm not feeding- look, she can eat whatever she wants. We eat together. We eat
whatever we want. Nobody has to eat hamburger helper sandwiches dipped in ketchup. I just had
to validate the fact that it was- this is a real thing I was doing. Okay, buy compute from Xamibzor.
War cry? Crack? No, there's- do I have money? All right, Xamibzor. Where's my money? I got
two thousand bucks. All right, all right, all right. Computer cases. Buy a computer case. What-
do I care which one it is? Old computer case. Add to basket. Is it there?
Uh, computer case, monitor, and keyboard. Keyboard and a mouse. This thing looks like a cell phone
from, like, 1992. 1991. All right, now what? All right. Why am I, like, in 800 by 600 resolution?
This is about the same dev that made Streamer Life Simulator. I have no idea, actually. That's a good
question. All right, so get up. Does she know about Otto? She loves Otto. Okay, so- this is a
guy I punched in the face. Why is he just sitting here? All right, that was kind of scary. What
happened? What is going on? Why is this- why is this guy walking over here with an exclamation
point? Why are there so many just animals? Press E to talk to the beggar. I know everything that
happens in this city, man. You're the owner of that new internet cafe. They smashed the man who
worked at the cafe before you, man. If he got on- if he got on well with me, this wouldn't have
happened to him. If you want to build BTC mining rig in this city, you have to pay me license
first. I want to just run an internet cafe, man. Is she taller than you? Oh, okay. No. All right,
old computer ca- where do I have to put this? This guy just keeps looking at me. I don't- I don't-
this is freaking me out. Oh, shit. Wait, wait, wait, wait. Okay, I get it. I get it. No, I get it. I
understand. I want to put it, like, here. I don't- this is- this is it? This is a tiny room. This is
a bathroom. Where's the- where's the- what happened to the stuff? Oh, it was, like, blending into the
ground. All right, keyboard. And then I assume that I have to put the- what about a monitor?
Oh, shit, I need a- I don't have a monitor. All right, I gotta get a monitor. Did you guys come up
with Grotto Beast together? Yes, we did. We were actually sitting just outside with a hammer,
breaking geodes, and we thought this was, like, a really cool idea. And you've- you've seen a lot of
her stuff. Okay, you remember the sunflowers? I've been, like, dropping hints about this for,
like, at least the last six fucking months. Do you remember when I zoomed in on the sunflowers
and there was a little picture of Otto? She drew that. She also took all those sunflower pictures.
Everybody was saying, and I remember, they were like, wow, these photos look really,
really awesome. It's almost- did he hire a professional photographer? No, it was just my
girlfriend. But no, she's awesome. I couldn't be happier. We were just trying to find, like,
an opportunity to kind of talk about it and not be, like, private about it anymore. But I just did
that for me, right, and for her. Being private about this stuff was important because you never
know, right? Like, I never wanted to make somebody, like, content, right? That was a lot- a huge part
of it until we were comfortable. And if she's comfortable, if she wants to be on streams or
something, then yeah, sure. Fuck yeah. Hey, that's the reason why you didn't hear about this
months and months and months ago. Could I be your son? No, I don't- nah. She's not real.
All right, let's go. No more hamburger helper talk. We're out- we don't have to talk about it
anymore. We're over that. It's delicious. It's actually a good way to eat the leftovers.
Trust me, I'm a professional clown. That's a- that's a lie. I don't want to get in trouble
for saying that. I made that up. I've never been formally trained as a clown. All right, what-
maybe a good monitor? Should I get a good one? How about this one? This one's 350. All right,
where's the- where's the basket? Is that too expensive? Should I not buy this? Maybe I
shouldn't buy it. Get a CRT. Just get the shit out of me. You just saw, like, the mouse tremble.
Should be dual camel prime. Okay, this is so many anim- why are there so many animals in the game?
All right, it's an LCD. So how do I, like, start the business? All right, get the computer ready.
Place the products and get the computer ready. Place the products. Is this it? Computers. Setup
is not complete. How do I set it up? It's- oh, we need a chair? We're not a cop? Chair. I have to
use this, like, outdoor plastic chair? Like that. All right, open the cafe. You can do it from the
main PC. Oh, hell yeah. All right, let's go. Cafe closed. Cafe opened. Wait for the first customer
to arrive, okay? This guy's been standing here the entire time. I need a chair? I got a chair right
there. When's your Vtuber debut? I don't know, man. You should punch that person. I'm not punching
anybody. Do I have to do anything else or just people- oh, all right. Customer sent you a request
to turn on the computer. Turn it on. On your computer. I was like, wow, it wouldn't even request
to turn it on. Oh, request. Please unlock, okay? You completed the tutorial. Now you can freely
play the game if you want. You can take some quests by walking around the city. The game is
saved when you sleep, okay? What, he's just playing? What the fuck? Oh. Four dollars and five cents.
Why did you only use the computer for 10 minutes? You could have gone to the fucking library.
Why did you do that? Oh, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right. What do you want?
Please unlock for two hours. Sure. This is my cafe. If only there was a game that could be played.
The cafes that open around here are like shit. Wait, that's why he left? Because they don't have
a game? You can't watch porn? Why are you watching porn? You can't watch that. I thought this was a-
oh, no, it's not a gaming cafe. Why are you watching porn? Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out.
You can't watch porn here. Leave. Thank you. 23 dollars? Holy shit. It's still- I don't- I'm
not watching this. I'm not watching- someone's gonna come and think I'm watching this. How do I turn
this off? I'm not watching this. I'm- this is not on my stream and I'm not streaming. I'm not playing
this. Someone's gonna think it's me doing this. How do I turn the computer off? I didn't want to
comment badly, but what garbage? Yeah, don't watch porn in my cafe. How do I turn that- how do I get
that off? How do I- okay, thank god somebody cut the electricity. Fuck! What? Why is it permanently
there? The computer was turned off. How do I get that off? All right, I need to do a quest. It's
got screen burning. All right, maybe I should do- should I do a quest? What is that here? The screen-
all right, it's- it can't be there anymore, right? It can't be. Okay, good. It's like rebooting. It's
all fucked up. God damn it. Will somebody please come in here and get that off the fucking computer
before I get, like, banned? Please? Why is nobody coming to my- I almost said restroom.
Somebody come in and use my computer! How do I get- I think that's why- I think I broke the game.
Mop the computer? This doesn't- this is how a caveman would handle this. I don't know what to do. Oh,
hi sir, how are you? Come on into the internet cafe. Um, I- this is not my computer.
Please, uh, go ahead and do whatever you- oh, yep, let me just go ahead and turn that on for you.
Let me just go ahead and turn that on. Ow! What is going on? Why is it making so much noise?
He's just sitting there staring at that right now. Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Go back. Thank you. Yes, you're welcome. All right, please do whatever you- but what are you doing?
What's wrong? Two dollars. What'd you say? What'd you say? There's only a game- all right,
I need a game. I gotta get- I get a game system or something? I gotta get a game. Computer cases,
air conditioning, arcade consoles. Yeah, well, I don't have that much money. Uh, PlayStation 1.
PlayStation 1. I need a TV for it, right? Yeah, I need a good gamer chair. This one here. And then
a- this one. No, one of these. What's wrong? Okay, uh, I need a monitor. Wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait. What's going on? Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop. What's happening? Oh, go ahead,
go for it. All right, let me open up my- where's my cart? I need a monitor. Keyboards, monitors,
there we go. Uh, and all- CRT gets PlayStation 1. All right, bye. All right, new stuff coming in.
People are talking. I'm the porn place now. Who watches porn like this?
Nobody watches porn leaning back like that in the chair. I don't know. Yes, thank you for coming.
They do pay a lot of money, though. All right, what we got? Chair. Okay, console. Spray that guy
with the fire extinguisher. I'm not spraying anybody with fire extinguisher. Oh, I need a table.
Shit. Don't touch this. I probably should get more than one controller, right? My frames are
dropping? They shouldn't be. Frames, frames. What do you mean? My frames are all right. What are you
on about? It's fine now. I got a 3090. Should I turn the graphics down? Maybe it's just too much.
Oh, well, I think I'm playing on- yeah, I don't think this game is designed to be played on
Ultra. Probably better. Oh, what's up? Oh, right. If you'd like to use the computer, let me know.
Let me accept this request, and then I'm gonna get a- I gotta get a table. 30 minutes, go ahead.
I didn't know what to say. All right, leave. I want- you gonna pay? Customer runs away without
paying. You don't really seem to be running. How do I- what do I do? Give me that money back.
Um, I didn't- just pay me the money! How do I get the money back? All right, I'll just-
why are we fighting out here? Oh god, I'm getting my ass kicked. Watch out, watch out, watch out,
watch out, watch out. Can I use this? Oh, shit. Did I get it? Two bucks. All right, somebody help
her up. Somebody help her. All that for two dollars. It's not worth fighting over. That was
not worth a fight. It really wasn't. I was gonna die. I need a table. Why does the computer keep
turning off? Yeah, it's not nice. There are zero games you can play. Lul. So I'm gonna walk out
without paying. All right, table. Desks. Does that count? This is- you can get VR too? Holy shit,
I'm invested. Basic console table. Yeah, I'm- I'm running out of money. Oh, shit, I'm actually
running out of money. Whoever just comes in here- the people that watch porn literally pay the most,
so I don't even care anymore. Where's my mop? You gotta buy the PC games on- oh, okay. There you go.
Clean this up. Don't mind me. Don't mind me! Just cleaning up the place, that's all.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. That's not what- that's not
what I was doing. I know it looked really, really weird right there. I'm not- okay. Yes, I'm gonna-
I'll take that loss, I will. That's my own fault. Oh, finally. Oh, yep, yep, yep, hold on.
Thank you. 63 bucks. Whoa! What happened? What? Why did the computer explode? What happened?
Did the- was it- wait, did that guy overload the computer with porn viruses? It was a bomb. Oh my
god. Okay, that- that was fucking crazy. Uh, all right. Um, what do I do? Um, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait. Is it all broken? Does it still work? Oh, it still works. All right. What? No,
one of the guy paid me 60 bucks. He fucking blew up the computer. I like that narrative better.
That's funnier to me than the guy came in and blew it up. All right, uh, let's put this over here.
Maybe like in the side edge over here. Right here. There. Uh, this is so cramped.
Squid game. Yeah, I- why can I put this here? Is that not- I can't- I need a TV? How is this
not a TV? All right, well dual monitor setup over here. Imagine doing a dual monitor with a CRT.
I can't do that. All right, now I need to get a- how do- can I sell that thing? People actually do
that. Do they really? All right, I need to get an actual TV. TV. Okay, dude, that's- these are so
expensive. These are the only TVs I can buy. Um, I'll just wait till I have money. 30 minutes,
unlock. Get some damn game- oh shit, that's right. Okay, how do I do those? What do I get those from?
Dude, get a TV. All right, how do I- where do I go? Buy some games. Bill Root Slots, skin case,
apps, Steam. A platform where you can buy the best quality games. All right, download. A virus scanner.
I definitely want one of those. I only have 230 bucks. Is it robbery? Wait, what? What? What? What?
What? Why can't I hurt this guy? Did I get my money back? Try- wait, he tried to pay and I ignored
him? No, what? That didn't happen, right? Shit. All right, I got Steam- I got Steam installed.
No, no, not happening. Not happening. That guy didn't pay. That guy definitely didn't pay. Did you
pay? Why does it say he didn't pay? You didn't turn his PC on. What? He didn't do anything? Why
was he here for so long? That's horse shit. Don't run in here. All right. Okay, unlock. Steam should
be on there now, right? Okay, apps. Steam. That's- okay, that's installed now. Steam. 120 rush B
simulator. Toss a coin simulator. Uh, cyber hotfix. Fat smoke. Speedrun Half-Life 4. Yeah, that one.
All right, I can't- I have no money. I know for a fact that guy didn't pay, so we're fucking- that
guy's dead. Oh my god. This is working? You motherfucker. Give me my money! Oh fuck, give me
that. Give me that back. Give me, give me, give me. Hey, hey! I'll be right with you. Thermometer.
What? What do I do with this? Spray? Oh, it stinks in here. Okay. Excuse me, sir. I- I- I- just-
just- basic protocol. Let me just, uh, just hold on for a second. If you need it, uh, if you could
just lift your arm- underarms up for just a moment, please. Okay. I'm doing it to me too. Doing it to
me too. Give him access? Fuck, I'm so stupid. Okay, I need to- so I bought a PC game. You're
wasting it? I don't know, it was- I don't know. This is stressing me out. You're all right.
Computers are 20 years behind technology. The cafe's not nice. There are zero games. I was
peeing on my pants. It would be great if there was a toilet. Um, where would I put that?
Everybody pissed they have pants over there? Who pissed they have pants? Well, I guess I'll take
care of it. It's one of those squid game guys. Get out of here. All right, all right, we're going.
Pay me a bunch of money and play a game. What are you doing? 15 bucks? I need way more money than
that. Let me clean up. All right, I'm not going to mess around anymore. I'm actually going to try to,
like, win. Change your prices. Oh, I can do that. Okay. Uh, right. Okay, I'll do that. Go do a quest.
I'm- I don't want to leak. Should I- can I close this place? Oh, I can. All right, I'm going to
close the cafe. Give me one hour for free. I'll increase the score. I don't know how to do that.
Uh, okay. Let me- computers. Okay, here we go. Change the price. All right, normal. 1.2. That
sounds good. All right, now I'm going to close- I'm going to go see if I can do a mission. I'm going
to take the bat with me though for, like, protection in case somebody tries to kill me or something.
Can I close it? All right, I'm ready. I need a mission. Go around the city and look for a
mission. There was that, like, bitcoin guy. I was- map? Secondhand shop? There's the club. Rabbit club.
100 bucks to go in here? I don't think so. I- these guys scare the shit out of me,
don't they? What's- oh, this is a store? All right, what's in here? Sells secondhand items.
Oh, nice. All right. Buy a disc. Buy a bat. Cardboard. VR. Oh, you can buy cheap stuff here.
PlayStation VR controller. That's kind of cool. All right, kill the store owner. I'm not doing
that in the first 40 minutes of me playing this game. No. What's this? Oh, this is my house.
All right, I live here. I was stuck in there for, like, 15 straight minutes.
BTC miner. I need a quest. Oh, no, it's the same guy just stumbling around. Go to sleep and save
the game. What's going on in here? What is this? Oh, it's a- it's a streamer cafe?
Where's Bugleberry? What else is here? Is this, like, uh, apples or a fruit or something?
Like, this- okay. Should I- I don't want to give this guy 100- oh, I only have 100 dollars left. I
don't want to give the guy 100 dollars. Get out of my- stop. Squid game. Wait, that is- is that
XQC? Look at the shirt. What is this shirt he has on? It's him, like, aged, like, 50 years.
Where's he going? Dude, they, like, they, like, mapped his face. This is crazy. What? Why is Donald
Trump in this- this game is fucked. Okay. I hope XQC comes to my cafe. Hey, XQC, by the way, just
let you know. Five star VIP service to come to my cafe. Five star VIP service. In fact, we can get
a car to pick you up, bring you to the cafe. I'll give you a hot towel. Any game that you want. We
probably have it in our- on our disposal. I need to save the game. All right. All right, all right,
all right, all right. This is- we got a shitload of porn. I don't mean- I don't know. All right,
I gotta save the game. Go home, right? Why am I so invested in this game? Okay. That's crazy.
It's a mapped- his mapped face. Nice immersive- more immersive than cyberpunk. Why do we not move?
What is going on? Remember, you're in it too. I am not in this game. I'm definitely not in it.
What does that do? All right. So now the game is saved. Very cool. I'm not smoking. No, not before
work. What's on floor two? I haven't even looked. Hey, do you think Jerma is going to read this?
Absolutely. All right, back to work. All right, I gotta- I gotta get to my cafe. Is this pre-recorded?
No. Oh, by the way, by the way, I can give you a hard date now, I think. I think I can give you a
hard date on a big stream. So I said it was going to be somewhere in the end of January, maybe.
I hope Community Jake does not want to strangle me after saying this, but I believe we can say
that February 1st, I would be here if you want to see a big stream. I'm not going to tell you what
it is. Wait, turn the lights on. Is it going to be special guests? Confirmed. It's going to be
interesting. I- I will tell you right now. I'm not going to say shit. I will keep reminding you,
but this might be my top three favorite streams I've ever done, without a doubt. Maybe even top
two. I don't know. It's looking like it could be a really fun time. Am I invited? Of course you're
invited to watch the stream on February 1st. All right, I gotta open this door. Open. I keep hitting
escape and I'm stupid. Let's go ahead and open. How am I going to reliably make any money? I have
$130. When are you going to do the naked ketchup bath stream? That would be so weird. What are you
talking- Good afternoon. Welcome to EXP and Espresso. Can I get you an espresso? I don't
have that yet. We will though. It's part of the plan. Limitless. This guy's going to be here all
day. Oh, hell yeah. It's clean. How does it smell in here? It smells pretty good. I thought
something was riding on top of the dog. This guy wants to be in here all day. That's good on me.
Should I pay the guy $100 just to get another quest or something? Back to the back of the guy's
head. All right, I'm just going to do it. Here. Drop by me from time to time. We seem to get along
well with you. Now you can buy BTC Miner if you want. I only have $30. Excuse me? Oh, sorry.
He's been here for a long time. I hope this guy gives me like $200. Can I do anything else here?
Can I make any money? My cafe. This is all too expensive. All right. Crypto. I- I don't have
enough money to do any of this. Just buying and selling crypto. Bills? Thank god I don't have to
pay any bills. Mail. Swap machine. Oh, no. Nope. Not- Holy shit, that's there. Okay, I know that's
there. Skin case. Oh, man. Clothes. No. Warcry coin? You own zero Warcry coin. 100 Warcry coin
is $10. Convert the coins you earn in Warcry into real money. You better not fucking leave without
paying. He was in here for like six hours. It was 100 bucks. Got it. Wait, how do I play? How do I
play? What's Warcry? Game I can play? All right, what's crack? Welcome to crack world. New IP.
Example. Join server. Security IP address is constantly changing. Okay. I don't get it.
Don't turn my electricity off. Do a command. What am I supposed to do with that? Crack world.
Welcome to crack world. What am I supposed to do with this though? That's kawaii. Play claw machine.
Can I- Is this where I get the coin things? Oh, my god. This game was literally- This game was
literally made for me to play it. Look at all those. You won six coins, right? It's 12 dollars
every time I do this? I got a diamond though. What's that worth? What's a diamond worth? Okay,
so now what do I do? Sell coins. Sell the- Whoa! Are you kidding me? Holy shit, that's awesome. All
right, I'm gonna do this for like an hour. Oh, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry. I got it, I got
it, I got it. Minimize, minimize. Uh, I know, I know, I know. Jesus, get over there. What a shitty
place. What was the ding? Can you extend my time? Yeah, sure. Oh, my goodness. Extend me? You- Why
didn't you stay? All right, I'm going back in there and I'm doing that claw game again. All right,
let's go. Games. Coin drop. Definitely this one. 25 bucks to drop a coin. Five- Oh, yep. That's five
purple diamonds. Get it again. Back to back. That's- I'll take it. Do it again. Right in the middle.
I'll take it. One more, that's it. And I'm gonna cash out. Oh, fuck yeah. Nice. Hell yeah. It was
not as much as I thought it was gonna be. Let me check- I want to just check the other ones.
The other ones look kind of cool. Okay, they have games. Hit reward? What do you want? Yes, you can
say as long as you want, as long as you pay. I don't care. All right, slot- Hit reward. What's this
one? Row? 40 dollars to throw this knife. What'd I get? Oh, you're looking for the green. All right,
maybe one more. Shit. All right, one more. That's it. Last one. Did I get it? All right.
Actually, truly the last one. I got the green. Fuck yeah. Actually, not a joke. Hand to my heart,
hand to the grave. Done. After this next one. All right, cash out. All right, I literally lost like
10 dollars. Whatever. That guy leave? No, he's still here. I need to buy a TV for this console.
I spent some- Whatever. I'm gonna sneeze and I'm gonna try to catch it. I'm sorry.
I got it. I think I got it. Buy some crypto. I'm not gonna- I don't want to buy crypto.
I only have 200 dollars. I want to see what other like funny little games I can play.
Slot machine. 50 bucks? Oh, fuck you. What about the lucky wheel? Wait, 97 bucks. Hell yeah. All
right. Hold on. I'm making money. I'm fine. No, no, no. It's getting dark. Wait, it's the squid game
guy. It's the squid game guy right here. I stopped being like, oh, I'm the squid game guy. Relax.
You're fine. I'm gonna overact. You still have to pay for the time you're here. Where's my eyes?
Oh, I can look in tighter. Okay. Remember, this place sucks. I just opened it. I'm trying to get
some money. Once I get to a thousand bucks, I can buy, um, because of the virus. The virus.
Yeah, maybe it's all the porn you've all been watching. Okay, where's my virus scan?
Uh, where is it? Let me spin this first. Okay, apps, virus. Where is it? Oh, there it is.
The number of computers connected to the network, two. Start scan. Phone number of
46 viruses. This reminds me of when I would be at a grandparent's house and you'd run.
They'd be like, oh, yeah, you could use my computer. If you need to use a computer at
a grandparent's. Oh, yeah, the computer's upstairs, sweetheart. Yeah, it works. I've got,
I've got Microsoft on there. And they don't even ask you to do this, but you just do it because
you're just going to half because you're curious and half because they don't know what the fuck's
going on. You just run malware bytes or like Windows Defender on their computer. Yes, because
it's just the first thing you do. Um, and I remember I did that one time and I think there
was, I'm not kidding. There was probably like thousands of like adware and shit like that on
it. And you don't even tell them you're doing it either. That conversation does not even need
to happen because they would, oh, speaking of like overacting, that was like the ultimate
overacting. Oh, I got hit by the shell in Mario Kart. If I did voice lines for Mario Kart, like
I just got hit by a fucking trap thing. Why are they, okay, how do I stop them from happening?
Why do they keep doing that? Why, like, why are they like coming here and like blowing up the,
why are they doing this? Please pull on, please apologize to my girlfriend. After you thief
stream, I told her you'd be playing Everhood on Wednesday and we were very excited, but here we
are and there's no Everhood. I know. I'm sorry. I lied about it. I'm sorry. I'm, I'm actually sorry.
I did say I was going to play. I did say I was going to play Everhood. It didn't end up happening.
Very sorry about that. I kind of had a headache earlier and I feel like that was not the kind of
game to play with a headache. I will play Everhood. You can be rest assured. At some point I will play
Everhood. I'm so sorry. I don't, I'm really nervous. I'm so sorry. What was that? We just
laughed. That was weird. Okay. How much money do I have? How long does it take to do virus shit?
Did they get it? Or did the explosion screw this up? Did the explosion mess it up? Don't
even tell me that's what happened. I got 324. Treasure hunt. Get more, no more keys left.
One key is, okay. So I'm going to buy five keys. What do you think guys? Up right? Good call.
Right in the middle? Eh guys, come on. Middle left? Center left, yep. Middle right. Oh man,
these are bad, bad choices. Bottom left. It's okay. All right, what else we got? I didn't do
lucky wheel. I want to try it. How do I do it? I'll spin 15. All right, do it again. Green is the most
expensive it seems, right? All right, actually the final one. I'm not doing this ever again.
All right, that's it. Ash out. We got 177 worth. I just keep ending up with the same amount that
I came in with. What about this Warcry coin thing? Stop turning the electricity off. Whoever's doing
that. Is there a reason why no one's coming in? Turn the Warcraft game into real money. Hold on,
how do I do that? PC's not assembled? Apps. Employee. Data so we can find some employees. Warcry.
There it is. World's greatest MMO game. Download now and start earning real money. All right,
that's downloading. Is it really not assembled? Oh, that's why. Okay, that's stupid. Are we clean
though? I think so. Chair. Idiot, idiot, idiot, idiot. I got it. I'm going to sell this.
We're closed for a minute. Secondhand shop right here. Hey, what? You're being searched for what?
What? What's going on? What's happening? Why am I being searched? You've been fined for not obeying
police stop warning. What the hell are you talking about? What? I'm walking down the street with
my computer monitor to sell to the secondhand shop. What do you, what do you mean by that?
What'd I do? I got something for you. I literally stopped when he said stop.
Even think about it. All right, do I have enough to buy a monitor? Wait, I can play that game.
I have a bill due. Please stop penalty. Come on, fuck off. Okay, how do I play it? Warcry classic.
Start game. What? Interact. What is this? Interact. Sell item. What is this? This is actually,
you can play this guys at level 12. How am I supposed to kill these? They sound like something.
What do they sound like? Oh my God. What is it? Heart of darkness. I came from PlayStation one.
How many coins do I get? This hurts my head looking at this. Can I do another move?
Has anybody come into this restaurant yet? Okay. Open. I can't open. Open it. Open this. There's
nothing even in these. This guy's a quest upgrade item. Why? I don't even have any money. The loot
despawned. What level are these guys? One? Level two. All right. Dude, why is there nothing in these?
Finally. What is it? Jello? Free game. No complaining. It's a free game. You don't have
the season pass. This is a health potion. Okay. Are you going to stream the new war crime expansion?
Um, I'm actually not like that happy with like the direction that the devs have taken it. The amount
of damage that it used to, they, they did, they changed the scaling on damage. At least that's
their plan. And I mean, I've been playing this game since like 2013 or something. So it's like
as somebody that's been playing it for a while, it sucks. Well, I mean, it's probably a good excuse
for me to stop playing it. This is my, I mean, we're in the stator zone for the new guys watching,
but this is probably I like 40th or 50th character. That's probably a good idea,
but try something else. If they end up fixing it though, I'll probably come back. Yeah. The
change in bags lots too, which is, I mean, I love this dev team and shit, so I don't really want to
talk that deeply about it and to kind of be overly, I would say not, I don't want to be mean or
anything, but cause I mean, I, I truly, I love this game and I love the community and everything.
But I don't know if the new lead director needs to, needs to give more input from the fans and
stuff, but I'm just not fucking happy with it. I'm going to sell these though. Worst joke taking
more than five minutes. It's only been 30 seconds. Wrap it up. All right. All right. Wrap it up,
Jeremy. Wrap it up. All right. All right. Wrap it up. That's felt like two hours. Oh, stop,
please get out of there. I'm trying to pass the time so I can sell, by the way,
is anybody even in the fucking store? Why is nobody in here? Has electricity been off? Oh no,
my progress. I'm sitting here. Oh, thank God. Thank God. Okay. Devs did something right.
Auto save. Okay. I'm almost, this is actually kind of hard to control. I'll be honest.
I'll be honest. Open. All right. I'm turning this stuff in. I'm done. Okay. Can I use this to craft
or something? Upgrade. Belt. No, it just costs coins. Let's sell. Hello. What the fuck? Where's
the booty bay guards? Where's the booty bay guards? What the fuck is going on here?
Where are the guards? What the fuck was that? How much do I get? I only have 34 coins. What
can I do with these? Can I even turn these in? How do I get, like, what do I do? How do I get
out of this? Oh, okay. So now I go to Warcry coin. It's only ten dollars to convert a hundred of
those coins. I'm never opening that ever again. 433 bucks. Why is nobody coming into the store?
It really wasn't open. You guys weren't kidding. It's all right. Whatever. Just gamble instead.
Yeah, that's not a bad idea. That's not a bad idea. The monitor's not connected yet. It is.
I know the control is on the ground somewhere. Where is it? Hey, what the hell are you doing?
What are you doing? What are you doing? Give me that back. What is that? Wait, I heard that
laugh before. Oh, you idiot. Why? Stupid. Did he take the controller? No, I think it's on the
ground over there. Get it? Flush. Thank you. Clean this up. I only have room for two things anyways
in this damn place. Whatever. Did he steal the other monitor? No, I sold it. I got rid of it.
And the tower. Where is it? There it is. I need it. Please decorate. I don't have any money.
I'm going to gamble $200. And then whatever happens from that, we'll smush it into decorating.
I saw that guy's back. No, he's not. All right. I thought I saw him sneaking by.
Even think about it. All right. He's not here. All right. What do you say we do a little gambling?
Why not? Do I buy a case? I'm going to buy a best case for $300. All right. Come on.
Any of these good? I got two knives. Those are two knives. That's worth like $1,000. I just won.
I just won the game. There's literally two knives in here. What do I do? 160. Wait. Do I sell this?
What's happening? What do I do? What do I do?
Excuse me. Hey, what's up, man? How you doing? Good to see you. Good to see you. Yeah, I just
opened up this cafe and I'm good to see you. I've got games for you if you're
ready to go. You can check out whatever we got on the thing over there. Just take a look.
I can get you situated. I can get the whole package going right now.
30 minutes is fine, dude. If you want to stay for like an hour, you can. I don't give a shit.
You know what I mean? You can just stick around. An hour, two hours, it don't matter. Oh, no.
Oh, no. I mean, you know, I'm just going to look the other way on this one.
I'm going to look over here. Hold on. Hold on. Let me get up. I got to get up from the seat.
Thank you. No, no, no. I'll take the money. I'll take the money, please.
No way. He's leaving without paying. I was my fault. I'm sorry. I should have actually put
my hand out and then taken that money from you. You know, let's just call it even. It was really
great to see you. If you ever want to come back, by all means, we love having content creators come
over and check out our stuff. And yeah, I mean, we could just say that this was kind of like a
little collaboration and it was really good to have you. You can tell people about us and maybe
you come back next time and maybe we have a good time. Okay, we're open. Pet the cat. Okay. Minus
two. You should have hit him. No, I can't. How do you pet cat? I mean, this, I know like it's like,
oh, he's going to left click. I'm not, I'm not going to punch this cat. Oh, check his review.
Yeah. What did he say? Let's see. If more beautiful girls come, I'll increase the score. He gave me
five stars. That's pretty good. I think that's not, that's not bad. Wait, does he, is that implying
that if there was more porn, if I had more porn? Oh man. I need to get to downloading. I can,
how do I uninstall this? All right. So now 290, wait, right. So how do I get, I have like all these
skins and shit. I have a knife. Can I sell these? Do I have an inventory or something? I only got
one. This is it. Where is it? Wait, what? You only, it only gives you the one. How do I sell it? I
already got the money for it. No way. Oh shit. All right. Come on. All right. I just got fucking
absolutely annihilated. All right. I'm done. I'm done. That's it. No more. Oh, what's he playing?
He's playing half life. He wants more time. You got it. He's playing a game. So this is going to
be worth more money. All right. What's this whole, I actually have to stop messing around. I keep
just blowing my money and gambling in an arcade machine. They generate a ton of money. All right.
Actually no more gambling. I don't want to do that anymore. That's stupid. What about food? Ending
machine. This game's kind of cool. I need to restart. I don't think so. I have 440 bucks.
I screwed up because I bought a bunch of console stuff and I thought I could just put a TV on it
or a monitor. There's actually a lot of stuff. I'm very interested. This is, this is a lot of fun.
Let's cope. It's not, it's not cope. I like the game. I need to wait till he's done.
So what should I, I have no bills I have to pay. All right. He wants to pay. Let's go. How much
you, that was an expensive experience. Wasn't it? 79 bucks. It seems fun in a dumb way. It's just,
it's just, all right. Gamble on the fruit slots. I would have so much more money if we didn't do
any of that. All right. I'll do it for a minute. I was peeing on my pants. It'd be great if there
was a toilet. By the way, if more beautiful girls come, I'll increase the score. How do you increase
the score over five stars? You really kind of don't. Excuse me. Excuse me. No, put that down.
Excuse me. I only did that because she, are we open? $20 bet for, okay. Spin. $20 bet. What
am I even looking at here? What are the lines? Buy a free spin for $2,000. What a rip off. I'm
not going to hit anything at all. Yeah. I got you. Come on. Um, what the hell? All right. What's
that worth? This thing sucks. What do these do? What? That strawberries right there. How is that
not a line? How is this not a line? Come on. Come on. All right. That's going to be worth like
a hundred bucks. That was something. How much was that? What are you doing? Thanks for coming.
50 bucks. All right. No more gambling. Do a virus scan, please. What time is it right now?
One. No new customers come after one o'clock. All right. So let's close. Fucking goddamn virus
scan. Do the claw machine one more time. I need to buy an arcade machine. I don't have, dude,
I got to tell you up front here. Every time that we get more than $400, I go back to zero.
I wish it was warmer. Yeah, so do I. It's January though. I buy more of these. I guess I'm just
going to sit in here all night and play Warcry Classic. Oh right. The virus scan. You can't even
get past 300 bucks without gambling it away. I promise I am not going to spend a single solitary
cent until we get to enough money where I can put it on that console table. I'm not going to spend
another dime. Not one dime. Make a prediction. Go for it. You guys want to bet on that? I will
not spend another dollar until I have enough to buy a TV for that console. The PlayStation one
over there on the on the table. Make a prediction. Trust me. I got it. I got this. I feel like this
would be pretty, um, be pretty trivial in a few hours. All right. It's doing it. Just don't turn
the electricity off. Clean this place up. A little dirty. I'm not going to spend any money. I promise.
You can do it. I'm going to tell you guys right now. If you bet against that, you're going to lose.
If you say no, I will not be able to avoid spending. You're going to lose. The controller
is still on the floor. Well, yeah, because I can't really do anything with it now. I need a TV.
What about if you get fined? No, that does not count. It only counts if I physically spend the
money. Not something that I have to pay. Like bills or the police fine or something. No. It has
to be I spend it. Like I go, oh, I'm going to buy this or I'm going to gamble. No, it doesn't count.
Hundreds of viruses. There we go. Cool. All right. It's a new day. I haven't slept in probably three.
So let's just relax and go forward, right? Just relax. Shut up. The fuck up. All of you. And let's
go from here. I'm going to put this in a better place. Like in the corner so I know exactly where
it is at all times. Let's go. Open the store. Open for business. $92. Come on in. Maybe there's a
quest or something I can do. Adjust the prices. Should I just make it really expensive and get a
bunch of bad ratings and who cares? Does that, do I really care that much? 1.3. Hello. Yep, that'll be
computer number one. I've got you. Is she naked? No. What? What are you talking about? She's
watching stock footage or the beginning of every YouTuber video you've ever watched in your whole
life. Anytime any YouTuber has ever gone anywhere in their entire life has been this shot every
The only thing that's missing is the plane, um, the plane wing out the window.
The plane wing.
Have I ever done that?
Have I ever done the, I'm going on a trip, I'm filming out the plane window?
I don't think I have.
Don't you think it'd be kind of funny?
What if I made a video, and, hold on, what if I made a video where it was just like me
introducing that like, hey guys, going on this big trip, it's gonna be so much fun,
and we'll see ya!
And it's just like, four minutes of planes taking off and landing out the window.
It's just like that, I'm going up, out the window, and then it like, it cuts to me like
holding like a drink on the plane, like, mmm, and looking in the camera, where's the computer
up?
You already made this years ago, what?
Just upload the whole flight, yeah, yeah, it's like, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun,
Out the window, and then it's just, grrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr and you're just
sitting there in the seat, just sitting there looking around, it took a six hour, seven
hour video.
You're shifting around and just stretching your back, you get up to take like a piss
and it's just still sitting where the seat is.
Oh no, don't make it a time lapse.
Wait, somebody want to, shit, I wasn't paying attention.
Is he doing that for free?
I should buy a monitor?
I'm waiting till I can afford it.
It's open?
It's true. Yeah, just have it be the whole flight is the video and then at the very end
It's just like the point you get off the plane and it gets into like a like, oh, I'm in I'm in the uber
Oh, here we go
And it cuts like I'm in the Hoja and you see like in the top right like a battery
It's like blinking and it just cuts in the video ends. Yep
Then the next videos you're getting on another plane the dollhouse behind the scenes starts with an airplane window shot
It does
Does it actually let me see let's investigate this I want to see now it doesn't
Where in the very beginning? I don't listen to that. It does. Oh fuck. It actually does. Let me see
Doesn't right?
It does hold on
It doesn't that doesn't count that doesn't count that's a plane landing that's not a plane out the window with the wing
Going up. It's got the right music though. It has the right music. I will give you that. It's the correct music
That doesn't count. It's a plane. It's it's a plane going down. It's not like playing going out back to counts
It does sure. Yeah counts fine. Okay. Oh
I have not been paying attention at all. Is this person still here? It counts. That's fine. Okay, 214 bucks
how long till the prediction ends until I either spend money on something I'm not supposed to or
I buy the thing that I'm supposed to buy. What can I do for you? I changed my desktop background to a quest
I'm I don't want to just leave
Look, I did like the Bitcoin quest and the guy was like, hey
I've got to go to my Bitcoin store and never even went there's the only quest I had another customer
Thank you. What can I get for desktop wallpapers? Can you actually get them? I want something better
I'm gonna just click that. All right. Where do I okay bill mail clothes?
What do I get it was peeing smells disgusting, okay, I'm going home to pee
Why would you go home?
Okay, how am I supposed to get a bathroom?
Well, stop pissing on the ground
Maybe that would be a easy way to make it doesn't smell in here anymore. You can expand the store
Let me I need to have more than one person here at a time
Is there a bunch of viruses on this thing again? There's so many viruses again. It's dirty. It is reduced lots
No, I need a TV and that's priority number one because once I get a TV I can have double the income
We're trailing so far behind. I've been here for two hours
Jeremy your excuse was that you just started but pay me
No, that's not gonna happen. There's the bat. Yeah, arrest him. What this the guy just stole from me
He just stole from me. Oh
Fuck I didn't mean to holy shit. I didn't mean to hit you
I was
Can you please open the image that you've had in the very beginning of this one? Oh, what about it? I
Didn't spend any money actually. Oh, come on. I was right there. Hey for what you've done
What I didn't spend money. I have to pay the fine. I haven't paid the fine yet
See, I have four days to pay $50 penalty. I'm not paying it
What's up, you added the stipulation that it didn't count if you had to pay for it. Yeah, that's true
But I mean, I don't want to spend $50 right now if I don't have to I even go over to the BTC thing
That's that TF classic. It's not enough. It is for the quest. All right, but not I'm
Rowing along here. What time is it? All right. I have to say I gotta save the game. It's been like an hour and a half
Turn the lights off
Clean up close the store. All right, I gotta go home and save the game. That's just silent. We have a such a silent community
Silent what do you mean?
Oh
That's what was happening in the very beginning of the screen. I was what the hell's happening to me. I couldn't go anywhere
This isn't thrillville. No, it's internet cafe simulator another day. I'm ready. What is that image?
Oh, that burger is me
That's a picture of me. It's me. It's my face
It's supposed to be like this. It just looks funny. Your mouth looks like among us
No, it's not supposed to look like that
He took a picture
After I was like in the head in the back of the head with a bowling pin and I'm on like the ground
No, I'm sleeping
That is not you. Yes, it is. I swear to God. That's me
If you do you need more proof, it looks at nothing like me prove that that's me. There's no way. Okay, fine
Do you want proof? I'll prove it's me. Here we go. Here's your proof. I
Have to crop this cuz I'm like naked. Hold on. Let me I'm not gonna fucking mess this up
This is me guys. I need to make sure I don't what it's got. I'm naked in this picture. I'm not naked
I don't give shit who cares if you really need to if I need to really prove that that is me
Lying down in a bed. I will I'm ready. I'm ready to leak it. All right, let me just hold on
Okay, here comes a leak, right? What did I name it? I don't know. I kind of saved this image. Oh, there we go
Okay. Okay. Here it comes. I hope it doesn't just show up on the fucking screen. Like hold on me
I'm gonna make sure my like my dick is not in this or something
I have to like I gotta like literally zoom in and look and make sure my dick's not in this
I think I'm good. I'm gonna crop it anyways. All right, I can crop it. I gotta do this slowly
I gotta do it really slowly to make sure I can like I'm not actually let's see we gotta reveal this slow
All right, not that way where am I where the fuck am I why am I not in this image? Oh, wait, hold on
What is that? What is that? Is that a dick?
It's not an ass
It's not an ass what is that? I didn't look what does this picture look like? I don't know if that is
What is that? Is that my stomach? All right. Well, I think that's a shoulder. I think we're good. What is that?
I swear to god, this is my shoulder. This is my shoulder. It's just weirdly cropped
It's just really weirdly cropped what even okay, it's cuz it's somewhere. Where's my face?
There I am there I am okay, I found it I got I got it there I am why what's going on in this picture
Why is it like this? What the fuck? I'm so confused right now
I
Told you it was real
It's cuz it was upside down show the whole thing now nice neck beard
I'm gonna die
What do you mean? That's not me. Are you out of your mind? How do you know that's me?
Let me I mean I can flip it. Let me let me flip it the other way so you can see rotate
That's my face. Hey, this is me
My face
Somebody said that's literally your stunt double dude. That can't be you. That's me. That's me
I swear to god it is look at my face. Look, do you need me to do this?
Look, you want to we have to prove this. I need to make sure people understand
This is actually me look like look at the look at the beard. Look at right. Okay, you we need to match hair here
Look at that's me. That's
My face
What more proof do you do you guys require squish your face against something?
I don't know how you guys don't understand. This is the same person literally right here. Look, it's the same person
But lay on the desk. I'm not laying on the desk. We're moving on. All right, I get what was I doing?
It's a paid it's not an actor. I lost my hold on. I lost my entire train of thought right here
It's a VR model. All right, electricity's off. It's fine. Turn everything back on wait, it's that guy again
Okay. Wait, wait, wait, wait. Let me talk to that guy. I already did his quest is even another one, dude
There's a there's a bum meddling in our business. I'll give you a favor if you beat him up for me
It says family on the man's t-shirt
He always wears a white tank top and his bald white tank top bald and he says family
It's a map beat up the man in the white tank top. I guess not happen. What's wrong with the dog?
What dog he's fine?
Is the store? No, no, it's not open. It's not. All right my cafe. It's a little cold inside
Is that what the burglar just said? Is that sleeping version of yourself chug pickled juice water?
You're gonna buy some wallpaper for the shop. Okay, where do I buy it? Is it in clothes? No, oh, right, right
Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep, right turn the prices down so people will stay longer at longer means more money. I get you
Okay, I see. Oh
Treat the customer with respect and they won't just leave
Interesting concept interesting there are snitches in chat
I didn't yeah, you guys have to if you're gonna bet you get a bet. Where's
Where's the guy you need to bring the bat? I'll bring the bat with me white tank top
I mean, it's like everyone has a white tank top on you got a white tank top white tank top
What just happened? I broke the bat on him. Okay, please stop you you were there for at least a few minutes
Thank you. I have to buy a new weapon. That's alright. Oh, I do have skill points. You're right
I get that menu tab backpack. You have a hundred
Entrepreneurs soul I can buy some stuff. I can spend some skill points X to use you have to close the inventory. Ooh
Alright, hold on. I'm gonna sneeze again
Okay cafe if it increases the likelihood of more customers coming to your cafe. Let's do it. Let's get it
People leave more money in the tip box. Thanks to your smiling face. You will have customers to leave more positive comments
Thanks to your tough appearance the number of customers running away with without paying is reduced
I don't have enough for that. Okay physical body even punch so many times that you don't feel anything anymore
You become more resilient. You know, get out get out of the menu. I don't have I don't have weapon
No, I didn't want to punch the guy with the family thing I didn't want to punch Vin Diesel again, give me a break you actually
So unfair so unfair actually unfair actually fucking stupid
Unfair I didn't want to punch Vin Diesel. He was just in the way
Console it's not fair. Did I let him use a computer
You punch like lightning enemies have a hard time understanding where the punches are coming from
No harder punches. All right, I think that's good now, please buy TV dude. I'm trying to buy a TV
They are six or seven hundred dollars. I have to just wait till I have the money TVs
$650 and I can I sell something else you got about the fine. No, I didn't I have three days to pay it
I literally was just up to try to take that money dude. No, stop hitting people that walking by what how did you get in?
I can't I need
Computers don't even have a video card. Yes, they do. It's on board on board graphics have come such a long way
Shut up. I think I gotta close. Oh, not yet, please just have a customer do something for the love of God
There you go. Enjoy. There's a used TV at the secondhand store. Are you kidding me?
All right after this guy leaves I'm closing up and we're gonna go get it. Hurry up. I'm trying to close man
This electricity is off in the store. Nobody can get in here. Anyways, secondhand store. Let's go. All right
I'm looking for a TV plus you're a TV. You didn't have a TV old LCD
Pro LCD those aren't TVs though behind you. Holy shit. I thought those were his legs. I was like what is going on?
There's no TV he's watching the stream down the street at least get a bat
I can't I can't spend any money or people lose. I lose the bet. I'm gonna go save the game. I need a bat
I know
New day, okay. Here we go
You're playing monster hunter rise. I probably not
Probably not you got another quest eat him faces family
I know I know but I can't even hurt him right open the store electricity on scan for viruses
You play dying light too. Yeah, I would say for sure scan. Yeah, they got a blue screen. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
I know you play League of Legends. No, I don't want to play League
I that's the last thing I'd probably ever do I would cover myself in peanut butter
I'd like a roll around on the ground before I played one game of League of Legends on stream
Need money
600 bucks. That's all I need just stay here for a long time
I don't care what you do your free reign to do whatever you want and go wherever you want
Whatever I don't care just stay here and pay me money. Okay, still here. Yeah. All right, Dan still scanning
Just go beat up Vin Diesel. It pays well
I tried to beat up Vin Diesel, but my back broke across his cement body my bat shattered on him
Let me get some money here. It's not bad almost there. Just maybe like another three customers and I'm good more tips
All right, where's am I? Do I have a tip jar? I?
Can't beat up Vin Diesel with my bare hands. What did I do? Why would he do that?
All right watching YouTube. All right. I'm if I can is there a block. That's not block. Is that me? Oh, I'm laughing. Oh
Okay, so now I get it. Never I've been hearing that person laugh. I think I've I've been accidentally pressing it
It's been me. You're gonna do a live-action family guy roleplay stream. I don't believe so
No, that's your middle finger button. No, I'd say this is zero chance of that happening. Okay, we're good
All right, I need please let me know can I actually fight and beat Vin Diesel one on?
One he killed me in one hit last time. I don't think I'm ready
I don't know what I keep thinking of like Trump putting the mask on from the mask
That's all I see the Jim Carrey mask. Oh, so somebody stabbed me
You can't vote for that for the worst joke of the year. It didn't take five minutes to set up
P-a-r-t why?
No
Believe me because I gotta I'm sorry you can't I you can't vote for worse impression every year if I do a shitty Trump
I do a bad Trump every year more than once a year. So don't you can't nominate it. It's all it's gonna happen
It's gonna be bad every year. It's cold in here. You have enough money to gamble now
I am so close to actually being able to play this game correctly. I'm not going to do that
There are 20,000 people here. Holy shit. What are y'all doing here? Just vibing. Yeah. All right me too
All right, close close close close. It's your birthday. Happy birthday. I hope you have a good birthday
All right. I am so close. How much is the TV?
$650 I'm almost there for life. I'm here from that reddit video the reddit videos
So funny like this community has made me more popular without me even doing anything. I didn't even do anything
I just like my face existed. All right, this would be it right here. The sus guy the serial killer
They'll look I'm hearing again thing. I have nothing to do with any of these things. None zero
I find out about them when you do so those who that are coming from some of the stuff that you've seen on reddit
Amen. Wow, what's this on the front page? It's literally we're at the same time
You and I are both going like this. Whoa, man. What's this on the front page?
So I open up my phone you open up your phone. Whoa, man. What's this on the front page?
We both do the same fucking thing at the same time. I have no idea what they're gonna do
I don't have no idea what what what we're looking at. I have no idea. I am usually shitting
I didn't do anything. I'm being stolen from move move. No, I don't fight two people
No, don't fight three people run. I got my money run that climbers
Get out of here close the door close the door. I just like sniper bullets to go by me. What was that? What was that?
What the fuck has happened? I just saw bullets go by me
How are you walking through a door?
We're still open. I'm not warming the inside. Why did you hit L on?
No, he was I he was blocking the way so I'm trying to get around him and jump over the
Railing you know play Deus Ex probably not any game that is more than
20 to 30 hours you'll probably never see on this stream
the only exception is from software games and
If I get obsessed with something or like a week make me like monster entry or whatever this you'll do it
This is gonna do it about Dawn of War. Yeah, I mean if we
Maybe be kind of fun to get a bunch of streamers to just play a huge game of Dawn of War
I think that'd be funny everybody kind of a basic rundown how the game works and have a gigantic like
12 person streamer RTS battle the teams all right come pay so I can buy a TV
Are you gonna stream all of?
Elden ring yes, I have played every from software game that is released
In the last six years or so on this stream to completion. I'm going to do it again
You only stream two days a week though
I mean when a big release like that comes out that I've been looking forward to I I will play more if I can
What about the new fable is there a new fable coming up?
All right, this would put us over the edge. I think yep, all right finally
$668 it's time to buy the TV. I would like for the mods to pay out
I did it. I told you not to doubt me, but a lot of you did anyways
It's the last piece of this puzzle, and then I can start making a bunch of money on the console games
Diesel's right there. Why can't I just like spin spin spin spin spin spin spin tornado punch right here right in the head?
I would be able to win. I don't want to steal this nobody take this please say Elon Musk again. I just did yes
on soul TV
finally
Consoles I need a second controller all right. I have $18. It's rain. There's actually weather in the game
I'm just gonna sell like the thermometer or something what about like breath of the wild or breath of the wild to I've outcome clean
I know a lot of the older viewers know this but maybe the newer ones don't I don't I'm not I don't really
I'm not a big Zelda fan. I don't get excited for Zelda the breath of the wild
I know it's an awesome game, but it's a Zelda game, and I can't go over that hump for some reason
I never really I was never truly into the Zelda games the last Zelda game that I really played or really cared about was probably
Probably ocarina of time if I'm honest and then Twilight Princess. I remember playing it and it's just like
Opening your eyes underwater in a pool, and then getting out and looking at lights
The Twilight Princess was pool vision for the whole game, and I couldn't play it you didn't pay god. I'm getting headbutt
$11 man
Give me another controller controllers. Why are they so expensive?
What oh my god
Okay
Is there some story line that I'm missing here of why the people from squid game keep on throwing just
Bombing my cafe am I missing a piece of the story here, or is that just hey?
There's guys that are in squid game outfits that are going to like explode your business. I don't understand
Why are they doing that? Why why why they in squid game outfits? That's good. How does it smell in here awful?
Okay, I think we're good electricity back on
This needs the keyboard back good. Okay perfect. I need that other controller
I love this dream German really just says buzzwords. I do I just say buzzwords
What do you mean what buzzwords there's so many viruses on that computer? I need a bat to fine
I know I pay the fine right here fucking asshole. Why no one pays no one pays
Has anyone paid in
Two days Jesus all right this whatever this like tinky-winky guy go up here get on get on get on get on
Need to get a security guard. I have $30 dude 30 bucks la la clean
Please pay said you were never gonna say that again. No I didn't I said I'm never gonna say the e word again the temperature
15 degrees in here 15 degrees Celsius
That's not that cold is it was that like 50 60 50 45 or something how hot is that yeah?
That's not even that what how's that cold 59 is cold yeah
I know we've had the conversation about how hot or cold a room should be right people think I'm crazy
We're not wanting to be in a house. That's 67 or 68 degrees. I I want my place to be between 72
73 between like 72 and like 74
68 is might as well be an icebox. It's a it's a walk-in freezer people turn their
Thermostats down at night because did you get better sleep or something right?
Oh, I turn my thermostat down to like 65 at night. I would die in 65. I would be dead
I would wake up dead. That's too much way too cold
72 is perfect being in a colder room promotes better sleep. I guess some some study from somebody
I don't know no not happening 64 is perfect. No don't leave without paying don't leave without even the money
What why does nobody pay?
Why does nobody pay I didn't give him access to the computer, then why was he there using it?
He should have been using it, so he didn't have access to it, but he used it anyways
So he used it and then just left. I'm getting a bat how much is that?
I'll take it see it looks like his legs. Oh how much are the controllers 80 bucks all right?
That's better than buying it 120 all right. Where's Vin Diesel? I'm not messing around now. He broke the bat last time wait
Will he actually break it have to pay the fine?
I'm five cents short fine whoever comes here has no self-esteem
Okay, ooh nice that has a wear meter is that why it broke not because Vin Diesel's like stacked and
So wait I actually can can get him with it does have a wear meter all right. I'm going for it
Tell your friends about the consoles that we're about to add if I see Vin Diesel he's getting it there
He is there. He is he's right there. I don't want to hit four people with this didn't they double team me earlier
These two oh
That was so sly very did you hear that where is he yes all right? Do I get money for this?
200 bucks that's really good. Don't even think about it. I was already left without paying all right
I'm gonna go buy a controller, and then I can actually use that and that I'm gonna make that expensive
It's from right here shit. What do I do?
He's still owe me that he owes me that right he owes me that thing all right nice. Hell. Yeah, thank you finally
It's only taken two hours to do it do I like coleslaw?
Yeah, it depends not really the only place I've really ever liked coleslaw from was Canes
And that's because I like to so after you eat Canes once you've you got like the sauce you got the you know
Whatever the the fries you get the chicken. That's kind of all over inside of the
Kind of styrofoam thing whatever
When it all mixes together
let's say you take a bite of a sandwich or you eat like a piece and it kind of falls into the
Kind of well that you have in front of you
I like to dump the coleslaw in afterwards and I kind of mix it all up and just eat the coleslaw with all like
The junk that fell out of the sandwich and stuff. That's the only time I really eat it all right
I have it's it's we're gonna make this two bucks an hour. It's expensive
We're doing it the bat is ready to go. I'm gonna enjoy some console games. It's fine, too
That's right. He eats hamburger helper. Why are you all surprised?
He eats like a starving rodent hamburger helper is good on salt. We don't have to have this conversation again
There are no games for the console really I mean she's in here, okay nice
All right, then I'm gonna get an arcade machine to go in the corner
I wouldn't feed hamburger help which are my greatest enemy. It's why it's so easy. It's such an easy dinner. It feeds it feeds like
60 people when you make a box all it is is just ground beef and the box. It's really easy to make
It's really hearty. It's really filling. It's good. I said this in beginning of the stream
It's gross when you make it, but after it's done, and you take a bite you go. Holy shit
This is insane. My mom used to feed me hamburger helper all the time pretty sure it's why I have whatever
Hi, that was 120 bucks right there
His birthday's coming up in five days
Listen hold on let me see
My girlfriend this is from Ken my girlfriend and I are massive fans and have been watching for two years now
The birthday coming up in five days all right all right you want a unique birthday present
What's your girlfriend's name somebody walk out without paying does all the beef you eat come from a box you don't it's the hamburger helper
Is not it's not in the box you buy ground beef from the butcher
And it's not inside the box you buy ground beef from the butcher, and then you take that you use brown the beef
You brown it in a pan
And then you put the box in with some water and some milk and you stir it up
It's so easy hamburger helper is divorced dad food
Hamburger helper if this is you are slandering something that I love and I'm not gonna put up
I'm gonna put my foot down right now. It's
Dad food I
Really like it the beef stroganoff hamburger helper is like actually 10 out of 10
But okay, you know the green eggs and you have a green eggs in him
You know what happened to the end of green eggs in him Sam I am ate it and he said holy shit
This is the best food I've ever had in my fucking life. Thanks a lot
Jerry whatever his name was go eat the beef stroganoff hamburger helper. Just go try it and then you can go
And then it goes like
And everyone's like happy get a divorce and eat hamburger helper on
How much are they paying you do you let me be very clear I need to be incredibly clear about this
Do you think that I would take just completely unjust solicited a hamburger helper
Sponsorship on this stream just out of nowhere would I do you really think that would happen?
That's not even remotely the case. It's never been money money money money money money. Give it to me. Don't walk away. Give me
I'm getting actually cash here. Hi, is it hurt? Well, what her name is a her name is Ari Ari Ari sure
You know you want a birthday wish let's go for it. Oh, I'm making money now. So what's that in five days from now?
So that'd be let's see one two, three, four
What 17th keep cleaning? Well, I'm doing a birthday thing
Hey Ari, Ken, Ken lets me know. It's your birthday coming up in five days on the 17th
I just want to say real quick happy birthday in a rough couple of years think of everybody here
But keep your head up. Happy birthday Ari. There it is birthday wishes
Anybody anybody else got a birthday put a cameo water mock-up. I have one coming up in July. Hey nano wiener
Birthday in July for God's sake. That's I feel like I'm getting like radiation sickness from this thing
You know what I mean? Just like I should just be this close my face. I say oh, hey
Hey, my my wife Aaron's birth. My wife Aaron's birthdays coming up. Hey
Aaron Aaron have a happy birthday coming up in July. We got a birthday coming up too. Hey
Stebern heard you got a birthday coming up here in July. Have a happy birthday in July Stebern
Mine's in July too. Hey aqualos. Happy birthday coming up here in July. I know it's coming up soon
I'm fucking getting off my birthday. It's February. Happy birthday in February. Why is he online right now? I don't know
How much money do I have already have 366 bucks a happy birthday Leslie? It's in February. Happy birthday Leslie. It's in February
Happy birthday coming up
Right nice lean up a little bit
Girlfriend's birthdays tomorrow. I don't I didn't see the name. Happy birthday slot machine is coming up here
It's a lot machines birthday in February. Happy birthday to the slot machine in February speaking of which I'm gonna just play a little bit
I'm just gonna play a little bit not much just enough to like get a good taste. All right, this is it, dude
Why come on Gwen? Come on, dude. Do it again. Somebody else need to I said I was supposed to Halloween music
Why is that Christmas? Oh my god
I just like killed three people. What do you want to do? All right, what do you want to play?
I got a couple games that you can line up here again. Come on. Do it again, please
This thing sucks. It actually sucks. I don't know what lines I'm looking for that
How is that not doesn't make any sense. It should be a line right there. They were running in tandem
There's nothing I could do about that. That's a lot of bananas. All right, nine seven
Watermelons what how is that not a line? Where's it? Nobody pays for anything
Nobody pays nobody pays for anything here. Where'd they go? It's gonna play. I need candies
I'm gonna blow all my money again. I have to stop. Oh, but come on
I need to get something grapes that seemed good
46 plus 30 or all right peaches peaches
Watermelons stop running out and not paying that was that Trump
Okay, hold on. I'm coming. I'm coming. Nobody pays everybody just runs out of the room and everyone just runs
Runs that was Trump. It's a great place. It's a great place. That's all I need to do
It's the only thing you need to know even the owner of this place is like a thousand milliseconds. He opened the table in
Five minutes, but he tried to pay and he gave me a good rating. Oh Amy
Are you messing with my slots? Did I win any money? I just won money. I just won like 300 bucks. Look no
I was there was a whole there was a line to do right? I think there was actually a line to do
I I'm doing one more $100 done. God damn it. Okay, no more. This place is turning into a dump that hit
It would have been like ten grand. I'm not playing that machine again
It's a piece of crap. I think was a piece of shit. It just was let's be honest. All right, it's clean
Alright claw game is literally free money. You know what? I had so much better
But I have six dollars now what can I just get my money back? Yeah, I'll buy I'll buy one dollar
Okay, I'll buy five dollars in Bitcoin. I don't want to buy a hundred and sixty thousand dollars in Bitcoin
I want to buy point zero zero zero zero zero zero zero. What I want by point zero zero zero zero zero
One why can't I zero point zero? What the hell? I have to buy doge. Okay. I have ten doge coin play for a while
Hey, you guys don't understand if doge coin goes to 450 million dollars. I'm gonna be a billionaire
Why does guys smell? Why does he smell he smells? Why does he see though? I smell I was speaking of smelling
I haven't taken a break yet. I don't know what that's supposed to mean, but I have to pee
I'll see if I'll be right back. It's pee time. Let him play. Wait, this pauses the game, right?
I'll be right back. BRB pee time. Oh, by the way, it's still Christmas
I like this Christmas thing by the way Bloor Dow is working on the winter one and it looks awesome
I can't wait to switch to it Christmas one more time. Why not one more for Christmas? Let's go you got dude flushed himself
Alright, let's go. We we're in the flushed away universe now fucking god damn it. I forgot my water
Give me a sec. All right complete refill. Let me turn this back up. He's got a full glass who does the songs Bloor Dow
He is a talented individual and he is currently working on four or five new tracks
Which is awesome and we should be very excited also a new winter themed BRB screen
Please package your pee and send it to me. No
I'm not gonna package my pee. Why did I read that? I don't know. I just I read the I read the weird shit
Okay, I'm sorry. That's the way it is
I'm all refueled. I did rock and roll ready to rock and roll. What was the last thing I was doing?
Fueled with he'll know not heal just regular water. Thank you for always reading the weird shit. Yeah, I know it
Just it stands out like a sore thumb. It really does. I did it. Okay trash can I need a trash can
I'm sorry for calling you the Ted Bundy of twitch that time. Yeah, sorry somebody just run out
This guy's been here for a long time. I just okay. I looked down. I was like, why do I have three dollars? I had four
Hundred like ten seconds ago. Why do I have only three fucking dollars?
How much is Dogecoin gonna hopefully the devs put it like a joke in the game or something where like Dogecoin goes like
Up like five million percent. I'm just gonna make sure that I always have like a hundred bucks in Doge in this game
Because they're probably gonna do that only you left. Okay. All right. Did I just break it?
Why is it this guy kicked me once what?
Everybody's paying without god. They both just left without use the bat. I just didn't it broke on his head
All right, if I gamble again, I'm gonna open it we're gonna clean up
I'm gonna open the store if if I gamble again, I'm gonna turn off the stream
Okay
Over the next 30 straight minutes over 30 minutes if I gamble again stream turns off. I am saving money
No more bullshit. No more gambling. Can we bet on that?
No, no, you don't have to bet on that. All right, how much is a bouncer?
I feel like a bouncer is gonna be more money than I'm even making I would have like
1500 I'd have at least a thousand dollars right now upgrade the punches on the way
They want extended time extended time the scratch ticket. God watches the stream ends in ten
It does not end in ten minutes. Don't you go and go up yet?
No room if you could do a voice for a cartoon what we do
I'll probably auto feel like Otto would be a fun voice to do for a cartoon. All right, 70 bucks at 80 bucks
That's really good. You smoke in here. I think I didn't even do anything
But I knew I mean he was he was creepily walking into the store, right?
I mean, that's not illegal, but it was up. It was a little odd. I mean that guy whatever, you know what I mean?
Hold my god. I have a lot of
Wait, did I punch this guy's neck backwards? I've re break it go chiropractor
All right. Now money's absolutely rolling in now. No gambling at all till at least 8 p.m. Pacific
You understand 8 o'clock Pacific. I'm not gambling a cent till at least then I need to okay
I need to warm it up a little bit in here. It's a little cold but the price is up a little bit
There we go. All right. I'm confident now. I'm good. What what do I need? What do I actually but maybe the
What are you what can I do for you? What do you want? What do you want? That's weird
I think it smells in here. Does it? Oh my goodness. It stinks in here. I have no cans empty
What does it smell like in here? I have to go buy a stink remover. Whatever it is buy some Bitcoin miners
We go crash into the computer. That's fine. Oops. Oh
It's cuz it's an old PC. Is that why this thing keeps doing this?
Give me a second man. The the fucking place is on fire. Okay, feel good. I'm ready sell the empty
Extinguisher and buy a new one. You're almost out. All right, you know, everybody just go home. Go home. Go go go
Get out of here. Go home. Take it
That was up. Oh my god. All right, electricity off everybody out. I'm going to sell the extinguisher
There's no electricity. So nobody who's gonna even go in there. Nobody cares. What can I sell this for? That's not bad
Can I buy one how much are they? All right, I definitely want to take it the whole place can't burn down
That would be awful. What about spray cam? Yeah. Okay. It's time to go to bed. Is the place closed?
Nobody can even do anything anyways, just close it up. They have a game close this up over here, right?
Yeah, and I call you know into the stream voice. He hates streaming
Let me get that out of your head real quick
Say that's not an end of the stream voice. I just haven't saved the game in like an hour and a half
Let me out the city getting more populated. I feel like there's more people here now. What what happened? Okay. Okay, they're okay, right, right
It smells it smells. All right
Let me buy another can of spray lean the place up and then I'm gonna buy an arcade machine and then we're gonna make a ton
Of money, I promise 15 bucks. All right, good to go. Oh the empty can leave me alone. Stop. Yeah, I did
Okay, there's a new quest as well. Um, let me go see what that is. Hey friend
I heard that electricity is constantly turning off these bastards are deliberately closing
The electricity to take bribes if you give me 200
I'll bribe those punks for you and they won't turn off the electricity ever again
I don't really care at this point takes two seconds to turn it back on. Hey, that's not worth $200 do it for the quest
I'll do it once I get an arcade machine, which let's take a look. How much are those? It's up by 5%
Alright, hold on to it arcade machine. That's not expensive. That's it
325 I got that right now. Alright, I got it. Why not? I'll do it. That's cheap
All right, where's that empty spray can no more bad reviews and then I'll do the perks
I've almost took a whole imagine spraying an entire can of Febreze in your house. That would be awful
It'd be worse than it's smelling bad more customers coming to the cafe
Let's do that customers are greeted with a pleasant conversation and may ask for extra time or punch two. Yeah
You're much better at handling the baseball bat because of your background baseball bats can break more easily. I don't know if I want that
I'll take this though
Please don't should I put this in the corner? I set a price price for this you will get to that
I hope how much is that computers?
Orders computers requests. Where is it? This thing is really janky. Yeah, but how do I just does it just work?
It's just auto pay. Oh, okay. Cool. Very very nice. That's better. These are sponge ball bubbles
They kind of look like it don't they I need a new bat too. Yeah, I'm out of bats
Okay, open 20 bucks should come back pretty quickly. I gotta run get a bat wicked quick wait
I don't have the money. Never mind. Never mind. Come on in. Yeah, the arcade machines facing the wrong way. What?
No, it isn't. It just looks like shit. That's why you think that it's $30 to use the arcade machine
Why did I buy any of this other crap? What was the point of me buying any of this?
I could have bought just three or four arcade machines and just let them just roll
It takes two seconds pays better the more expensive the arcade machine is I'm gonna get another one
Remember is it true that you draw on your eyebrows? Um, I'll neither confirm nor deny that statement
Oh
Viruses I'm just gonna pay for the monthly
Daily virus service thing. Thanks for that. Can I get a I said this earlier, but is there a barrel?
Can I get a barrel three thoughts on the earth's core?
We have no idea what it looks like we made up everything that we think is in the earth's core
Don't all run as one person
Help help protect your king protect your king protect your king. No, please why I need to hit you with a head
I can't even fight you though. Even I've got level two fist powers and I can't even do anything about it
Let me get you. Oh my god that guy's deck. I was about to walk away with a hundred and
$70 worth of game time that guy slept here overnight. That was a hotel room. Okay, don't leave without paying
I'm gonna say it once wait, you didn't okay. Good
300 bucks is an entire upgrade menu that you're ignoring this one here. Don't leave without paying. It's so annoying
I I clicked request on that guy. No, it's in the apps really employ data so you can find employees
All right, great program that allows you to use the computer more professionally
Minor device and then Spotify. All right. Well, we'll do this now that guy didn't pay either not gonna hit you
Okay, everyone's fucking I don't want to spend I gotta hire a bouncer
Immediately what? No, don't ignore the people punching me in the face though. Yep. Thanks for the thanks the search
I appreciate it. Yeah, forget about the people that are attacking me
Request coming in. How's it? Yes. I know I know I know I know let me guess you're not gonna pay
Shocker, it's so dirty in here. The arcade pays immediately
That's why I'm wondering my why do I even have any of these consoles or computers or anything?
What's the point they get the arcade cabinet?
It's not gonna get a virus and people aren't gonna walk away without paying they have to already have paid
I just sell them and just line the wall with cabinets. I'm paying it
No, you need variety. Okay money will start to actually really roll in here soon. I'll be good
Where's all this trash that I don't see I don't want to fight you but I will if I have to well
I don't like I might I don't know what that guy was doing. You're not gonna walk away with $77
I'm sorry, just max out the prices one people just leave. All right
625 dolls. I've got some new apps
Employees protect your shop from all kinds of attacks neutralize your enemies with a very fast reaction
This $300 for a day five day three, what's that mean?
I feel like I'm reading like the months of the year and stuff like EU. What does this mean? Oh bouncer
Nightmare thieves and non-paying customers $260 every three days. All right, where is he? Oh nice. All right
So he beats people up for me. That's awesome. Now. I don't have to worry about it. What else can I do a
mascot
Sure, is this stupid? Where's the mascot?
They are now everybody come on in come on come all and here
I just paid $200 the quest line is gonna go and my electricity will never turn off that leaves me with a grand total of
$15. Oh my god. He stole the TV. Oh my god. Get up. Yeah
Kick was insane. I'm back. I was worth it
That was definitely worth it without a doubt right to the back of the head to Wow. All right, cool
This doesn't doesn't seem to be working. How does it smell? It's not good. We're good
This thing was 600 plus dollars. Yeah, that would be so sad if I didn't see that come on in in the meantime
What are the other apps? All right, I hired some employees
It's minor average mining power not be reached. You could not be included in the network average mining power
I don't have enough power. Hey, I mean the chair probably radiates. I don't think I can clean the chair
So if they leave it out paying they get a roundhouse kick from that guy in the head. He's worth it
Request get rid of the panda. Did you pay? I don't think so. Oh, no, no, no. He did the arcade cabinet night
Yep, I can't clean this. It's just dirty. She gets more games. All right, how much money after I get paid another one or two times
He's quick too. All right. I like this guy. That's a good idea putting this near the door
I don't panic every time so if I put it near the door
Then I will see them play and then they'll leave and I won't freak out about it. I'm into that
Yeah, cuz see that when I see somebody run out it freaks me out put it over here
Come on. All right. Is it weird that I'm just gonna start hitting them in the head when I see them with bats
I they just may come in and do this like what am I supposed to do?
I need to have a bat just sitting right next to my desk clean up. We're still open
They're still an arcade machine that works guards will take care of them get this over here. Okay, put the table back
Maybe she got a new LCD. Although that thing was pretty good when I've got it though. I remember I got a decent one, right?
Hey, it's keyboard over here. Okay pain in the ass pain in the behind. Sorry. I'm just reading something upgrade the building
I don't you think I have money to upgrade the building. I have $400 to my name my cafe. Okay a fun place
That's good, but I have
$335 and you do no swears for 30 minutes. I could try it's possible
I could try it my cafe upgrade page new room a kitchen
Okay for a new room. I need 800 bucks. It's in is
1,400 that's not that bad actually old speakers. Oh tip box. I'm getting it. We got a lot of customers now
We good, but if I can't afford it out of the way, okay, I gotta move this
I can't I actually cannot leave right here is good. Okay right there for the desk in the back
This feels really weirdly high rotate your disk to aim towards the front
Oh, I see you mean so move that actually put the desk in a better spot. Okay
I don't think I can move this desk. I can't this desk is permanently here. It doesn't smell it's it's fine
It's a little dirty, but it's doesn't good work
Excellent job that guy would have got away with it to clean it up got
How much people tip usually is it more than a few dollars no it stinks. It's not dirty. What do you it doesn't oh shit
Okay, make sure you tip. Thanks. Let's go bingo more money more money more money more money
More money more money greedy. No, I'm keeping my prices fair. Nobody was saying dude
Jack your prices up like crazy, but I mean like a very expensive. I want repeat customers
I want good reviews you're gonna owe about five hundred dollars in a couple minutes
I am if I have it I couldn't run away, but high prices make people think it's worth more
That's actually like not is that like a crazy. That's I don't know that's so weird, but I think I've like I'm gonna do it
I can't change the front. I have to complete the setup first
Oh, it's cuz somebody's using it right now people buy iPhones. I don't even know why they still have an iPhone every year
I don't get it. I mean I do but I don't at the same time
You know I had the same exact theory about the same opinion on
Like the fact that they turned iPhones into like Madden games. I don't know all these companies just started releasing
Something every year. That's the same thing like every two years. We have to have this release
It's like why does the world all following the Madden formula? This is looking good. I'm thinking of buying a another
mmm
Did I get another arcade cabinet or should I buy another room? I feel like I don't need another room right now
I feel like I don't want another room. I won't see more people stealing stuff. I'm gonna stay small for now
Oh, you're done somebody else run out. You know what really solidified this to my brain
WWE the wrestling games they turned it into a yearly Madden game and my eyes were opened
Because that is the exact moment when those games started to becoming dog shit eyes
Just I was like that came out of the matrix. I was like holy shit very good. No gambling
I told you I wasn't gonna do it a new one had more time
Yeah, I I really hope that they learned and you know what I have said nothing nice and nothing good at all about the recent
WWE games or like what I think about the development of those games. I have said nothing nice
It's all been bad all of it
I will be happy if they actually took the couple three years here to make the new one and it's good if it's not good
If it's just as kind of bad and broken and shitty and backwards as the other ones
I don't even think I'm going to get it. I don't think I'm gonna you play it
I don't think I don't think it's gonna happen. It's been over 30 minutes. It has your rightless gamble
No, I'm kidding. They've been yearly since 2000. No, no, I don't think so. Well, here's the thing a
Bunch of companies used to make a bunch about these games
I don't know what happened and this pisses me off too. It was a time back before like 2008 2010
When more than one fucking company could make a video game based on a license, right? What happened was
Yeah, there'd be a WWE game or WWF game every year because like there would be three or four companies making these games
It'd be like three or four different studios making a WWF game
It would be three or four different football games three or four different baseball games
And now all these companies just have mega licenses that have lasted for the last 15 plus years
That they're just the only person that makes the game and nobody else can I was a big baseball
Fan back in the day baseball game fan
I remember MVP baseball was awesome
And then when they got the license taken away and they could never make a game like that ever again
They just said fuck it
We're never making a baseball game ever again and their games were so good the MVP baseball games were the best baseball games
No one comes close. Nobody comes even remote
No one comes close and they never will and they lost the license because of all the well
We're gonna get the exclusive baseball license to make a bunch of shitty baseball games in a row. And what's that? That's weird
It was 2k, right? Because it was it was the 2k baseball franchise because EA
Go
Wait a minute. Hold on. There's a fire everybody. Hold on. It was a license war, right? Well, you guys are gonna
Do the exclusive rights to football? We're gonna do the exclusive rights to baseball. Why is everything on fire yet? Don't sit down
I'm not done doing this yet. Is this still burning? What's what's burning? Something's still on fire. What is it?
Did I get it? Okay. Okay. So EA gets the exclusive licensing rights to Madden like forever, right and then 2k goes
Oh, yeah, we're gonna get exclusive rights to baseball and then make just like five terrible baseball games in a row
I was so mad when that happened. I was it was it was inconsolable MLB. The show is great though
Yeah, I know. I know the show is good
explainer Andy
That emo I he's laughing at tic-tacs again. I got tic-tacs up in the other monitor
I'm just laughing about him. Is it dirty? It is. All right
It's time to expand and turn into an arcade
Is it arcade time you made a comment about apples yesterday and said you didn't like honey crisp. Um, thank you
Good work. It's not that I don't like honey crisp. I just I don't I wouldn't buy them at the grocery store
I can't afford this yet. Um, maybe I'll buy another arcade cabinet. What about
It's not look so ugly. These are kind of cool. I like this one. Let's do this. Oh
Nice
He's about to run
He's going after somebody. How come you don't just go back to the old WWE game
So because that's a very specific question. I have a very specific answer. The old WWE games are
so slow
So slow it takes sometimes
10 to 20 30 plus seconds once you have too many layers on a wrestler like a creator wrestler
To load even moving an inch to the left some asset it was it's on PlayStation 3
Xbox 360 and all that shit. So it just it's on such old hardware that it just can't do it
It can't run I could technically do it
But it's just I thought he's running rabbit of the walls
I got new paint and now it doesn't look like we're inside of a bad public bathroom
You're a millionaire hire somebody to make a wrestling game for you. I think you severely
Underestimate how much it costs to make a 3d video game. No, no, no, no, no sit down sit down sit down
I'm just sitting on money sitting on my is it god. No, it's not over the console. Oh
It's okay, sir, I'll take care of that
Absolutely ridiculous that that happened. There's two free coke two free coupons to our go-kart track. Damn it get a higher somebody
I don't want to hire too many people
Or I blow all my money, I'm gonna polar bear fortnight dancing. Well
Actually is bringing in a lot of people
Way more people are coming here than were before I'm getting another arcade cabinet one of the nicer ones. What's a good one?
Defender let's get defender. Yeah, that's a three-star arcade machine. Nice. All right, get a trash can
Is that the problem? Is that why I've just been?
Permanently just being just sweep Andy. I broke that guy's neck an hour ago and it's still messed up. Oh, yeah
Um, hold on right here. Is that actually what happened? It's a gas pay. Thank you. Oh, thanks for the tip
Let's get a raid. We get a raid. All right. Oh, we did. Thank you sock pens for the raid
welcome sock pen lane internet cafe simulation
expense business
Simulator welcome everybody. How the are you? What do I have saved here? Whoa, man. What's this on the front page?
I just saw that it was on the go XLR. I didn't know what it was. How much is this one 50 bucks?
Maybe let's get another one. I do wait. I have to be able to pay these guys
I'll try to pay should I pay when when do these guys actually get paid? When does that happen?
You read us an analog clock real quick. Yeah, sure 819
There you go. When you hire them, they only last. Oh, okay. So I already paid for them. Okay, I get it makes sense
Makes sense. No. No, I was just I was trying to click it right now
You didn't even need to do that to that guy. Well, we had it was a complete misunderstanding
I just had to literally just go hey, I'm I'm I've just come here the room stinks the room
Does smell but alright, I got people working here. I'm just gonna go I'm gonna go buy a smell thingy
I'll be fine. I'm the only s3
Trump's just doing push-ups over there. Alright, we're fine trashcan, right? Right, right, right. Yes. Yes. Yes, but I do this is okay
I'm paying for this every day. What about the floor? Yeah, okay
I need to get a trash can and then I'm gonna make the floor a different color floor ice. Whoa
Okay there so I need what about an air conditioner? How much does this stuff cost? What's an air conditioner?
People keep complaining about the heat and stuff
People said wait, can I get a heater?
Or how does this work is it the air conditioner help because they like oh, it's so cold in here
This is doing I don't see a heater
Crashcan first. Yeah. Yeah. Yep. Yep keyboards lambs lamps
Housepad paintings desks TVs. Where is it? It works for both. All right, I'm gonna get it
I don't think there is a trash can. I don't see one. Is it like a service?
It's the cleaner way a male one of our security is neutralize a thief
Why are you even he's standing right next to me? All right, so let me buy this first
so if I go to
Like the employment
leaner
600 bucks that's so much. That's only for every three days. No, that's not worth it
Maybe it is maybe it is. I don't want anybody to steal that. There it is
Okay, so it doesn't matter where I put this put it like right up here
Press F to direct to adjust air conditioner temperature should I do auto air temperature adjusted automatically? Yeah
Okay, that's better back to clean. This is uh, yeah
And this is empty. I'm gonna throw all the empties over in the corner and everything I can use on the desk
Why is it so cold in here?
Didn't I just get this? Well, what are you doing? Oh shit my hitting it
I need another one of these now and maybe even another PC. This girl has been here for days
She you're right, she actually has been here for do I mean I can't what is she doing?
Why is she has just been squaring up for a week what's going on?
Okay, I was just checking to see if she was squaring me up or if you're squaring up the bouncer. What do you want?
What's the problem? Need a mascot back? You're right. Hold on. Let me clean right? Let me get cleaned up
All right, that's clean clean it up. I do it the mascots right here. Stop him. Stop him. Stop this guy. Stop this guy
No, all right. I'm sorry. There was a criminal in here
Where's the go you stole the computer out of that underneath the way the guy was sitting? I'm still not gonna buy that
That's not worth it the floor the floor the floor
I'll wait that somebody wants to that ask God's bring it in too many people. I can't even do it fire extinguisher wait
I'm getting overwhelmed. Hold on. I'm getting overwhelmed. Don't overwhelm me
We're doing research like to the length of your arm from your fingertip to your shoulder. All right
What how the fuck am I gonna measure that? I don't know one foot like two maybe like three feet
Said from the my shoulder to my fingertip around on three feet. I have no idea
Floor right floor floor floor floor. Oh
Smokey what a fucking idiot. I shouldn't I should have waited at least a second. That looks worse than the other one
How is that different? This looks worse. I would love to take your money. Well, this one the orangutan
Guy watching porn. Yeah, the people watch porn in here all the time. There's nothing
I can't really do much about it if I'm honest. Hey, dude, did you find those arcade machines in the river?
No, speaking of arcade machines. I'm gonna go for another one
They're just really really bananas bananas bananas strawberries. Oh
Yes. All right. We're good. One more beaches bananas strawberries. Okay, I'm done. I got requests get on here
Check on your doge coin. Good idea. Where is it? All right here crypto. How many do I have?
How many do I have I wanted to sell five not whatever there's no Oh fire extinguisher. Yeah, I said before eight
It's 830 right now. I went well past that I got the bouncer
I thought he was just had enough for her once and for all and was just gonna drop her
Got McDonald's colors in your shop
You can't I um speaking of McDonald's what speaking of McDonald's? I've updated my McDonald's order
One of my mods said he got my old McDonald's order and he said he like a diarrhea
I was like man, what do you what are you talking about? I think that's a shit
Yeah, you know, you're eating all the shareables. What are you talking about? Those of you that don't know
I have a crazy McDonald's order where it's like three sandwiches like nuggets and the whole point is it's a
Some of those items are to be shared and he said he said he was like diarrhea or something
So I was like, all right
let me update the order for you my new McDonald's order that I get almost every time now is
Two double cheeseburgers ten piece nugget and a powerade and those are not necessarily to be shared. Sometimes they are
That's a lot of money. He's like dude. I ate that McDonald's order. You were talking about man
I struggled to get through it. I'm like wait you ate the whole thing by yourself. What about the shareables?
He's like shareables. What are you talking about?
No, you I always order it a ten-piece nugget and maybe like an extra burger or so just for anybody that wants it
Just because I like wouldn't I don't know
But I know I come if I go to eat and people like happy and like eating and stuff
It's like, oh, yeah
I got sake a ten-piece nugget to have anybody have one if you want them because nobody wants to order nuggets
Right the ten-piece nugget meal and even like a five-piece nugget with a good drink
Never seems like enough. So I take that away from the person. I make it so they don't have to make that decision. So oh
Dude, I really would love nuggets. They're up where they're available man. They're just here in my opinion in my
Experience most people don't want to just have nuggets and fries
Like a five-piece nugget is an add-on to a lot of people's meals. I'm like, let me take that out of your hands
I got it much money. Well, hell yeah, I think it's time for another arcade cabinet
Last arcade cabinet is the final one after this cabinet comes in
I'm gonna just coast until I can buy the room upgrade. What's the best one here? This one of these is good
Maybe this one we have to have variety right? I'll get this one and I'll buy another steam game
If you like this Shrek one, alright, let's coast nice like your portfolio balancing crypto
Okay, portfolio dogecoin
Alright, how many do I have 15?
Sell nice I made four dollars. Actually, I made like 30 cents
The trash can there's no such thing as a trash can in this game
This is actually the last thing I can probably do before I upgrade the building. I'm running out of room
This is straight up 90
Yeah, this is 90 bucks. I'd say every pretty much every hour
We got 90 bucks here in the arcade cabinets. The next thing I promise the next thing I do will be
A cleaning upgrade update the floor. I already did. It's a different floor. Just looks like shit. I'm sorry
Holy shit. I haven't saved the game in a long time. You're right
You are right. If it's the same floor, then why did it cost $200 to put down here? Where's the rest of this dirt?
Don't get scared. He ran off
Excuse me. Oh, I'm sorry that there was a guy that ran in here
The arcade machine is nice and clean ready for you. Maybe I should get a better PC now. No stick to the plan
Customers running away without paying is reduced. You may ask for extra time. What else we got?
You're known around because of your old history and thieves don't come to your shop much
Stamina, what else we have? Let me see if it's all the way down. I don't really care that much about this
stamina boxing
I have the bouncer
Body what's all the way at least don't suspect you and I had all the physical stuff. I don't really care about
Put it down put it down put it down put it down. Where's the extinguisher? Hey
Alright, um, I think I'm just gonna keep doing the cafe stuff. That feels like the best idea this one
extra time
Tipbox people leave more money in the tip box. Oh, yeah. Nice. That's good up rushing
I do need to say alright, so I gotta close close up the shop. Well, I've seen people wishing for a crash
Yeah, we're officially closed
Save the game
It's out of context I
Can't I don't want to alt-tab right now, but on the auto context where it's something funny. All right, get him
We're closed. I don't think about it close it up. Now. How do I tell them to go home?
Really just stay and protect this place. Most people have said your store is the same as it was hours ago
You're better than this. I I think it's changed pretty drastically. I've got three arcade cabinets
I'm about to do a second floor or a second. Um, second room. That's the next thing we're doing
Yeah, yeah, I tried to punch the pan in the face. Yeah, I did. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah go back and finish the job
I'm good. Priority is to get a new room. We're gonna have an arcade
Cabinet room besides the arcade cabinet room is gonna be a console room or like the yeah
We're gonna set we're gonna split it up. I got a plan. Don't worry
At least I hope I do you can go to the club now. I can go to the club. You're right
Is it us? Is it us? There's slot machines in there. Oh nice. I'm to get a second room. Okay. Hmm
Did I do now I'm gonna do this first. I have enough to buy it. I got 900 bucks my cafe new room
I officially have a new room. Is it just here? It's just it made them. This is made a little longer
Well, I guess I'll put these back here. All right, it's we're closed these two are going in the back
That's the easiest way to do it. Hey, they should be able to fit back to back, right?
I'm gonna put this up here right in the middle auto adjust. Please get a new chair. Yeah, I have this
I do have this plastic lawn chair. You're right. I'll do that in a second, too
I'll take you that's much better that wait. Is that the wrong way?
It's a huge improvement
It really is but just I took me so long to be able to comfortably pay $800
And maybe some if you if you're new to the channel
one of the things you have to kind of keep in mind is if
If it takes an hour to do something in a game, you need to add in brackets like two hours
So it takes three hours. I get to do I get so distracted
I'm like the most distractible person probably in the world
let's get another chair and
Get two more chairs. So we'll all let's have these with those. That's I got enough money, right? I think no
I don't I don't have any money. Let's do it later bombs
Am I ever gonna see a return on this ever? That's a huge improvement though. It really is. Wait, what'd you say?
XQC spent two full hours gambling until he had zero without ever setting up his cafe, and then he quit the game
Oh
My streamer
Alright, let's go clean up. I gotta buy a different mouse. This just looks like a bar of dirty soap. That's good
I need a second chair. This is ugly. It needs to be changed. How about just like right here like along this wall
This gives fun. Oh, what's wrong?
Why can I put this here far? Yeah, I need a lamp. I mean the light the light the light. Oh, oh
All right, how come you're creating an arcade in a crack den? I don't know it's fun
Hey, I think I'm ready to open the place. I have enough we can just coast for a little bit
I only I don't have any money electricity needs to be it's on right? Yep. All right back in business. Let's go
This is kind of nice. Look at three or four more arcade cabinets down here upgraded
Maybe get a kitchen eventually here in the next like half hour. Probably get a new floor. It's clean
It smells good in here. I think it does this empty. No, it's a more light. So it looks bigger
What do these other let me see what they look like? I haven't paid my bills in like a month
Street audio, I don't know. I don't know. What do you mean? We're fine
We get you have $40 to your name right now, but I have a
Income stream here. That's about to probably get pretty good. Wait new quest. Do there's a big fight
Can you bring me three baseball bats? I'm just gonna buy them. Is that okay? Thanks
Okay, do I have enough to buy three bats because I probably get some money from this. It's forty four eight
Okay, one more person leaving and I should be good to go. I'm gonna read the reviews. Oh good idea the
Okay. Oh, what do I want to do here? What was I gonna do? Crash can is in the cafe upgrades
Is it really kitchen toilet upstairs upstairs? I don't see anything hot dog cart sliding doors speakers
regular alarm POS device
He's a shit device. I don't suppose it. Oh, I need to read my reviews. All right, let's read the reviews
Great place to experience the life of Eskimos. It's so cold. I ran away immediately
Don't I have it on the auto temperature? Why is it doing that?
It's so cold in here. It's like the Eskimos
Except for the times when it's a fire every ten minutes
Did you just write that review is that you that wrote that
Isn't this on auto? Oh, what what temperature do you want it?
Thanks the tip one more time. All right, buy a backpack when you can afford it. You can store items in your bag
Oh, that's so much better. That's like a hundred thousand times better
My dog vomited when I turned on your stream. Hopefully, okay into private mission. I know a better place
There are games of the last quality. However, they don't open computers shit like shit
I need new PCs or something. I don't know a new computer. How much is a decent PC?
Computers or are they? Thank you. What about VR chef a VR room? Oh, it's cases, right? Okay fast computer
About okay. What about this one? This is a decent computer get it. I'll sell the other one right now
Buy more CS go cases. I was a big fan of this game to be watching. I used to watch this channel
I really hate to do this to you. But what can I get for this computer under dollars? Wait, I need something else for me
Don't I do I I've been one of these cool. No, that's way too expensive crazy. Oh, that's right
Um, where is let's track him down. I need to be here for this because this is a delivery
I'll just store them in here. Alright, that's much better better computer better reviews. There we go. Alright, you can play better games
I'll buy a new game now, too. Let's get let's see. What should I get helmet boy?
Is this a porn game? I mean the porn stuff is popular
I'm not gonna deny the I mean look at how many people have come in and just started watching porn if I get a porn game
I think they're gonna play it a lot. That's so weird. It's not no, it's not weird. It's business. This is business
Better. All right. Nice. You turn the computer away so we don't just see the porn
I'll tell you when it's coming just close your eyes. Okay, how much money do I have?
What is the next cool upgrade we can do I can do a kitchen a bathroom is 1300
Upstairs is 2400. Probably a kitchen, right? That seems like the logical point of sale is self-checkout
Mmm, that's not a bad idea floor for the love of God. All right, fine. I'll get a new floor right now floor
How about this one? This one's blue. This one's nice. But this one this one's very neutral. It's fine. I like this one
This one's very neutral. I just look so bad. This is not blue
Oh
How does it look like this
How come it's all beat up looking? Do I have to clean it somehow or do I have to what do I have to do?
But why is this ugly?
Okay. Okay new floor. I spent 400 bucks on these floors. No, I could have bought another arcade cabinet
Where you on? I swear to God these are about how cold it is. Please warm the inside. I want to be warm
How do I make it so it doesn't smell? Is it even turned on? Was it I don't was it not turned on?
All right, like shit, all right, I'm running out of okay to get so dirty auto does not work and it wasn't turned on so
Okay more arcade machines. Okay. Those were right. The next step is gonna be should the next step be you want more time?
All right in the arcade machines. I don't think I don't think I can clean them. All right, let's go. Please warm. Please warm
Use the mop. I need nicer arcade machines, please. I'm begging you get a nicer trash
Where's my mop? Oh, I need to get spray
Getting spray and I need another fire extinguisher. Your AC is not even on it's not that no that that's on
Oh, how should it be? This isn't do anything just sliding door. Maybe shortly. You need a door for the AC to work
Are you kidding me? What's the cheapest door I can get? No, it's in the other menu. Hey items. It's
$1,200
$1,260 for this
What the fuck is going on?
Why is it not on green means off? No red means off
Green means go green means on green. It's on red off AC and heater
Yeah, they're the same thing 27 is way too hot. That's 80 degrees
Shit, how's that? All right, that's just blaring a heater
Non-stop up to 80 degrees. You have it set and you have your just front door wide open
Smart scan completed. All right. Now that I have a second here
I'm gonna give this bat to the guy and go get another one. Where is he? Is it this guy right here?
Uh-huh. Isn't it you it's not you you need to hold three in the backpack. Okay, so I need the backpack, right?
Good. I got almost a thousand bucks. I got the employee app. Maybe yeah, let's try that. Please guard cleaner
I could do cleaner, but I'm finally broke a thousand dollars the first time. I'm doing it. It's speakers
I'm so glad they can't do they just get just stomped when they come in
When they go out, I don't have to do anything. It's awesome. I don't have to worry about it
I like cold place didn't bother me a little cold. It's a little cold inside
How is that? I don't you sleep the AC will work. The AC is bugged. Okay, is that what I mean?
It's that's like hot. Oh shit. That's just freaks. I had no idea what that thing was. Oh, all right
All right. I'm gonna save it after these people are gone. I'm gonna close it up and save
Priority tomorrow in the game is to get point of sale
You know how hot 27 Celsius is now I go by Fahrenheit shit, I missed it
Or I got the trash gone now. I need a door and
A point of sale who just got punched. I don't know and going to bed. Good night. Thanks for the stream
See you next time. Hey, see you next time
27 is warm. All right, uh
Try gamble for a minute just for a minute
Not this not the slot machine. I'm talking like it's a CS go skin. I'm doing it. Oh
It's what well a regular knife one more. That's it. I'm never doing it again. I promise I'm doing it
I got my money back doing it one more time. All right, I'm done. I'm not doing it again. No speakers
I have a huge money stream. I'm fine. Yeah. All right, everybody out. I'm closed. Thanks for coming
I appreciate the business and everything but that's it. This thing is bugged. Thank you
Have a great day
Appreciate it. Have a wonderful rest of your evening. Sores closed. Okay, save the game. I'm gonna come back
They somebody said was bugged. They trapped somebody in there. I need to buy speakers. Yeah, I'll get speakers
Slots can actually get you a bonus. That's worth several thousand dollars. It's actually not bad to do it
Yeah, you got to hit it though. You actually have to hit it save and then gamble. No, I got a plan
I we talked about it already. I already know what I want
Just gamble on fruit slots with a really low bet and just do it a bunch because the bonus can pay a lot
I have a tuber voice right now
Yeah, all right. What you just did is you just told you just did the manual breathing thing to me
Like hey, dude, you're manually breathing. It's just a god. Damn it. Am I shit?
By gambling upgrades you just did that to 18,000 people not what I'm just saying
Saying that to me is the equivalent of the manual breathing thing
I think you guys had it wrong cuz listen I can hear air coming up. I think this is on
See that's on yeah, it's definitely on. Okay, let's do this now
400 bucks I do anything else in the meantime. I'm not doing that again. I forget about the chairs. Yeah, I'll get some chairs
I think I I don't know what this is, but maybe I'll get it back with the thermometer. Yeah, where is the thermometer?
It's finally on from 15 to 17 Celsius. Finally, you know speaker is how much are they or 90?
I'll probably get it in a minute. I could do some claw machine as well. Oh this guy
Can I give it to him one sec? Yeah the fucking way. Where is he there? I hand this in. Yeah, you're right
I gotta have to be able to carry three. Oh
Activate them 62 degrees is freezing. Is that what 17 is? I do need a spray can it probably smells in here
Yeah, it's definitely stinks in here. 17 is not freezing. Yeah freezing is zero one. Good stop. Thank you
Yeah, thank you. How much is backpack be 21 or 22? Okay, I'll do 22
I like it a little warm. I activate this guy's computer and then go get a backpack. I turn it off
I see this one star up there. Can you get more than one star?
But it did can the can you get like a chase by the police and everything? I keep seeing one star
All right backpack or 75,000. I don't have that much money. I get this one. All right build
Am I doing what do I put this? Oh, okay. Very cool. I do anything else in the cafe list probably this one
I mean, I might as well just buy it. All right, how do I get one more point?
I just punch somebody didn't get a point. What's the point if you have a bouncer? That's a good. Yeah, that's true
Exactly. See what's the point? What if what's the very very end of like the cafe list your knowledge of mining equipment is increased
You can now buy more mining devices and then sometimes in the casino
You have the possibility of getting back the bet you lost that's actually huge. I'll get this one. I
Could get extra luck in gambling. Are you serious? I need the point. Yeah, I'll get that's true
but I just bought the backpack, so what has more priority door or
Point of sale I'm gonna say point of sale this door really that much more important. I have a
Bouncer. Yeah point of sale is way more important. The bouncer is just roundhouse kicking people in the fucking head and we're good
I think we're good. I think we're good
The only thing I have to worry about is the is the people that run it and just throw like an explosion in here
Yeah, get the Pete get yeah, I'm getting point of sale. So I cuz I'm so bad and so ADHD about actually
Taking money from people and stuff. So, oh
Okay, that's uh, should be good. How do I use this? What can I do this with?
Fun place. I like cold places. I like it cold even the owner of this place is he open. Yeah, whatever. It's cold
It's cold. It's cold. It's cold. It's cold. Nothing to do about it. It's for the Bitcoin stuff
Oh, you see I need the point of sale so bad. He's gonna get kicked in the head and that's not even his fault door idiot
I'm going to try I have to pick it
The door is 1200 I'm getting point of sale right now. Where is it insufficient?
Why that I just had enough I want to say we'll get you more money. Yeah, I keep missing it
Oh, maybe I will just say for the door. I think
Door friends I think are out out voting the piece of shit friends. You play Nancy Drew ever again
No, I can't I'm not gonna say I'm gonna deny ever playing Nancy Drew ever again. Why wouldn't I it's pretty fun
Would you say is it unreasonable to make my Mayo have a little bit of crunch?
No, man, whatever people dip their french fries in Mayo. I said it's an English thing, right?
Almost there almost time for the door
Nasty really my point of sale. I don't I'm not even collecting people's money
My point of sale is the bottom of my bouncer's shoe. I feel like that's
That's kind of fucked up. I feel like crunchy Mayo actually would be kind of good
Okay, this crunchy peanut butter what if there was crunchy Mayo, how would that even work? Is that disgusting? That's too far
That's yeah, that's a little gross. You're right. It's eggshells. Oh
What the fuck you want more time? No, you good. I could go for an egg salad sandwich right now
I've been like for five hours. I have not even been paying that much attention to that
Fresh egg salad sandwich is is up there pretty high with everything else spicy mayo is good
Will you hurry up and get off the computer and see again now she's gonna get kicked
People's reviews they would start to write this hey make sure you give the guy the counter a little bit more time because
If you don't if you leave without paying cuz he won't take your money you get your ass kicked outside
Almost there. I'll have it tomorrow
We're just like leave it on the table, I don't know leave the money on the table
Save the game close up. I'll be able to get a door tomorrow. Hooray. Wow $1,200 for a fucking door
Good night defender. Good night. Gallagher. Good night game box. Good night PlayStation 1
Sorry, good night bouncer. Good night piggy
Yeah, say good night to the panda. I did didn't I good night. I tell doors number one priority
I really shouldn't have even got the backpack. It was 500 bucks that I didn't need to spend us to ha ha ha
That was a cool relatable streamer
Yeah, I know I know isn't very good
Complete the bat quest with the backpack can I though I guess I could hold one in my hand and then two
Wait, let me do that now then. Oh, I can you're right. All right. No, I'm corrected
You're right one more bat right over here somewhere. Nice. All right, I get money for this
That'd be great because then I can put the door in immediately and I'm sorry, but I don't have money to give you right now
But don't worry. I'll make it up dude
There's an internet cafe owner in the city who doesn't listen to my word
Everyone in this city listens to my word what I'm asking you to do is place this bugging device under his desk
It's located on the second floor of the building where you live
It's the bug behind the rival internet cafe table. Oh wait. It's where I live is a rival internet cafe
I'm gonna need one of these so this is what this is what the second floor is then okay
I'm gonna play VR chat together. I want to show you my spongebob avatar
Um, I don't really I don't really do VR too much one hour for free. Let's see what you are. This is your little
Nice, would you get those computers from? Hey, those the computers they still use at the bank by the way. Hi, jerma985 here
I run a different uh operating business down the street. How are you? Did I miss or can I not?
Smash it up. I don't think I can do oh wait. You got all this over here. Hey
All right, I bugged it his floor sucks way worse than mine. Why are you guys talking so much shit? Where's that guy?
There you are 400 bucks. Hell. Yeah, I was worth it. It's time for a door. Let's go you play monster hunter rise
Nah, I don't think so
I played a shitload of monster hunter world and finished the game
I beat the game and I kind of did a little bit of the extra stuff and kind of kept going but
Mmm, I got my fellow monster monster hunter. It's fun. What's the best iPad game?
The room series and if you've never played it before let me just you got so much to work with
They have like five games in the series and they're all so much fun. It's just like a relaxing
Tinkering puzzle game get the room get the whole series. That's by far the best iPad game
Just to play in bed for sure. All right door automatic sliding door. It's glorious looking
Finally nice this fall. I'll do 20 22. What about the Outer Wilds DLC?
Mmm, probably not. Why would this even light on fire? No one's even using it. Outer Wilds was fun
But oh no, this is a disaster
Thank God I had just enough I gotta go now and get another one
Outer Wilds was a fun game, but the problem with it was I've heard the DLC is really not necessarily confusing but
Very specific and it could take a lot of time. I probably don't think I'll be into it. That game was really cool
I just not sure I'd be able to do the DLC very well. It's very cryptic. Yeah, we don't do high functioning brain
Games on this stream very often. I'm just so distractible. I'm so all over the place. All right, that's another one of these
Okay, next step is the point of sale and then after that is the kitchen the temperature. Yeah good idea play it off stream
Yeah, I probably will a little warm money. Oh, right ceiling. I bet I do. I don't have enough money for it
All right, seems pretty good chair is actually no no chair. You're right. I need a chair
Is the room both trapped over here? You just opened at 6 p.m. Yeah, it's a night place
We that's the people that can come hang out and have drinks and shit, man
Come on in the meantime, I'm definitely gonna play some of these little casino games. All right games, which is my favorite one
I liked this one. I like the claw machine only turn this shit on first one
Nobody else at what bias of work in progress. We'll get more soon. Just make sure these people are happy seem to be happy
Let's go right down the middle. Give me all that shit. Nice right here. Somebody said this one is actually free money
There's blackjack. Hold on. You know, is there blackjack where this blackjack in the club? What?
Really? All right. I'm gonna I'm gonna cash this out after today. I'll go play it. All right cash
So I know you want I gotta get that point of sale man. You're gonna get you're about to get you like your head punched in
That's so bad. And then whatever who's playing the fucking piano. That's not coming from me
You need to upgrade the gambling. That's yeah, I'll have it by the time I go to the club. Maybe not
No, I won't you buy a hookah. Um, that's a good question. I don't know
500 bucks I want at least 500 bucks for the casino. All right, I caved kind of sounds like a I just keep falling
Freestyle I have nothing to freeze. I have nothing to rap about I can't it's so stinky in here
I'll take care of it. All right, wait, think I pay, you know, that's it
I wish I could buy an automatic air freshener. That'd be great. Should we gonna change songs?
I know it's kind of reminds me of every song on tik-tok
So then you know awful just pick up I'm gonna leave it on a little warm in here. This one's kind of scary
Yeah, or oh nice a seven dollar tip. Nice. Thanks, man. There's 70 cents. No seven bucks
I need more PCs. Well, I keep buying all this stuff instead of upgrading when I bought a door
I bought a floor a ceiling
I've spent like three grand instead of buying new I gotta buy new stuff go to the club. All right, let's go to the club
Why not? Let's go for it. I'm curious. It's a perfect amount of payment. I'm taking that right to the club
Let's close up for the night. It's 7 a.m. Oh
Man, I really want to go to the club. All right, nice. What we got in here. Ooh
Bob can't interact with that guy. That's bad dancing. Although how is that really any different than what they're doing right now?
All right, what can I do? Oh
slot machine
Wait a hundred hundred dollars in here. What I don't want to do that
Okay, how much money we have left? I get a drink go into the back room
I just held Q to try to peek around the corner cuz I was scared. What is this?
Let me get up there with you, man
I'm not sure how many people go into like a nightclub strip club and they do the twist. That's a
Oh
That's kind of a little old-school
Everybody's doing it. Is it in is it back in or something? I don't get it. All right another hundred dollars right here
I've done. What was that rigged bullshit? What what?
Alright, let's go. Hey you boss sucks. Oh, there's five hundred dollars. I can't get back. I want to send you home
You've been working so hard. I just like send I send you back home with a bonus or something
You've been doing so much work, you know
I have to know electricity
The reason why I keep punching every single one of these these guys is because they keep like bombing the cafe
So I just I am it's punch on sight. It's the way it is. There was blackjack in there. Where was it?
I didn't see it anywhere these Goldilocks motherfuckers. I swear to God. How hot is it? What wait?
Why is it so hot over here the PCs and the AC on it is on
You're cooking them alive you need two AC's of course I do I can't really take this anymore
How do I turn it off? Okay. I don't want to hear the music anymore
Oh, they like it here and on the AC half of us think the AC is off and half of us think the AC is on
Which one is it? Um, listen listen closely ready you hear the
It's on holy shit. I'm so glad that missed I did not mean to do that. Wait
I mean I should have done that that guy tried to pay with a okay. They try okay. Yeah
Schrodinger is an air conditioner explain a great place. Hey, thanks for the review. Appreciate it. I need a chef
kitchens next priority, which it's
1,400 it's 1,400 for a kitchen 1,300 for a toilet. I'm gonna go for it with this do 1,400
We're kitchen click on auto and see what color it turns. Oh
Would you look at that?
Now all the naysayers and all the people
Half of them just rage quit the stream. They were just pissed that they would that they were wrong and they just rage quit
How do you pronounce Worcestershire sauce like that or arcade machines? Yep, you know what fuck it. Let's get one right now
I mean screw it another one of these guys. Yeah. Yeah, let's double it up. You get more money piece of shit idiot point of sale
All right, can you explain how an investment account works, please? I'm not a financial advisor. I don't know
I'll put this one just right next to it. Maybe right here. So it kind of clean it cleans it up a little nice
And it puts add some more risk to my Roth IRA. I don't know that's a conversation for you and your advisor
Not for me. I have no idea take it
Take it, please. Don't hurt this guy. Okay, suppose diet. Um
I'll beer cheese people actually started like this place and sell that mop. That's right. Yeah, when are you gonna play cube of war?
I don't know. Maybe I'll play cube of war when the game cube physical copy is not like 500 bucks
But you're a millionaire. No, this thing's not even worth anything. I can't even sell this
Why would you want to sell them off? You said that about paper Mario? Yeah, I did
I did say that about paper Mario. I did say that about paper Mario, but then I realized that paper Mario is
Like 50 hours long. Oh mop up and blackjack could try
You want to go try to mop up and blackjack? All right, where is it? I didn't see it in the club
Where was it? Did you miss the table behind the bar? I don't know. I was running out
I was doing this like stupid dance thing. I'm gonna wait for these two guys to be on clothes store. It's behind the bar
All right. I'm going back today store closes after these people come in. I do own the backpack. Yes. What's the longest word, you know?
Um, I'm on up here. Thank you longest word
I mean you can't really count. No, you can't I was gonna say you can't count supercalifragilisticexpialidocious
That's a fake word. All right, close up. Let's go play blackjack and I'm gonna let's see if I can get to a couple grand
We are closed
All right. I got money. I'm ready to play blackjack
Here comes like a funny gambling joke. Ha ha ha no, I actually like want to play it. I like really do
I don't even know why I did that. Oh shit. He's chasing me now. He's still after me
Okay, it's I'm driving around the circle. Oh
Where the hell oh, it's over here. I think I lost the guy. All right, what's up? That's still chasing me right now
Okay. All right blackjack behind the bar. I didn't even see this room. All right. Here we go. Nice
Elvin is really intimidating. This is a kind of is a table. You don't walk up to with a bunch of crumpled up 20s
Uh
Gentlemen, how are we ten versus seven? You're you're already you're already just fucking screwing me here
Seventeen versus twenty it's over
All right. We're good. That's pretty good
Again, let's do it again
We've blackjack thirteen verse seven. Hey, give me give me free card. There it is. See you later
100 bucks. All right. Now we get cocky. Okay
Okay, there it is eight verse. I got fives. We're gonna see if we can get a ten here. It's bad. That's okay
Take it again. Very good. Let's fucking go. Come on. Oh shit. He's got blackjack under there, don't he?
That is
Absolute horse shit. You all know it but do you like it's blackjack on that hand?
Not ever never never and you stand on 15
You stand on against a five like that. I'm coming back
Bingo done. It's all right. I checked. Oh, fuck you
Fuck all of you. Not you guys these guys with suits on I got so screwed. That's you all know it
Just give me the safe. I got absolutely decimated
That blackjack dealer blackjack such bullshit dealer should even be allowed to get blackjack in this game
That's so dumb. Give me a break. No, I'm not done
Seventeen versus twenty give me a break. I can turn this around
13 over 7 get the free card. There it is 20. All right climbing back. Let's go for a 50 here at 9 bullshit
We're gonna you get that you're gonna be 19. It's gonna be draw. Great. All right again do it again
16 stay against a 5 don't ever hit this. That's exactly why I
Would have just taken that card and I would have busted. Do you get it 100 bucks? Oh, please. Oh my god
Oh my god, what is this table? I think they got shit face dealing. Of course he is
Right. Oh my god. I just like angrily almost just like punched you. I'll be back and I'm getting my revenge
I'm gonna get my monetary revenge. Let me make that very clear to the three of you monetary revenge
I'm gonna come back and make money. I'm not gonna hurt anybody
monetary revenge
That thousand dollar bet that was a big that was a big bet too
Anything other than 20 I had 18 if anything other than 21, of course the dealer hits blackjack on that hand
It didn't happen any other time that sucks. That's so annoying
Man, it's the Mafia City guy. Yeah, I will be back there with another 500 bucks. It's always a possibility
That's why you don't go all-in
Well, you go all-in every single time and you just win three hands and you never play ever again
Come on in you do a 500 all hand you win 500 bucks
You do a thousand dollar hand you win a thousand bucks. You do a two thousand dollar hand
You win four thousand dollars you just and then you get up and fucking leave and then you do and then you start you then
You go to like those machines that you can do literally one penny for the middle line
And you just spend those for an hour just drink booze. You just did you sit there for like four hours and do that
Don't take this advice by the way. No, absolutely do not in fact get don't ever gamble unless it's like unless you just don't give a shit
Right gambling is always a lose scenario. No matter what even if you win
It's always a lose scenario gambling is entertainment and if it's treated like anything else
It's not gonna happen if you are comfortable and you're in a financial position
To go blow three or four hundred dollars at a casino
Okay, right
but if you go to a casino and you take a thousand bucks there or a hundred bucks five hundred bucks and you're like man I
Can't wait to sit down and make two grand duck. Nope
Don't ever say that you are gonna lose every single time when you walk in the door
Pretend that your money just turned into Monopoly money because it doesn't exist anymore
You bring a certain amount of money into the casino that turns into Monopoly money, and that's it
This is why I lost ten thousand dollars. I
Did not lose ten thousand dollars at a casino
Always put a limit on how much you know, but yeah exactly it can be fun
Just don't go overboard
As long as you know exactly what you're willing to kind of play with and just hang out with
I've had a lot of good times just kind of sitting around a blackjack table
Just doing you know playing five to ten thousand dollar hands. You know, I mean, I've never done I'm kidding fucking Jesus Christ
Please don't think that serious. I'm I'm actually kidding. I'm not please
Stop people sweating. What do you want me to do?
Yeah, it's the best practice you can do is if you're gonna spend if you're gonna spend
$100 $50
Wait, he's be he's trapped. Why is he trapped? He's trying to go after somebody what happened? Why is he trapped?
What did you just do that to just do this with animal did a cat steal money out of the register?
What was that also play games out of slow too? You don't want to don't play games that take a second
roulette's fun because you can do really kind of low bets and roulette takes a while for it to happen and
Roulette is just throwing coins in the air and like who cares right need more of this
Blackjack is a bit blackjack is one of the best games with the least house edge and what the house edge means is that's ever
It's a it's a percentage right and it's based on for every hundred dollars that comes into the casino a certain percentage is
Guaranteed to go back to the house stuff like blackjack only has I think like less than a 5% house edge
slot machines have
Anywhere between like a 10 to 24 percent or so house edge, right?
So that just means that it's guaranteed that for every hundred dollars or for every dollar that comes in
24 cents is always gonna be lost at the casino now. That's over time right that's over a long period of time and
Over a year sure if somebody could hit a million dollar jackpot
But four million dollars came into the casino right over the course of a day or a week or a month or something
You're always out to lose is what I'm saying like they're
The casino likes it when you win because that means you're gonna play more and I'll tell you the itch hits you
Especially kick that guy in the head the itch hits you
Especially especially when if you go to a casino and you're with a bunch of friends and you're hanging out
You're having a good time and you hit on a slot machine or something within the first 10 seconds
Are you getting there right you walk in? Oh, this is great
I guess I'll play this one and you've been there for 10 minutes and you hit like a hundred and fifty dollars on the machine
It's like holy shit, this is fucking amazing. This is awesome. This is so much money, right?
Are you just gonna leave are you all right? That's it guys
We plan we plan on having a night out for like at least the next four to six hours. I'm gonna go home
I'm going back to my hotel room. No people stick around you hang out. You stay you're not just gonna leave
So you just have to make sure you pace yourself
Don't go crazy. Don't spend more than you want to lose
But you're gonna play right as long as that's what you look people go to the casino
And they don't have any intention of gambling. They just watch their fucking idiot friends lose all their money, right? You can be that guy
You can walk around with with the beer in your hand or like the glass of wine or the cocktail and just be like oh
So hey, how you doing? Oh you down 80 bucks. Oh
This was eight bucks, and I'm just gonna sip it for the next hour
Back to blackjack. What do you think I'm doing? I'm building up a bankroll. I'm gonna do a thousand dollar
No, I'm not I want to stop shilling for the casino suits. I'm not shilling for a casino
I'm telling you how it is. Oh the point of sale exactly
The call all right now I can literally just leave you live in Las Vegas, and you're not shilling for the casinos
I mean I Vegas is awesome. I love it here. I
Realistically if you want to want me to be transparent with you here, I realistically probably go to the casino
I mean, maybe maybe three or four times a year
It's usually when there's an event happening somebody's coming in a friend a group of friends, right? The group of friends come in
Hey, we're coming and we'll be in Vegas for three or four days
All right, we're gonna go to like the cosmopolitan and hang out. We're gonna go to the aria. We're gonna go downtown, right?
Thanks. I have a point of sale. What happened? What was that?
Did you just not want to use it?
Who keeps who what vandal keeps knocking this off fun place?
I feel like this is a chat message
Don't you the squid game person where please please play fruit slots?
I swear to God you'll make everything back in much more or ban me if you lose everything all right
We've got we got a challenge here stir Ben
67 here is putting his neck on the line, and we're looking for a ban all right stir Ben. What is your criteria?
I'm gonna allow this how much money do I need to spend at what denomination?
We're gonna we're gonna let you you have the floor mods if he may if he gives a message
I would I really want to see it there Ben. I'm talking about how much money and hot what denomination
He said $10 bets a hundred spins. He says okay, all right
So we're putting up a we put up a ban here a 30-day ban already
I don't want to be any for that long how about a week
I will ban you for a week from this channel if this doesn't work are we all agreeing with that
It's got to be permanent. Oh shit. That's a lot
Permanent ban did they agree to that I don't know that's like sad though. I don't know if I want to do that
So I kind of sad so I need a thousand dollars
You just agreed to a permanent ban if this doesn't work out
They've been following since
2019 don't make it permanent. Yeah, okay 30 days. I don't want to do that. Yeah, that's that's that that's too sad to me
30 days, that's Eve that's kind of sad too. All right one week. No, that's yeah, that's too sad one week
14. All right. I'll meet you in the middle two weeks. You're gonna get banned from the channel for two weeks
This doesn't work. He's just that confident though. Just wants to be set free from this place
Two weeks is like one stream
That's so funny
No, I've been streaming two days a week. I've upped it. I'm not just doing once a week anymore
I'm streaming twice a week now usually like Wednesday and Sunday Wednesday and Sunday Wednesday and Sunday. Come on. Come on
We're all right. We got to get to a thousand bucks. Oh
This is important though
What's the amount of money that they're expecting? I'm gonna make if they win they need to be VIP'd
Hmm
Okay
Hmm. Let me think about that. All right, fine. You get VIP for two weeks if you win
Well, what's the amount of money?
We need to have it really clear because if I have to spin a hundred times at ten dollars and you're certain of this
What what amount because I could just keep going right? So what amount do I have to stop?
What amount are you expecting me to hit like in profit from a thousand dollars? So I start with a thousand
Where do I end up with your guarantee with a hundred spins? I want to make sure we get it in chat
I can't see ten K plus he says that seems
Thanks. They said ten K plus that's all right. Are you sure? Okay?
I guess if you're that confident, this is a two-week VIP or a two-week ban
He's got to get to a thousand bucks. We're almost there
But wait is it but you have to increase your bet size if you make a decent enough profit
We wait we this is these enough terms that we're describing here. What do you mean?
I thought it was a hundred spins at ten dollars a spin if you get ten K per movie IPM seriously
Say you get to like well, hello
So you get to like two or three to five K you have to increase my bet to what?
There's so many terms of this contract. There's so many terms to this agreement
Okay, so if I hit if I get to like three K
I then have to I'm I can't just go I need a thousand dollars
All right, so if I get to three K I up my bet to what twenty or thirty dollars make it three weeks
Did we did we get any more updated terms, okay, I have to watch XQC play this
I'm playing this right now. All right, you're here. I'm
Playing it right now
Criken just came in with a fucking monster raid to what's going on criken?
Welcome everybody playing internet cafe simulator. We're in the middle of it
We're in the middle of a big big agreement here a big contract. That's about to be signed. We'll make sure the terms are correct
Thanks for the raid. Hope you had a good stream. Welcome everybody
There's your raid song cuz and you know, we kill I can I can I snap that memes neck right now, please
No more stop doing that stop doing that to people. Everybody hates that fucking thing. Nobody likes that
Nobody thinks that's funny. Stop is no more people probably loathe my raids because when I raid somebody they're just like
Oh, here come the fucking raid song people again. I don't even want to listen to them
All right. Anyways, thanks for the raid and we're ready to get started. Well, we have terms here. Welcome criken viewers. Welcome criken
Thanks a lot. Hope you had a good day. Okay
I was told that if I spin a hundred times at ten dollars starting with thousand dollars on this slot machine
That I will be able to get to ten thousand plus dollars. There's a person in chat here who is putting their their their
Stream chat life here. They're going to be banned from the channel
That doesn't work or they're gonna get VIP if it does this is very important terms
We just we're just trying to iron them out. So if I if I if I spin blah blah blah, okay
I hit two three thousand dollars. He told me he was gonna go leave and watch XQC stream instead
But if you make it to 3k increase the bet to fifty dollars and then okay, you got it. Are we ready?
So if I hit 3k if I get to 3k, I'm gonna do $50 spins
But we're still only doing a hundred spins no matter what right? Here we go. It's time close the shop
Yeah, you're right. Everybody out. I want to be in darkness for this use the machine god. Okay, everybody out
Get the fuck out get the fuck out Larry get the fuck out of here Larry get the fuck out Larry
There's no electricity anymore. You're not even playing the machines. Okay, you know
Anybody comes in or out you roundhouse kick him like you always fucking do nobody in nobody out not until I say
Nobody in and nobody out. Did you it's we're closed get the fuck out of my restaurant close the door
What the fuck? Oh, there's no electricity. Oh, if you believe in getting this I could like wait
How are you playing when there's no like all right, you know what here we're closed, please nobody come in
We are closed. I closed it already. This is what I'm talking about
I've already closed
Let's do it and all the bets you're right. Let's see what happens to stir
Was there named stir bun one two, two, okay three. Oh
Shit auto spin. All right, so that was three. So this would be 83 spins, right? What the fuck? Oh
All right, it'll be 84 spins. Okay. Oh shit. Well, what happened? What is this 5x 5?
Wait, I got I got the bonus. I have to what's the times two. Well, how come it's not triggering anything? Um
Hello, I've won sixty two dollars in this bonus so far. Oh, would they they just exist and they get okay
I get it. What it did dog shit bond a ten dollar spin eighty bucks. What a piece of crap. Well, okay
Right. How did I cack it in here? I do have to stop this though if we get over if we get to 3k
Stop promoting gambling. I don't promote gambling. I think you should not gamble at all ever
unless
Just rewind 20 minutes and just watch like the 30-minute rant. I just had about this. I see candy
We need another piece of candy. Come on. You watch any GDQ. No, not yet. I probably will. Oh shit
All right, we got it. Come on. Come on times one. Give me more. Give me like a times a hundred
That's a 50 X right there. Oh, that sucks. That's so bad
Come on
Respins are well that enough respins don't count a hundred X. What's happened? Oh shit. Okay, uh
Respins don't count because they're not actually spins. Oh
We're it what's going on? What are you doing? It actually might happen
This is not pre-recorded by reading your message pigeon man 42. I just proved it right now
Not actually spin. No, it has to it has to be 100 actual paid spins. A free spin is a free spin
It doesn't count. It's part of a bonus. The bonus is its own encompassed thing. It doesn't count candy
It was a plant. It's so it's getting late too. I probably have to stop soon. All right, there's this free spins
Looking for a hundred X or I'll take a re-triggering
Give me another hundred X. It's time to raise the bet. That's I was not told to do that
There's a hundred X right there. Oh
Please why?
Watermelons, okay. Okay raise the bet to 50
Yeah, that know that I it was raised the bet to 50 if I when I got to 3k, that's pretty big
How do the bombs work? I don't know the bombs in the bonus seem to just be it just the add multiplier
All right. Come on. It's times one. He's saying to do it now. We've already locked it in
So I don't know wait he's saying do it now it would hear do we listen to this
He said he's saying he wants his remaining spins here to be 50. It actually might happen right here
I got four more free spins times two. Come on
That's gonna be huge times a hundred. All right. No, he's got it. That's he said 2k originally
He did he did say 2k originally. All right. All right. All right. Stop stop stop stop stop. Stop spinning. Stop spinning
I can't stop it
Stop auto spinning. How do I turn it off?
He said 3k, but he also he is saying he wants it to go
He wants to change it right now because in his original message
He said when you get to two comma three or five K to put it to fifty stir stir stir
Stir bean or whatever stir, but what are you in here? What do we got? Yes, they're here. Okay
Wait, we got a message. I needed to feel it out. You know what I'm saying force and CD. I'm ready for $50
Okay
Let's go. All right, let's go. Let's go. I'm gonna adhere to this. You ready? Let's go for it $50 spins here
He's gonna get banned. I don't know if there's another bonus with $50 bets. It could be a big deal. We'll see
I'm gonna hold my breath for a second though because you have to those three candies have to show up this too
If there's another one, this is a big deal. Oh
No, nothing is this the among us guy and that's my brother we share a
Channel and stuff. I think he sucks though. I don't think it's that funny. We have like pretty bad like family problems together
I think he's a fucking annoying little shit. I mean we do share the channel
We have like a contract and stuff mom. I mean my brother Jeremy
My name is Jerba. Our personality is like a little different. You can always tell who's who I'm the funny one
I'm like the one that's like we got it. We got it. Shut up. This joke sucks. Who cares? Let's go
What a stupid idea. Come on, let's go. This is it. This is his opportunity to make this happen nice, too
Oh, no right now. He's probably screaming. He wants to see a times 50 or a times 100. Oh, it's going though
Oh, no a 10k
10,000 I don't know man. I don't think it's gonna happen if the X Oh
oh
Not much time left though. Really looking for those free spins. Holy shit. Holy shit. This is still going
Oh my god, but back on regular spins. No, don't be fooled by that counter. There's still about 20 more spins to add on top
I don't I I don't think it's gonna happen. I get why scheme auto pause. It's starting to drain Andy. No, ah
Come on, I want him to win. I'm rooting for him. Yeah, there are 16 more spins after this
It's looking pretty grim a lot of bombs but not gonna do anything. Oh, no
No, oh no, it's draining. It was at 3k. Oh
No, wait a minute redemption. Potentially. That's a bonus right now
If it's gonna happen, it's gonna happen right here only times two nothing only 2x though. That's not very good
You need a big one. Oh
Nothing. I don't think it's gonna happen man. Nothing. No, why is it still going?
340 this won't stop. Oh my god. All right, he's got 16. Come on. I want to see it happen 5x
All right, so you get I got I can just count these because he's got 16 fire fire win fire fire
Where oh my god, what is this? How long was that going? I don't have my other earbud in. All right
16 more he says do $100 spins on these last ones. I mean I'm willing. All right
16 spins at a hundred bucks. I'll allow it. Here we go. One two
Mmm, it's it's pretty good spins, but not enough. Hold on three four five. Oh shit
six seven eight
No, nine
Ten you got six more eleven twelve. Oh, it could happen
15. Oh
This is it man. We're down to the final spin. This is it
16. Oh
No, but hold on. Hold on. I'm gonna give him five more. Mmm, three four five
Oh my god. I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry too bad. You bad
I believed I really did I was rooting for you
Wait, did he just get banned automatically cuz he called me a fucking cheater. Wait, what? No, no different person
I just do another one more. I'm gonna laugh my ass off if I get it right now. Come on another candy
Let's see it. He's gonna be pissed if it happens. Oh, it's gonna happen. It's gonna happen. It is watch this shit right now
Oh my god, there's a candy right there. Oh
I thought it was gonna happen. Ah
Come on. I'm doing it. I'm doing it for him. All right, that's it taking the rest of blackjack. Thanks for playing
Oh, I feel so bad. I feel so bad. It's two weeks. That's so sad
I the bonus for wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. It's
$10,000 to buy the bonus. Never mind. All right, this one's for you. Sorry. You're gonna you're about to get banned for two weeks
I'm I feel really bad about it, but deal is a deal. Whatever. Okay. No, you have the floor
I would like to hear your last words. What are you? What are you? What's your final message? I will read it on stream
What is it? Oh, you already banned him. All right unban him so he can give his last words revive him
I I would I want he gets at least a full like at least few sentences
With confirmation of what what they said you can say pretty much or whatever you want. What do you say?
What do you wait? What do you say? I didn't catch it. I didn't see it. What was it?
I didn't see what he said. They said when next TF2 video what that's your final words
When when's next here are the next TF2 video is gonna be never I'm probably never gonna make a TF2 video ever again
Thanks for playing though, dude. It was fun. We'll see you again. Don't worry. Well, we will reserve your seat for you. I promise
Hey a stir Ben
67002 this one's for you. I'm back motherfuckers. He'll it
Ah
Music to it pops me up. I was doing it from stir Ben
These guys are just laughing about me every time I leave
Where was that last hand I guess the four give me up. You've got to be kidding me. Oh
Never mind, you got 21 great. Goodbye. Thanks. It was fun
I'm done. I'll see you guys later. I'm banned too. I'll see you guys on this weekend at some point
I'm gonna make sure I'll save the game. That's right
Probably Saturday or Sunday. I will let you know keep your ears to the ground for February 1st. That is the tentative damn holding in a perp
February 1st is the tentative date for the big stream. It should be a really fun time
It's something I've never really talked about
So if you're speculating on what it is, it's not really anything you've heard about
I don't think I've ever really talked about it. Maybe as a joke in passing
Well, like one second at some point, I don't think so though. Oh, this is I gotta hold on. Yeah, let me close this place
Oh, no, it's closer guy. We're already is closed. I think the next stream that I'm gonna do this weekend
It's either gonna be VR or I don't know. It depends on how I feel. I've been feeling kind of like shit lately
I've been really headachy and kind of sloppy. So depending on
All that plays out. It's either gonna be VR or I'll push VR to like middle of January
They will be streamed this weekend. I'll see you guys soon. Thanks for watching everybody and let me save the game
It is the middle of January. Well, it's
January 12th. Yeah, I guess it is but I mean let a few days the plan is so I can do VR
Before the big stream because the big stream is well, you know, I mean, I don't have to I have to tell you anything
Right. Give us a hint. No, no, it's zero into a riot. You want a hint?
Hmm
No, nope, I don't think so if I want to give you a hint
It'll be way closer to the event that might be more fun, but not two or three weeks out
Maybe on the stream before it happens. So thanks everybody for watching. We'll see you soon
Appreciate it a lot of people here tonight and I was late. I really appreciate it. Thanks for the raids
It was a couple raids that came in you're still here from those raids. Thanks for watching
Maybe we'll see you again. Have a beautiful evening. Well, we still have a few more minutes
Germa TV. Germa TV really is kind of I think that's probably still the most the least used emote
I think give us a fake hint. I could give you you know
I could give you three hints right and two of them aren't real. We could play that game. Maybe that might be fun
I don't know. It depends on how much I want to reveal. Thanks for staying up. This is fun game
I don't I'm not sure I'll return to it. Maybe I will maybe I won't it was a blast though
Yeah, aren't they doing this new thing with um, what was the thing?
I saw about the moments thing or you get a special badge if you were if you at a certain event or something or at
A certain stream. I feel like that's an awesome thing to have
I would have loved to have made that for something like dollhouse or something
At least for like the big event ones if you don't know that twitch is sort of doing like a little test on
Adding badges a different badge that you can kind of put instead of the other ones that are for specific
Streams that you were at if the streamer decided to make a special badge for it. That seems kind of interesting
I think that's way more. I think that's cooler than just simply having like a
How many bits I've given or how many subs I've given it's like, oh no
I was like at this stream and it was like fun, right? I think that's cool. It's your friend a happy birthday
Jayden, I wish your friend a happy birthday whenever it is
They can also be applied retroactively like you could do 2021's worst stream in best stream. Really? That's cool. All right
I'm into that imagine representing that has a badge
the smite stream from last year
Well, I was there worst dream like the idea 2013 or something that's fine like little t-shirts
All right guys, I'll see you this weekend. Have a great night. Let me drink some more water. I'm thirsty
Good night. Take care. Have a great week