How do you change character? I want to be I want to be like a look freak show. Okay, or you can just get it
I want to change my character. I don't get it. I don't want to be the default fucking guy
Greetings mr. Freeman. Oh that headcrab is sure a big headcrab. Mr. Freeman. Oh
Oh god
Get it. I grapple onto it
I do I have to hold it every time I do it. Oh god. Okay. I'm on
Wow, whoa, whoa?
whoa
God, what is this like a subterranean vehicle or a plane?
We're getting out of here. Am I going to still stand on this?
This is like this does not seem safe at all
Yeah, you're telling me that this a grapple hook is going to keep what do I have like glue on my feet or something?
This is ridiculous
You ever played just cause you're driving us into trees
Doesn't really matter
I'm dead
Are you out of the plane?
I don't know what any of these things are but i'm gonna buy one. That's how you learn. Oh, yeah, that's like a
Motorcycle baby. So what's the boost button for you? I'm not telling you
Fuck you. What's the boost button?
Whoa, whoa
What the what?
What?
In the name of god
Is going on
what
It's just like
What is this
You know what that reminded me of
It just looked like some kid
took
Went into his toy box, you know, I used to have when you were a little kid
You know how you used to have like a toy bin
With like yeah, I throw my brother into it off the top bunk. It really hurt. I'm sorry. Sorry
Yeah, that that thing that's full of a bunch of shit, right?
You have like your race cars you have your helicopters your planes your your dolls you will not your dolls
I mean, maybe you do have dolls. I don't know but that was just the battle of the toys
That's the battle of the toy chest and we're gonna go be a part of it right now
How the hell am I ever gonna explain this to you?
Hi, okay. There you are. We're gonna we're gonna get into dude. These two helicopters just crashed into each other
I hope I just got what the fuck is shooting me
It's you of course it is
Well, look at the dude. There's there's like a freaking atomic war going on though to the right. What the hell am I supposed to think?
All right, so we're gonna go to the battle of the toys
Which toy what?
All right. Let's let's go. Let's go tear up some toys
There's aromatic yeti over here. I'm gonna get shot down for sure. There's like no way this is gonna happen
Look out for that toy
Whoa, did you get shot down?
No, i'm i'm i'm good
That's just like shit yeah, I do because we're just dropping people it was ridiculous, man
I'm getting this helicopter. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa
What is it? No, dude, what's happening right now?
We're okay
Oh this plane this plane
No, whoa. Whoa, what do you get out? I don't have anyone to go
How do you bail?
No, don't get in the helicopter. No, I don't want to get out. Fuck
You can grappling hook it. Yeah. Ooh
really
Drive by me
No, it didn't work
What you mean to say is you suck. Um, i'm not entirely sure what's happening right now
I have no idea what's going on. I'm going back to the airport, dude
We're gonna have a good grand old time
Fucking jesus. I didn't
Is it crazy that this like works? I can't believe this is even a thing
This is truly unbelievable that this like he's even able to be supported. How is this even supported?
What's this?
how
Oh, we're the policemen. We're gonna save the day
I heard there's a there's a big toy