Welcome to the new year. Welcome to the new year.
To the new year. Welcome to the new year, right? It's kind of how I just said that.
No, that wasn't even- I wasn't making a joke. All right, hold on.
One second. Still with the road stream. Ah, eh, eh. Hold on a minute. I gotta stop the road.
Let's start in a minute. Slowly turning into the emote that I truly, truly am.
I'll be right back. Just gonna grab one more thing.
Hey, only like 382,000 more games left to play. See you in a moment. Okay.
I'm sitting here trying to clear my throat. Sinuses, my nasal passages.
There's Vegas air. Some of the cleanest in the world.
I kind of get this frog throat. After like an hour it goes away.
But yeah, today the plan- I could, you know, I could probably today- oh man,
I could probably do a pretty good Dutch right now with this kind of Vegas nose and Vegas throat.
Arthur, I've got a plan, Arthur. Just stick to the plan.
No, not deep enough.
You, Arthur, need to have a little faith, Arthur.
That wasn't bad. He's making that face right now.
I make that face every single morning when I get up.
That's the first image that you see when you see me in bed.
In fact, that image was taken. Kim took that picture.
I got up. We both sat up at the same time.
So I, you know, Undertaker rose and made that face.
She snapped a picture and right after that I said, oh, my back is killing me.
In bed? O-W-O? Why did I read that out loud?
So who did the filter thing? What filter?
What filter? I don't know what you mean.
I've never taken a photo with a filter in my life.
That's not real. I want to show people reality.
The real me. No dog noses on this streamer, I'll tell you that much.
All right, so here's what we're doing.
We're going to do the rest of the 700,000 games.
Last night got to a point where it was- I was a little- I was kind of exhausted,
so I figured we'd just close it out today.
And I'm not sure what's going to happen after.
Because this might actually take us like at least three, maybe four hours to do this.
So I- this might be another full stream because there are a lot left.
And then we could probably maybe take the things that we were going to do
afterwards and just do them another time.
I never like to just rush into shit, you know?
I'd like to take my time. Like right now.
I've been live for five minutes, and we're at the starting soon screen.
And the Spaz just gave five community subs.
Coming in going, boom!
Dropping some community subs.
Thank you so much, Spaz.
My husband listens to you more than me.
Uh, you listening right now?
Communication is so important in a relationship.
Listening to each other's needs and wants, and making sure that
you're both taken care of.
It's very important, Rick.
German never listens to me.
All right, that's enough of the intro screen.
What do you say?
Here it is.
That- okay, look, it looks like a lot of X's, but trust me, it's not.
It isn't.
That may look like a lot of X's, but when you take the X's away,
we got like half the games here.
It's an optical illusion.
Speaking of optical illusions, I want to make sure I bring this up before we go and even start here.
Um, how do I look today?
No, that's not what I- that's not the thing that I want to talk about, but
let's see how bad this is.
I'm gonna look like such shit.
Let's find out.
Ready?
You want to be the big face reveal for today?
Not that bad.
What's wrong with the camera, though?
Do I look like weird to anybody else today?
What- do I have eyebrows?
What happened to my eyebrows?
No, they're there.
I forgot to pencil in my eyebrows.
You look shattered.
I think I'm just- I am actually just getting old.
I look at- yeah, look at this.
I'm gonna have to start wearing, like, makeup.
Ugh.
Aging rapidly.
Yeah, it's been one day.
No, it's the lighting.
Hold on.
Let me- let me- Phil- Philips Hue!
Philips Hue!
Oh, you- no, you don't speak to it.
It's not like Alexa.
It's the lights.
Hold on.
You look like Draco Malfoyle.
Well, my house is Slytherin, does that make sense?
Let's make this better.
No.
No, cause- I don't like this because I feel like I'm in a movie theater.
Now, let me- let me ask you.
This is very important before we get to the- before we get to the thing,
before getting to the thing, before getting to the thing I originally wanted.
To talk about.
Does anybody else here hate going to the fucking movies during the day?
I do.
I fucking despise it.
Ugh.
No, yeah, cause the lights.
It- it- it's like one o'clock in the afternoon.
A day movie.
You- okay, you hear me out on this.
One o'clock in the afternoon.
Oh, yeah, let's go see a movie.
You get in there and it's like, oh, yeah, that'll go.
It's like- it's bright summertime sunshine right now.
It's like 95 degrees out.
Let's get in that movie theater.
No, that was just the right one.
Here.
The whole- I can't-
It's light out right now.
So this is not- this reference isn't gonna work in-
I'm just gonna have to describe it to you, okay?
It's currently light out right now.
And I'm turning the lights off in the room like it's gonna do anything.
I- I hate going to the movies.
When it's, uh, when it's light.
Because you get in there and it's pitch black
and you have this beaming light in your face.
It's as if you're holding a fucking iPad in front of your face.
And then it's like for two hours you come out, you're like,
oh, and it's like so bright.
You feel- I need to go to bed after a movie.
Greasy hair?
No, it's shower.
I feel like it needs to be dark outside to see a movie.
That's at any time.
No, at night.
At night it's- it's-
The sky is- is black.
Coming out of a movie at two o'clock in the afternoon,
it's like- it's like drinking during the day.
Like that- that- ah, uh-uh.
No, it's like the same feeling.
I feel like I'm just like, I don't like any of this.
At the- yeah, the sky is black.
Yeah, it is.
It's a scientific little Elon Musk thing for you.
The sky is scientific, as Tesla taught me that.
The sky is blue and black.
He's stalling.
Well, I- I'm not stalling.
Spaz gave another five community subs.
You guys wouldn't believe how much light actually fucks with you.
Light gets inside and fucks with your brain.
You know why it's- it's so hard to fall asleep sometimes at night?
Because you got that light.
Humans are all just made out of light.
You know, you're 70% light.
So which one are we going to?
What would you guys say?
If you were to make a choice here.
And by choice, I mean click on the screen.
14-year-old philosopher.
Well, we're not- we're definitely not going to do, uh, check- uh, I keep calling it checkers.
Oh, the- I forgot, yeah, right, the- the optical illusion.
All right, so here, hang me out on this.
This is for real, while you're voting.
Can- can- can I just see a shitload of the German old emote, please?
And I want you to look at it.
When it's next to other German old emotes, at least three or four of them.
It looks like a different emote.
It changes.
The face changes.
It's a fucked up optical illusion that I did not intend.
Some of them are, like, smirking.
Some of them have a frown.
It's really weird.
Well, that's- actually, this is impossible.
Because this too- the chat is going way too fast.
Some of them look older than others.
All right, how- how do I turn the chat off for a second?
Because I'll do it.
Any mods know how to just turn off the chat?
Like, can- can I just turn the chat off for, like, two minutes or something?
Is there a way to do that?
Is this- does this do anything?
Oh my fucking god.
Just scroll up.
Streamer bans 3,000 people.
You can't stop us.
Well anyways, okay, when you have some free time,
just do the German old emote a shitload of times and look at them.
They start moving.
They start talking.
They start talking to you.
I had a whole conversation with three of them.
All right, so we're going to...
Distinct Worlds.
I don't know what that is.
Distinct Worlds?
What is that?
What is it called?
Robotic Worlds.
Okay, cross your fingers.
Let's hope it works.
It works.
Now, but it's going to be an issue, but hopefully I can even open...
That was fucking loud.
Just give me a second.
Ah, yay, yay.
Uh, I have no idea.
I can't even see what I'm selecting.
What am I even clicking on?
I don't know what I just did.
It's just- the music stopped.
That's all that happened.
I'm going to reopen this.
What the fuck?
All right.
No more votes.
Thank you for voting.
I appreciate the votes.
Yeah, I turned it off because it was just so loud and so horrible,
but it's going to happen again.
So I'm going to go like this.
Let's see if you guys can see it.
Let's try it again.
This time I'm going to have to not move.
Robotic Worlds.
Incoming.
What?
That's it.
That's Robotic Worlds.
What a great game.
It's fantastic.
Okay.
That was Robotic Worlds.
Rigged.
Uh, oh, there's nothing I can do about that one.
Thank you.
Thanks for voting for it because they don't- it don't work.
Where- where is this?
Where am I?
Robotic Worlds.
It seems like all the interesting ones just are the ones that don't work.
Try again.
Don't click on a red X.
Don't click on a red X or it might ball up the tiles around it.
Okay, people are liking the, uh,
Riverboat.
Mermaid.
Uh, Nasty Diamonds.
And there, you know, there's always going to be 10 to 15% of every person that's going
to click on Connect 4.
Even when explicitly told.
This is my fair part.
This is the human mind at work.
Explicitly told that that I'm not going to play it.
I'm not going to click that.
It's not going to happen.
I'm going to do it anyways.
Nasty Diamonds.
Sounds like a strip club.
Chaotic Neutral Chat.
No, uh, 50%.
How many- how many fucking chaotic doofuses are in here right now?
That's what I wonder.
Well, it's this one up here.
It's, uh, Aquamaria.
I don't know what that is.
Let's see.
Aqua- what's it called?
Aquamania.
Awful stupid.
Lawful stupid.
I remember that whole thing.
That was fun.
Okay, let's see if this one works.
Aquamania.
It's opening.
It's closing.
Aquamania.
Okay, two in a row.
Is strike three going to happen?
Let's strike two.
Okay, really- we're really picking great ones.
And it's not even anybody's fault.
It's- it's this video game's fault.
I really am curious as to- we have to keep an eye on which ones don't work.
All right, aqua- aqua- there it is.
Uh, try again?
Strike three ends the stream.
No.
I just turned it on.
I- all I hear is a faint slap when that picture comes up.
Jerma, just play the game.
I just tried.
I just tried to do two different games.
All right, we're gonna do- looks like, uh, riverboat?
Riverboat.
Extreme riverboat challenge or something.
Whatever the hell it is.
That is over there on that second pack.
All right, riverboat.
I'm not gonna do connect four.
Extreme riverboat racing.
Well, it opens.
What a good sign.
The question is, can I get this in a window?
You got me.
You know, you don't- oh, what?
Wait, why?
You don't have 1920 by 1080, but you have 2048 by 1536.
What resolutions are you even attempting here?
What monitor size is this?
Is this like a- is this like a vertical 28 inch monitor?
I don't get it.
Run riverboat again to change resolution.
Okay, well, let's run riverboat again.
Five by four.
No, that's like a five by two vertical riverboat.
Let's open it again.
Let's see if this hopefully makes it better.
Hopefully it's not just like a fucking cube in the corner of your screen.
Are you trying to tell me that I made it unopenable?
No fucking way.
I made it.
I've made the game unopenable by changing its resolution.
I didn't do anything.
Why?
Hold on.
Let me like- oh my god.
Why is this happening?
I'm gonna have to go edit the INI file.
Yeah, if I don't- does it even have one?
Oh my god, this is fucking ridiculous.
Okay, what the hell is this thing called?
Riverboat challenge?
I'm shocked that this is three in a row here.
This is not even on a list.
Best game hits five and six.
It's not even here.
It deleted itself when I changed the resolution.
Yeah, that's what happened.
The game deleted its own folder when I changed its resolution.
No, there it is.
Okay, extreme- it's extreme riverboat racing, not just riverboat racing.
Okay, here we go.
Data.
Graphics.
Menu.
D3E.
No, this is none of- there's no INI.
There's nothing here.
No, it's over.
I can't- I can open it in safe mode, but this is a batch file.
I'm not double clicking a batch file.
Oh, what the fuck.
Hold on.
All right, maybe- okay, what if I just run it in 640x430?
I can do it- okay, I can run- I can force the game into 640x480 in the compatibility tab.
Let's see what happens.
Did it work?
Nope.
I don't understand what would be causing something like that.
That's such a- that's such a specifically awful bug.
That changing the resolution of the game makes the game no longer able to open ever again,
even if you change it back.
Holy shit, this is unbelievable.
I don't even know what to say.
Can I like-
Did you hear that little laugh?
I'm gonna be honest with you here though.
I don't- oh boy, this joke again.
What? Which one?
What did I do?
What did that do?
I should just be a country singer by the amount of times my voice cracks, seriously.
Bring back Super Frog.
No.
Terma is such a millennial.
I am a millennial.
Oh, I get what you're doing.
You're doing like the reverse boomer thing.
Okay, thanks.
All right, we're gonna go to Fantasy Island.
36%.
Fantasy Island.
Rollerball Fantasy Island.
Okay, are we going 4 for 4?
Is it possible to go 4 for 4 with games that don't work?
It's opening it in the other window.
Oh my god, it's-
Don't open in the other window.
Open in this window.
The one that's right here at my main monitor.
What the fuck?
Where is it gonna open?
Rollerball Fantasy Island.
Start game.
No, now it's opening in the main window.
Not doing that again.
I'm not doing that to you guys again.
I changed the resolution.
The phrase changed resolution.
All right, we're gonna change the resolution to
1152 by 864.
But look at how bad that-
All right, cartoon style.
Oh, I get it.
It's like fucking it's in the newspaper.
All right, it worked.
But you still can't see it over here.
I need to like make it-
I need to drag it to the left at least.
Probably be all right.
There we go.
I got it.
How bad is this?
This is so loud too.
There's only so much of the same five second loop
and it's speech volume.
Oh, you're a booter.
Wow.
Oh, it was funny.
Don't do it again.
Why is this here?
Sorry, but he's dead now.
Oh, it was awful.
You lost him.
Oh, you're a booter.
Wow, it was funny.
All right, I like this one.
I like this one because of that guy's voice.
It's the only good part about this.
All right, let's go.
Original levels, lost levels.
Like anyone's going to click this.
Snowland, Greenland, Fantasyland.
Which-
Okay, which Sonic the Hedgehog level should I start at?
I'm going to say green hill zone.
Oh.
Normal, hard, easy.
So what's the difference?
It just adds more like fucking sprinkles.
That's all it does.
I'm just going to do normal.
Level is complete.
Oh my God.
This guy, I turned him up louder than everything else.
Ready, go.
You know, all right.
So listen, I figured out what all these-
These games are the preloaded after school games.
Is that just Facebook?
This is what is allowed on your eighth grade school computer.
It's just the after school games.
Did I miss one?
Pass all the gates.
I did that, right?
Congratulations, level is complete.
The guy didn't scream at me, so I didn't do it.
Ready, go.
Should I keep cartoon style on?
What do you guys think?
No.
Get them all.
Tonight we go on a rock.
Tonight we gonna rock.
I need to get that one.
How do I get the secret one?
Is this one even humanly possible to get?
You can't get that one.
Jump?
What do you mean jump?
I can't-
Guys, I can't go this way.
It's an invisible wall.
What the-
All right.
No, you saw me try that like five times.
Ready, go.
It's the hit boxes that are the problem.
Not me and my big brain.
Okay, let's try that again.
Ready, remember.
Remember guys, Jeremy's stupid.
That's why I couldn't do that.
Remember, always remember.
It's always Mr. Jeremy's fault.
Flag.
Congratulations level is complete.
Ready, go.
All right, how much more of this can you guys take?
Congratulations level is complete.
Ready, go.
I was trying to get the other coins, man.
Doing this with the mouse just-
Okay, why was I doing it with the mouse?
What the fuck am I thinking?
It's so much easier with the keyboard.
Congratulations level is complete.
Ready, go.
I just want to make sure I get around there.
I don't-
Who cares if I don't get all the coins?
Does it really matter?
Don't do it again.
Ready, go.
Does it really matter if I don't get all the coins in this sloppy game?
I've eaten fucking sloppy joes that were easier to handle.
Congratulations level is complete.
This game's like Tommy Wiseau's dad.
This game-
Ready, go.
This game is Tommy Wiseau's dad.
What?
I don't-
Maybe that went too fast for me to see what you wrote.
What's happening?
I'm stuck.
Oh, stop it.
Oh, troll level.
Kaizo block.
Ready, go.
Congratulations level is complete.
How are you bad at the game this easy?
I don't think you understand.
This game is very hard to control.
Have you seen my ball?
Ready, go.
It looks like it's based on physics but it's not I can assure you.
It's based off of-
I don't know.
Something else.
Got out.
Got out again.
This is-
No.
I'm fucked.
It's over.
There's no way to get up but there's no way for the player to be able to get back up.
There was a skip over there.
Oh, not again.
Ready, go.
Sorry but he's dead now.
It's not easy.
Trust me when I say it's not easy.
I understand that this is Serial Game number 460 but you don't-
That guy actually fell down and hit something.
Well, that was fun.
Oops.
That was Boomer Ball.
I don't know what it was called actually.
You have no idea.
I'm not going to do the Lost Levels.
Oh come-
You want me to do the Lost Levels?
I-
Watch.
I'm going to open that.
I'm not going to be able to do it because he's going to say-
No!
No, it was-
Oops!
Fine, I'll prove it.
I'll just click on Lost Levels and he's going to say no.
Just to make sure nobody-
Because guess what's going to happen if I don't do this.
50% are going to click on Connect 4 and 50% are going to click on Lost Levels game again.
And there's going to be like four guys that actually vote for another game.
So I have to do this.
Let's go.
This is not the Lost Levels.
It's the same thing.
Ready, go.
It's not a Lost Level.
Oh, it was awful.
Ready, go.
Get the amount of space that I have to get this.
You have to do it like that.
Even one pixel.
I don't- why do you guys want me to be in this one?
Actually, you know what?
I know why.
Because it's the only one that has worked since the stream has turned on.
So I get it.
No, I do understand.
But I want to get Cartoon Mode off.
Never mind.
Graphics-wise, I really do appreciate the cell-shaded technology.
How do I get those?
Is there a jump?
Oh.
Congratulations.
Level is complete.
Ready, go.
Just jump.
Flag's over there.
Do the Lost Level.
How are these the Lost Levels?
Congratulations.
Level is complete.
Ready, go.
In my opinion, they're not lost if they're a clickable menu
in the first- when you click on Start Game.
Shouldn't this be like a sequence of events you have to do
before you get to see the Lost Levels?
They're very much found.
They're right in front of you.
It took Nintendo like 32 years to unleash the Lost Levels for Mario 1.
Congratulations.
Level is complete.
Ready, go.
Oh, you're a butcher.
Well, ready, go.
Congratulations.
Level is complete.
1048, I counted.
It's still currently- that was currently at the 10-second mark.
Oh, no.
Ready, go.
Actually, a good game.
Yeah, it was.
It's too bad it's never going to be seen again ever from this channel.
Maybe some other channel might play it and be like, nice.
Not me.
Who the hell was that?
I don't even know what that was.
One through four was right there.
Now, I appreciate the joke to try to get me to open it again.
There, look at everybody.
A full quadrant.
A full math class quadrant.
Still clicking on connect four.
Okay, now you almost got a full- you obviously had a measuring cup there.
You had a full measuring cup.
So where are we going?
Elf bowling.
Cosmic elf bowling.
Let's try it.
Cosmic- Cosmo Alley bowling.
Didn't I try this one last night?
It didn't work.
Did I forget to put one on here?
This one doesn't work.
I didn't put an X on this one.
Okay.
What's next?
Put an X on every game.
Uh, none of them have worked.
Except for the Super Monkey Ball game.
Yeah, we must have.
We're getting all landmines today.
We avoided a lot of landmines yesterday.
Surprisingly, Mega Pinball is coming up.
Let's see if it turns on.
Hey dude, you know what works, dude?
Connect four.
You're right, it does.
Connect four does work.
Okay, that's just like somebody's
engineered TF2 profile picture.
High color, true color.
Oh no, what have I done?
I clicked on true color.
Oh, I think I'm gonna blue screen.
Don't blue screen.
Damn it.
This is, okay, this is what this means.
You guys thought that this was
maximize or minimize window?
No, there are two windows.
See, there's one and then one in front,
one in front, one behind.
This is just putting the window
that's behind up front.
So it's just shuffling the two windows.
You guys thought that was minimize, maximize?
I'm sorry, you're just wrong.
Let me try to fix this.
So I need to just stretch it out a little.
So I'm gonna stretch it out
and then down like that.
Let's see if that does anything.
A little, almost.
Pinball version 1.0.
That's horseshit.
That should be 2.0
because this is version two of 700,000 games.
Oh, I got it.
I got it.
No, that's Cosmo Alley Bowling.
Wrong one.
Mega Pinball.
That's as good as I'm gonna get it.
I can't fucking around with it anymore.
Is that even a pinball machine?
Name player one.
Damn, what's with the suit?
Pinball Mania 3D and oh,
but here's like a James Bond tuxedo.
All right, we're gonna go with this one.
This one looks like a circus one or something.
Go.
I don't, what is,
even your grandmother likes Mega Pinball.
Okay, well, how do I play?
What's flipper?
Z and X?
Oh, it's Z and,
it's Z and slash.
That sound is fucking horrible.
That's a sound I don't want to hear.
You know what I'm saying?
I don't like that sound at all.
Everybody hates that sound.
The ball is at like nine FPS.
Really?
This whole thing is a slideshow of PNGs.
There's no animation here.
Where'd it go?
Now you must, oh.
All right, listen.
When the Windows 95 space pinball machine is better
than your pinball,
that's a huge problem.
That makes me just want to play that one.
And that's, that's the Diablo 2.
I know I made a Diablo 2 reference yesterday,
but this is all about references.
These last two streams are just referencing
anything I can reference.
That's the patch.
Where's the ball?
Did the ball go down?
Was that not paying attention?
Did it go through?
Where is it?
The ball is, now it is safe to turn off your monitor.
That's scary.
That's a scary piece of text.
Is there like a tilt?
Don't some of these games have like a push or shove button?
There it is, okay.
What does it say?
I can't read it.
You've been warned the movie.
What?
You've been warned the, what does it say?
You've been warned.
You've been gnomed.
Move your mouse, but don't forget to play the game.
I can't do anything.
I want to see the other machine.
I love that face so much.
Uh, all right, what's next?
What do we have?
What about this one?
This is like Swampland.
This one's an alligator.
Is this one a higher, move your mouse?
I know, I know.
Shut up.
Shut up, guy.
Uh, cuckoo clock.
Anyways, what I was saying before,
if you spam the germa old emo enough times, it looks like I'm just kidding.
Does it give me a fart sound?
Better.
Yeah, it does.
I want to get it in the alligator mouth.
Get it in the alligator mouth.
Come on.
What happened?
What's this going on?
Hello?
What is it?
Now what?
Sorry, but it's your last Dan.
What?
It kicked it back into this.
How?
Oh, that was bullshit.
It actually can give you a square ball.
What?
Uh, press escape.
I'm out of here.
That was atrocious.
That was the worst game.
I don't even care the ones that don't work.
That was worse than the ones that don't work.
I'm going to keep the screen there for now.
Mega pinball.
Here we go.
Make my desktop background tiles of the snort witch.
Now that's going to give me a headache.
You don't think that'll give you a headache after like 20 minutes?
Tuxedo level.
I can't select the tuxedo.
The tuxedo is unselectable.
It's just there for flair and for fluff.
All right, so why do some of these not have percentages?
Magic Spears.
Jerma can't even beat the first level of Starcraft.
Yes, I can.
You start out.
You're in the castle.
And I got to cleanse all the grain.
The grain is all dirty and it's making people get the plague.
So you got to cleanse the people from the plague.
The culling of Stratholme.
I remember that.
It's the first level.
I know it.
That's not a WoW reference.
That is a Warcraft reference.
Not a World of Warcraft reference.
It's a Warcraft reference.
All right, this one works.
Always check.
Are you kidding me?
It's the first game ever.
Oh, and it's got full screen?
Kidding me.
You got to be kidding me.
Thank God.
The only game in the goddamn pack that allows you to do this.
And it's got sliders.
It's got a gamma.
Landscape quality.
What is this even changing?
Well, I don't understand what that's doing.
Fog type.
Table or vertex.
On some old video cards, table fog may look strange.
Switching to vertex fog.
Turn up the mute.
That's just render distance.
All right, we're ready.
Welcome to Magic Spheres.
I'm actually really excited for this.
Start adventure.
Screen saver.
The one I didn't do this.
I don't like this.
I don't like how this is doing this.
This is fucking scaring me.
This is the best game so far.
Once upon a time in the blessed country of Tyroding.
Good and evil locked horns in eternal combat.
The evil wizard, Catalyne,
Stolen and imprisoned in fragile magical spheres.
Souls of the righteous.
If they're not released before the hour of the wolf,
the souls will become subjected to the mighty villain
and Tyroding will vanish into oblivion.
There's only one sorcerer who's equal in strength to Carolyte.
Young player.
Luckily, player dared to throw out a challenge to the wicked magician
and Carolyte offered to play the game.
In which souls are the tokens and the Tyroding is the game board.
So be it.
The battle will take place atop squally mountains
and the stake in the game is the future of our magical world.
Oh, come on.
No.
What?
Ah, it's this.
I'm actually, like, upset about this.
Such an epic journey we just went on.
Of the imprisoned souls, people that play Candy Crush every day
and we have to, like, fucking take their iPads from them.
This is what happens when you play Candy Crush.
For, like, fucking 12 hours a day and you spend, like, four grand.
You turn into a cube
and then you have to get sucked up from a marble vacuum.
Release all souls before the timer.
All right, I can get this shit.
Close.
This ain't a real match three game.
Square always works and it turns into a fucking bomb.
What have I got?
Got it.
That's its thermometer.
That's how odd I was.
Souls released.
Click anywhere.
For each level completed, you've received one upgrade point.
You can spend it on upgrades.
Click the plus button to purchase an upgrade
to sell an upgrade and get upgrade points back.
Click the minus button.
This every will allow up to five souls on the screen at one time.
It's now only four.
This is a skill tree.
Low level bonus.
Make a row of four spheres to get this bonus.
When activated, this bonus destroys nearby spheres.
Yeah, that's what I was talking about.
Well done.
Don't forget that the stake in this game is the innocent souls.
Break the spell of carolite.
The earth is too small for magic.
Carolite's black serpent and your white swan have soared skyward.
The wizard has placed the first game board
with souls above a peaceful meadow,
smelling of honey and white flowers.
All that Great Britain dialogue for this.
Yeah, see, it makes a bomb.
Now this is what I'm talking about.
The next time I do it, bingo.
We got another row of four.
Boom.
Bomb.
Explode.
Go ahead and do it at this one.
Boom.
Pretty good, huh?
Let's see.
How many souls do I have?
I don't feel like I'm going to play this one for a little while.
This one's like fun.
The halos of the souls.
Okay, I need two more.
Each successful move fills up your status bar.
You need to fill the bar to activate perfect mode.
I need one insane strung together moment
where I get like a hundred thousand points.
Yeah!
I was...
No, don't scream.
Come on.
You're too old for that.
Got two minutes left?
Oh, check this out.
Ready?
I couldn't catch it.
All right.
Oh, we're getting a double here.
Watch this.
Oh, I'm ready.
I'm ready.
Ready.
Check it out.
Bang.
Oh, wait.
There's a halo.
I need green down here.
Come on.
Come on, chat.
Give me your energy.
Watch this.
65 degrees Celsius.
That's pretty cool.
Lightning sequence.
Make rows of spheres of the same type,
one after another to activate a special effect.
To get a high level bonus,
you have to make a row of five spheres.
Yeah.
Uh-huh.
Bless it is your way, young wizard.
Do one more good deed.
Save 15 souls in prison here.
Is this too loud?
The five.
I remember the five makes like the rainbow sphere
and it takes away all the same color.
Yep.
Get all the gray ones.
That's a terrible bonus.
This shit's too loud.
So don't fuck with that.
I like this one.
All right.
How many souls?
15.
15 souls is what we need.
Oh, my God.
Okay.
How many more do I need?
15.
Get it.
You might, it might sound crazy,
but I would pay like $1.50 for this one.
Perfect mode.
Come on.
This is perfect mode.
Holy shit.
Oh, dude.
Dude.
You paid $11 for it.
Yeah, but I'd pay a dollar like,
I pay like two, probably like $6 for this one.
What do I have right now?
I need that five in a row.
It was worth it.
Look, I'm telling you,
I'm gonna get a cube one eventually here.
Got it.
You are what's wrong with kids today.
What?
Why?
How could I be what?
I'm playing like an old game.
All right.
What's this one?
Make a row of four to get this bonus.
It calls it so that you need,
this is a row of four.
No, wait.
They're both rows, not columns.
Mining sequence.
Yeah.
I think I want, hmm.
I'm gonna, I want more spirits on the screen.
Why is this so in-depth?
Do you want to take a break after this brilliant success?
Draw a deep breath and continue.
20 souls are waiting for you to release them.
Even, people are gonna get mad if I don't finish this.
Even though the mountains are snow-capped,
the struggle for the innocent souls of the future of
Tiroding becomes even hotter.
I told you I was talking about how hot I was.
Level two, one.
I'm gonna beat this game on stream.
Please actually win this one.
I actually beat this one?
It's fun.
I'm having a good time.
It's such a simple game.
Come on.
I need that, I need that perfect bonus.
Did I fuck it up?
Not yet.
Hold on.
Oh wait, it's a one, two, three, four.
It's all right.
Perfect bonus incoming.
This is so exciting.
Uh-oh.
Fine.
Give me some blue.
Um.
Uh.
Uh, this way.
Activate this.
Check it out.
Activate that.
The red one's bad.
It's like, why don't I just play Bejeweled?
That's like the good one.
This one's good.
Bejeweled doesn't have upgrade points.
Bad move.
Okay, I'm gonna try to get rid of as many
soul.
I got four more souls to free.
I'm kind of getting
over here.
Go right here.
Five.
Got it.
Do it.
Come on.
Ah, I had an opportunity to do that.
I'm just, it's perfect mode, so I'm freaking out.
Just five, five, five, five, five.
Two more souls in a minute.
Come on, upgrade point.
Where's it going?
Time shift.
Two rows of spheres of the same type, one after another.
That gives you 45 additional seconds.
This is the, make a row of four.
This is the vertical one.
Or do I want, yeah, I want the vertical one.
Vertical one's good.
Anybody else find it funny that every single level
going forward, the text gets smaller and smaller?
That was a huge bunch of stuff to read.
And then it's like, oh, and then a little bit of that.
One more problem to solve, but the villain is tireless.
You need to release 25 souls.
They had an elaborate, the problem over the
snowy mountain caps and through the treacherous dirt.
No, I don't care anymore.
I like this one.
I unironically think this game is fun.
I really do.
It's weird to say.
Let me think about this.
I got a minute.
It's because you're a casual.
Oh, this would be the last one.
I'll do this one off stream.
I'll play this one for like an hour.
It's Candy Crush with upgrade points.
Here's the difference though.
Candy Crush is a total horseshit video game.
And all the iPad match three games follow the same formula.
And that formula is the games are free to download.
But after about 25 levels, the levels become
nearly impossible to complete.
Unless you buy their little booster upgrades
to blow up a row that you could not get before.
So you have to spend like a dollar per little
axe that you can knock one of those blocks out with.
And every level after that is the same way.
Oh, we're in perfect mode.
Hold on.
Like anybody actually cares that we're in perfect mode right now.
Like, I'm going to look over here and see everybody going like,
oh, nice.
Whoa.
Cool, man.
I'm missing so many.
It's because I started talking.
Blow it up.
Fiver right there.
Oh, and it's a fiver into a four.
Into another four.
Bring it.
Oh, let's see what the text is like this time.
And I will move on after this one.
All right.
I have two upgrade points.
My magic book says you'll need to deliberate 30 souls.
But don't forget to use the magic gifts such as adding time.
I have to stop.
I have to stop doing this.
Right?
You have initiated.
So the same color.
And then I get plus 1500.
That's a lot of points.
You have hundreds of games to play.
That's true.
We can't get addicted to one of these.
What's this?
What does it want me to do?
How do you match this one?
You just match in between?
All right.
This will be the last.
Could we do have like another 150 games to play?
So this will be the last one.
That's it.
One more.
Time slow.
Nice.
There's a double angel here.
Don't worry about it.
Just get what you need.
Yeah, we need to get out.
I need to get like a huge explosion.
Where it's just like a string of like 30 things happening.
It's close.
Come on.
Let's see it.
No!
That was supposed to go the other way.
Damn it.
What an idiot.
Blew it again.
No, I didn't.
I was perfectly thought out.
God.
Why did I do that?
We're never going to get to see the crazy sequence, are we?
That's all I care about.
It just scratches my brain.
All right, we have four.
Four into six more.
Where are they?
Two down here.
Two blues.
That should line it up nicely.
Not really though.
Hold on.
I blew it.
He blew it.
Did I though?
They're down here.
Just got to bring some grays down there.
And some yellows.
And what?
I got a minute?
I got a minute to figure this out.
All right.
Nice.
More money.
All right.
That's it.
It isn't time to admire the scenery.
35 souls is what it's going to keep going up.
So this is it.
That's it.
This is the last one.
Five.
Got it.
Come on.
I got to keep it stringing together.
Five again.
Got it again.
Two fives on the board now.
Two fives on the board, ladies and gentlemen.
You see what's happening here?
I'm queuing up like five fives.
And it's going to explode the whole thing.
And I can finally move on from this addiction.
I can finally get out of here.
One.
No.
I fucked it up.
Why do I keep doing this?
Resident sleeper.
I know.
Trust me.
I'm very well aware of how resident sleeper this is probably.
But I need to follow through.
You guys see what's happening here?
You guys see what's happening?
Reds.
Up to 35 yellows right here.
All right.
Good.
Had it before.
Perfect mode activated.
Oh, got it.
Zeus is taking over my body right now.
He's making all these plays.
No, no, no, no, no.
Come on.
Get.
I have to do it.
I don't want it, but I have to get it.
There we go.
That's exactly what I'm looking for.
I didn't even do the thing that it wanted me to do.
What's next?
Up here.
Not anymore.
13 more?
Double.
Sure.
Take double time, bro.
All right.
I'll stop.
I promise.
After this, I'm done.
Which one?
This one?
Yep.
Ended on a good note.
Do I even have any halos?
I don't.
Where's the last halo?
What's over here?
Complete the whole game.
I can't do that.
Why is it not ending?
Oh, there we go.
All right.
So your wisdom is years beyond your age.
Use it to...
All right.
Let's do this.
It's a joke.
I'm kidding.
That was really good.
That was really fun.
It's the longest we spent in one the whole entire time.
Oh, no.
53, 54% of you guys
are going up and down here.
Gems of Amazon is currently in first place,
but not by very much.
All right.
What is that one over there?
This is just another match three game.
Oh, I'm like...
It's all right.
Gems of the Amazon is on here twice.
Okay.
Well, here's Gems of the Amazon.
Thank you for voting.
Oh, that's unfortunate.
Gems of the Amazon doesn't...
Oh, it doesn't open.
Saved.
Click on the other one.
I can't find it too.
All right.
I'll try it.
Let's try the other one.
Gems of the Amazon also does not open.
Both Gems of the Amazon don't open.
If you're going to have it on there twice,
at least have one of them open.
Well, one of them work.
What the hell is that?
Okay.
I already got it.
What is this one?
I don't know what you guys are looking at here.
Something popper?
35% for...
Which one is that?
That's Teapot Poppers.
Let's give Teapot Poppers a try.
Here we go.
See if I can fix the video settings.
Yeah, this is Teapot Poppers.
A lot of people have been waiting for this one.
This music.
This is a regular Nintendo song.
Let's try it.
I'll restart it.
That's Snake, Rattle, and Roll's theme song.
I've said that like 12 times over the last seven years,
and it never is the case.
All right.
Nice.
We're good.
And it opens in full screen.
Would you look at that?
Let's hear it.
What's the music?
Where's the sound?
Oh, okay.
Your cannon is near the camera,
so you scan, shoot anywhere.
Bounce your ball off of objects
to reach balls that are otherwise inaccessible.
This is just a snood, right?
Buster Balls.
What's it called?
Oh, the ball.
This is just power-ups.
All right.
Sure thing.
What the hell am I looking at here?
I don't know what you're eating,
but it's definitely burnt.
You left it in the oven for a little too long, I think.
That may have been a casserole at one point.
No, it is just Zuma.
That wasn't right.
No, it's because the objects.
This is not just there for fun.
Careful, guys.
These might start talking and singing songs about the house.
Like, really, at least.
It's horrible.
I'll do the sounds.
Fine.
I gotta get a string.
Awesome.
Cool.
Failure.
Working.
This music overlapping itself.
No, no, no.
Where we going?
Cool.
Frenzy.
It's pretty even.
What's up there?
I don't know how to play solitaire,
so I'm gonna veto that one.
I can't veto all.
I have to play all of them.
I'm gonna veto.
So that is...
Actually, it's kind of a fight between the two of them.
Crystal ice quest or crystal ice quest is...
No, it's not.
What's going on here?
Oh, it's because people can just spam click it.
Sometimes it just makes that happen for some reason.
Now you can't do that.
Go ahead and do it again.
What do I do?
Just click what you want.
Yep.
Just click the screen over a game
that does not have an X on it that you would like to see.
It's not working.
You might have to activate or click on this.
It's an extension.
So you might have to refresh the page.
There's probably a button there that you can press on the screen.
Maybe that's like, oh, he's got an extension going.
You're on mobile.
Oh, oh, it probably doesn't work on mobile then.
All right.
Looks like we're gonna play a crystal ice quest.
What are you linking me here?
Yeah, what about it?
What do you want me to do about this?
See, now the real joke would be if you were to put that onto one of the witch's faces.
I mean, that would have been well, that's what I would have done.
Anyways, let's go ahead and move back over here.
So we're going to go.
It was what was it?
Ice crystal ice.
This one is in its own window.
Thank God.
So hard.
I'm not touching any of these.
Get in a better spot for you to actually see what's going on.
Sound volume too high.
All right, let's play.
Uh, why does it stop here?
You have such a huge map.
This is it.
The link.
Click the link.
Hold on.
That is.
All right, let's go.
Let's take a look.
Oh, my God.
That was fast.
All right, level one crab.
This is, I don't want to play this too much for my brain.
I already don't think I know how to do this.
Move a piece of ice using the left mouse button.
Use the right mouse button for rotation.
You can throw unnecessary pieces of ice into the fire.
You can light the fire by using wood.
Each amplification reduces time of flaming up by 20 percent.
When the water is filled with pieces of ice, you lose the level.
Bonus purchasing.
Left click to bonus purchase.
Make pieces.
Press to make the next piece of ice appear.
Disaster has fallen upon the inhabitants of tropical islands everywhere.
A relentless frost has crept over everything.
Palm trees are iced over.
Fish are frozen solid in the seas.
Birds cannot take flight.
The Snow King has chosen a new location for the capital of his icy domain.
Only he and some penguins are happy about the frozen wasteland the world has become.
But fire still burns on your island.
You still have a glimmer of hope in your heart.
To return life to these once-blessed places.
Reach the palace of the Snow King.
Oh no, this is gonna take extra brain power.
This piece of ice contains a bonus fish.
Okay, I got a fish.
Okay, let's go, let's go.
Uh-oh, now I got it.
Press for use of the exempted bonus animal.
What the fuck are you talking to me for?
Part of fish.
Click.
The game crashed.
No it didn't.
What? I didn't, I couldn't even read it.
What did it say?
I don't know.
I have no idea.
Nope.
Oh my god, that's all it does.
What a piece of shit.
Throw unnecessary pieces into the fire.
Oh, the fire's gone now though.
I think I lost.
I think I lose.
I've only done diamonds over here.
I haven't done anything else.
Shit.
Uh-oh, where are the other pieces?
Come on.
Give me one more piece.
Burn it in the fire and that's a perfect score.
Level two is turtle.
Okay, this fills the grid, adds extra points.
I can't sit here and read that.
What?
What does the snail do?
Slows down time.
Oh, now they're introducing different pieces.
No, I gotta save these.
Nope.
No.
See what I mean?
Those have to go in here.
Fuck.
Shit.
What does this do with these?
Oh, then none of these are ever gonna fit ever again.
Press to make the next piece of ice appear.
Why would I do that when I'm already so far behind?
Oops.
I fucked that one up.
This one's fun.
I actually truly believe this one's fun.
What did I do that for?
That was such a not funny fucking thing to do.
Get it all in one go before they all fall in the fucking water.
All in one go.
Watch this.
It's my attempt.
Ready?
I don't like the individual pieces.
It hurts to try to do them one at a time like that.
Why did I do them like that?
All right.
We're good.
I'm gonna throw up.
I might.
I'm gonna slow down.
We can do that more than once.
I should have thought I didn't know what it was doing.
All right.
I'm not gonna lose.
I'm fine.
All right.
This one's fun, but I gotta move on.
That was interesting.
This game's actually cool.
One of the only interesting mechanics.
All these new pieces to bring in.
What a cool game.
I fucked it up.
That was interesting.
What was that one called?
That was called Crystal Ice Quest.
Drop that one down if you want to play it.
All right.
Let's.
I gotta pee.
Every time the stream has been up for two hours, I have to pee.
I need to get a urinal in this room.
Just mute the microphone and just go piss into the wall.
I wonder if I ever had a million dollars,
I would install a urinal in the closet behind me.
Think about that.
Think about how easy that would be.
So we're gonna play Solitaire, it looks like.
So thanks for the votes.
But honest to God, right?
Imagine if there was in that closet right there,
there was just a urinal.
And I could just slide it open and just go in there
and just the whole back wall would just be a porcelain.
And just all the way down in a giant drain in the bottom.
I just piss directly into the back of the closet.
Great.
Or just the floor.
If right here underneath me was just porcelain
and just it was a drain.
I think we've already said this before.
Yeah, we have.
We have talked about this.
Imagine you could just piss directly into your floor
and it would just go down into your plumbing.
Who wants to get up and walk down the stairs?
That's revolting, please stop.
What's revolting about going pee?
That's revolting?
Pee is revolting.
All right, Solitaire it is.
Spider Gold Solitaire.
This is going to be fun because I don't have any idea how to play this.
I don't know how to play Solitaire.
Not a single clue.
This is this image is fucking going to haunt me.
And it doesn't even matter because Solitaire does not open.
So we get to save ourselves about 15 straight minutes of me
clicking on random cards and asking if I'm doing it right.
And just for the sake of everyone thinks, well, he's a liar.
We've got a liar here.
Solitaire Gold.
Click.
You see the spinning wheel?
I don't see it anymore.
We don't got a game.
No game.
Still a liar.
We just cover that up and go again.
I will see you guys in two seconds.
I'm just going to go pee into my closet directly into the back of the porcelain wall.
And please vote for something that you'd like to see.
That's a nice traffic light.
Is this streamers choice?
It must be.
You just made that's just a train symbol thing.
The train sign.
There's a train here.
Railroad crossing.
I think that's what that is.
All right, so I'm going to play because people don't want to have
anything besides a long shape with two circles on the ends of it.
Not everything we draw is a dick.
Are you sure about that?
To me, this looks like it looks like people were drawing a very long shape.
And then other people came in to try to save this.
That's what I think happened.
What kind of a dick has six balls?
You know what?
How about we just move on from this topic?
And I'm going to play the pyramid of gold.
Now the train.
Good job.
This is this is a solitaire.
This is salt pyramid solitaire.
All right, let's see if it opens.
Oh, well, all right.
It's it's time for streamers choice.
I want to play the pinball game up there.
Ace's pinball wacky worlds streamers choice.
You know, this is really bright and painful.
This hurts.
Oh, Jeremy, we know your name.
Reset its transformation and just go like this.
That looks good.
So I'm punching you guys in the face.
I'm sorry.
All right.
So this is score is health options.
Let's just start.
It's pinball.
How is this pinball?
Oh, it's one of these.
That is one that's never that ball is never coming back down here.
Where is the ball?
Look, do you see this?
Which is too many balls.
This is too distracting.
So it's this one.
It was balls of bread.
Seriously, in a game where you have to catch the ball,
having all these other tiny balls throw off at the same time is just very distracting.
I hate it.
Multi ball.
What the fuck?
I got it.
I got them both the same time.
Thumbs up.
Hey, if you like what you see,
give the channel a fucking four out of 10.
This is kind of cool.
I'm getting a picture up back there.
This is cool.
It's not, but it is.
It's all right.
You get rid of these falling down crystal ball things
and I think you got yourself with a pretty solid,
let's break out type game.
This is where I get a shine here.
Oh, nevermind.
I got a bad one.
Those lemons wasted.
Small ball.
I've been holding on to this for days.
It's been like three days, two days.
I've been, remember what I was going to say?
Oh, thank God.
That's been trying to happen for like two straight days.
I feel so much better.
If you watched the stream yesterday,
that's tried to happen twice,
three, four times during that stream.
Man, I feel great.
That was fun.
I don't want to sit there and play it.
What was that?
That was, that was a streamer's choice.
It was a wacky pinball.
So we got another Solitaire game.
I hope it doesn't open and we'll find out.
This is Klondike Solitaire.
I don't think any of the Solitaire games are going to open.
Nope, none of them.
Might as well just get them out of the way now
because they're not going to open.
What would you do to play Klondike Solitaire?
Would you quack like a duck?
No.
Are you sure?
What about the delicious chocolate crispy filling?
I don't know about that.
Would you bark like a dog?
God, those commercials made me fucking.
Oh, go watch the Klondike Bar commercials
and just be like, damn,
I wouldn't do that for a fucking 39 cent brick of ice cream.
All right, cover that one up.
What would you do for a Klondike Bar?
Where is it?
I know the last three might cover this up.
I know it's a joke.
Where are we going?
Solitaire.
All right, Solitaire doesn't gold.
I'm clicking it.
It's not opening.
None of the Solitaire games work.
We might as well just skip them all.
Nope, it doesn't open.
I just clicked it out of.
No, try again.
Liar, liar.
Solitaire doesn't gold.
Nothing.
None of them are going to open.
It's because I've run.
I've, I've, don't listen.
I've run as administrator.
The whole thing is running as administrator.
And when I go in and do administrator
and compatibility, it does the same thing.
And force it to 640 by 480
and take away the DPI settings
and reduce arrow and all of it.
What is that one?
Fairy Tail Quest.
Let's see how bad this one smells.
Thank you for voting.
Let's give it a go.
Fairy Tail Quest.
It opens.
Hooray.
But, okay, it is.
It's going to be a match three game, isn't it?
I maybe.
No, okay.
Okay, hold on.
No, I know what's going on here.
No, I don't.
Adventure.
Wait, let me fix this.
Start here.
I get to read something in that.
Medieval fantasy voice that I do all the time.
Rotate chips to combine three or more bottles.
Yeah.
The game board clockwise.
Click them to the right of the board.
Oh, no.
I don't like this.
Yo, you have to open the...
Yo, you got to open the chests.
Okay.
To beat the level, you must open all trunks.
Bottles in a line against...
Oh, my God.
Do your own sound effects.
Again.
You want me to do that?
I need the music at least.
Okay.
Go.
I've delayed sound.
What the fuck was that?
The game like fucked up?
That one goes too fast.
I can't do that.
What was this one?
Adventure or something.
Fairy tale adventure.
There it is.
Go on.
You guys just going through all the ones
that have quest in the title.
No, that's the same one.
That's the same one.
They just put it there twice.
Why is it here twice?
I hope it doesn't open.
No, it's the same thing.
It opened again.
It's fine.
Here it is.
It's not a different game.
But here's the crazy part.
If it is a separate game
with a separate folder,
why would it still have Jay here?
I just opened it up again
from where I just was.
It reads your system name.
My system name is not Jay.
It's Jeremy.
My system name is not Jeremy.
My system name is marriage
because it's Jeremy backwards
and nobody would know that it was me.
You have to move the key.
I...
Why would I even begin?
It was the same thing we just did.
Restart.
Let's go.
Are you making fun of my username?
Your marriage.
Or should I say Jeremy?
Fast food.
I wonder what this one's going to be about.
Fast food mania.
It's got french fries on it.
This one looks kind of fun.
It is one of those games
that's stuffed in the corner
at 640 by 480 though.
This one could be pretty good.
Yep, there is a window log.
So that's good.
Right off the bat.
What the fuck are you doing?
I can't see where it is.
You're going to minimize when I do this?
Get back here.
Oh god.
It's scared.
It's just running away.
All right, hold on.
Almost there.
That's as good as it's going to get.
I'm sorry.
I'm not doing that anymore.
All right.
Looks good.
Play game.
Do you want to continue your last game
that you've never started?
One, six.
I can start on six.
One, six or eleven.
Why would you be able to do this?
Start.
Start on one.
Greenville.
Day one.
Today is my last day of high school.
Finally, my life can begin.
College, new friends, a great job.
Life's going to be good.
Day two.
Unbelievable.
My parents spent my college fund
on their new business.
The girl of my dreams, Nancy,
had agreed to go with me
to our graduation party
but now she's with Daryl.
A zeal upstart.
Life is over.
Goodbye, dreams.
In one day, this happens.
What a fucking journal.
Not even 24 hours go by.
All right.
You can't even have that be day
like seven or eight or like day four.
You can't have like this progress.
Oh my god.
Okay, it is.
Day three.
I need money but what can I do to earn it?
Next day, I'll work for a delivery service.
The most important thing is for me
to work fast and stay alert.
Plus if I do a good job,
the boss will pay me extra.
No, it's not a match three game.
Click on the product.
Click on the order.
This is horrendous.
This is barely a video game.
I need to see how the story plays out though.
Don't you guys want to know?
I mean, when does it end?
I need to...
Hold on a minute.
First of all, this...
I got a really important question for you guys.
This guy make...
This guy make $2,400 in one day?
Why the aliens invaded?
What does that have to do with anything?
I just made $4,100.
Okay.
On day five, I buckled down and worked hard.
Today I learned that if I deliver several orders
of the same kind in a row, I'll be paid extra.
Deliver several orders the same kind in a row
to earn extra money.
I did that, right?
You can queue them up.
Shit.
That pop-up was like a fucking troll pop-up.
Do aliens invade every day?
That's a real question.
That we should be having.
That person gave me a $2,200 tip.
Holy shit.
It's 10 grand in one day.
Delivering donuts.
And for my night job, I'm part of the Earth Defense Force.
We're not getting more lore?
600 bucks.
Just wait till it's french fries.
Who cares?
Oh, you have...
French fries?
Nah.
That's a donut double.
No, no, yeah.
I'll look at the donuts.
Don't get the UFO thing, but I'll get it 100% every time.
This is more fun than the actual video game.
So I made 20 grand in four days.
Here we go.
Day six.
Our mechanic says he could upgrade my truck
so it could go faster for short periods of time,
but he needs money for the improvements.
Okay.
Speed up.
That's four grand.
I know how to make my truck faster.
Click on the bonus icon to activate it.
No, geez.
Come on.
Got it.
What?
I hate this.
You guys could still click on the screen that whole time.
I mean, that was just getting to be kind of mind-numbingly painful.
But what happened?
What happened is I played the game for another three or four levels in a row
and made like a hundred thousand dollars.
And then did everything that I wanted to do.
What is that one?
Montezuma's Quest.
We can't click on the last row.
Yeah, I know.
You can't click on the top row either.
I wonder why.
Is it really a surprise that the top and bottom row is pretty open?
We're going to have to just do them in a row.
All right.
Montezuma's Quest.
Let's take a look.
What up?
What up, Jerma?
Hey.
What up?
It's just, is it going to be Zuma?
It probably will be.
Okay, the slide screen is selected.
Alt F4.
What kind of game encourages Alt F4?
All right, instructions.
Yes.
Oh, God.
I don't want to read this.
They have their one piece of lore and then the game starts
and then it's just a match three game.
Oh, I missed it.
Just pretend like I read it.
Oh, go back.
Can I go back?
Archaeological Museum, Cancun, Mexico, 1935.
Graduate student Emily Jones didn't know what she was getting into when she accepted
to some position at the catalog exhibits at the Archaeological Museum in Cancun.
We heard the job provided an opportunity to study some of the most amazing artifacts
of the ancient cultures that had resided in the land known now as Mexico.
While elbow deep and dull paperwork, she was drawn to a mysterious stone,
her edifice, in the center of the museum's library.
Ancient notes penned by a Spanish monk who had served as a missionary to the Aztec
tribes mentioned a similar structure.
He claimed it was a map pointing out to a secret Aztec city.
Numerous legends said that the city was resting place of Martezuma's calendar,
a supernatural relic that granted its possessor a long life.
The monk's notes said that sun stones that could be acquired in a game of magic threes
would show up on your iPad on a week to week basis, at least 10 of them a week.
But the stone construction bore no instructions for playing the game.
Undaunted, Miss Jones searched for the museum for clues to eventually
found a dusty box of colored tokens in a forgotten corner of the repository.
Noting that some of the tokens were adorned with gems,
the young woman began stealing them and got real rich real real fucking quick.
As each one of those gems is worth about 250,000 pounds.
When she found the correct order, the tokens disappeared though.
Leaving the gems behind, even more incredible new tokens appeared in their place.
I can't sit there, you know, if it's the same thing we did before, I don't think it's like
a waste of time at that point. That's a waste of time to sit there and play.
I found the good one, which was the bubblegum crystal ball one.
Now we're going to the hidden object collection.
I'm going to laugh my ass off if this is just all of them that are in the game
that are on the disk in one spot. Let's find out.
Pirates, Egypt, Zoo, Haunted. Let's see if we can find the witch.
That's all that matters. Where's the witch? That doesn't count.
There she is. Where?
That's great. The people that are actually playing the game. That's not the witch.
How is that face not a witch?
Might be. That's not the witch either. Can somebody find the vase, please?
There's a more button. Anybody see a mug? Or a mug and a roll?
Yeah, this mug doesn't work. That's a squash. That's a hamburger.
That's a noose. That has a foot.
It's just this one spot. That's unbelievable. Okay.
Well, what else? Okay, what do you want to do now?
We're only doing one more of these. I'm not opening all of them.
Pirates? Click the X. No, we're doing pirates.
Can you get it?
It's the same song too. Oh, it's...
These are all wrong. What are you clicking on here?
Why is everybody... a bunch... what's with the parrot?
Fish? You got a spider on your screen. All right, that was fun.
No, no, we didn't finish it. No, no, no.
Imagine this is what the zoo looks like. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait. Hold on,
before anybody does anything. Look at how fucked up this is.
This is the zoo when all the cages get let open. You're not going here.
Imagine how fucking dangerous and horrible this is.
It's like centipedes. The entrance to the zoo is right there.
They're all already escaped. They have a fence. Oh yeah? Mr. Alligator and Mr. Elephant
have a lot to say to you about that. And the elephant, by the way, is carrying
a giraffe inside of this basket and a cat and a megaphone.
And there's a tuba. Where is the tuba? This is the people that they've eaten.
You know, like a band came in here. Some lawyer, a witch was here, a farmer.
These are all people that have been eaten or killed here.
They even brought the witch in. The witch couldn't do shit.
There's nothing up here.
He's been so long. Get a hint. What did the hint do? Hint. Brush. Help. Monkey, monkey, monkey, monkey. What?
There's nothing here. There's a piece of wire or there's a hose over here.
Right. Okay. I get it. I understand. That was hidden objects for fun.
No, we don't have to finish it. Finishing it is not necessary. Did you have fun? Yeah?
Those of you that are curious, after we pick this. So it looks like, I'm not sure.
Is that Builder Bob or is that Adventure Tales? Probably Bob. Okay. It's Bob.
So those of you that are curious. Yes, we have this and all the X's around it.
Uh, there's also these. There is this one. Builder Bob incoming. If it opens.
That is Builder Bob. Builder Bob. Builder Bob. Where is it? It should be the right one.
There it is. It's Bulldozer Bob, not Builder Bob. No, that's what.
All right, come on. Open. Nice. Oh my god, this looks terrible.
I feel like my video card in my computer is just in physical pain right now.
The amount of resolution changes that my computer's had to go through.
Version 3.5. The best version, from my understanding. All right, Bulldozer Bob.
Your terrible crackling audio needs to be reduced. It's all right. Game speed, that's fine.
Start. Classic, advanced, or metal pack? This is going to be a Pac-Man clone.
So don't collect the bags of money. The bags of money kill you.
In what game does that happen? The bags of money are too heavy.
So I have to collect the bags after I crush them on the ground.
All right, let's kill this. Did he just take the money? He just took the money.
I feel like it's steal the money. That's kind of bullshit. Right here. Up, up, up, up. No,
don't come over this way. He's coming to get me. His AI might just be going in a random
direction though. I may be spitballing here, but I'm pretty sure that's not what a Bulldozer
does. Eat dirt? Oh god, fucking damn it. That's it. I'm not doing that one anymore.
Why does the Bulldozer have hair? I don't know. Why does Tom with the tank engine have a face?
There is no explaining it. All right, what's that one? Flybot? No, that's not the one we're
doing. Something Champ? Something Champ. It's hard to read. Billiards Champ 3D. It's got
3D in the title. So you can imagine it probably won't open. Let's give it a shot.
Is it going to open? Nope. I think more. I'm going to sneeze again.
Wait, why would I turn that on? I should turn that off, not on. What was the point of that?
Why would I? Why don't I want you guys to see me sneeze? There's no reason for that.
I'm getting excited so you guys can watch me sneeze. Now we're going to Flybot.
That's a huge amount of clicks. Flybot. You can tell this one's going to be good.
I'll show you why. Because Flybot, I don't have any idea what the guy next to Flybot is.
Take a look. Flybot is on the cover. I'm not sure what's going on here. Or what this is.
We've seen monster doors. But that's Flybot. He's the mascot. Thank god I was supposed to
get so angry.
Down. Turn it down. It's still too loud. I have to do this one at a time.
Now. I have to. Okay, so it's got to go down to the right. So we got down to the right.
I'm going to say like right there. Let me know if it's right.
It's a little off. It needs to be up. Go up like half an inch. Like that. It should be okay.
Just as good as it's going to get. Start game.
Frozen hands planet. Be careful. This is a very cold and snowy place.
The hands that inhabit this planet are frozen. Hence they are not dangerous. The
aliens on this planet are studying flies behavior in cold conditions. Your objective
is to save the flies from becoming icicles with rocket launchers, grenades, and guns.
Right. This is a first platformer of the whole package. Free all the flies.
Free flies. It's just raining hell at all times. Alright, let's go jump. Hints. Z, X, C, V. Choose
weapon. Alright. I only got one. V. I need to sit down on it. Okay. X is. Do you kill things
or is it just knock them out? I think he's dead. Did I free the fly? I want to save
that shit. Oops. What is the music that's playing?
I have plenty of energy. 99 energy. What does that guy up there for?
Box right on top is the worst. Alright, that's three flies. I got it. That's it, right?
Wait for transport platform. Alright. Impatient, but it's fine. I win. We just go again. Don't stop.
Oh, okay. Shoot at the switcher.
Alright, I'm gonna get there and then I'm gonna turn this game on.
Speedrunner, let's go. Look. Oh yeah, I died. Mission failed. The Earth is left
without flies. Click here again. That's good. That's a good thing. Flies are fucking horrible.
I'm glad. That's great that they're gone. Year 2009. April 38th. Monday. Yeah, the 38th day
of April in 2009. That was real fucked up. Remember that? No fly with any insect
dignity will ever forget this day. Yeah, that was the day when hordes of alien scum
attacked our little green planet. These monstrous green freaks had harassed three grasshoppers,
stolen spots from the ladybug's wings, but most importantly kidnapped all flies from planet
Earth. Some say they took a bug with them, but that information was later reputed by two
stampeds that insist it was a bear, not a bug. We can only guess. This is a writing assignment
for a third grader. This is a writing assignment. Talk about, give a story of how the aliens came
and took the bugs. The British intelligence sources have proof that the reason all flies
were awarded to the alien spacecraft is because of their brains, or lack thereof to be exact.
The aliens wanted to know how flies managed to think without having this important neural
organ. So far the aliens have performed one surgical brain removal to one of their own.
The experiment was deemed to be a failure. Right now all flies from planet Earth are packed inside
one gallon glass jugs and are hidden on five different plants. But the flies called John
and Hans got lucky. They managed to befriend the alien who had his brain removed. He turned
out to be a real groovy dude and let the flies out. In the room next door, John and Hans
have stumbled upon the latest model of the alien combat robot. Hans turned out to be a
great mechanic. He got inside and started the robot. John used to live near the pilot's
cafeteria before he managed to learn robots navigation system. They called their robot
Flybot. Now with such powerful weapon at their arsenal, they've rushed to save their
fellow insects. May the force be with them. May the force be with you. That was, I was,
I was a joy to read that. That was better than the game. Hold on. Don't click yet. Don't
click yet. I was looking for this game for ages. Well it's Flybot. Where are you guys going? I
can't tell if this is another checkers joke or if this is the one above checkers and it's a
hundred percent. Why? You guys that hell bent on the one that's above there. What is it?
This is Mystic Store. Mystic Store. I'm gonna have to change this if it opens.
Let's hope it does. Oh wait a minute. I spoke too soon. It's opening
and it's already in a perfect spot. Player one. These are shotgun sounds. Yeah they are.
They really are. I wonder what Mystic Store is going to be about. I'm actually excited.
All right let's go. To make an artifact for the guests, pick up magic elements.
You can cheer up a guest with the help of potions that finish the level.
Pick up magic elements and use them. Okay.
Once upon a time the wise elf L'Oreal built a store where he created magic artifacts with
the help of ancient spells. Soon after he left his shop and moved to distant lands.
Many sages and magicians have tried in vain to master L'Oreal's art. Since those times
the shop is empty and does not please the visitors with magic goods. But it is likely
you'll be able to master the magic of L'Oreal and become the owner of the Mystic Snort.
Day one of 25. Click a group of three or more similar elements to collect them. Look at that.
Make an artifact. Over time a guest becomes impatient. Oh I need to give you what? What do
you want? Wand of water. Sound effects are pretty good. He didn't get what he wanted?
Wand of water. Number two where's the second guest? I don't know this one's just kind of dull.
Sounds are all right but the game itself is just click on groups of three or more.
It's not that thinkable. Just the giant color on the screen. The door knocking made me go outside.
PSVR. Hey enjoy that man. Spend rubies. Buy the secrets of the artifacts of the rubies you've
collected. Who cares? I need 60 rubies. What's wand of fire? I got it. Wand of gnomes.
If I had the wherewithal I would take a one second clip of the
and cue it up so when I clicked right here it would do it. But I'm not going to do that.
I'm just going to click the X and save everybody's pain. I'm surprised that one actually
opened. Click away. Where are the clicks? What happened? What's going on with this pole?
Is it broken? Where is it? I thought it was not there. What the hell? I think it's screwed up.
No it's there. Maybe it took a second. Maybe I did it too many times that I broke it.
We already picked all the good games except for cubic frenzy. We were thinking about
our choices. All right cubic frenzy. Boy this is going to be interesting. Do I have
logic slider cubie groups? Click three. I need to change. Hold on. There is no options menu or
anything. Uh a second. I gotta drag it down to the right. Let's see how good that is.
How does that look? Eh close. Almost. Close enough. No it's not. I can do better. It's
just a little bit more. All right that's fine. All right what does click three mean? Click
three cubie groups or logic slider. Click three. Flood puzzle arcade flood.
Normal. It's the same thing I just did. All right I'm going for a full page of blue.
Only blue. I want a full stack of blue. Oh kids mode. It just turns into strawberries.
And now we gotta get all pandas. What happened? Have you used the combos?
Am I supposed to be moving them? No it's happening. It was coming.
Play the monster game. I already did the monster game and I didn't like it. Actually yeah I did.
Did I? I don't even remember liking it. Where was that one? Oh monster village is what you're
talking about. Monster village. Not monster doors. It's the village where the doors are.
You get to actually go in their houses now. Where the hell was this? I don't even remember
what. Oh it's cubic frenzy. Okay monster village. Let's check it out. Island maze escape has a rat.
Well we'll have to check that out another time. Monster village does open.
Private player. Play game. In a small town by a bridge lived a group of
hobsters. A whimsical race of inventors. They created an earthly paradise called monster town.
Word of the settlement spread across the land. Envious the evil monsters banded together in
a desperate campaign against the good-hearted villagers. Luckily Zach and Jack learned about
the plot and prepared for the assault. Surrender or we'll tear your town apart. We'll never give
in. Taste our bullets. What? Why is it only two monsters? Why are you only attacking with
one fish? Hold down left boss button. The guy on the top is doing all the work. Can I speed this
up? Catch it. Machine gun. This is actually kind of good. Bonuses and red circles have a
negative effect. Avoid them. This game. Good choice. Who picked this? Excellent choice.
Avoid bullets or hit me. I need to up the difficulty. That's the super weapon and then
you right click to activate a super weapon. Very effective. This machine is harmless but
soap bubbles it launches will hinder you. It's not harmless. Your rank is private.
I could hear the audible gasp in the audience there when I didn't get that.
Five. This game had upgrades. I could see myself playing this on like mini clip
three or four hours straight. Shitty games with banging soundtracks.
The stream. Not necessarily wrong. Rename the stream. Shitty games. Well, bad games
with banging soundtracks. I'm pretty much already done. I want a boss though. I'm
gonna say level one. Location one level five is gonna be the boss. I have to see
the first boss. Mute this one and do the sound effects. There's no way. I'm
not. I'm only human. I don't have to overlap sound effects. Not fast enough.
All right. There's the boss. I'm ready. I'm ready for the boss. I'm ready.
That's the guy from the cover. We just saw the ears monster. Now I can end this happily.
Incoming large enemy. I thought that was it. Two gumbos. Art. Art's not bad.
Game's relatively fun. It's a little easy. It's kind of a fun game. I can't click the X.
What happens if I get bite? Can you lose? They're just... holy shit. That was
Let's cover it up. I hate this wallpaper. Well, I'm sorry. I'll change it if I get a good one.
This next one is either pyramid escape or island maze escape. That looks like pyramid.
I can see the bottom of that. That's pyramid escape. Give it a whirl. Please wait a bit.
This window won't appear again is what this says. Why is there a countdown? What do you
mean? What are you doing? Why? Oh, all right. Hold on. The way to the treasure is shown on this
map. This road might lead there. Full speed ahead. Have you seen that? Oh my god. You
got to see this. It's fucking outrageous. I knew what was waiting for him ahead. No one
managed to avoid our trap to escape alive. We'll have a real cool time.
I remember this one. Remember? I remember.
Prize on his back. Just fine. Look at the game world. This game world has been created
especially for novices and kids. This game world has been created for more professional players.
Gameplay demonstration. That was a pretty good move. Can I get it?
Got that one. Two more? I think I can drop these guys down.
Right through here and then grab this last one. That's it.
Shift Z X. Move the cursor. Dig a hole. Why didn't you do this in the gameplay
demonstration for me? What the hell is that? I can't move. Just dig down. I can't.
Try this one. Supposed to be the easy one.
You got to be kidding me. Lost to pyramid escape. Yeah, I did. But that doesn't embarrass
me at all. Oh no, I lost to pyramid escape. Suck and what? Oh no, that's seek.
I thought it said something else. Because my window is a lot smaller because I'm not
full-screened over here on OBS. That's why I'm reading these so incorrectly.
Seek and find collection. We're getting close to the end here. Seek and find. Oh no,
is that not seek and find? No, it is. That's seek and find. Oh, where the hell is that
though? Game one. Is that on? Because I had to chop up a couple of them because they were
too big. There it is. Seek and find collection one. Let's go. All right, what clicking for
now? Old bedroom. Southwestern room. Flower riot. We're gonna do flower riot. Click anywhere
on either image where you spot a difference. Find all seven before time runs out. Yep,
that's green. Look at all these chatters here. Rioting. Um, there's too many colors.
I can't do it. Yeah, I see that one. This is horrible. I feel like if I lean
in and cross my eyes, I'm gonna see a magic eye image. This is a jump scare game. Yeah,
it is. It's the same kind of... All right, you guys do it. I can't look at it anymore.
I can't. My brain... Do you find them please so we can get out of this?
Nice, good job. Nice, good work. I already got that one. All right, which one over here?
What are you trying to get over here? I already got that one. We only have 224 seconds.
Doesn't this the one that boos at you if you don't do it? All right, come on. Help me. I honestly,
I think I broke the extension. I've used this. I've restarted it and turned it back on so many
times that I may have destroyed it. I might have to reinstall the extension after this.
Nice work. Power riot mirror. Oh my god, that's even worse. No, thank you.
Sitting room. No, I don't want to. No. Thirsty. Anybody else here thirsty? I need like more drink.
I need like a tall glass of water. I'm gonna go. I need to hydrate. You guys vote. I'll be
right back. Sorry this is the second break in like less than three or four hours, but I'm
gonna go grab the water because I had like a Coke and I don't want that anymore. I want
like a tall glass of cold water. Be right back. Okay, all right. I'm hydrated. I'm good to go.
Where are we going? I don't know where this is being clicked on. I'm gonna say that's
island escape. If I were to take a guess, island maze escape. Good luck. I mean I got a screen
here. Oh, it wanted to work. No, it didn't. V-sync. Be very careful because this one is
on the edge. Go ahead and do this. Drag it down. This one's so cute. Wait till you guys see this.
Island maze escape. I just fucking ruined it. No, I didn't. Let's go. Kids play or standard?
One. I tried to solve. What am I solving?
What do you solve? Solve it. I'm not sure what I'm solving here. So why can't I not walk?
Is it because of the different shapes? I can't walk backwards now.
Fucked up here. Walk back this way. The clicks don't register.
60% of every click doesn't work. All right. You saw that like how many times did I click
that? Two. One. One. What the fuck was that? Two. Three. Three clicks. One. One. One. Two. Three.
What? Why is it randomizing the amount of clicks it takes me to go?
Do it. I'm just gonna spam it. That's how you do it. I have to click as fast as I can.
Click and hold. It's not doing anything. Literally. Literally. Why? Get over there. Go! Oh, my fingers!
I need to listen. Get it in this bright spot. Mute the fucking audio. You ready?
I can't get back there now. I can't do it anymore. I can't do it. I'm sorry.
I guess he wasn't lying. That's a first. We think I'm just making up this shit all the time.
What do you mean he's not lying? If I say something's happening, I'm not going to pretend
that it's not like it's happening. For what? Why would I do that? Oh, it was left click. It
was left click. Yeah. All right. Where is that? That was called click between three and seven
times to get the character to move one space. Mind numbing. No, don't click on that. It's
not what's going on. I see 29% over here. 29% currently on garden land tycoon. Okay. Let's
give it a try. I'm going to have to change this. Casual Force Entertainment is the name of this
company. Cool. It's been over 24 hours and he's still going. Yeah, the stream has not turned
off. I know everybody wants to meet it, but it's one of those things where it sneaks away
when I click. That's not bad right there. All right. I'm ready. This what is called
garden land tycoon. You didn't hear the music. Harvest five bags of sunflower seeds to complete
this level. This is the number of points you'll earn for completing the level minus 100 points.
Okay. You will also earn bonus points depending on how fast you complete the level.
Click on the close button. Planning spot. Sunflower seeds. Now click on the sunflower
seeds to get an action menu. Water. The watering level of your sunflower can earn an additional
heart. The more hearts you earn, the more produce you'll harvest. Watering levels decrease
over time so keep an eye on them. Do the dirt thing. Mute the music. Why? I hate games like
this. Please clap along with the music. Why? Is it desynced? I don't know why it's always
desynced. Is that not synced? What is the delay coming from? Some weird OBS delay going on.
Here are your points. That's weird track that's taking the game. Remember this is
literally a quake ripoff. What the fuck? Play something else. You're right. I don't want to
give time to a game that's a quake ripoff. That was boring. Boring. We're getting real close.
There's only like 15 more. I think it might be that time to start opening them. They're
just blowing through them. Does it open? Yes or no? And yes? All right. Let's go.
All right. Where we going? Right in the middle. Flower garden tycoon. Oh my fucking
god. This is the same game? Flower land tycoon. Flower garden tycoon. It hurts my ears. I'm going
to mute that because it's going to hurt yours too. This hurts very badly. Holy shit. This is
terrifying. Hold on. That's why everybody wanted me to play this so badly. I wonder if this
one's any different. The lady is more scary than anything. All right. Audio should be fine.
My gardens. New garden. This one. Clean the screen. What's going on? Oh, it's actually just
a garden simulator. Give me one second. Oh, I forgot to talk. I haven't been talking for like
two or three straight minutes. I was too locked in here. Wait. It's worth it. Trust me.
I'm going to mute a bunch of stuff for now. Just wait one second. No, it's going to take too long.
It's going to take too long. I was going to have like 30 gnomes looping this loop and then
like fucking like, nevermind. It's going to take so long. All right. Here we go. You guys
right. I don't want to get gnomed anymore. Okay. No more of that. That was that was that was a
telling. That was that was every time I've ever been gnomed. This should be just throwing it
hitting the X button. All right. Where are we going? I think I just I just caused my internet
have a problem from that one. Like dropping frames now. I angered the fucking gnome gods
sacrificing every gnome joke. Stop doing it. Dick. All right. Where was the where was it?
I don't even know where the hell this is. No. Oh, it's right here. Okay.
Where was that gnome? I don't know the hell it is. It was called garden mania or something.
Garden fun. All right. It's time for streamers choice. Put the fire on instead of the X.
My computer will crash. I don't even know where it is. Where is it? It's right here.
All right. There you go. That one's currently on fire. You guys are real funny.
This is hysterical stuff. I mean, we're talking just like talk. All right. It's time
for streamers choice. I'm just going to go through them. There's only like 10 or 15 more.
All right. You've lost it. Privilege is gone. Somebody said I legit want mystic diamonds.
So that's what I'm going to click on mystic diamonds. Sure. I wonder the internet is kind
of having a problem. Sometimes it does this maybe once every couple of weeks.
Since the when it was fixed permanently, we drop a few thousand frames usually fixes itself.
So all right. Where is that? What was it called? I don't even remember what it was. Help me out
here. What was it called? All right. There it is. Mystic diamonds. Mystic diamonds. All right.
Options. Can I full screen it? I can. I'm getting into a fit here and I got to get myself.
I have to get myself. Okay. Quest. Pirate ship is mission one. Whoa.
Wow. There's a lady flying. Whoa. I can. Hold on. You can drag it. This is a match three with
hacks. This is no clip match three. Tetris. No clip match three. This is cool. What have
you said to play this? Good job. Good work. There is no limit. There are actually no limits.
I can go as far as I want or as short as I want or as small as I want or as big as I want.
No limitations. I just pogchamped myself into a headache. How did that happen?
I pogchamped too hard. What's that? Slow down. Wait. Watch this row. That's a problem if it
comes up here. Come on. All right. Now I think it's safe for me to be able to go like this.
Uh oh. Wait. Come on. There are no limitations. That's what I keep forgetting.
Just drag it from anywhere. All right. I gotta stop doing that. I'm actually going to give myself
fucking migraine. What? I can hear him. I can hear him. Pogchamping.
Like all these little breathing and mouth noises. Oh my god. Oh, that was, that joke was funny,
but that one wasn't. Minus. I didn't even get it. Yes. Again. Again. Again. We'll do it
again. We'll do it again. Wait. Wait. I get him. Nice. No. No, no. I gotta take, I gotta
take a break. I gotta take a break from physical comedy after what happened yesterday. I was
about to just fly back in the chair as hard as I could with an open mouth and I would have
got hurt and it would have been another one of those, oh wow, you'd like hit yourself.
I'm taking a physical comedy break after yesterday. Stuck in laughing. What's happening
here? Oh, I got it. I missed it. Gotta love that 10 second loop. Yeah, that was a good one.
Actually kind of fun game. That was that one called enchanted squares, mystic diamonds.
Gold runner? Yeah. Let's just go. I mean, are you really going to vote on like another,
there's like eight on the board. Gold runner. Let's just go. Let's do it. Where is it? You
guys just have to help me find them. There it is. Thank you. Gold runner. It's not gold
runner. There it is. I know, I don't even know what the song is. Is that a, is that snake
rattle and roll? I can't even, what the fuck? Bricks legends. Is it supposed to look like that?
That's her bricks legends. I think this game might be a little bit broken.
I don't think that one works. Gold runner. What else is here? We've got a hunt for treasure.
Might as well give hunt for treasure a try. Cash games. Probably hidden object.
If it's going to be. Did he notice? Did I notice what? What was I supposed to notice?
All right. Welcome graphics. Play relaxed mode. Complete the tutorial and learn the basics.
Find all the items on the list. There's more, somebody like burnt something.
Uh-huh. Find all the items in the scene. Look closely as they might be well concealed.
You can also find coins. Don't tell, what's going on? What are you talking about?
700,000 pre-recorded streams. You guys just play. I don't fucking care. I mean, let's be real.
Yes. Click dog. All right. Stop giving me tips. It's not the parrot.
Parrot. It's getting darker. Why are we blacking out?
Oh, diary. You click on the diary. None of you have found one item. Really? Moon out window.
I'm clicking on the spots you guys clicked on. There's nothing here. Click dog. I already did.
Why do you have an umbrella in your fridge? This person's fucked. This person. All right,
get the dick off the screen for a second and realize what we're looking at here.
This person has, they have an umbrella, a bowling pin, and a fire extinguisher in their
fridge, a mousetrap, a microphone, and they have poison.
This person has got so many issues. I don't even know where to start.
Imagine putting some of this shit in a full watermelon.
Two cooked lobsters in a balloon. Oh, this is slaying me.
One huge carrot. A fucking giant carrot. A live chicken.
The ice cream has a shell. There's so, there's so much in here that's worthy of dissecting.
This does not belong in the fridge. This belongs on the counter. It's a salt shaker.
A full birthday cake. All this stuff in here probably stinks. Imagine storing a cooked crab
next to a birthday cake and none of them are in any type of storage.
This cake is going to taste like dead salty crab fish. Oh, I can't handle that anymore.
I gotta go back. Oh my god. I don't even know. There's a baseball in the fridge, isn't
there? I need to stay here because there might be another scenario where there's another
fridge with stuff in it. I need a truck and a pencil. I didn't, I accidentally just clicked
on that. Where's the truck? Can anybody see a truck? Okay, keys. Are they keys?
I don't care. Just give it to me.
All right. Items to use. Puzzles to solve. Items to use. It's flying the plane.
My name is Gordon Jones. I'd like to come in. I called you about your grandfather's
disappearance. His plane vanished and stormed over the Pacific Ocean.
His dialogue options. Was he alone on the plane? Yes, your grandfather was a great pilot
and had rented a light plane for a day trip. How did he get caught up in the storm? I
don't know. He had access to the local weather report before he left. By the way,
do you know his company specializes in treasure hunting? Of course. Grandpa loves stories
about lost treasure. I want you to meet Dick Robinson. A German character name. His assistant.
I had the honor of working with your grandfather. He told me a lot about you.
Which treasure was grandpa seeking when he disappeared?
Our last quest ended in failure. We spent a year looking for an empty tomb.
I bet grandpa was upset. He was. Someone found the tomb and raided it right when we got there.
Shortly before his disappearance, he asked me to draw up his will.
According to this document, if he dies, the company is yours.
I'm his only heir? Correct. However, the will includes the condition you must satisfy,
and I admit it's quite unusual. That's just like grandpa. I'd be surprised if
all I needed to do was sign it. You'll have a limited amount of time in which to find the
items mentioned in the will. Do you agree to its conditions? Sure, this is going to be fun.
If time runs out, the company gets a new owner or is put up for sale.
Hey, that's Fang. He's from South America. During one of my trips there,
he clamped onto my boots so hard we had no choice but to adopt him.
Thanks. I got time. Let's go. Help. We're staying in this one. This one's great.
And grandpa, you sure were fucked up putting paintings on the ceiling.
Okay, why? Why are these paintings up here? They're all crooked. Grandpa took a baseball
bat to his house and just started putting like command strips on the ceiling.
Horse. We've got a skull. That's not it. That's not it.
Net tortoise on stairs. Yeah, but I can't click it. Net key butterfly.
What are you guys looking? Horse. Refresh. Net horse butterfly key. How much time is left?
I can't go in a key at the bottom of an aquarium guarded by a piranha. That's grandpa
for you. It must be hungry. We can't go in there. The time. Guys, guys, I'm about
to lose the company. I'm about to lose the company. That's a golf club. Why are you clicking
on the golf club? None of these are right. It's locked. Nobody clicked on the thermostat.
That's not even. What? Why? Oh, I get it. You guys are clicking on the bullseye.
This is fucking stupid. Where is a net? I already clicked on the horse. Give me another
one. What? Sometimes the dark hides important things. It looks like there's something behind
the plant. Use the net on the piranha. All right. Get out of here. I can do it myself. I can.
Net on piranha. Great. Now we can get the key without losing an arm. Get the key. Key goes
into the cabinet. Key on cabinet. Great. Now let's look inside. Might contain the items we
need. God, what a disaster. Okay. Got the calendar. Ruler, butterfly, horse, eraser.
Horse. I don't even know what it's bubble tape. Okay. Horse, ruler, eraser.
Uh oh. Uh oh. Horse, ruler, eraser, butterfly. Horse, ruler, horse, eraser, butterfly.
Horse, ruler. Coin. Horse, ruler, eraser, butterfly.
Grandpa taking his wedding ring off. What the fuck is up with that?
Eraser. Top left corner. Re. All right. Got it. Butterfly. Horse, butterfly. Behind.
That's a picture of a horse. That doesn't count. That's a picture of a horse.
Okay. Where's the butterfly? You fucking gotta be kidding me. Okay. Got it.
Found all the items. Where's Chad?
Chad. Now what?
Is there something we need to be doing? By the clue. I don't have a map. I'm going...
A dry plant? No one's been in here for a long time. No one has entered your
grandfather's office since he disappeared. It's a watering can. Bell number.
And the ship. That's a ship right there. Fuck off. That's a ship.
Here comes a blue screen of death. Click the link. Click the link. Wait. Hold on.
What do you want to click? That's a new background.
Oh god. I think the internet just died. Are we still alive?
I just like dumped out on the internet. I think we're still alive.
We're going to be running into another problem.
Yeah. I gotta make this right. Hold on. No. Just keep it where it was. It was fine where it was.
Uh oh. We're going through hell right now. Hold on to your hats. I'm currently trying
to wait out this latest internet hiccup. All right. Let's see what we got.
How is that a ship? But that isn't. Up there.
Huh? That makes no sense. That's a ship up there. Zoom in. I should try spinning it and
inspecting it from all sides. It looks like something is written on this side of the globe.
Five. Oh my god. This is going to be unbearable.
Just so I thought it's locked. I need to open this safe. Classic model made in 1957.
Unfortunately, your grandfather was the only person who knew the code.
All right. Are you guys going to behave? Come on. Help me out here. This is a tough game.
All right. There's a watering can. You found a large watering can. Water the dried plant.
That's not how that works. I just sat in this room for like three months.
I'm probably fucking starving right now. Is that a ship? Oh, it's a bell.
It's not the piggy bank. Flower, weight, bell, and number. Bell? That's a number. Holy fuck. How
did you see that? Bell. Nice catch on the bell there. Shit. Coin. There's a coin right there.
Alligator. I need a flower and a weight and a boomerang. Flower. Click the flower.
Oh it's the plant did that. I would that that was whatever. I was thinking of like another
I don't know. I thought that was part of the game world. Not part of the actual thing to click
on. Knight's glove. Not down there. Bell. Looks like it but it's not.
Nothing in that bottle. Uh-oh. It's going dark.
That's it right there. Give me a break. I know it. That's a hand.
What? Is that not a hand? That's not a glove. Somehow. Where's the knight's glove then?
That's a fork. I need to enhance. Click on the curtain. This computer is blue screened.
Dude's computer has just been blue screened forever. That's not a knight's glove.
God damn it. None of this is working. There it is. What is this?
No that's a boxing glove. Boxing glove. Where's a bell?
Oh everyone's freaking out and clicking over here. Where's the bell?
I clicked that like three times. There's the boomerang. Number bell and a weight.
Grandpa why did you make this so horrible? That's not a bell that's a pawn. Bell on the chandelier
but is there though? I keep clicking here and it's not doing anything. Why are we still playing
this? Because I need another fridge scenario. That looks like a weight doesn't it? All right
what the fuck are they talking about? It was the number two. Two six one five.
Yes I thought it's locked. Two six. I know. Two six one five. Open the safe.
Let's try one six one five. Abracadabra. And it didn't open because that's not what this says.
You got it wrong.
Abracadabra.
That's so funny. Diary. Let's say grandpa's social security number. Key bell and weight.
There's another bell and there was a weight in here somewhere probably right?
I don't see a weight. I don't need those car keys. Wait a minute. iPhone. Coin. Two coins.
Top left.
In front of the gold statue. That's a gun. All right help me out here.
Oh look who it is. Wait. Wait. How is this my desktop background but I don't have the image?
I have to get these ready to have them come up when they pop up.
I'm gonna add image. These are fucking perfect. But the hell am I even saving these to?
Save to the... Does this one have an alpha channel?
Now we're gonna get these set up. So they're always right here.
And then make sure that he is in the right spot. He is. Okay.
I'm gonna add the other guy. Okay. All right. I'm ready. Let's go.
What the fuck is this? It's another person. No there are two people. Two.
Oh Gordon Jones I presume. Yes. My name is Richard Rosenberg. I have a business proposal
for you. Do we talk in private? Sure. Let's go to my grandfather's. I mean to my office.
As I said I have a business proposal in which you might be interested.
I'd like to purchase your grandfather's company.
Why didn't you approach my grandfather with this proposal?
I approached your grandfather several times but he didn't want to hear anything about
selling his business. I assume he had a reason for turning you down.
Only his stubbornness. Had he agreed he would have been living in a mansion right then.
But who knows where he is. What are you saying?
Nothing. I'm stating the facts. Now will you excuse me? I have urgent business to attend to.
How'd it go? He seemed to be a very unpleasant person. I'd rather step on a poisonous snake
than talk to him. Is he dangerous? Let me put it this way. He tends to engage in foul play
and do whatever he takes. It does whatever it is to achieve his goals. Who's that girl?
Catherine Queen. She's the leading treasure specialist in Rosenberg's company.
By the way she's a professor of archaeology. She majored in ancient cultures and graduated
with honors. So that's who we're competing against. I have a rather tactless question
to ask. What did he say to his proposal? I said I'd think about it but now I have
a feeling he didn't tell me the whole truth. Take my advice. Don't believe in a single word
he says. Then I'll definitely say no. At least until I figure out what this whole treasure
hunting thing is about. Besides, where else could I find such an exciting job?
Glad to hear it Mike. Welcome aboard. He needs to be off the screen.
And then he really turns... visit the museum and collect all known information
about the expedition. Oh nothing. Sometimes you can find very useful things in museums.
Let's start here. Can we find any treasures from the sunken ships in a museum?
Of course not. But we can find a clue that will lead us to them.
I had a more romantic picture of what a treasure hunting would be like.
I know. The treasure map of a spade and a chest full of gold.
A chest full of gold would be perfect right about now. What are you looking for?
Anything that relates to the archaeological expedition and the sunken ship.
Please. Please do not touch the exhibits. This is a museum after all.
Oh sorry about that. I didn't mean any harm.
Please be careful. Some of these items are so fragile a single touch can damage them.
The only problem with this museum is it doesn't allow anyone to use the exhibits
for personal reasons. That includes treasure hunters.
What do we do now? We distract the guards using the fire alarm.
What? How's that supposed to help?
They're instructed to evacuate all visitors and leave the premises when the fire alarm goes off.
Well we have to find a way to stay in the museum so...
We could get lost in here. There are so many nooks and crannies.
I know. Look at the guy back here.
Um excuse me. How do we get to the hall where they keep the artifacts from Greece?
Gordon. Gordon we can t look for anything in the museum as long as the attendant is watching us.
Let s activate the fire alarm to get rid of him.
Help me search for something that would help with that.
Alright let's go. Why am I still in this one?
Is there a reason why I'm still in this? What are you guys clicking?
I can't click anything unless it's the thing that you need to smoke?
Have a cigarette. Oh the fire alarm.
The museum s heat detector which is connected to the fire alarm.
Use a small flame to activate it. A lighter or cigarettes or something?
A lamp? I don't know how to do anything.
Trust this. Why did you just link this to me?
It's me like sucking on swallowing hot dogs.
This is not relevant at all to what we're doing.
Not even remotely close to anything going on on the screen right now.
I clicked on the wrong one. This one.
Oh my god. This one.
We have like 30 more games to play.
Alright I'm just gonna do the cheat code.
I already did this. I know I already clicked on that one.
I need something that makes heat. Heat.
Heat. There are matches on the ground.
I mean that's a necklace.
I'm using these hints. I know. I get it.
I have to buy some more coins.
Do I need to go back to the map?
Hold on. So wait you're telling me that I have to go back into grandpa's cabinet?
Cigarette. Cigarette. Cigarette.
Spider on glow.
Is it backtracking?
There is backtracking.
No it's not.
Yes there is.
Unfucking believable.
You're getting shit in me.
Attention! Do not panic! Everyone leave the building!
Hiding inside this sarcophagus was a great idea but aren't you worried about the curse of the pharaohs?
Don't worry. This is just a replica.
If you knock on it you can hear it's made of plastic.
It sounds like stone to me.
Sounds real to me.
But there's no point in worrying about that now.
We're already inside of it.
When was the last time you saw my grandfather?
Week before he disappeared.
Do you remember what you talked about?
He said he found something really big.
Something what?
He didn't tell me. I only know he was going to Paris after his vacation.
I never realized how uncomfortable and dusty the inside of our sarcophagus can be.
I haven't heard any mummies complaining.
Now come on. We don't have much time before the fire department gets here.
No that was just a match.
The door has a code lock.
I wonder what's behind it.
We only have to pick matching pairs of numbers to open it.
So we'll know soon enough.
We'll definitely find something useful in here.
Spider.
Film reel.
Sea compass.
Police helmet.
I mean that's a...
How is that not a police helmet?
Is that just a regular bike helmet?
How?
Film reel.
I know there's a scary cat in there.
I see it.
I need spy glasses.
A bottle?
I know those two are outside.
Lighthouse.
Let's get these out of the way.
They're both right here.
This is all wrong now.
Let me change it.
I know.
Don't click this.
I know everyone's going to go...
Cat! Click on the cat!
Click on the cat!
Why is it 100% up here?
There's nothing here.
Glass.
Lighthouse.
Sea compass.
Police helmet.
A lot of S sound in that.
What are you looking at over here?
Why click on lady?
Well, that's a painting of a lighthouse.
Good work, guys.
I need three more spy glasses,
a sea compass, and a police helmet.
Everyone wanted me to go in here apparently.
Spy glass.
Coin.
Spy glasses.
Looking for spy glasses.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
People are freaking out about the police.
Okay.
I don't...
I don't live in England.
Okay.
That's not what a police helmet looks like.
Where I am.
It didn't say click glasses.
Spy...
No.
Those are glasses, guys.
Those aren't spy glasses.
There's a difference.
Sea compass.
That doesn't do anything.
Go back to the cabinets.
Cabinet.
I can't believe I have to go back in a cabinet.
Wall.
No, this isn't even right.
This is all different now.
This is just the bonus level.
This equipment might be new, but it's not new.
It's still reliable.
Let's watch the movie.
Great.
We can watch the movie.
And 20 years ago when Grandpa Stevenson went down to the pyramids,
he found himself trapped underneath.
After 25 hours of nearly starving,
Grandpa ate his way out of the pyramids with a spoon.
The pyramids, if you did not know,
funnily enough, I made out of cinnamon sugar.
What the fuck is this supposed to be?
Okay.
Found the camel.
I was waiting for something to happen.
I was filling air there.
You motherfuckers clicking on this every time.
The fish is dead.
There's no reason to click this.
The fish is gone.
Golden egg.
I don't need to be here.
This is not progression.
This is not progressing the story.
I'm going back.
I need a sea compass and two spy glasses.
Get on it.
Nice.
Spy glass.
Come on.
Get on it.
Everyone does the same fucking thing.
You click on the cat eyes.
The glasses.
I just want to just find it.
There's nothing here.
Just buy one.
What is it telling me to click on?
There was nothing here.
Huh?
Fuck.
The last one's in here.
Got it.
I don't have to do this.
How do I get back to the fridge?
It had to be done.
I'm sorry.
That had to be done.
It did.
We were trapped in that one.
That was very fun.
But we were stuck there.
I know it was the only one that we liked.
But we gotta get through them.
What was that called?
A hunt for treasure.
Finished another stream.
I might just open it up one day.
All right.
Next.
What's the Tahiti hidden pearls?
It's the one that's right next to it.
Don't worry, guys.
You're gonna get to do it.
We're gonna do it again.
Because this is absolutely by probably the same company.
And it's probably just another version of it.
It is.
It has to be.
Okay.
This needs to be bigger.
All right.
Let's go.
The legend of Princess Papith starts a long time ago.
On a beautiful day, King Pamir went to a magical place that was hidden deep inside
the Tahiti island.
There he discovered a magical pearl.
It was shining bright like the sun and blue like a clear sky.
He showed the magical pearl to his daughter, Papith, proudly,
who was intrigued by gems and pearls alike.
The pearl possessed a magical glance and the kingdom of Tahiti perished in its presence.
We are in need of your help, traveler.
In Tahiti, there are many tokens of mystery and magical items
to be found that will help you unravel the legend of Papith.
The hidden pearls of Tahiti contain the essence of Princess Papith.
Finding them and bringing them back together will help her.
You will travel to many locations and encounter many obstacles,
but the truth awaits those brave enough to endure the full journey.
Let us guide you in discovering the Tahiti hidden pearls.
Welcome to Tahiti.
I heard you are in need of a tour guide.
You wish to embark on a special journey.
I'd like to introduce you to a female tour guide, Ma'eva.
She takes care of adventures and
and seekers of mystical tales and lost fortune.
Hello, stranger.
I am one of the Tahiti tour guides and would love to show you around.
Since this is your first day,
I would like you to get familiar with the surroundings.
We will go.
It's just a hidden object, ma'am.
Hey, listen.
If it seems one of our guests has lost their guitar,
but I have to get back to the hotel.
Perhaps you could spot it.
You get an extra hint.
Find four hidden pearls in each level.
I'm not doing that.
If you click on the wrong thing,
it actually takes control of your computer.
There's a bike.
I didn't even click on a bike.
I don't want to do it.
We just did that too bad.
Seek and find collection two.
It's going to be a piece of shit just like the first one.
So don't worry.
You're not going to be missing much.
This one is paint sewing shop kids at play.
Let's do kids at play mirror.
Wait, wait, wait a second.
Wait a second.
What in the name?
What does the regular image look like?
What is this?
I don't...
So this is scary in one image.
One of these kids is missing.
That was a whole lot wrong.
That was something wrong there.
I don't want to play that one.
So where are we?
We have super staircase invaders,
star cosmic invaders.
Sorry, let me get that right.
Help you guys here.
Just terrible space invaders.
And it's so loud.
I got to be one level.
And then I'll be proud of myself.
Happy and done.
What's the big turtle ship dropping?
You can't play that for more than 30 seconds.
I don't think you can.
So then we got star...
Oh, it's by the same company.
Star cosmic invaders, star cosmic bust out.
Star cosmic bust out does not open.
How do you have one working out the other?
I don't know.
That seems impossible.
So what is left?
Let's give you a little bit of a tally here.
We've got 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 14 remaining.
Only 14 remain, except for these.
Now, I'm going to give you guys a little bit of an insight here.
Two of these we've already done.
But these are...
There's not much in here.
Trust me.
None of these are worth opening.
Going from top to bottom.
This one is just Zuma, but like 500 levels.
This one is just a Zuma again, but with like a thousand levels.
This is also Zuma, but like 20,000 levels.
This is just Mahjong again.
There's like a hundred levels in Mahjong.
I'll do this one.
This is super crossword games.
That's kind of interesting.
Chess brain teasers.
There's a hundred thousand of them.
This stupid...
Why do I want to do that?
Mahjong, chess, solitaire.
Solitaire, solitaire, solitaire, solitaire.
Some of these aren't even worth opening.
2002 games is like, okay, maybe we'll click that one.
Giving an excuse.
Well, I'm just saying.
Let's just see where we are when we get done with these.
We still have 14 of these.
You have to at least open them.
I will.
Each one of those is getting 30 seconds.
I'm serious.
So that leaves us with...
Let's start the countdown here.
Well, not yet because we're at 14.
We're looking for down here in the lower left.
Let's get some of these done.
Volcanic blocks.
The game is being optimized for quick download.
This happens only at the first game start.
What was it downloading?
I already have it installed.
Virus.
Full screen.
Let's get it off full screen.
It is 3D.
I think this is a 3D version of Mahjong.
All right, play.
Oh, okay.
To throw a rune, click left mouse button.
You can only throw a rune when there's another rune in the way.
Combine three or more runes of the same color to destroy them.
Your task is to destroy all kinds of runes.
Yeah, it's just Zuma.
I told you we're at the point of the 700,000 games
where every game is now Zuma.
All of them.
Just different versions.
30, 3, 40.
Best throw.
Cool.
We should just end this with Skate 3.
I'm not going to play Skate 3.
What are you talking about?
I don't have an Xbox here.
A Skate 3.
How do I go up?
I don't think I can.
What did I say?
30 seconds?
How long has it been?
20?
Spam this chip to help...
What?
What the hell is that?
It's a PS3 version.
I don't...
What the fuck was this called?
Volcanic blocks.
And right above that, flowers in bloom.
Check it out.
What is this spam here?
What does that mean?
Someone want to enlighten me here?
He said yesterday this would take 30 minutes.
Can you imagine if I had kept going yesterday?
If I had continued to play?
Because that was seven and a half hours.
So you're talking seven and a half.
Yeah, that would have been...
That would have been like a 13...
Almost 13 to 14 hours.
It's like going on essentially because it's been five, right?
12?
Flowers in bloom.
Let's check this one out.
Hello, sweetheart.
I want a trip to Paris.
Imagine that.
Are you going there alone?
Yes, it's a trip for one.
But what about me?
But honey, it's only for one month.
No, I miss you too much.
But I can't pass up this opportunity.
I won't let you go.
But honey, please.
No, you can't go alone.
I will.
I don't need your permission.
What the fuck is happening?
I...
I reacted horribly.
I need to do something special.
I could decorate her house with flowers.
I have time to arrange everything.
Before she returns, I even...
Why would you put them...
You have a month to trash her house and ruin it
and put flowers all in places they're not...
What wonderful weather.
This day seems ready-made for work.
What's that sequence in the beginning?
Oh, who cares?
The image of the house...
It's like...
It's not a gingerbread house.
That's how it was being treated.
You have a month.
You're going to spend a month fucking up somebody's house?
She's going to come back and be like,
Um...
Can you...
Can you do leave?
I got to...
Hold on.
I got to complete level one.
I got to see if there's some more lore.
Because that was just a tease of lore.
Is there anything else?
Do I get to decorate the house?
That's important to know.
I'm making good progress.
If I keep doing this well,
everything will be ready for my girlfriend's return.
Click on the highlighted plant to decorate the place you'd like to most.
I ordered these plants from the botanical garden for my girlfriend.
No one in the city will have more flowers.
Honey, why the fuck did you put them on the roof?
That's it.
I don't even want to see it.
I just needed to know.
That was called Flowers and Bloom.
And right next to that is Deep Sea Marble Pup.
But what happens next?
Can you go more than that, Cameraman?
Screen is fucked always.
Screen is fucked every time.
Each one of these is a separate game that opens in a separate window
that opens its own separate game options.
And there are 700,000 of them.
Fuck hints.
Let's go.
Classic.
That's the most roundabout way to get from here to there.
I don't even know where we start.
Where's the end?
Is this the start?
So, okay.
Zuma?
Yes, it is.
I told you.
Yeah, it's Zuma.
The fish just died.
What else we got?
Power pipes are right here.
Yes, I'd like to use my GTX 1080 video sync.
I don't even know what the fuck is going to happen when I press play.
GTX 1080 leaked.
Wait, wait, wait.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
We need to, I gotta back.
This is important.
We need to turn the music down.
I want to hear this guy.
Everything he says.
I gotta drag this down a little bit.
You let me know when it's in a good spot.
It's gotta be bigger.
Bigger and a little bit to the top right.
So, I'd say like that much bigger and then like up there.
Let's give that a go.
Not even fucking close.
Come down.
I mean, that's, we can fix it one more time.
This should be good.
Got it.
Perfect.
Okay.
I don't know what color off.
That's cursor.
It's not color on and off.
All right, let's, let's go.
Action.
Time trial.
It's just like a game.
Okay, buddy.
Listen up.
We have only two batteries.
You have to charge up the left one while the right battery feed the city.
To do this, connect both sides of the playing field by wires.
Then I'll swap the batteries, but be careful.
If the clips fill up the playing field, oh, you will lose.
Incoming air ball, air ball two.
Sorry, air ball two.
All right, this is called air ball two.
I'm ready.
New game.
This one.
We already played this one.
It's just another version of the same exact game.
No, it is the same game, isn't it?
Is there a difference?
Size minus.
If I can get it up there, that'd be actually pretty awesome.
Let me try to get it in the corner.
You know, you sneak it up there.
Get it stuck.
Get it stuck in there.
Come on.
Get in there and get stuck.
Noise.
Get stuck.
Rare loot.
That was so distracting.
It just made me almost lose.
Give me the bonus.
Rocket.
Holy shit, look at all that loot.
Magnet.
Power ball.
Extra score.
All right, I'm going to try to do this with my eyes closed.
Ready?
I got it.
Let me try to do it with my eyes closed again.
You guys don't believe me?
Fine.
No, that's not going to work.
Ready?
You have to, I have to prove that I do it.
So here we go.
Ready?
I got it.
I wasn't peeking.
I was not peeking.
Do it with no hands.
You can't even see the game.
100 levels.
We're in the final 10, aren't we?
Break ball time travel.
Let's see it.
Rapid fire.
Not going to open?
Break ball time travel also does not open.
So what do we got left?
Arc pinball.
Wait, we already did arca pinball, didn't we?
Arca pinball neo worlds.
No, we didn't.
This one looks terrifying.
It's another one.
It's the same thing.
It's the same exact thing that we just did.
This looks like Stardew Valley.
I can assure you it's not going to be like Stardew Valley.
If it is the same thing, it's instantly getting X'd.
Oh wait, it looks like it's the same.
How is this pinball?
It's a unique take on the breakout genre.
But who wants a, who wants a breakout game?
Is it just because they can make 500 randomly generated levels
and say it's 500 different video games?
I can't think of any person that wants this.
Not even old people.
Old people don't play these.
Your grandmother doesn't give a shit about this kind of game.
It's too hard for her.
Little breakdown.
Where was that?
Grandma pinball.
Is this one?
We've got Chinese chess.
I have no idea how to play this.
I don't have, I have no idea.
I don't know what any of this means.
Is it the pawns or can my cannon shoot his cannon?
Is there like a kill button?
What's the, what's the kill button?
Well, we both lost because green.
That is green.
It looks like black.
GG.
Idiot.
This whole side is almost done.
We just have fairy flower vines and vogue tails.
Fairy flower vines.
What the fuck?
You were holding the controller upside down.
I hope that was on the screen.
Match three or Zuma related.
What do you think?
Enclosed by mysterious mist, the magic flower land exists.
Above the ridge there's Lumendor, the famous castle made to soar.
One day an old prediction said, a day of whitening mignonette.
An elven girl will come to land in water,
Lily's leaf shall learn the magic of wildlife,
will solve new quests like playing the thief.
The mist will cover the earth no more and she will enter Lumendor.
And she was born and here she is and here's her fairy mentor Liz.
What the fuck?
Yeah, yeah, it's the pipe game again.
I'm going to turn the camera on because this is exactly the position I've been in for like
the last two minutes.
Fuck.
Oh, fuck.
Holy fuck.
Vogue tails.
Come on, vogue tails.
Let's go.
I don't know God all day.
Yeah, 3D mode is fine.
I just jump scared myself with my own face because it minimized.
Too much, too much, too much, too much.
There we go.
That looks fine.
Yeah, yeah.
I thought that just said Hillary.
No, hi Gary.
Okay, play.
Somewhere in the suburbs.
I wonder who else remembered.
One more present from grandma.
Top priority, open on 18th birthday.
She promised to give me her mastery secrets.
Oh well, I'll wait till the morning.
That night, the dummies woke up from an unusual noise.
The dummies?
Holy moly, a robbery.
Give it back.
Oh my, the secrets.
Wrong.
They went to London after them.
But where are we going to get money for tickets?
Wendy.
Was the guy running out of the house going like,
I'll see you in London, you pieces of shit.
How would they know that?
Well, now I'm completely broken and the tickets are expensive.
To work.
What?
Let's learn to make clothes.
Take a pattern sketch from the table.
And it's one of these walk back and forth,
diner dash fucking games.
Please wait while the sleeves are being steamed.
You want a green dress.
Look at the magazine.
Who is on this magazine?
Did she just eat it?
She's eating these clothes.
Excellent.
You have your first sale.
Click on the money to take it.
If you complete the orders quickly,
just like now, you'll get a tip.
$27 tip.
Throw it out the window.
You threw the dress in the trash.
You couldn't just put that on sale.
Somebody would have bought it.
Open the store.
Green dress.
What a waste of materials.
And a blue coat.
That's closer to the uh-oh one that I was talking about before.
Same lady, you're back.
Could I have another one of those green dresses again, dear?
Steam it.
Oh, marvelous.
That was...
It was.
I don't remember.
What was it called?
Oh, Vogue Tail.
Oh, we are down to the last...
Where are we?
We've got Astro Color Twist.
And...
Okay.
Astro Color Twists.
Oh, there's also one more.
There's...
What is it?
Something...
I can't even read what it says.
Let's see.
Okay.
Oh, that one right now.
That is Lovely Kitchen.
Let's do Lovely Kitchen.
Powered by TGV Blam Games and Selectsoft.
Free recorded stream.
Ah, it's not.
Nah, it ain't.
All right.
Hello.
Simulation mode.
Casual...
This is...
This is Diner Dash.
Yes, it is.
It's just Diner Dash again.
But just called something else.
Hi, my name is Mary.
I'll tell you an exciting story about myself.
When I was a child, I dreamed about opening my own restaurant.
I wanted to become a famous cook.
I played for hours imagining I'd make tasty dishes in my restaurant.
And give them to my friends and relatives.
You would feed your friends sand cakes.
And you made them have indigestion.
And you caused them a lot of fucking digestive problems.
Thanks to my mom, I mastered the basics of cooking.
It's more sand.
That's all we eat here, is sand.
I've grown up and entered the culinary academy for a restaurateur.
There's sand under there.
After graduating the academy, I decided to make my dream come true.
So I started to look for suitable premises.
I love this image so much.
My dream has come true.
Hello, opening.
Now we finally met.
My name is Mary.
This is our first working day.
Our clients are waiting for the restaurant.
Good luck.
Don't start the tutorial.
I know what to do.
Wiping your brow with sweat and you're gonna touch food.
Do you and your four twins care if you sit together?
Did everybody want cupcakes?
All right, I got two cupcakes.
You.
Coffee.
And you want, what is that?
Tomatoes?
What are you, what is that?
I don't know what that item is.
It's not here.
Just, well, it's just baloney.
He just wants baloney.
Give me some baloney.
Microwaving and your dream restaurant.
You gotta be fucking kidding me, mate.
You just opened the fucking place.
And you're already microwaving frozen fucking food.
Oh my God.
I can't even put this shit down.
How do I put this in the trash?
But I mean, that's absolutely fucking, that's a disgrace.
Microwave.
Where's my fucking microwave baloney?
This is bullshit.
I want four slices of baloney on a piece of white bread.
And I am living that I don't have it.
I'm gonna give your restaurant two stars.
I don't know how to, I can't do this.
I fucked it all up.
Can I leave?
Can I close?
That's it, I'm outta here.
Can I just, can I deck him?
Holiday Rush.
Sounds fun.
Let's give it a try.
Rule of thumb, these games are right next to each other,
which means it's gonna be a reskin of that game.
But Christmas time.
Maginmon?
Maginmons.
Yeah, I see it.
What am I gonna do?
You think I'm just gonna skip it?
Holiday Rush.
Career or survival?
Survival.
I don't get it.
How do you survive that?
Please select starting episode.
Episode one.
Start game.
Another job search.
Looking for waiter, looking for janitor, looking for salesman.
It's time to start my own business.
Something that would be profitable and also make people happy.
What it could be.
That's enough.
Tired of working for somebody else.
These people need a good vacation.
Oh, a travel agency.
No sooner said than done.
Here's my office.
Well, it's nothing special, but you have to start somewhere.
Now everyone start working.
Don't keep the customers waiting.
Hold on.
So Guy, Guy is actively talking about how he's
looking for a salesman, waiter.
Like, I don't want to work for somebody else.
And like, I want to make somebody fucking happy.
How could I make somebody happy?
And not be like a shitty boss, work for someone else.
Get to fucking work and don't keep people waiting.
You flipped real quickly, man.
You went through the evil villain arc.
It's less than fucking one panel.
Welcome to the travel agency.
It's time to learn the basics of the tourist business.
Get ready to help our first customers.
First.
Okay.
This is your first customer.
Click on her to find out what kind of vacation she wants.
Please wait while she considers her choices.
It's a very odd place.
She wants a resort tour.
Now take the blank paper sheet from the stand.
And give it to a worker responsible for resort tours.
Wait until she completes her work while you stand there.
She's just angry.
Look at how fucking mad they are already.
This is a hellish work environment, apparently.
What the fuck was that?
After receiving his order, now take the customer's order.
If you pick up the incorrect item, you can dump it into a trash can.
What did I do wrong?
Oh, the paper, right.
It's for $420.
Excellent work at Cheaty Legs, this is guaranteed.
New service discount tours.
And it's just another desk.
My whole computer just locked up.
Hopefully we're still live.
We are.
Okay, good.
That was holiday rush.
I don't know why that's not called travel rush or agency rush.
Why holiday?
Well, holiday is English.
It's a European term for going on vacation, right?
I thought it was going to be like Christmas presents.
All right.
That leaves us with only one or two that remain.
Astro color twist.
But that's all, hold on a minute here.
That's also, that's part of this.
So we have magic, magic mons.
Here we go.
Everyone's been waiting for this one.
People have actually been waiting for this one.
Doesn't open.
Hold on, let me try a different tactic.
Let me try, let me see if I can do what I can in the folder.
Every time we try to do this, it doesn't work.
But maybe the one time for the last one here, it might work.
I'm willing to give it a shot.
There it is.
Let's make sure we got this in full compatibility mode.
Administrator, it's on.
We've done this before.
Let's see, is it going to work?
Sorry, let me hold and change.
Maybe let me change one thing.
Hold on.
What about disable full screen optimizations and reduce color mode?
And actually, I don't want to do that.
Let's try this.
Not going to happen.
I was waiting for so long.
And just like that, all of the actual video games have been opened or lack thereof.
Did the fire crash?
The fire crashed.
It's not even running.
What a journey.
Thanks everybody for joining me on that journey.
Now we have a few more to open.
This one, by the way, is going to be rapid fire crystal caverns.
Crystal caverns of Amon Ra.
Astro color twist is on this list.
Don't worry, don't worry.
Oh, look it.
It's Zuma.
Can you believe it?
Wow.
I'm glad we opened this one.
Glad.
Very glad.
Very, very glad.
Let's start.
Enter your name.
Dick.
Okay, Zuma, Zuma, Zuma.
But this one, can I please just put the X on that one?
It's the same one.
It even shows the balls.
It shows the balls flying down.
It's the same one.
You're not going to let me skip this one.
I really have to click dynasty of Egypt.
This line of the next three or four are all Zuma's.
It's actually the same thing.
Look, start.
I wonder what's going to happen when I press start.
Oh, enter your name.
Saint Font.
Yeah, yup, yup.
Oh, this one's a little different though.
This one.
Take a look.
Buy Maginmon's on Amazon.
If it doesn't work in this game pack, why would it work if I bought it standalone?
Fuck, I wanted to end this before this happened.
Okay, good.
I almost just clicked on the X on OBS.
I hope you guys understand that.
I moved my mouse up to click on the X on OBS.
Just get it on the Wii.
Buy Magin...
Hold on.
Let me just look this up.
Maginmon's.
Maginmon's Electronics.
Everyone unlock the power of the Maginmon's and a faraway kingdom live the Maginmon's,
magic pets that help the good wizards keep the forces of the world in equilibrium.
But that stability is threatened when a powerful evil sorcerer captures the Maginmon's
and hides them in his dark catacombs.
Without their influence, the imbalance of magical energy could tear the whole kingdom apart.
The great council of wizards has chosen you as their companion.
Now you must travel deep in the labyrinths of the dark wizard.
Bring back the mighty Maginmon's and restore the natural balance.
Over 30 levels.
There is not one single result under videos for Maginmon's.
Not even one.
How is that possible?
No one on earth has done this.
But it's going to be a match three game.
We don't know what this is.
It's going to be match three, guys.
It's not going to be anything spectacular.
Corner the market.
Be the world's first Maginmon's streamer.
There's a free demo.
This shit's Zuma.
Look at it.
Is this Pac-Man or Zuma?
I don't want it.
Look at that.
Look at the image.
No, that's a Pac-Man like Zuma game.
I don't care.
It's just another Zuma game.
We have so many other ones to play.
Oh, jewels of the Nile.
I remember when I had the Nile River.
I remember when I went there.
I've seen it.
When I got there, as you see, there's these red, orange, and green balls.
I'm happy that I'm opening all these.
I missed it.
Fuck.
Gives the credits every time.
You might want to see a doctor.
For what?
What's wrong?
Mahjong.
Hexagon.
I actually am looking forward to Super Word games.
I feel like that's going to be sick.
So here are the thousands of games here.
Seagull.
Yep.
Magic Mons are riot.
It's not going to happen.
You're going to be so disappointed.
I'd rather you think it's good.
So in your mind, it'll always be good.
This is the part I'm talking about here.
Super Word games 10,000.
Word search.
Quickie crosswords.
Word scramble.
Hang man.
Absolutely.
Thank you.
Economics.
And we're going to do economics three.
What the fuck does that do?
I choose hang man.
Play click.
Play click here.
And choose mode.
Choose category.
Mode is just levels mode.
Press play.
Economics.
No.
Category economics.
Puzzle random.
That's fine.
Can't take much more of that music.
All right, so this is economics.
A.
It's got an A in there.
R.
Oh, he doesn't want to get too many books.
Hair.
Economics.
Tear.
So what was it?
Question.
Testion.
Quizilla.
Zow?
Wee Zow?
Wetzel?
Isn't Wetzel?
Pretzel?
Quetzel.
Erd.
O-T-E-R-R-D.
A-T-E-R-R-Y-D.
Atoward.
Cat.
Category.
Currency.
It's not currency.
Skateboard.
What?
Oh, it's a-
The-
Economics.
That's a great economical theory there, the skateboard.
Don't you love that?
Category.
Biology.
Frogs.
Ants.
Eggs.
Not even one letter.
Really.
Biology.
A-
Easter.
N-
That's the endotherm.
The ender dragon.
A-
Something-
A-a-a-a.
I-
I-a-a-a.
O-a.
B-a.
T-a-
What's-
What's the-
What's this?
Huh?
R.L. Stein.
Famous people.
Oh, it's not biology anymore.
I thought it was like a-
I thought it was like a fucking Pythagorean theorem.
You know what I mean?
Famous author.
K-A-
K-A-a-pla-
Apple. K-A-Apple. All right. Biblical. J-E-S-U-S. Dammit. G-O-D. Dammit. P-E-T-E-R.
Esther. Easter. What? E-A-S-T-E-R. Okay. Okay.
Alicia. Famous people in history. What? I didn't even press Y. A famous singer. Remember,
this is circa 2004, probably. I only have 30 seconds. Oh, no.
No. Victoria. Victoria. Victoria. Victoria. Victoria. E. Oh, okay. I got it.
So, we're building more time here. I like this. Locations. Anne. Anne-Anne.
Anne. Bann Tan. Bann Tan. Bann Tan. That, what's his name? Bannamus Tannamus?
What's his name in the show? That's his location. Tunnel. It wasn't Ban.
Another location. All right. One more. No, oh yeah. One more.
Locations. The- and. No. Or, for.
Do, oh, something, something, something, the, something, something, for, something, something,
and, something, something, e, t, something, something, v, something, something, r, something,
something, i, oh, riot, something, something, shp, uh-oh, something, point, New Zealand,
something, point, New Zealand, I don't know what's there, new, noom, noor, noo, noochie,
noochit, noochit, no, nood, nugget point, oh, it's nugget point, okay, all right, got
it, famous people singers, Duran Duran, Tony Hawk, why would I do a W, you just said
Ben 10, Bean Teen, Tori, Tori, Tori Aoli, Tori Aoleo, last one, this is it, biblical,
J-E-S-U-S, no, what was it, it was Elisha, is he gonna first try, that didn't count,
mythology, it's just repeating it, isn't it, what, endem form, endems, that's not
even right, it's different, it's different this time, it's actually different, Enderman,
end, end, the meme, endimism, endimism, that one didn't count, one more, famous
people singers, last one, here we go, Natasha, Natasha, what was it, a Y, why would they
be a, Natasha Beffington, Beddingfield, all right, one more, birds, O-S-T-R-I-C-H,
Parrots, Aardvark, a parrot, I don't know, last one, finally, final, final, final, final
one, it's a bird again, it's a bird and it's gonna be O-S-T-R-I-C-H, fuck, I thought
it was there, I thought that was it, Hornets, damn it, all right, I gotta get one more,
birds, what's a three letter bird, doe, no, that's a sheep, that's a fawn, owl, it's
not owl, emu, a ganu, a ganu, it's not a ganome, it's not a ganu, what, no, no, no,
I needed to know, I needed to know what that was, what happened, what was it,
holy shit, I hate that, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, Tyrannosaurus, that wasn't
very relaxed, all right, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay,
okay, crossword, crossword puzzle, we're gonna do fruits, fruit four, okay, so
we got cross, Marionberry, I have no idea, we also have banana, these aren't even
numbered, how am I supposed to do this, is this just two, is this two across,
this is not even listed, oh my god, what, down, pear, I don't get it, what is this
doing, fig, Newton, well that game sucks, word search, electronics,
electronics one, domain, digital application, what word is this,
what is this, this is electronics one, application asynchronous, got it,
Toonbroom, Trombone, Trombono, what, it's not Trombone, Trombone, Trombone,
Trombone, what, this is wrong, it's not Trombone, how the hell was it not
Trombone, what was that, if it wasn't Toonbroom or Trombone, Slippery, Slip,
Slippralo, Sirloin, Sirlplue, the Swirlpool, the Swirlpool,
Swirlpool, single reed instrument, I don't have any idea what a single reed
instrument is, clarinet, there's no C, tuba, got it, what else you got,
vacant, vacuum, octave, kazoo, kebab, cabal, from Mortal Kombat,
what, so this is all single reed instruments, I got us out of there,
we had to do it, chess, Sudoku, I don't know how to play Sudoku,
I have no idea, that's loud and I'm very sorry it is, no it's not,
it's already turned down, I have no idea how to do Sudoku,
not a single clue, I've never played it before, I don't fucking know,
no idea, this is probably really cool,
somebody would think this is really fun maybe, I did it, solved it,
I win, I don't know, I don't want to do that, I clicked it,
you can't say I didn't, chess, solitaire, more chess bullshit,
this one's just bigger, this one's just a bigger version,
this one's just huge, what happened, I mean I did it fucking easily,
I had soap on my hands for that one, I got like slipped on it,
chess, reversey, it's got reversey, oh my fucking god,
chess brain teasers, I wonder what it's going to be, can you guess,
the fucking balls, the balls, look at this, do you understand the balls,
let me show you some balls here, look at the balls,
just look at these balls, put your face on the screen,
100,000, 100,000, 100,000, 350,000 games on this disc
are levels in those stupid chess brain teaser games,
this is half of every game on this whole entire collection,
are chess brain teasers, the balls, now let's do mahjong, 25,000,
what the fuck does that mean, I don't know what that was,
that was, okay, that was scary current gen computer horror movie shit,
that probably happens in unfriended, I wouldn't be surprised,
chess magic 30,000, sorry it's not 350,000, it's 380,000,
380,000 games, this is 2002 games, very, very, very vague,
let's see what it is, oh my god,
I wonder how a different animal herder one is going to be
the animal herder six, this is alien ship shoot,
oh my fucking god, it opened a virus window,
what, oh, nice pop out window, no, I can't even play it like this,
what the fuck is happening, I got it,
they were making better games 30 fucking years ago,
this is uncalled for, faster, faster, faster, faster,
I got it, no I didn't,
aliens are taking over the world, game over, hold on,
use your rocket to shoot the evil alien spaceships,
hit space bar, button, I can get this,
I'm so used to how fast it was going before,
oh man, I got it, that hit box, got it,
I can't get past 22, oh, I got to get past 22,
no, get out, get out, there are, alien shoot one,
that's not even the right one, this is the correct one,
one, two, three windows, let's go, alien ship one,
the difference is that the rocket is a different image,
I bet you 100 million dollars that alien ship two
is going to have a different college ship, 21,
oh no, I don't think it's possible to go past 22,
I don't think it is, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27,
oh, it's alright, X, alien ship two,
I definitely have a virus, see, look, who cares,
just look at the thumbnails, yep, that's a different ship,
that's a different ship, that's a different ship,
that's a different ship, this is alien snipe show,
boy, this is going to be fun, no audio either on any of these,
instructions, the objective of sniper is to take down
as many armed opponents as possible,
to shoot an enemy, use the mouse to position the crosshair
over the enemy and the left mouse button to fire,
for each enemy you shoot, you will be awarded 15 points,
but watch out, the enemy shoots back,
your health meter will decrease when you're hit,
every 30 enemies killed will progress you to the next level,
but be careful every time the level progresses,
the enemies get a little bit smarter,
and the weapons get a little bit stronger,
as you play you will encounter power-ups,
health packs, and shields, I'm ready,
this such severe lag here on this mouse,
am I walking forward, you'd get an F in a game design class
if you fucking presented this, I can't do it anymore,
oh my god, I deleted everything,
sorry, we can get right back into 2002 games,
okay, the difference is they're robots,
they're a different kind of alien,
they're an animal herder one,
which one do you want to play the most,
lions, tigers, chickens and donkeys,
cats, donkeys and shih tzus,
foxes, bears and hyenas,
or gorillas, or dinosaurs, elephants,
and birds, I guess this one,
move your cursor to herd the animals into their correct pen,
your cursor will repel the animals,
so you have to maneuver them from behind,
if all animals are correctly navigated,
okay, I think I get it,
the first sound, Jesus Christ,
what was that noise,
what the fuck is that noise,
oh god, they're falling,
they're falling out off the planet,
good try, you got six animals,
I don't think I will,
asteroid fight,
there's ten of these,
I'm going to pick this random one,
this one has audio,
asteroid fight, click here to start game,
this hurts my eyes,
I'm not playing any of these,
baby beaver,
the stork is dropping a bunch of baby beavers,
earn points by catching them with a time bonus for every ten items,
catch the clocks for extra time,
did I just kill one,
oh, I'm killing them,
oops, I don't know what that was,
okay, this bounce out,
I'm not playing it,
bows and arrows,
this one doesn't even have a starting screen,
press F to fire,
oh, I don't even need to do it again,
that was fucking beautiful,
bubble bugs,
click and drag with a bubble wand to blow a bubble,
around a bug,
the more bugs you capture in a bubble,
the more points you get,
this bounce out,
I'm not gonna play any of these,
next one is called car dodge,
gotta find the right car,
I'm gonna say this one,
car dodge,
okay, ready,
I don't even understand how,
I feel like I could make this game,
I think I could,
chicken cross,
are we at the point where it breaks the computer?
chicken cross don't open,
I broke it,
I don't understand how that's possible,
I'm doing this the fastest anyone's ever done this,
no, no,
I,
you fucker,
it's impossible,
get out of my way,
I did it,
you can't win,
you can't, it's not possible to win,
it's not possible to win,
even with superhuman fucking strength,
I can't beat it,
the headphones out, I'm gonna get on the ground for this,
I gotta get on the ground,
I'm still here,
it's not possible to win,
fuck this dumb game, I can't fucking believe it,
it's not fucking possible,
I can't believe it,
chili race, can't win,
how to keep an idiot busy,
I refuse to read that,
you just said that I'm just bad,
no human clicks as fast,
as German985,
no human alive,
download an auto clicker,
I don't even know where you get an auto clicker,
hold on,
auto, auto clicker,
just auto clicker, that's what it is,
I'm getting it, I need to know,
this is just like an exe file,
is this safe,
is the auto clicker from sourceforge safe,
it's just an exe,
yes, I've used it, okay,
don't say no,
this is actually a virus,
no, one guy did say that,
but I trust him,
okay, here we go,
auto clicker is open,
here we go, okay,
I'm ready, click interval,
repeat,
50,000 times,
now just repeat until it's stopped,
okay,
current location, pick a location,
right, hold on, I gotta get this,
chili race, start,
so,
location,
repeat,
every 1 millisecond, right,
0.01 millisecond,
0.01,
I can't do that,
I can do 0,
I can do like 0, 0, 0, 0, 0,
1 millisecond,
this fucking music,
oh, my stomach hurts,
okay, so, 0, 0,
0, 0, 0, 1 millisecond,
repeat until stopped,
okay, so,
pick location,
pick cursor position,
no, not right there, not right there,
not right there, hold on, I gotta get it right,
click or press escape to pick, okay,
it's right there, escape,
to pick,
exit of the fucking game,
it should still be in the right spot though, right,
no, it'll be in the right spot, right here,
it's gonna be in the right spot, right,
okay,
you ready, here we go,
I'm gonna beat this motherfucker, I'm gonna show you guys,
0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1 millisecond,
1, 2, 3,
toggle it,
on current location,
oh, here we go,
1, 2, 3,
go, what's happening,
oh no, it's happening too fast,
uh oh, how do I stop it,
F6, F6,
got it, okay, we're fine, where's my mouse,
so, it's too fast,
too fast, 1 millisecond,
2 milliseconds,
1 millisecond should be fine, okay,
pick a location, again,
start game, ready,
here we go,
it's not gonna register a thousand clicks a second,
I mean it is, look,
switch it to current location,
I mean it's on,
it's still too fast, how about,
how about 200 milliseconds,
current location, start,
500 milliseconds,
start, hold it, I mean, I am holding it,
click type single,
there's only single or double,
click type, there's no hold,
it doesn't work, repeat,
repeat 50,000 times,
25 milliseconds,
single click,
current location, start,
I need a hotkey then,
alright, this music's gotta shut the fuck up, I can't even handle it right now,
hotkey setting,
it's F6, so if I hit
F6 right here, F6,
current location,
25 milliseconds, 50,000 times,
F6, maybe the repeat is too high,
use the
razor tool,
restart the application,
I mean, it's very clear that we were just doing that
correct, like every other time,
unplug it, alright, I'm gonna try
a different auto clicker,
the game is gonna only register hardware
clicks, it probably doesn't register software clicks,
that's probably what's happening,
different auto clicker,
I'll give you a fucking auto clicker,
this is for all the fucking marbles,
mouse click to
scroll wheel,
that's not gonna happen, mouse
click to scroll wheel,
but I can't even do
that, how the fuck
do I do that, let me try,
hold on a second, repeat
until stopped, 10 milliseconds,
current location,
hotkey, make it like fucking
D, or like 6,
who cares, just regular 6,
G,
okay, it's currently set to G,
100 milliseconds,
let's open it up,
this fucking music is going to
drive me insane, okay,
so this is perfect,
so you're saying, get right here,
do 1 millisecond, it works,
350 milliseconds is perfect,
I'm gonna just double click type,
tab into the game,
alt tab into the game,
what does that even matter,
single click,
alright, I'm gonna have to tell you right now,
if everyone's trying to help me,
I've been told like 6 or 7 different things,
minimize the clicker,
look Jerm, look, let me see,
what am I looking at here,
free chili time, be the best,
you win, yeah, that's a lie,
you cheated,
do you see how unbelievably
fast I was clicking the screen,
yeah, you watch that clip
of me pressing the mouse like
400 times a second,
alright, that's it, I'm candidate,
that's it, I'm out,
I can't alt back into the game, it's clicking,
do the online version,
okay, let's see,
I'm curious, where's the online version,
somebody uploaded a YouTube video
of them beating this,
yeah, good job, you have your auto
clicker, you have auto clicker set up to
500,000 times a second,
nobody can fucking do that, no human can do that,
I was trying to beat it as a human,
and look, you can't even hear it,
look at this shit, that's bullshit,
I almost beat it as fucking human,
alright, alright, no more fucking around,
I'm done, we are done with this bullshit,
I'm moving on to the next game, I'm not
spending anymore time doing this shit, I swear to
it just, shit, it just teleported,
it just teleported,
no, I did it, I fucking did it,
I actually did it, I wanna see that,
I wanna see what happened
last time, fucking stupid shit game,
I'm fucking believing it,
I wanna see it, show it to me,
show me that shit right now, I wanna see it,
let me see it, show it to me,
that's not it, that wasn't it,
that wasn't it, that's not,
god damn it, you wanna fight,
don't fuck with that,
it just, shit, it just
teleported, you wanna fight,
don't fuck with that,
gotta get the right position,
I'm gonna fucking beat this motherfucker,
tools without any bullshit,
I've done it so many times,
that my hand is fucking cramping,
at the very end,
get out of my wheelchair, I'm doing this shit,
I'm lying down on my ground right now,
you have no idea, I'm taking this dead fucking
serious, I'm
face down, I'm proning,
I don't understand,
I don't know what's gonna happen in my life,
I'm fucking stuck, I can't get out of this fucking
traffic,
it's not,
it's impossible,
it's actually impossible,
I'm fucking out of here, I'm done,
I can't,
I can't, I gotta get,
I'm done, I gotta get the fuck out of this game
before I fucking scream,
what, play the online version,
okay,
hold on, let me get this on here,
and the music, the music is
driving me fucking crazy,
I need a second, okay, I'm ready,
this is the online version of
chili time, I'm ready to fucking
destroy this game, are you ready,
I hate this game, I hate this,
I hate it, I can't, I hate it, get me out,
delete, I spent so fucking
much time,
I'm not playing that, Christmas bounce
is next on the list,
I can't,
I don't even know this is happening,
I just ran two miles,
that's not possible,
by the way, if you're curious,
I need to go get this frick like
a fucking gallon of water,
what you can't do, you can't catch both
at the same time, fucking god,
I'll be right back, I need to get this,
alright, I'm good,
had to get a little bit of water in me,
Christmas time, Christmas bounce,
defeat the north star,
this is so, wait, there's too many
of these, loved streamer,
crazy streamer goes hollow
on stream,
so thanks for the love guys, you guys are great, thank you,
I think this game is illegal,
let's find out,
let's find out just how illegal it is,
okay,
very illegal, not playing
dino drop, I'm going to play driving in LA,
fence the roach,
we're almost at G,
so we're doing well, fence the
cockroach in with boxes,
get them first,
is that somebody naked, get them first,
there's also genie, no, I'm not playing
that, galaxy shot, not playing this either,
let's play get them first,
little martians are trying
to shoot you, so
what do you do, get them
first,
gift grab,
nope, grab it, nope,
heard the animals, already did
it before, hit the duck, nope, not
doing that, ice cream shout out,
shoot out, perry the penguin
presents, ice cream blow
out, not even the right name,
scene one, ready,
set, go,
how do I shoot,
space invaders,
invade the aliens, yeah,
yeah, yeah, invasion of galactic
goobers, last shot,
paintball, nope,
leprechaun, nope,
nope, nope,
moon lander, nope, moon landing
ten, nope, mr.
amazing, oh absolutely,
welcome to the world of mr. amazing
where you battle against bugs, cars
and wine bottles,
use the arrow keys to navigate the space part of fire
your eye ray, if you get by
flying bottle of french champagne
you won't be able to use your eye ray
for two seconds, after 30 cars go by
the game will be over, good luck,
did this just break my nose,
hit the car,
who's throwing bottles at superman,
okay, I see, I see,
didn't hit
ocean hunter,
no, I don't want to play any of these,
play the drums,
oh,
you're about to hear something
fantastic,
it's hard to do this with G,
B and N, I can't do it like this,
the keys are too close,
it's too hard to do this with my hands like this,
it's hard to do that,
ah, ah, ah,
yeah, animal, slow down,
this is just racing in LA,
no,
shill game, basketball,
okay, keep an eye on it,
just want to let you guys know that I
might be like a fucking 10,000
frames a second eyes,
now you missed one, it's okay,
follow that diamond queen, queen, queen,
snake shooter, it looks fun but I know
it's going to be bad, it wasn't rigged,
really, yeah, no, I can do that, the diamond
queen one was, the guy was doing all kinds of
tricks,
I win,
snowball elves, nope,
I don't think we're going to do this, space battle,
space out, no,
I don't think so, oh dear,
well, this is where they gave up,
okay, there's still
140, whoever was
designing this, spaced
the fuck out, space out, there's the original,
well, here's space shot,
I'm going to, probably 50 of these,
star fight, tomato
bounce, sure,
that other noise threw
me off pretty badly, so what
happened there is, those of you that would
flash, they just went off the
stage, kind of, and then
had to come back around here and they were
loading up this way into the, back from
the stage,
that was very interesting, UFO shootout,
don't want to play it, why'd the chicken cross the road, this,
the character art's fucking crazy,
why did two load,
pretty good art, ow,
where's the, oh, I gotta,
what,
pinball
one, ai ai ai,
oh no, it's opening a command
prompt, no, no, no,
don't you, don't, okay, hold on,
are we good, okay,
card and casino, bingo,
poker, jackpot slots,
got my
attention, let's see what we got here,
jackpot slots, 400 credits,
this is so blurry,
I can't even tell what the denomination
is, 25 cents,
it doesn't even spin,
this many, spot the card,
super slots,
ooh, I like this one, this has got some
art to it, alright,
so, max bet,
it's 100, I have, I have 100 credits,
and spin it one time,
super slots,
4th of July, super slot, it's just
the same, everything's the same,
bank robbery,
it's the same clown,
the same clown,
is there anybody that has a different, is it,
it's always a clown, I don't wanna open this one,
this is definitely one of those
fucking command prompt ones,
guess the color, guess more or less,
puzzle and board,
jigsaw puzzles,
matches, no,
sports, bow and arrows,
one, darts,
no, they got baseball,
go-karts, no,
hot, okay, this is what I
want to see, that's what I
wanted,
take at least 10 baskets,
that sucked,
is it all the same exact game,
ping pong bounce,
shooting range, what,
the fuck is this,
don't open a command prompt, it's shitty enough where it would,
how is that sports,
wacky bird hunter,
squid hunter, speedway,
how,
look at how many versions of
wacky bird hunter,
there's almost as many wacky bird hunters,
oh, uh-oh,
no, that's not good,
uh-oh,
this is the time where I feel like somebody took over the computer,
press enter to begin,
I don't have a mind right now for this,
I don't,
this is probably really fun, that's it,
tangrams, does it
open, it does,
oh, it's just, I don't wanna do that,
that's pretty, that's pretty much
the end,
it's taken us more than 14
hours to go through this shit,
we're so close,
we've got, I don't know what
pentaminos are, but there's
2000 of them here, okay, it's just like
windows, dos,
3.1,
archaic, no,
not doing that one either,
500 solitary games, we already
know I'm gonna skip this one immediately,
mini golf, I know, I know,
I don't know how to play solitaire, so I'm gonna take a,
I'm gonna tell you guys what
I think solitaire is, and you can,
I'm gonna, chat's turning off,
I'm not looking at chat, solitaire
is you have a series of rows,
right, columns, and you have
to put, uh, down
or up for like
a suite, right, a suite,
suite, what?
Denomination, so if it's king,
you need to put a queen,
a jack, or a ten, it's gonna go down
in a line like this, so I don't
have anything, so I have to flip over here, so
ten, nine,
right, ten, nine, eight,
then you can move this one over here,
so then I have, now I need a
seven, or I need a jack,
there's an eight, that doesn't,
that didn't help me though, I got a
six here, I can go five,
six, you go
down or up, right, and
suites match, and
you can hold, so I can go
king, there's a
seven, I got my seven, that's what I needed,
puzzle board champion,
all right, you guys, come on, give me a little bit of slack
here, guys, I
just clicked my mouse,
maybe, maybe four
to five hundred thousand times,
I gotta get a little bit of slack here,
queens, chess, words,
bingo, battleship, knight,
checkers,
reversey, jigsaw, turns,
what is, what's battleship, I know battleship,
no, you don't even,
tokens, there's no tokens,
if there are no tokens, this is bullshit,
well, it doesn't even load, so, well, maybe it does,
I mean, no,
you don't even have graphics,
just lines, what the hell was that,
that was puzzle and board,
crystal mazes, actually,
this one, I'm actually intrigued
with what crystal mazes would be,
what is a crystal maze?
well, I was supposed to
put them into the
gold, is that what it was?
Kakuro games?
I don't know what Kakuro is,
wait, what did somebody say?
what did somebody say?
I'm seeing somebody being quoted and tell how funny
that was, what did you say?
what did they say?
I've actually seen those before and that they're
interesting, I mean,
like, Picross or
GTFO, as the kids say,
I'm a big fan of
Picross, Japanese
crosswords, and
I think, I think we got
ourselves exactly what I wanted,
one, two, three, four, five, six, seven,
eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve, has to be
the, yeah, this is Picross right there,
I could sit here all day and do this,
this is Picross,
I can't believe it, this is great,
one, two, three, four, five, six, seven,
eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve, third, the whole
thing is thirteen, it's gotta be
at least the middle, it's gotta be in here too,
so this is twelve,
twelve, it's kinda hard to gauge that,
nine, eight, three,
that's the only one, so we can go like this,
there's two here,
so it's either gonna be one,
two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight,
nine, ten, eleven, twelve, that's exactly what it is,
so now we can cross
these out, so
I'll give you a quick little rundown of how
I love these, I do these all the time,
I had
two of these for the Minotenno DS a long time ago,
so, essentially,
Picross is you make a picture,
and you're given a bunch of
numbers on the edges and the top,
and what you're supposed to do is,
whatever the number is on the left side,
that's how many filled in squares are
in this area here,
in this row, it doesn't tell you where,
they just, hey, twelve of these are filled in,
hey, ten of these are filled in,
you have to figure out with logic
and your mind where they go,
also, you know why, what's going on with the
eight and the two here, what is that, what the heck is this,
that means that there is a space between
these two, so for instance, let's
say the eight was here, so one, two, three,
four, five, six, seven, eight,
or because it's here, let's just
do it this way, let's say it was one, two,
three, four, five, six, seven, eight,
this two has to be at least
one space open, that's what that
means, so, that means that there's
a space, sounds real, oh it is real,
this is one of my favorite damn things
in the world, so, thirteen was
easy because it was, there are
thirteen spaces, so it has to be thirteen,
so where it gets tricky, so this is
three, so, here's
the thing, because it's three here, it could be here,
or it could also be here,
there's really no way for me to know that right this second,
because this row is also three,
so it would have to be, let's say if the three
was this way, it would have to be one, two, three,
which would fuck this whole row up, so it is
not there, that is not where that is,
I'm gonna go ahead and put an X,
because I know that this is just a three,
nothing else is here besides
a two, and three is in the end, so
this whole side is gone, because
it's two space and then three, therefore
there can't be anything here, so it's like
Minesweeper put better, yes, way better,
in my opinion, it's actually kind of cool,
it is very cool, some pit crosses
are
hundreds of squares,
and they have insanely elaborate,
it's not just, oh a starfish, it's like a whole
picture, they're awesome, but I mean,
I don't want to bore everybody
and do it, because I'll just sit here,
no fun allowed, this sounds sweet, it is,
so we've got five, I'll do
it, fine, so five, this row has
to have five, and there are two here, so
it's very possible
this could be down here at five, because we got four,
but then space one, two, this might be part
of the eight, so if this is part of the eight,
which it is, I mean one, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight,
it has to go this way, has to,
because I don't think there's
any possible way that you could have the eight go this way
without the two getting screwed up there,
it's really easy to count, so there's
thirteen spaces, right, one, two, three,
four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten,
one, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten,
like they have to be here,
at least, fill a random
square, though this is twelve, but remember
this is three down here, so you have to be
careful, five and then four,
this could be the four, it's definitely
the four, three, again, this is just
three, we can mark these, nothing in here,
and nothing here,
because it has to be either
one way or the other, so they're going to keep deducing,
it's all about deduction, so that way,
six, one, two, three, four, five,
six, one, two, three, four,
five, six, can't really tell at this moment, so
I bet you it's going to go
one, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, ten, which that
would be the three there, and it kind of makes sense,
I'm going to go for it, so then this is three,
there has to be a space,
three is actually the end, so there has to be
a space here, two in the top row,
so there can't be anything there,
so we've got three somewhere, there's a one,
so six there, four, one, two,
three, four, five, six, one,
two, three, four, five, six, it's kind of tricky,
but I'm pretty sure you can go like this,
because that would be one, two, three, four,
five, six, one, two,
three, four, five, six, so they have to be
in the middle here somewhere, so that means
this is part of the eight as well,
looks good, I don't know where the one is,
one, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven,
twelve, one, two, three,
four, five, six, seven, eight, nine,
ten, eleven, twelve, very possible,
has voted to play this game
for one hour,
what, do a full
pick-cross stream one day, it would be fun
to start off slow, that would be kind of
fun, nine, six, just depends,
because this six is part of the
eight, this is three, one, two, three,
space, one, two, three, not quite,
has to be, okay, so yeah, this has,
so there we go, there it is, there's your six
right there, six is done, I
like how a lot of
pick-cross games, when you actually fill
a row or a column,
it will gray out the number, so you're not looking
at it, I wish this did it too, but
this is kind of one of a, this is one
of the more bare bones
pick-cross games I've seen,
I mean, I've seen quite a few, so again,
three, we've got two
positions here, this could be four,
and that would be one, two, three, four, five,
it could be like this, it might be,
what a gamer, no, this is just
relaxing stuff, I just used to sit here
and play these all the time, so this is three
and then two, which it could be one, two, here,
this feels like a joke,
it's not, it's
not a joke, so there has to be two,
therefore, no, this is done, so you just
mark this, it's so relaxing, I mean,
at some point you have to make a good
educated guess, so let's just
say one, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, one, two, three,
four, five, six, seven, eight, nine,
I'm already kind of pushing it, three,
it would, it's probably this,
but it might be the bottom, no, but
one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight,
I don't know about that, what about over here?
one, three, nine, twelve,
eight, two, five,
and then, well, it could be here,
because that would be one, two, three, four, five,
and then one, two, three, four,
let's just see what that looks like, therefore,
one, two, three, four, five, six,
oh shit, one, two, three, four,
five, six, one, two, three, four,
five, six, alright, alright,
alright, hold on, one, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, it has to be
here, that's nine, one, two,
three, four, five, six, seven,
five, six, starfish
Jupiter, which way does this go,
because it could go either way, it probably
is, well, if you take a look at the
just got her in and confused, ah, I'm just
dicking around, well, you know what, here it is,
it can't go this way, there's no three
it can be here, because there's no space,
so this is one, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight, has to be
the three, this has to be three,
either up here or down here, there's no space,
that's it, which then we may have just got
ourselves the one, mmm,
the one might be here, it's not that hard, no,
it's not that hard, it just kind of
takes a minute to look at it, peacocks,
oh, why, did cocks come in
and delete some frames, three,
two, if that's the case,
then one, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight, nine,
it's probably this, I'm going to go for it,
if I'm wrong, I'm wrong,
because then that would be one, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight, I'll be wrong
if I need to be, which would then be one,
two, one, two, three,
space, one, two,
three, let's see if that focks anything up,
one, two, three, four, five, six, seven,
eight, one, two, three, one, two, three, let's
just see, because then that lets,
that's one, two, three,
four, five, six, seven, eight, nine,
ten, eleven, twelve, that's it for this,
there's two somewhere here,
I think this comes out too, because that,
it's the way the image looks here,
so this looks correct, so I'm definitely
going to need, let's see,
because now it has to be one, two, three,
four, five, six, seven, eight, nine,
uh-oh, wait a minute here, one, two,
three, four, five, six, seven, eight,
nine, something's wrong,
I focked it up, restart,
I don't think I need to restart,
that'd be one, two, three, four, five, see if that helps,
five, six, seven, eight, nine, well that's one,
I mean it's a little janky over here, but I can fix it,
this might be, no, no,
has to be there, one, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, right,
it has to be there, ah,
is it though? Because then this might
have to be down here, one,
two, three, four, five, six, seven,
eight, that's focking wrong,
I think the three column is correct,
yeah, it's the perspective,
what is the two,
two would have to be like
here, here,
the nine has eight filled now, yeah,
I know, I'm just trying to figure like how I
focked this up, if the nine
can't be like that, then the threes must be down
there, yeah, bad
version of this game, no,
it's just kind of a sloppy version,
it really, I really like it when you
can actually see in real time, it helps
with being able to see,
some of them actually have it so you have like
two X's, you can do a one X that you can actually
screw up, threes, yeah, the threes
aren't identical, like that,
cause then that would be one, two, three,
four, five, six, seven, eight,
and that's based on two,
one, two, three, one, two,
one, two, one, two,
one, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven,
twelve, that's not right,
you would have to go,
it's almost there, it's almost
done, cause the starfish goes like
this, it's like the legs come down,
like this one, so almost like
this is wrong, two, three
can't be filled with it, yeah,
three, that'll be one,
two, three, four, five, six, seven,
eight, nine,
hmm, these are easy,
yeah, I know, I haven't done
them in a long time though, this is the first time I've done it
in probably like a couple of years,
and sometimes when I play these, I mean, I'm obviously
my, I'm very fucking tired,
my brain is like
a little slow at the moment,
yeah, I could do it if I sat
better, I know I could, and like I could do it,
but there it is,
I had it pretty close, I don't want
to sit here for like another twenty minutes,
it was close,
I see, right here, yeah,
I had this right the second time,
yeah, it was down here, this is what was screwing me up,
I had it correct before,
oh well, but no, seriously though,
I'll be completely honest, P-Cross
Nanograms, they are,
they are a ton of fun,
and if you are like, what the fuck are you guys
even talking about, you can start out
with like a tiny cube,
that is like this big,
hold on, can I go back, select
puzzle, as you see here,
right, they get kind of
wild, I'm looking for one that's
just a tiny one,
I can't sort by
size,
that's kind of annoying, size
nine by thirty,
just looking for like a really small one,
ten by twenty,
ten by ten is usually
very very easy,
five by five is just
absolutely impossible to fill,
but it teaches you how to do it,
twenty five by ten, that's not terrible,
one, two, three, four, five, six,
I think this is, yeah, it's twenty by twenty, so,
you can sit there and
like here, like watch,
see, do the house
tube, and this
is very,
yeah, and it's zoomed out too,
but you're probably looking at this like, oh, that's kind of crappy
looking, I guess it looks like a fish,
kind of, there are some very
very loud, especially the one for the DS was awesome,
if you search Picross in Google,
you can get a bunch of five by five ones, yeah,
they're a lot of fun,
highly recommend, they're good for
just hanging out, and hey, there you go, there's
your thousand and one
crosswords, two thousand
and two space out games, I don't want
to play it, I know what it is, I'll open it,
it's mini golf time,
oh, look, a thousand
and one space out,
so we have to go to a thousand,
wait, hold on, there's more, two thousand
and two space out games, there's twenty four
hundred of them, there's more games
on the disc, we're almost done,
we're almost done,
two days, and
fifteen hours of time,
I can't fucking believe it's almost
done, oh, don't get,
don't jump the gun that quickly,
hold on, you got Sudoku
mania,
Sudoku mania, doesn't open,
gone, I knew I should have
yeah,
are you sure about that, I don't,
there's nothing open,
my computer's
starting to slow down, it's lagging out,
no, they're multiplying,
get them up, you gotta cut the head off the snake there,
jigsaw,
three thousand jigsaw puzzles,
new, oddness,
number of tiles,
animals three,
animals three, are there any in here?
what?
porn, porn,
okay, I'm not,
I can't even open it, none of those folders
had anything in them, you
fucking psychos,
no, no, I'm getting off
that immediately,
one thousand and one mini golf games,
this is what you waited for, you guys waited this long
for this stuff,
start, where do I want to go?
more golf courses, no, this one's fine,
let's play it one,
course one, hole one,
there's a thousand and one levels apparently,
albatross,
ooh, this is gonna be fun, watch this one,
full power, straight ahead, I'm not sure
how you did that any better, how, well, how is that different?
how was that an albatross, Jeremy,
you took forever, that was like a par eight,
really, fans?
you can't even get a hole in one on this game,
uh oh, what?
I don't, you can play a better version of the game
you just watched right now for free,
it's like eleven or twelve different websites,
we already did mahjong,
we already opened this one, remember,
I did actually open that one already,
two left, we've got
the lost mine,
a thousand and one treasures,
the lost memes, somebody said,
sorry I just flashed you,
alright, challenge mode, this is gonna be match
three probably, this is a very odd
match three,
we've come down to the end,
I've opened, I've done it again,
every single one of these
fucking games has been at least attempted
to be opened, another
medjooled, so thanks
for everybody for watching this behind the scenes
stream,
three years later,
for the 700,000 games video,
because they are all
the fucking same,
end of the stream voice, yeah,
it is, it's getting there, eight hours,
little more for the bits
and the subs, it's probably like a nine
or ten hour stream, I've had
enough, changed background, I don't even know
what I'm looking at here, that one's kinda cool,
I like that one, no, dumb,
dumb, dumb,
dumb, that was kinda cool,
astro color twist is
the final thing to open,
let's see what we have in store,
for the final click,
please play through that museum hunting
game with a story later,
if you guys really think that that was
fun, we could come back to some of these that were
more elaborate and do them,
and what do you know, 700,000
games, here you go,
final click, it doesn't do anything,
astro color twist does not even turn
on, it has been conquered
on stream, 700,000
games, what a way to
end it out, let's take a look, oh yeah,
nothing I missed, right,
that's the same, by the way that is the same
astro color twist,
I just moved it over here because I wanted to have
some extra space,
there are not two clickable
astro color twists,
welcome to hell, thank you
for joining me, everybody,
I would call that an adventure that was
about 15 hours, two days in a row,
missed one, middle
one, what, where,
what are you talking about, what did I miss,
middle, in the middle,
no that's on fire,
yeah that one's on fire,
that was the gnome one, yeah that's it,
the one with no X is the one
that's on fire, yeah,
we burnt that one, on the left
I don't see any, I think
we did them all, no we did
them all, yeah I see, we did them all,
alright guys, so
I will see you again,
today is, what is today,
today's Friday,
for me,
probably really late, so I will see
you guys again on
Saturday sun, I'll see you guys on Monday,
I'm going to
take the next couple days off,
have a fantastic weekend everybody,
thank you for sitting
through this,
this last two streams,
was this three days in a row,
yeah it was, because we did the,
was this, did I do
three streams three days in a row, I think so,
I had a lot of fun,
yeah we're going to get to the bits and we'll do the subs as well,
speaking of subs, WWW Memers
Club just gave
five community subs,
thank you so much,
what rating would I give the game,
a zero, a zero,
ten,
was this better or worse than the previous one,
it was the same one,
I don't, there was
maybe a half
dozen differences,
give out the game keys,
I don't have game, you think I have
game keys for gerbil drop,
this was the patched version
from the last one, say something
nice about it, okay I will,
it's a great
time waster,
how can I say something nice about this, every single game
in this entire collection
can be found for free and way
better online, from
various websites, you can play checkers
online with other people in
real time, you can play chess
right now for free against somebody,
miniclip exists,
newgrounds exists,
every single one of them, you can play pool
online right now for free,
you can play
mahjong probably right now for free,
hundreds or thousands of different ones, solitaire
is for free, solitaire comes free on every
computer that's ever been built,
jigsaw puzzles,
they're for free, you can get them anywhere,
but can you play super frog,
no you can't,
so there are, there were a couple
of gems here, there was,
the mystery
chad and grandpa mansion,
use the disk in monster rancher,
I probably will, I'm going to hold on to it,
now it,
look, anytime a company tries to do
something, it's an interesting idea,
to hey there's 700,000
get, but I,
you gotta, you gotta at least,
they have to work,
and if you're going to sell them, if it's going to be on
store shelves, you could buy this
game at like fucking target a couple years
ago, I mean if like half the games
on the disk don't work, at least have the
games work, and make sure that they
work, magic sphere was
really good,
super frog, always
a pleasure, that's it,
actually Jeremy, each level is a game,
so there are way more than 700,000
games, I like
the idea, I don't like the execution,
but I mean am I really giving
a rating to 700,000
games,
you can't, it's timeless, it's a classic,
it's a classic compilation
of games
that were made probably
20 years ago, that
somebody kept on a thumb drive,
and over the years they had a company
and they built it up and built it up and just kept putting them on
disks, give it a rating,
one out of 700,000,
41,
40, yeah,
410, 410,
listen, hear me out,
it's a great experience,
I had a bunch of fun, did you have
fun, I had fun,
imagine a scenario,
first of all, imagine
a scenario where this compilation
doesn't exist,
and never existed, we wouldn't
have gotten the immense joy
from fucking around with it,
and I wouldn't have the immense joy
of reinstalling windows,
because that's why I'm taking two days
off, anyway,
let's get to the bits, thank you so much
everybody for participating and watching,
next time use a virtual machine,
boomer boy, I've used
virtual machines before and I always have problems
with them, I'm too much of a
boomer, but let's go back,
let's teleport ourselves back
8 plus hours ago,
see you guys on Monday,
we'll have some fun on Monday,
got some stuff, plus
the date, the 23rd is coming up,
so, gotta prepare for that one,
hey, one key on, thanks for the one dollar,
quick, I need a pancake recipe, two eggs,
bowl of flour, bucket of
panko, breadcrumbs, sugar,
maple syrup,
use your hands, just get the fuck
in there, and then that's it,
and then don't cook that,
don't eat it either, don't make
any of that, hey, divas, thanks
for the three dollars, divas,
thank you norman games for the one dollar,
for 30 minutes of connect 4,
no, we can play connect 4 another day,
it's getting late, hey,
Barney, thanks for the one dollar, Barney, thanks
for being an, thanks, Jerma, for being
an amazing streamer, thank you, Barney,
for your five total dollars, and you say
thanks, and you also say pride, 100,
thank you, Barney,
bake me home, thanks for one dollar,
lumpo, thanks for three dollars,
congratulations, new subsound,
I'm not sure what it was, but I'm sure it was
strange, kitty,
skinny time, thanks
for the one dollar, I'm watching
this in the bath and I laughed and dropped my laptop
in the water, thank you,
be fucking careful with electronics
near a big body of
water, oh my god,
be careful, thank
you C4G for the one dollar, hey, Jerma,
do you remember that stream
teacher noise, do you remember what it's from?
does anyone in chat have a clip?
the teacher noise stream was one of
the last streams I did from Massachusetts,
I remember because I had
one of those bulb microphones
that was like right in my mouth,
it was at some point in
late September, I'm pretty sure that
may have been the last stream, or one of the last
streams from Massachusetts, hey
it's time for SLAM, thanks for the one dollar,
it is the background that we had
the image with the slap
and the weird glowing eyes face
from earlier, thank you,
that's fucking god,
I can't even look at it,
Norman, thanks again for one dollar, please go to
rehab Jeremy,
what, why, what did I do?
thank you Ocean Gun for the ten dollars,
I find myself always looking
for your videos on a daily basis,
and honestly you're the only streamer I ever watch,
thanks for the laughs and I hope you have a
great evening, you too,
thank you for
watching, thanks for hanging out,
and always looking for my videos on a daily
basis, that, that means a lot,
I don't even know what to say, thank you,
I'm just glad you enjoy them,
and thank you again Ocean Gun for the
ten dollars,
Yaku Sai, thanks for the
one dollar, hey Gerald,
was watching your Marge Simpson stream
VOD the other day, he was thinking how much
I think you'd like Psychonauts,
I'm sure you'd appreciate the humor and charm and
think you'd have a lot of fun, it's not a
brain quiz game, by the
way, yeah I know
what Psychonauts is, I've seen it,
I've played pieces of it,
for like ten seconds,
hope you had fun with the 700,000 viruses by the way,
yeah, they were great,
it was a lot of fun, it was a journey,
if people didn't think that Psychonauts
would be that boring, maybe I would do it,
is that something that,
is that a streamable kind of game
that people would be engaged in and have fun with?
I'm all for it,
I found the teacher clip,
oh there you go, teacher clip is going
into the chat,
Kelly Dinas, thanks for the one dollar,
hey Gerald, I'm a big fan of Monster Hunter World here,
I was curious if you kept playing the game last year, and if you might
ever stream it again,
cheers, cheers to you,
I did continue playing,
I completed the whole game,
well that's not, I mean the whole game is not real,
I beat the campaign,
I went through the whole storyline,
and a little bit past it,
but I don't think I would stream Monster
Hunter World again,
I got everything I wanted out of it, I think,
I put at least,
probably 70 to 100 hours into the game,
something like that, over the course of
four weeks, I thought it was fun,
it was great,
but I'm not sure I would want to go back
and do it all over again,
what about God of War? God of War is
one of those games that's on the list currently, still,
that I need to play,
and streaming it is
very possible,
hey Timmy Timtan, thanks for the one dollar, another poor soul
lost to the evils of match three games,
wow, just play Slime Rancher,
that's another one that I've heard
is really fun, smelly boy, thanks
for the one dollar, this is a Jax Creepypasta,
Jax Creepypasta
Captain Wargon,
thanks for one dollar, Jerma NG
is more scary than BF Bugleberry
ever will be, Sir
Feline, thanks for the one dollar, the virgin Jerma
versus the Chad Daryl,
smelly boy,
thanks for the one dollar, this is melting my brain,
all of them
melted my brain, I'm pretty
brain melted, honestly it was the chili
speed clicker,
that took probably two or three years off my life,
if I was going to live to be like
140, which I mean,
come on, I'm probably going to live to be like
now, but
thank you, thank you FGWGWF
for the one dollar, Jerma, thank goodness he gave me another
chance to live, just whatever you do, don't read
this, call back to yesterday,
smelly boy, thanks for one dollar,
honestly can't tell who's the shitty or new character
Jerma Witch or Jerma Goggle,
so combine them, why
can't they be like a Goggle Witch,
hey space bread, thanks for the one dollar,
I played this game like 10 years ago and thought
it was just a fever dream, thank you for reviving
this memory, my pleasure,
hey RFLSA,
thanks for the two dollars,
no message, just cheer 100
twice, thank you, mandum
requiem, thanks for the one dollar, two dollars actually
from mandum,
Jerma Woggle,
Goggle Witch, Witch
Goggle, memory or
thank you Jess for the one dollar,
can you show us the capacity of your beatboxing
talent, maybe when
you originally gave this message five hours ago
maybe, I'm a little drained
right now, I'm not sure I could give you a proper
performance, but I do it from
time to time, there are people that are way
way better than me at
doing that, but sometimes it's fun
to do, hey compact viewer,
thanks for the five dollars, hey it's
me again, I don't know if you like Star Wars
games or not, but I think you should check out Star Wars
Republic Commando, it's a tactical
FPS shooter
and he links the
trailer, anyway, enjoy
the rest of the night and keep being you
I will definitely watch the trailer
let me just skim through it now
I think I've played this game
before, I feel like I've played this
I think I've, I swear to God
I've played this before
I'm not sure I would stream it
but, definitely an older one
right, it was 20
when it came out
yeah yeah yeah
thank you for the five dollars though compact viewer
I do love Star Wars
well, I do
I'm not a big fan of Star Wars
games though
maybe like, I'm trying to
think of a Star Wars game that I truly
really really loved, but I can't think
of one, but I never played The Force Unleashed
never played the Lego Star Wars
games, I played a lot of the older ones
Bounty Hunter comes to mind
I didn't play the Battlefront Star Wars
games, but thank you Alec
for the one dollar, why are you doing a gnome
what, am I killing the gnomes
look, the
gnome portion of the stream tonight
was I was
metaphorically putting every
gnome that I've had
in a gnome circle
and then
my clicking X
fire on the corner
of the screen of justice
Return of the Jedi arcade version
I metaphorically
killed the gnomes
is the Google witch in chat now?
holy shit
that's too many, that's
too many things going on
that's wrong
that's all wrong
that's a reference
to a reference, that is also a reference
to another reference, it's too much
at some point to get lost
thank you Unclean
or Unclean
for the two dollars
it's a YouTube link, let's mute just to make sure
this is not a gnome
it is, it's a gnome on a phone
is this recent?
this feels like recent
did this guy, did somebody tell
this guy that his video was famous and now
he's gonna cash the
fuck in, I don't blame him
oh man, I would
he's gonna make like 400 million
dollars from that
gnome phone app
thank you for
phone gnoming me
C4G, thanks for the one dollar, I'm sure you've answered this somewhere
but have you played the
Spider-Man DLC campaigns yet?
or have you considered them for streams? I have not
I have not considered
Spider-Man return
for a stream? I don't know
are they good?
ET phone gnome, I was gonna say that but I didn't
I was afraid we were gonna get
minus twos in the chat
I was thinking it and I was gonna say it, but you said it
so therefore you get the minus two, not me
but I don't have any plans to go back to
Spider-Man, and I haven't played the campaigns
off stream or anything, so
don't think so
how many more terrifying images of me
exist on the internet, I wonder
my fucking grandkids are gonna
see these, somehow
thank you, the only guy ever for the
one dollar
now I see why, I asked around there
and I got a word that you make your living playing children's games
and making an entity out of yourself
live on camera, so I just had to check myself out
check out for myself
glad to see you're still a loser like you always were, little guy
I also remember
I just want to let you know that we're engaged
and she's chilling with me
later, okay
that was four hours ago, where did that
come up?
at what point was that put here?
I wonder, what was I doing?
I know it's a meme, I know it's like a copy
Chad pasta
but, I mean, but
I don't even remember when that was
why?
oh, my stomach
Artium, thank you Artium for the one dollar, yo
check this sick filth out
thank you
hey, Dorkcube
700,000 games
it's not your name, but I'm gonna say it
because of today, thanks for the dollar 90
oh my god, all the photoshopped monstrosities
in this game are so good
they are, they're very good
it's probably the best part of the whole compilation
uh, thank you Jen Pendulum
for the 10 dollars
I'm so glad that I get
I'm so glad that I get on the stream as soon as
Jerma pulled out a troll face
troll face?
I made a contender for the 25 dollars
there's no
way in hell
that image is going to be an emo
no way in hell, I'm not gonna
ever click that image again
oh, that one
but thank you for
thank you Jen Pendulum for the 10 dollars
thank you Tingy for the one dollar
thank you Jerma for the one dollar
you're welcome
ape808, thanks for the five dollars
it's another image
my grandkids are gonna be like
what was wrong with grandpa Jeremy
uh
heampixel, thanks for the one dollar
how many of these games do you think will make your best
games of 2019 list
um, probably
nearly zero
nearly zero cause it's possible
that one might make it
goldenfoxy, thanks for the one dollar, hey Jerma long time fan
hey can you unban my other account
uh, you say you were banned
for no reason
well, I'll tell you
account bans on the channel
are discussed by the mobs
people uh, don't get just banned
for no reason
that goes through about whether or not someone should be actually banned or not
so I don't know
I can't just be like you know what here
unban
I have no idea what the context is
can you unban
my mother
without context I can't really help you out there
but that's something that
you could probably hit a
mod up on the channel
and figure out what happened
sorry that it happened but I don't really have any context for you
and you'll say long time fan
how's it going, it's going great
hopefully you're doing well as well
goldenfoxy, thank you
hey smacklesmore, thanks for the one dollar, Jerma this stream
Jerma Pluto, Jerma Jax
accurate
roadhunk, thanks for the one dollar
himpixel, again thanks for one dollar, hope this is enough to pay for the new mouse
after eating all those chilies
yeah
I should have been more careful
unclean, thank you for the one dollar
again, good job
beating chili time
it's the truth of it all
rflsa, thanks for the one dollar, Jerma heart seems good
thank you
sirfeline, thanks for the one dollar, literally
2002 games inside the
700,000 games package
that sounds like a good deal
kappa, yeah there's another box
inside of the first box
this 2000 more boxes
inside of that 700,000
box, I think
hey cyan tf2, thanks for the one dollar
I've been drumming for over 10 years
every single non-drummer that tries to play
the exact same beat Jerma
ended up doing
well you're talking about the
hey zeets, thanks for the one dollar, not quite my tempo
elbertson, sorry
it's time for slime, thanks for the one dollar
number one chili time streamer
there's an image
I don't even know where that picture
that image is from
thank you himpixel for the one dollar, I can't believe a boomer
doesn't know how to play solitaire
well, you found him
korbiter, thanks for the one dollar
hey Jerma I caught a rare glimpse of the ghost that lurked
in your closet last night, I'll give you a funny story about that
so last night, here's the image
last night I turned
my webcam on
and everyone kept saying
the closet, the closet, the closet
so I put my phone in the closet
with the flashlight on facing out
with the brb screen up
and it stayed there
funny story, part two, the phone
died up there, I forgot
about it, I think like maybe
an hour and a half after I put it up there
the light is off, phone died
fast forward to today
where's my phone, where is it
oh right, I forgot
I put it up there last night
gg, idiot
thank you korbiter
hey bet3, thanks for five dollars
it's really fun watching you do p-cross games like that
I like hearing your narration
and seeing the picture take form, it's just very relaxing
don't be surprised if one day
I turn this stream on
and I got a really high quality
version of that game
and we just sit back and just sip on
some fucking tea
and just play that for like five hours
I'll be surprised
but thank you for the five dollars, bet3
George Maka
thanks for the one dollar
we have a survivor
Germanius
what do you mean Germanius
we have a survivor, it was a gnome
hey Logan, thank you Logan for the five dollars
hey love you germa
don't know if you saw that or not but my friends and I
cooked coffee and cheeto
styled chicken
oh my god
the quintessential germa joke needed
the quintessential meal, we made coffee, chicken and
sauce, cheeto chicken
and sauce, and finally a mixed coffee
cheeto chicken, the cheeto chicken was the best
by far
oh my fucking lord
that's fucking hilarious
I love that
food network
sauce spoon drag
that you have in that picture
that's high quality shit
good work, that's awesome
thank you for the five dollars
goldenfoxy thanks for two dollars again
wait germa I need to tell you something important
and that's it, thank you goldenfoxy
hey train, thanks for the one dollar train
just want to say how you've helped me throughout the harsh times
I watch your VODs every day
when I come back from college
and they cheer me up every time
cheers for you and to the chat
PS please play
dusk, I actually was
going to, yeah
it looks actually pretty fun
that's that old school FPS
doomer, boomer, whatever
that's what they call, the boomers that play doom
that was definitely, I was checking it out
thank you so much
train for the one dollar
and it's my pleasure, thank you
crockylemmons thanks for the one dollar
I can't wait for the picross stream jeremie
don't be surprised
thank you jack for the one dollar
end the stream by watching the old video
the old video
oh the 700,000 video
we'll save that for monday
we'll compare the two just because
I'm fading here, I need to get some food in me
the old vid
because that's like a full ten
we'll start on monday by
just going very briefly
over, kind of
I need a couple days to compress from what we just did
are you going to forget?
I won't forget because I got
700,000 chatters
that will remind me
so don't worry, remind me to do that first thing we do
hey jenvy thanks for the one dollar, is this better than the uya?
oi, the uya
I forgot about that
fastest just
skydive into the ground
the thing about the uya is, it's probably going to be worth a shitload of money
in like 25 years
just because it existed
hey, yes is online, thanks for the five dollars
yes, I went to a bar and got shitfaced
and you were still playing the shovelware
any plans on playing the resident evil 2 remaster
yes, by the way the storyboards
for when my crew shoots with the green screen footage
in boston are almost complete and we've got a production
company that did a super bowl commercial helping
holy shit
that's
really, really, that's wild
but, resident evil 2 remaster
yes, I'm going to, day one
I'll be
one of the 500 million people streaming that game
day one
just seems like a lot of fun, I love resident evil 4
I love resident evil 5
and they're kind of doing that, they're going back and
remastering it in that style
except not really, but kind of
third person over the shoulder
I'm sure I'll love it
and the demo is already out, that's true
but I don't want to play it because I want to experience the whole thing
and I think giving myself a 30 minute demo
would just tease me
but thank you
and yes, expect that on day one
golden foxy, thanks for the one dollar
been a fan since 2012
I have something important
what is it
you say there's something important and you don't say what the important thing is
is it the band thing?
as if it is
and I talked about it about 15 minutes ago
hey Lars, bloodaxe, thanks for the five dollars
google doesn't even sound like a word anymore
good stream
goggle doesn't sound like a word anymore
not google, goggle
if you say a word enough times in a row
it doesn't sound like a real word
hey siroc, thanks for the dollar eleven
like zoinks, germa, there's a g-g-g-g-g-g-ghost
in your closet, man, you should like
call the fire department
I sent this at the beginning of the stream
but for whatever reason you-
I don't need to do it anymore, but for whatever reason you missed it
also add germaengi as an emote
fg, wg, wf, thanks for the one dollar
I wish some movie studio would just give you a budget
and tell you to make whatever the movie you want
I feel like that might be the funniest movie ever
so I guess I'll put this dollar towards the live action
death and life of
harold straight saint
sludge foundation
I mean I would
if I had a million dollars or like 10 million
dollars to make a movie
I don't even know there's so many things that I would think would be fun to make
I don't think I'd even want to make a movie
I think I just want to make a series
of like 25 different
videos and just upload them
I'm not sure a movie
there are too many things I'd like to do with that money
but thank you
golden foxy, thanks for the one dollar
do you still have your playstation 2? yes I do
it's currently in the ghost closet
it's ready to go for another night
when it's deemed necessary
hey trotter, thanks for the one dollar
saw this in chat a minute ago, thought
I'd get your eyes on it
hey germaengi, I'm planning on proposing to my lady friend
that I would love to have you officiate the wedding
from me and my loved one
I'll pay for your licensing
and we will fly to you
is that legal?
is that legal for me to do that?
officiate a wedding
oh it would be bad
it would be bad
I could stand in front
of a hundred thousand people
and do a bit
but you put me in front of like
a couple hundred of your closest
friends and family members and I'm officiating
your wedding, I'm going to turn
purple
oh my god, I would
I wouldn't know what to do
that makes it better
oh my god
imagine officiating a wedding
I don't know really either
one of the two people
we're getting the pre-recorded wedding joke scene
it's a perfect stream
oh god
well first of all
to answer that
I would really need to really think about that
the joke is you don't
know anyone
a lot of wedding officiate
orators don't know the bride or groom
it would be so hard for me to do
I could dress up in a clown costume
and fucking ride a tricycle
across the stage and have
fifty thousand people in that crowd just
pointing and laughing at me
but you give me like a bible
and stand there at the front
in like grandmas in the front row
I would
be very nervous
fly to you
you coming down to Vegas?
we are Christians so it would be in a church
just want to give you a fair warning
Vegas
make sure like
old grandma Esther is aware
that you're in like Las Vegas
that's fucking
all jokes aside
that's really really
incredibly like humbling and
grounding and that somebody would actually
want me to do that if it's not just like a joke
if it's for real
that is so I can't even fucking believe that
that is so
that's so
it's equal parts unbelievable
and equal parts
the word I want to say is
just interesting
lots of people get married in Vegas not just shotgun weddings
yeah I know
I'm just kidding around
but seriously though
if that's for real
then I would have to think about that and figure out how I would want to do that
and I'd have to like
muster up the courage to be able to do something like that
so at the moment
I'm going to have to think about that but I'm going to have to kind of
respectfully decline
just for the sake of
I don't know
if the wedding happens
invite chat
waiting for the wedding stream in five months
thank you so much
message even if it's not real then it's not real
we just spent about
10-15 straight minutes talking about it
and if it is
then that's something I would really have to think about
I'm absolutely floored
that you would even want that to happen in the first place
thank you the Jewish bro
for the one dollar do you keep Kim
up with your streams yeah
she watches them sometimes
and you know when I'm done streaming
she's usually like oh how'd it go
what'd you do
10 minutes and we just kind of move on
but yeah
thank you Ike Turtle for the one dollar I made a contender
for the 25 dollar sub emote
that was the
that was the one that was the hot dog
hot dog in the mouth
I'm just going to do this right now just to make sure
I show this right now because this will never be
an emote I'm never going to have that as an emote
just want everyone
to be very aware get
your cameras on get your snapshot ready
because I'm never going to link that again
but thank you Ike Turtle for the
I'm not even sure what that is
but thank you
Thevious thanks for the five dollars
hey Jerma just turned 20 at midnight and I'm glad
I could spend a part of my birthday watching
my favorite streamer being 20
is weird because I don't feel that old
but I'm also excited because it feels like a new chapter in my life
has just opened anyway keep up the great
streams Jermboy Jerma Heart
yeah you 20s
20s from 20 to 30
is an adventure
you learn a lot about yourself
you learn a lot of your opinions that you had
when you were a teenager kind of mature
and you start to
craft who you want to be as a person
in your 20s
happy birthday if you're still here hopefully you still are
hope you had a great one
and good luck on the next chapter of your life
Garfield the Monday Killer thanks for the one dollar
hey there Jerma what a Garfy stream you just did
I can't believe that Garfin
Garftacular you know what I mean
Odie couldn't believe his eyes I mean holy
guacamole I'm playing Mario Odyssey with
Odie so I do a very good Garfagraph
haha but it's still pretty great
alright Garfield
the jig is up here
you've become self aware
in this paragraph uh oh
I think it's time is up
you broke the fourth wall Garfield
busted thank you
the Jewish bro again for the one dollar have you heard
of uh Alcus
Breach? I have not
I don't know what it is
I don't know what that is
so there you go I don't know
hey Creel thanks for the one dollar you should play
Return of the Obra Dinn it's made by Lucas Pope
the guy that made Papers Please
it's an insurance investigator game at sea
with minimal color
yeah I actually talked about how I was going to stream it
three to four days ago
it looks really really interesting
and Papers Please was great too
so that is very possible you might see that
I have so many games to play and stream
I do but they have to
it has to be the right time
I have to be in the right mindset and be ready and want it
you know I want you know I can't just do it
I can't just stream
Return of the Obra Dinn I have to be ready
and want it and I
don't know when that would be I know it will be some point
didn't know it was made by the Papers Please
guys oh yeah Papers Please guy
that was a fantastic game
uh Kumo Tosin
thanks for the one dollar hey Jermbo
I guess I'm going to be a vaude nerd tonight since
I fell asleep right before the stream
I wanted to know if you'll ever play House Flipper again
those streams are great and the devs are adding a garden DLC
if the garden
DLC is significant
enough to do a whole
full good stream of that game then yes
if they add enough
where I could justify turning the
stream on and
going through it then sure
I love that game GoldenFoxy
thanks for the one dollar
the important thing oh the important thing here it is
I have no idea where to go
and ask about the band the mods
by the way have a good night
I finally got my grades up before
my grades sucked
that's too bad I'm sorry to hear that
if you want to find a mod
they have a sword next to their name
and on discord they have a purple
name that's how you can always tell who a
moderator of the channel is
sorry to hear about your grades
hope you get them up
take care of yourself thanks for
the multiple
you gave at least five
to ten dollars tonight thank you GoldenFoxy
IkeTurtle thanks for the one dollar here's a dollar
look at this I need you to know your thoughts
I hate it
I hate it I hate that especially
the one on the left I hate both of them
both of those guys look like
funny joke youtubers you know what I mean like
that's like a joke
I'm a youtuber thumbnail
I hate both of those guys I don't want to
watch their videos and finally
the jewish bro thanks for the one dollar
it's AlChestBreach he's a
streamer and we have similar humor
I've never
watched or haven't really
don't know who it is
there are a lot of streamers on twitch
that better be the thumbnail god
but finally here
thank you GoldenFoxy for the one dollar
when I watched this on movie night
with the green screen did you really enjoy that video
I had a big watermark on there I was gonna ask
that but it's when I got
banned if you did thanks
oh well
all the videos that were played during
the movie night stream were
were all good they were all worth watching
some of them were
incredibly elaborate and had a lot
of work put into but that doesn't mean that the other ones weren't
worth watching and weren't fun
so no absolutely
every single one of those that was on stream
was great what are you
doing yeah I've seen this already
I've already seen this image
yes I know and why did I just paste it
it's already here
like 30 times
I've already seen this fucking
image and it's gonna haunt
me forever for the rest of my life
this is me kissing
me do you understand
how odd this is to see this
it's so
it just if I could
then why did this just pop up again the hot
dog thing came up again
why do I have so many of these
I'm going down
my tabs
and there's just fucking hot dogs
in my mouth like six times
does it have to be this many
hot dogs alright
here come the credits
thanks everybody for subscribing
if you see your name
point it out much love to you all
I'll see you guys all on Monday
this is not a hot dog image
but that was my background for a while
whoa that's me
that's me
there I am is there another one
you guys are gonna really fuck up
my grandkids
just when you think the images can't get any worse they do
I don't even know how you guys
are this fast
how do you do that that quickly it takes me like
30 minutes to make an image
like that oh my god
grandpa what are all these weird pictures
of you with hot dogs in your mouth
and you eating a hot dog from the other side
in a witch costume when did you do this
I didn't you see
back when I was
in my younger years
there was these things called fucking
chat memers
that what they did is
oh he's asleep again okay
just walk away from grandpa
let him have his space
don't tell me that happened
no
no no no
why now
it's been like three years of links
you guys are killing me
thank you Ike Turtle for the one dollar this isn't a hot dog
image but I made it a while back when you found the snake
in your room perma band
that guy
you can't
don't make me turn off links
I don't want to
I don't want to have to have people give permission
to post something if they think it's fun
or relevant or funny don't make me delete that
it's like strike two
you're better than that you're better than this
don't you gonna make me press the button
just delete that twitch user
why did I repost it
I've seen this before
use your infinity gauntlet
it's infinite gauntlet it's not
infinity gauntlet
alright that's it I'm out of here
last uh yep so thanks for the
one dollar uh toast to the end
of the worst year of my life
two hospital trips serotonin syndrome
major depression and no way to pay for my
medications just have my birthday on
the 9th keep making videos
jerma forever in my heart
well happy birthday I'm really sorry to hear that
I always feel so fucking terrible
when people talk about that kind of shit
that makes me feel so bad
that somebody's having that much of fucking
problem that much trouble
I sincerely hope from the
bottom of my fucking heart that you feel better
and that your life can get on the right track
I really do truly
having to deal with all that kind of shit
we got a great community here
we fuck around a lot
but that I mean the heart is
like solid gold you know it's like a solid
you can
I mean that's aluminum but it's made
it a solid gold I really hope you feel
better take care of yourself
thank you for being a part of this community
I appreciate
and cherish the fact that you're here
and so does it I would assume everybody else
thank you so much Yepso
hope you feel better
solid gold aluminum that's right
Yepso 10 bucks from Yepso
right at the end you're too kind
and I love you all thanks but I'm a tough cookie
good that's really good to hear
my heart is made of doge coin
that's solid gold aluminum
that's solid aluminum gold
touch the screen
and finally right at the end GoldenFoxy thanks for the one dollar
I'm going to bed but I gotta say
something Jerma thanks for being an amazing person after this message
I'm going to sleep have a great night
maybe see you on Monday
PS sorry I'm annoying
also if I get banned again I still
won't care
I don't think you've done anything particularly
annoying right now what are you talking about
you're good maybe we'll see you Monday
take care
what was the plan for Monday
I might actually blow
the fucking dust off the Dreamcast
and actually get that going
for Monday
it's possible
it's probably going to not happen
if I say it enough times
it'll come out of the fucking ghost closet
and we'll actually be able to use the damn thing
but that is it
I will see you all
I am exhausted
700,000 games
have a wonderful rest of your night
see you all soon take care
butterderp one dollar I'm sorry I posted the P word dad
please forgive me you're in big trouble
you are in big trouble
are you admitting to the crime that you committed
you're in big trouble
might actually have to put you in
I'm not I'm done being dead serious we're going to have to
make an example here
no forgiveness for an unforgivable sin
put him on trial
hey
hey I just wanted to let you know sorry I put
pornography in the chat
the thing the one thing that
you always say please don't do
sorry I did that
your trial will be determined
what happens to you don't expect me to go lightly
here at least he was honest
alright I'll see you guys
later goodbye good night
I'm like I need to go downstairs right now and eat
I'm starving I'll see you guys on Monday
take care have a great rest of your night
see you soon