This game is called Path to Die. It has two Steam reviews. It came out last week.
I might be running into a another um no no no no once like once every three or four months
there's like a bad stream oh hope not the stream goblin shows up and he's like
yes today is the day that i'm going to make the stream suck and he like grabs me but i'm
from like the back and pulls me back rips my neck forward oh i see you wanted to play
oh space channel five you loved the second one
and he fucking throws his hands out and casts like a bunch of magic spells at me
or sneeze whatever you want all right let's try this one it's called path to die it looks
like a top-down hotline miami-esque samurai game you control with the right stick i don't
know it might be great it might be a little hidden gem it might not even be worth playing
but we're going to try welcome to the stream everybody thanks for joining me
we may have found a great game i'm okay with that it looks pretty good let me just change
this delay on that anymore with this thank you for your patience guys i don't plan on shit
like this happening but sometimes it does here we go let's make sure the options oh this
is not plugged in better with i got a gamepad plugged in i was i came prepared for this one
so let's see turn it up a little effects graph graphics oh no ambience this looks familiar
it came out last week so maybe it looks a little familiar i am interested i'm just gonna
make sure this is loud enough for me okay that's better new game here we go so this is this
is a game where it's a well let's just experience it together brother the clan is
under attack they are killing everybody bring your family to the backyard hurry i will keep it
clear brother they killed her i couldn't save her now i'm dying too you must save my daughter
at least please dad no this takes place and um i don't know monsters you want to kill my
uncle go away but sir no exceptions no she would probably be running if i keep following
this path i will die fighting against the clan nagano by myself is something only a madman
would do i could run away live my life and die in bed as an old man but if we're going to die
either way i prefer to die with the blood in my hands i'll make them pay for what they did
good morning sir currently the entrance tax is 50 mon are you alone the others went to grab
something to eat you're really unlucky then with this heat and the blazing sun i think i'm
lucky waiting for them here in the shade i say you are unlucky because now you have to
fight me alone young man what why who are you my name is katsu akabashi akabashi you're from that
clan but they said they were no survivors your clan is going to pay for that mistake prepare
yourself use the left stick to move around you can hold right trigger to run but this
will consume stamina if you tap your character will dodge to the selected direction avoiding
damage except enemy arrows press a to interact with the environment this will allow you to open
doors or pick up objects the hud shows you the amount of health bleed is the amber part stamina
is the white ring katana sharpness is the white blade and arrows you have all right so red
circle is just health amber is the bleed stamina is the white ring and then katana
sharpness is the blade bleed limits the maximum amount of health you can have and
increases in a small proportion with damage received okay so that's just max health for
bleed katana sharpness affects how much damage your attacks inflict being halved with no
sharpness okay so that one i'm going to keep that up by pressing right bumper you can lock
on to enemies in combat you can change the target by pressing left stick the katana is
your main weapon is used with the right stick by pressing it you will unsheath or sheath your
katana with the sword sheath you can draw an attack at the same time only for left and
right attacks okay i have to try this with a semi-circle from left to right you'll make a
horizontal attack in that direction so you go like bang bang with with one from right to left
you the same opposite direction so bang bang with a forward movement you'll make thrust which
cannot be stopped by guarding but it is inflicted too much damage moving the stick back and forth
make a vertical cut that will break the enemy guard or inflict great damage the vertical cut
can be charged when you see a flash until you see a flash upon release it will inflict
double damage you can also pivot with left stick the 360 degree slash will help you create
space if you see yourself surrounded and will damage all the enemies around you moving the stick
towards the lower left corner and making a semi-circle the character rotates on itself
with a sword so you go down and all the way around okay extended what oh all attacks
consume stamina so be careful not to exhaust yourself in front of the enemy also the enemy
attacks a similar property so try to avoid guarding against a thrust so how do you guard
the yummy is the bow you will use throughout the adventure it can be very powerful
I can hear it but the amount of arrows is limited so use them wisely
I'm still here to equip the bow hold left bumper you can aim with the left stick to tighten it
and to move the right stick okay hold that bumper you can aim with left stick
to tighten it more move the right stick back and let go to shoot okay I'm gonna just play
around release left bumper to put the away the bow so you hold it pattern to the same
with keyboard and mouse I was recommended that I use a controller for this a good defense can
be decisive in any fight by holding left trigger you you'll start defending enemy attacks
you can continue moving with the left stick and you can choose the direction to look
to with the right stick this will also help so also make you lock on to the closest
enemy in that direction while defending your stamina will not recover as fast in their case
it's blocking if your stamina runs out your defense will break remember that arrows or thrust
cannot be stopped by defending in that blocking vertical cuts will drain a massive amount of
stamina don't worry if you can't remember all the attack patterns you can read it all again in
the weapon section of your inventory okay you need it now it's time to fight remember draw your
katana what was lock on right bumper okay here we go oh fuck do I don't have any arrows come
here fuck come on thrash him oh yeah I can dodge too there's like a dodge roll how good
is it how much health is he okay he's dead rest in peace young man the goblins behind
me stop stop stop stop stop rest in peace young man this is actually kind of fun it's not bad
there's no turning back now I can run as you can see on your left there are different types
of items in the game that represent it as packages red packages are food and recovery
health green ones contain drinks to increase maximum stamina temporarily and finally purple
contains bandages to heal bleeding and recover maximum health or wet stones to sharpen your
katana those bandages for bleeding and wet stones to sharpen katana not all objects will
have the same effect and some will be more effective than others also you'll find packs
of arrows for your bow or keys that allow you to open new areas get that mouse off the screen
the number of packages you can carry is limited to five for each item and 15 for
the arrows use them wisely navigate with the d-pad through your inventory press x to use the
selected object did I mute the music no I didn't you can also see a small table with a
brush ink and paper on it this is a save point and there are many more throughout your adventure
it is very important that every time you see one save your progress on it or you could lose
your valuable time since there are no checkpoints in the game be careful god damn it that's right
no checkpoints why don't you play mario tennis after this what the fuck up I got this okay
three is fine everything's fine everything's gonna be fine get out of here get out of my room
is it did I save it I did okay all right so we got okay we have that's healing this is
banned for okay how much bleeding do I have and then a wet stone okay so this is health
this is okay bandage let's just have the health I'm all right I'm all right on health
how do I run there it is oh fuck I'm almost dead how do you uh change targets again I'm
dead because I have a save point okay that's how you change target oh fuck oh fuck target
what I'm dead how do you change targets that I missed let me hey lake drinker thanks for
the five community subs thank you lake drinker for real uh what happened to the other wisdom
am I missing something here all right let me go back to my weapons how do I change target
again that's semicircle 360 degree slash what's the movement tutorial play the hotline
ost all right I probably should maybe I should stealth this guy okay click left stick shit oh
my god this is insane I don't even have my weapon out I'm dead
I got cut in half okay take out the weapon all right just one just get one at a time
no no no no no what are you doing I'm already almost dead watch that stamina oh fuck
back up back up back up back up back up okay good we're going okay I killed somebody where's
the other guy that kid that was over here I'm gonna go left let's see let's try left item
what the hell did I just do no that's not fuck I just took something why are you turning
around what the fuck are you doing right through the middle all right that's the stamina
boost thing all right easy I don't want to die here he's got arrows what do you got okay
a whetstone I'm good on sharpness the game has no soundtrack I need to sing
the game probably has music I'm just in the little first area what's this that's a person
okay I thought it was an item watch my stamina sing the hamster song I'm not gonna sing the
fucking hamster song right now why would I sing the hamster song god damn it I'm not gonna sing
the hamster song oh all right I'm getting better game crashed no no oh it's okay it's okay
my whole computer is locking up oh boy this is bad I can't even access yeah
yeah my whole I I'm locking up hard it's gonna be fine everything's gonna be just fine pretty
relaxed just open it again I'm not gonna get angry I'm not gonna get upset about any of this
at all we're just gonna try again and that's that's all you can do right that's it
everything's fine I'm happy can you see this on the screen yes you can okay I've got the
game pad end of happiness no I'm fine I'm fine I'm fine 2019 resolution I wanted to I wanted
to calm down right I wonder oh no I got two it's like three hits to kill somebody
okay you got to string it together send me energy I'm okay don't worry I just if I say
it enough times in a row it's gonna be true right where's this this is cool
ah the guy with the arrows is gonna piss me off I gotta string it together one two three
I don't know where I am I'm dead I gotta pull this guy back are you gonna follow me or what
what I missed where's the other didn't I pick there's no heel there's a healing potion
right here it's one guy all right cut them in half not bad I'm doing just fine I just
got to get the mechanics down and I can keep going I have no stamina all right where am I
at on the map over here so I'm gonna ask why am I playing this well um I had issues with
space channel five and it's all right I'm gonna save the game over here wait can I not once
I pass it that's the point of no return so what's up here oh come on is it really just
nothing up here no there's got to be something here no checkpoints yeah but I mean there's
got to be something though see if I can get them in one hit go go go go get out of the
fucking way what the fuck somebody said he's so sad no I'm fine it's okay kill the goblin
I can't he's invisible right can I like wander this away come here just walk into this
is he dumb enough kind of all right good mouse is not hidden I got it all right let
me try going up here again uh where did you come from was you this person wasn't here before
yeah they were gotta no this is a fun idea it is I can't block arrows all right this is the
guy that gave me the trouble before I still have a heal right this guy knows what he's
doing I don't like fighting this dude shit I'm going for it okay do you think we really
watch you for the gameplay come on give me give me a break I'm trying I'm trying here
there's nothing up here he's about to cry
what have I just turned on the webcam and I have tears of streaming down my face
what would you guys actually do I was hysterical like it is fucking streaming down my face
I would feel sorry but also kind of amused all right I gotta get this guy okay I would think it's
a bit okay I gotta heal again watch that stamina back it up look let me just get through
this first area and then I'll put on like the fucking Yoshi story theme song don't stab you
want to do that shit to me fine all right I made it let me grab the other items can you
take the weapons oh I don't think you can anything else down here is even more no
checkpoints either dude this game is brutal man the door is locked you need a key of course
they just don't make them like they don't make them brutal like this anymore no checkpoints
you got to find fucking key oh I wish Mario was like this all right this is the only okay so
for future reference if I die again I only have to go left did I get them both I think
I did shit I don't want them both at least I have a heal just one at a time
stop pulling aggro before the tank I'm sorry I can't help it fuck he hit me give me a fucking
break heal heal heal heal heal seriously key has to be right up here then that's only two I first
time I cleared this area all right we're gonna play mad libs okay once you're done in an area
you really get a sense of no it's not rep why would you even why would that even be okay
my sharpness is going down though retitle the stream to germa's unrelenting sadness shit come on
there's only one guy here nice key no hell wait you have more what else is here there's the
teeth the stamina bandage for bleeding you've unlocked a piece of the map press select to see
the new zone is there a save point I know there's no checkpoints but this oh yes okay
we're good well I didn't even see that guy can I do something with the cat I wonder if there's
like skill points shit I got hit I need a whetstone or something this is for this is for bleeding
I gotta use it right yeah I'm an idiot this is for what is this for special t
blocked it one asshole that was a good move that was a good move and I just got showed up
okay man let me just poke him yeah well I'm almost dead whetstone I'm not just a rock oh no
I need to sharpen my blade it took one or two hits to kill these guys before
I don't have any arrows either oh boy I need to sharpen my blade it's all right now I'm
gonna do this in the right order what is that I'm going to buildings what is this what the
hell is this a store this is a store this must be the inn I need information so I should
try to be friendly and ask one of the locals hello I talked to the well there's only one local
now there's two how do you talk well I just ate that's not a local I can talk to does eat
something no I talk to you uh maybe sit down well there's a whetstone finally this game is
called path to die and I don't I don't hate it okay let's just be clear about that I sit
I can sit at these tables well I'm gonna load the game because I uh I just fucked it all up
uh it's the bath I can't get in the bath or whatever that is there's a giant dog pee pad
I steal um unless there's a way um maybe it's a button I'm not pressing to interact
who about this person oh I'm stupid hello do you mind if I sit here can't you see I'm not
in the mood don't be like that just want to talk a little bit while we drink let me treat you some
sake deal so I saw a large building to the east on my way here do you know what it's for
that is the private gardens of hotaru nagano one of the sons of the feudal lord really is
there some way to meet this person that's not possible he is an eccentric man who rarely
leaves his house inside of the gardens even for most of us who work there would be
difficult so you work there could you let me in the next time what do you want to get us
killed listen you don't know these people they don't like outsiders and they are ruthless a lot
of people came to this village because they lost their homes in the war and came here seeking
protection and we have it but they treat us like dogs we work all day for them and they
barely give us enough food to survive particularly the captain of the guard is
really rotten they even arrested my daughter for confronting him she's just a kid I don't even
know if I will see her again I'm not gonna do anything that could harm her we shouldn't
have come here in the first place webcam turns on tears going down his face just like me
hey uncle training again why do you practice so much every day why someone has to protect
the clan from our enemies then you protect me and daddy and mommy of course that's my
job as a samurai what if i take your daughter back what are you serious i will take your
daughter back if you accept to help me what do you want with the nagano clan so badly
that you were willing to risk your life for it for a quarter of a second i thought that said
vegetables but it's a vengeance that's a huge one that's the biggest one we've seen all night
very well if you take yuki back i will help you but if you get caught i don't know you
that's fine where could they have taken your daughter everyone's getting timed up
you're all getting destroyed by night but there's a rectangular building in the center of the
village they use it as a headquarters as well as training should be there rectangle
building in the center of the village just whatever happens don't let them hurt her understood
i'll be waiting for you here in the room upstairs thank you can i get a better weapon or something
it's almost like spamming characters gets you timed out uh how was i supposed
is this out there waiting for me okay so we need to go in the middle of the village this
is a rectangle building right in the center it's all about getting them before they can
pull their sword out i think i'm gonna have to whetstone here
yeah somebody has a bow this guy's shooting them a lot faster than the other ones work
okay is this the building here are we in the middle i think i'm right in the middle
yeah stop right there this property is off limit state your business
i didn't come here to talk prepare yourselves what the watch out bow god this
somebody right back there oh my god no all right we're fine shit okay what do you drop
arrows finally hey a pick thank you for the five community subs anything else in this room
thank you pick is this more arrows i feel like i'm gonna need these and is that a safe one is
do i have healing i missed something make sure there's any health potions fight feeling
this is a boss so you the bastard's been killing my men what in the world would you
come this far for is it the stupid girl i've come for the girl and your head you're really
full of hate have i tortured you before i am katsu akabashi i will avenge my plan starting
with you i hope you are ready to pay for your life i dare you
wow he's quick whoa that's not how you do it what's the how do you do it
back it up oh no oh no i'm dead oh no oh no some right here let me actually use this health potion
back on the right stick
oh that's slow i think yeah i'm not gonna use the bow and arrow just walk
so watch out for the girl can the girl die no all right give me that hell give me give me
give me give me give me give me give me that wasn't a health potion i think dodging is the
way to go what happened where am i what you won't get away with this i'll enjoy your well-deserved
pain are you all right how do you know my name your father told me come on i'll explain it on
the car ride close your eyes until we get there we you don't need to see this my care holding
my carrier all right don't leave anything nice you put her in your pocket save game
yes please look i at least got to get to the first boss i missed the dun dun that was the first boss
didn't it didn't have a health bar it didn't count so we're gonna go back to the bar
i was supposed to be nice to the locals yeah the ones in the bar
daddy oh thank goodness you're okay i did my part now it's your turn i know take the key on
the table it'll open the garden's gate now you can get in there whenever you want but to get
to hotaru you need another key to his house i'll find a way you should hide when they
find out what happened they will come for you don't worry i'm done with this place i don't know where
to go but somewhere far away good luck maybe we'll see it another day i don't think i'm gonna
make this place out alive i will make it easy for them are you sure you want to give up your
life for revenge the last thing my brother aspie was to protect his daughter in his place
yet in the end she died protecting me instead it is laughable a little girl saving a samurai
there's only one way to repay them and regain my honor as samurai i will avenge them
even if it's the last thing that i do i understand i won't say anything more just
be careful farewell goodbye thank you sir for everything bye bye you're welcome i'll be taking
this too find a boss with a health bar and wait all right i have to pick it up they didn't
just hand it to me all right so this key opens which door again the garden door the one to
all the way to the right like this one right they literally said it's on the table
did they did they say that i don't remember well they said it was on the house like on the roof
what what the heck oh my god all right don't die here we're about to progress for the first
time we're about to actually progress a video game forward for the first time in two hours
this stream aren't you guys excited you use the key to unlock it you've unlocked a piece
of the map let's see this place is huge dot dot dot dot dot dot dot dot dot you only really need
two or three dots there after so many months i finally have a chance to begin fulfilling my
revenge they defined my way into the inner residence maybe i can find some supplies
around that i could use apart from the keys to the inner buildings and the guards will
not hesitate to kill me at sight after all what happened so i should be prepared to fight
at any moment uh well yeah sure did just open up this is huge yeah it is huge god
i'll take three hits on you don't do it don't do it don't do it i'll do it
i'm gonna just dance all around me message deleted message deleted message deleted
message deleted picto pics waiting room picto pics waiting room resident sleeper
picto pics waiting room god damn it i'm gonna fuck it up this time yes i am just restart
kill me no i can get him in like one hit i prefer picto pics waiting room where and
where is picto pics i will end this stream with picto pics i promise all right i can't do i
haven't i don't have anything to sharpen okay hold on finally okay i actually bought my
parents picto pics because of you and they really like it they're like 80 your parents
are not 80 years old that would make you it would make you like 48 that would make
you like 52 years old maybe you are and i'm just being an asshole and i don't think your
parents are 80 though your parents are 80 that's fine i'm glad you've got your parents that
game because it's a very good game it is so fun i need a whetstone let's give it a try
actually not that bad i can be a coward and just sit back how much damage is that doing
though i don't think it's doing very much actually yeah it is pretty good strat i thought
you're gonna do space channel five based on your tweet i actually probably should change that
tweet yeah i need to change that tweet damn it save the game i will let me get into the
middle here can i go through the bushes here no oops oops oops oops oops oops oh fuck what am
i doing what have i done okay i'm fine that entire zone is here ah could have played that
better yeah i know i know die no whetstone can i save it now i am i have no health i still love
you though now you guys are great thank you now even when i look at look at even when i have
all these problems and all this shit hits the fan on some streams look at this there's
three thousand fucking people here seriously back up back up back up oh my god i just got
headshot we're here just to make fun of you i've got to get through this area there's a
resident it's all right i think if you don't think they think they think the game is boring
that's all right it's um there'll be another one don't worry there'll be there'll be another
one there'll be another stream you'll see it again it'll happen i can't stand still i gotta
go after the guy with the bow first i'd like you to target that guy now let's pull up a
bow picked up extreme confirmed yeah i told her i'm gonna do it you have a bow too what
i didn't see you fucking swing at him whoa swing whoa no stop just hit him he's got a bow he's
got a bow you don't have to be concerned about the guy with the bow just go swing at him is
this the streamer who died to bow guy yeah it is i need a shopper and stone and i can't
find one why doesn't that not fire um video game i'd like to fire a bow where am i what's wrong with
me what am i stuck on did i oh i put the i i i no i wasn't stuck i was queued up in a big slash
had the bow put down it's no i don't need anything right now i need a whetstone that's
actually important why did you put that away i had an opportunity to make this right yeah
hold the hold left bumper up and then hold left bumper down up down what are you guys doing
i'm crying why did somebody just give 50 dollars 50 dollars 50 bucks for the technical
difficulty stream thank you so much regardless derma heard you're feeling a bit under the
weather the other day so i figured i'd splurge a little to help you pay for your doctors
five dollars you added too many zeros but thank you i really appreciate it that's a lot of fucking
money i'm glad you enjoy yourself nobody said germ is running out of ideas no just the ideas
that i chose to do today yeah it didn't work out i got plenty of ideas don't worry about
that i wish i didn't have a migraine because that god that was a big one that was a big
room that was the biggest one we've had a long time that's got to be like top five rooms has to
be uh anyway somebody just gave more money thank you judo upsetto for the five dollars i mean
50 dollars 50 bucks back to back don't cry jeremy wipe your tears with these 50 dollars
love you well thank thank you guys for the insane amount of money i gotta go save uh but
what i was gonna say is that oh no let me get to the safe point i gotta kill this person first
i have to what the hell am i doing okay you have so much health no my weapon is broken
i had a broken fucking weapon ah okay uh something rather gave 50 dollars too
thank you for 50 bucks something rather and you say uh oh no my apple juice money
germa pluto that's 150 dollars from three different people thank you guys so much and
then five community subs from jelen thank you so much guys and then as a hunt there's 100
dollars now the carano just gave 100 bucks they say uh hey jeremy my allowance got bumped
to five dollars this week i'm giving you a dollar from it hope it helps though it's not
much you guys really gotta check you always make sure you're in when you're checking out
you have the right thing selected but i do appreciate it unless you guys get some shit
loaded money people are going bankrupt to make streamer happy now it's not a competition
to you know give money that's a fucking lot thank you guys such an absolute insane amount
of money that was the best hundred dollar joke did i save it i don't even remember i'm gonna
go do it just in case uh 10 community subs from bebraham 10 coming in you guys are too
much thank you all of you oh what does that does that one that's okay that's just stream labs
catching up jesus but what i was gonna say is this was supposed to be vr but i've had
awful fucking headaches the last couple of days so i just can i couldn't get in that thing
today this week so that's why i had to think of something else to do in the meantime
and space channel five has been around for a while i figured we'd try it but you know
sometimes it just doesn't work and that's all there is to it and i'm gonna die you know let me
clutch this right now no i'm not how to do the big spin uh smashly gave 50 dollars use this
money to put a a hit on the rumor no that's insane a lot of money thank you guys you guys
are too generous to me what's the name of the game this game is called a path to die
and it really is not it's not bad it's not it's interesting i wouldn't be in it right now if i
didn't think so somebody will get this and they'll beat it in like fucking 40 minutes and
youtube it and it'll be like holy shit that guy beat this game in like 25 minutes i just
put them okay that guy these the ones that cause some trouble i gotta pee i gotta pee
and when i get back after let me try this another couple times okay let me try this
another two times to get like another save point and then i'm gonna i'm gonna throw the
towel in and play pickdoe picks for like three hours that's probably what's gonna happen more
a bit what are you guys doing uh nate natey kins thank you for the 50 bucks here's five
cents germa you guys you guys have lost your minds today thank you you guys are fucking way
too generous i need healing that's the problem no give me the bow okay that's a nice dodge
i have six arrows let me get a full charge kill him one hit that's close he actually just
yoda that thing now i really am almost dead buy him an island what am i gonna do with an
island stream from the island hold competitions this is gonna get real ugly if i do not get
a sharpening stone survive on a desert island stream did i actually just miss how embarrassing
that's an embarrassment oh this is bad oh shameful display all right last attempt and i'm
gonna go take a piss and we're gonna come back and i'm gonna and i'm gonna delete the vod no
i'm just kidding how am i supposed to all right here's my one gripe that i have with
the game so there's a mechanic where you the weapon dulls so you could be walking around
with a useless weapon but are there any other weapons to use because what happens if i just
don't if i don't find a whetstone here is just i just lose i have to hit the people
two or three times as many times zero sharpness is 50 less damage that sucks i wouldn't call
it a soft lock i would just i mean it's hard to handle i don't know block she went
through that oh man all right am i playing anything else yeah i'm gonna just play picked
up picks and we're just gonna chill it's a thrust yeah i have to like dodge the thrust
because i really am just screwed i need health i need my weapon is dull i need to shoot that
person with arrows that's so much easier because i don't think she can i don't think
they can block it oh my god she can dodge it though very easily and here comes the whole
zone all right i'll be right back we're gonna reboot we're gonna reboot the stream here i'm
just gonna come back and we're gonna play picked up picks and i'm gonna internal sunshine
of the spotless mine this game and then no that was fine the game was it was interesting
uh that's another 50 dollars from communist taco just came in right now or a minute ago
thank you thank you thank you for the fucking crazy amount of money hey jeremy use this to
buy the ps2 version of space channel 5 i don't think it's 50 bucks and i'm not sure i want
to do that but let me i'll be right back let me just grab some water and we're gonna
we're gonna hop into picked up picks and we're just gonna relax i'm just gonna be an old
band for like three or four hours be right back