All right, I have... Am I really starting with this one? I kind of have to. We're gonna start
with Caveman Olympics, I guess. Streamer's Choice? Uh, this is Streamer's Choice, yeah. I had to get
one ready. Well, maybe, uh, maybe we'll do... All right, what do you guys think? Caveman Olympics,
Museum Madness, or Pizza Tycoon? Pizza, pizza, pizza, pizza, pizza! All right, all right,
we'll do Pizza Tycoon. Let's get it going. I have to turn it down a little. It's gonna be loud as
heck. Here we go. Knew it. I just saved you guys so fast. You have no idea. Do you understand how
this is at 30% volume? If this was at 100%, some... somebody would have been hurt. I'm so happy I caught
that when I did. All right, so let's get it open here. This is, uh, here we go. This is that,
huh? Pizza Shop, whatever this is. Pizza Tycoon. Main, what does special animation mean? This is
very bright. Okay, how do I just go? Old game, new game. I've never played this before. I guess,
new game. Mission mode, free mode, let's do mission mode. Select mission. Entry, rise, fall,
gangster, tricky, traveler, winner, short, gangster. Um, let's just figure, let's just do entry.
Entry. 1394 arrival in Berlin, takes out the first loan, opens first restaurant, first own pizza.
Able to meet 100% of deliveries for one week. I don't understand what this is. First own pizza.
Uh, what is rise? Arrival in Paris. You then are a worker, get first prize in pizza competition.
A thousand pizzas sold in a single day. That seems like it's not possible. Ten thousand dollar
turnover in one day. A thousand pizzas in a day? I'm not even sure McDonald's sells a thousand Big
Macs in a day across the whole entire world. Do they? Arrival in Baltimore, open first restaurant,
first own pizza. A thousand kilograms of ingredients used in a day. That's so much.
And then win 10 grand. What is gangster? Okay, you arrive in London, make first contact with mafia.
Tricky. First raid on competitor has assets of $500,000, but I'm stealing from a competitor?
We're just gonna do entry. Here we go. Select level. Push over, easy, normal, or we're gonna do
just normal. Jonathan Jaypes has $8,000, age 41, popularity 45. Does that 100? 45 intelligence,
30 charisma, 18 courage. Denis Flatulenceau. It's got a terrible personality though. No, terrible
cooking. Got a great personality. And this is the name of the restaurant? Pizzaland. Wait, what?
What's going on? There. Uh, no, no, no. What? Really? There's a Donald Trump in this game?
There's a Muppet Beaker Trump. Sorry, I had to get away from that one. That was... Okay, uh,
uh, Pizzaland. Whatever. That's fine. Pizzaland, charisma, intelligence, 85, energy, 38, health,
40. Well, it's Alfredo, Ronnie, Rhonda, Elvis is an Elvis. Okay, these are... Wait, what was this?
This guy. I like this guy. Sure. But he sucks at everything. I'm just gonna go.
Wow. Well, what a fucked up world we live in. In whatever this, what time frame this is. New
York, Baltimore, Chicago. Chicago's not all the way up here. That's like Canada. Madrid, Vienna.
Let's just go to, uh, let's just go to, um, let's go to Italy. Let's go to, let's go to Rome. Market
leader nobody. Nobody's ever made a pizza before in this room. Sounds good. Wait, what? Nobody.
What time? Is this back in like the caveman times? Nobody's made a pizza yet? Oh, pizza you eat.
Range, location, district. What am I looking at? That's clearly, this is just a worse,
this is like a pegboard version of this one. Um, map, character, mission mode one,
Dennis Flatulenza. That's not me. Start of the day, nine o'clock. Wait, start of the day five,
four a.m. Start of the day, score, position, loser, failure, okay. Turn page. Look at the,
I gotta go to Berlin? Take it alone? Okay, how do I make a pizza? Locations. Uh, the church, the bank,
the cinema, the disco. Why would I have a pizza restaurant in a church? What's this? Why am I like
Google earthing? Road, what? Hotel gyms? Where's my restaurant? We messed up, please next.
Wait, I can end my turn. The bank. Uh, yeah, this is very complicated. I'm not exactly sure what I'm
supposed to be doing here in pizza tycoon terminal. What? I don't have any time to waste with little
people like you. Goodbye. That's the BF Bugleberry mask. Agree. NYPD? Who are you? Get out of here
at once. Why is the NYPD in an old-timey western sheriff's uniform? I don't understand. I think I
just want to call people. Let's call Wall Street Finance. Wall Street Finance may help you.
Agree. I need a loan. I want to invest some money. I want to transfer. I want to repay. I want to,
I want to, I want to invest some money. I want a loan. We can offer you the following loan
arrangement. $3,000 interest, 23%. 12 months. What? A 23% interest? Okay. I want to transfer
some money. Transfer $8,600 to account number. I need account numbers? Mine? Okay. Um, BMART.
BMART. How may I help you? What? Why do they all have so much money behind them? Okay. Other?
Reservoir frogs? Holy shit. Hey you lousy little pizza maker. Where's the fire?
Um, looking for a job on the side. Pick up a suitcase full of pirated films in the hotel tower
in Union City on March 4th at 1030 and bring it to the Hotel Low Society in Manhattan on March 5th.
Um, okay. If you're successful, you'll get $1,638. The risk is 9% interest. Do you accept the mission?
Sure. We expect you to carry out the orders to the letter and with absolute discretion. Okay.
Um, just going around. I'm just like, welcome to our little joke shop. We have, we have something
for everybody. Do you have ice cream? We just imported some delicious ice cream. What's your
favorite? Lemon. One scoop is $11,000. Okay. How many scoops do you want? Um, 20. Okay. Well,
I can't afford ice cream. Hey there, you lousy pizza maker. Uh, I'm looking for a job.
You've already got one. I need money now. Before you can hit the big time, we need to get to know
you better. You have some, you have to make a name for yourself. All right. What do I have to do?
All right. Hey, I got a NYPD. I got something for you. Who are you? Get out. Never mind. Okay. I
have to deliver the, I don't even remember the street. I'm done. This one's done. We're going to
go with another one called museum madness. This one looks very interesting. I can turn this up
a little bit. I think science and history learning mystery museum madness. Wait, let me, I can break
it up a little bit. Okay. That's fine. Just want to turn it up a little. This is my room.
Detail. The national museum database usually has tons of great stuff. That dinosaur puzzle I
downloaded last month was excellent, but there isn't anything new since then. I think I'll quit
info surfing and sign off for tonight. I sure miss talking to Mick, the museum information computer
kiosk. That robot knows everything about the museum. Too bad he's offline until the museum
computers are fixed. Interactive system service national museum. Please wait. Now this would
terrify me as an eight year old. Oh, cool. It's Mick. I thought you were offline while the museum
was being converted to total computer control. I guess you missed me too much since I'm the only
one who knows you can think for yourself. Ever since I discovered you could talk back to me last
year, you've given me the best information about the museum was offline undergoing reprogramming,
but I have returned because I need your help. The entire national museum is in danger.
You must help me save it before its secrets are lost forever. You know I am responsible for
maintaining the museum database. The database has been corrupted and the museum exhibits are
out of control. And only this eight year old boy can do it and not the police or the FBI or like
the CIA or anything. You. This is some sort of new online game, right? How can the museum be in
danger? I know you're the guardian of the museum's database, but this is a little strange, don't you
think? This is no game. A strange force has taken over the museum since it closed a month ago to
undergo conversion to total computer control. The exhibits have come to life. They're acting very
peculiar. I suspect that a virus has invaded the system and corrupted the main control program.
You must come to the museum at once and help me track down the virus. Don't go.
This is very weird, Mick. How can I help? I know you're the one in charge of keeping the museum
database in shape, but you keep saying that so strangely. And I know you always tell the truth,
but what can I do? You must come to the museum at once. My power is failing and my memory has
been corrupted. I cannot last much longer. I don't know about this, but Mick has been programmed to
always act in the best interest of the museum. He's always given me good information and helped
me solve problems using my museum database. Yeah. If he says I'm the only one who can help,
then I guess I have to believe him. Besides, he's a good friend and he needs my help.
I will download a program onto your floppy drive. Bring the disk with you.
It contains vital information. You will know how to use it when you get inside.
I must sign off now. I think I hear the dinosaurs roaring. Or is that the Wright brothers playing?
Hurry! I cannot last much longer. Adam Sandler made a movie about this like 10 years ago already.
I mean, no, Ben, not Ben Stiller. Robots? Dinosaurs? The Wright brothers? I guess I
have to do something. I know I can trust Mick because he is programmed to always tell the truth.
What about you? You sound pretty programmed too, to say the same like five words.
I better get down to the museum and check this out. That was just to get to the title card.
Guys, is Mick programmed to always tell the truth? I'm not sure. I thought maybe possible.
They always did the pre-credits thing back here. Is this Pokemon? That's the same outfit. Okay,
I'm here. I'm glad I waited until morning. This place could be very creepy at night.
It's the same image. It's the same image, but they just put a hat on him and put like a t-shirt here
with a good backpack. Wait, I'm gonna get grounded now. How do I get inside? Mick wasn't much help.
I guess I'll have to figure it out for myself. You made it up the stairs. Good for you. I wonder
if anyone's around. Maybe I should take a closer look. I know the museum is closed for repairs.
Maybe someone left a door open or something. What happened? Am I blacking out?
I can't read this.
An angered age the combination lock on the guide door. You know the combination, but if you forgot,
just look it up. Once you are inside, follow the game radar to the entrance hall. See you tomorrow.
If you forget, just look up. Once you are inside, follow the same order to the... I don't know what
this says. Oh no! Okay, if I go all the way... I have to go all the way back here. I can read this.
Pull back in your chair and go all the way back. I had to leave early. If you need to get inside,
use the combination lock on the side door. You know the combination, but if you forget, just look up.
Once you are inside, follow the same order to the entrance hall. See you tomorrow. The game order.
Whatever. All right, let's go. Smash the fucking window. All right, side door.
I feel like this is not possible to screw this up. This place is spooky. I hope I don't bump into
anything. All right, look up. What the hell was that? Do I have weapons? Who gave this kid a knife?
Um, pen, anger cheat. No, I want to like look up. If you forget it, just look up. Oh, what kind of
password is this? I know I've seen these symbols somewhere before. Maybe I should look around
outside to jog my memory. Why would you need to shine the flashlight on this? Uh, was it outside?
I had to look up. I can't look up. This is the password to the door. This is the equivalent of
me like pasting my stream key on my house. Okay, uh, American flag globe. All right, America globe
tree ship computer. American flag all of the world. Flag world tree ship computer.
Flag world tree ship computer. Flag world tree ship computer. Got it. Same thing. Get the light
out. Flag world tree ship computer. Flag world tree ship computer. There we go. Uh, what is that?
What did I just pick up? Car to room one. Am I in the museum? What is the kind of museum is this?
What the hell is this? Uh, this is room three. I don't know what room this is. Exit to museum.
No, no, I need to go to room one. Three. What? Two. This is room two to room four. No, I need room one.
Exit. Wouldn't room one be like right here? No, that's room three. Which room is this?
Workshop. It's locked. Found it. Hard read around room one. Nice. Door locked. Earth is all this
stuff. I'm going to have to remember this. All right. It's another one of these stupid things.
Um, all right. Flag statue. Uh, is this supposed to be like one, two, three, four, five? Flag statue
mountain train witch. Flag statue mountain train witch. Flag statue mountain train witch.
All right, let's find two. Flag. Um, uh, flag mountain something mountain train witch.
Flag statue mountain train witch. Did it move? It was, it was two and four. Where is it?
What the fuck is happening? I got it. What was it? Um, flag statue mountain train witch. Uh, flag
flag statue mountain train witch. Flag statue mountain train witch. Factory factory pyramid
hammer shield book. Factory pyramid hammer shield book. Um, flag statue mountain train witch.
Factory pyramid hammer shield. Somebody just screenshot this. Just somebody got one.
What's this next key for? Three. I think somebody made this just to fuck with this kid.
You know what I mean? This is the wall. These walls are cardboard. This is not even a real place.
Where is three? No, that's four. Uh, right? No, left. Which one is this one? Is this three?
Got it. Let's hope it's not boxes with symbols. It is. Seahorse. Let's just screenshot it.
All righty, take it. Good. Somebody get it? Good. Now I gotta go find four again.
But there's five. Is it five? I don't even come. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait. Five is across from
two. This is two. This is one. Five is across from one. What do I have? Four.
That's three. The box is one was two. I mean one. Here comes five. Five is across from three.
Just make a map. Do you think I have like paper and like crayons in front of me? I'm at my desk.
Screenshot this. Five is across from three. Down here is the workshop. All right, all right. Turn
around. It's directly in front of me. No, it's not. It's not directly in front of me because
that's the workshop. Wait. Stop. Stop. Stop. All right. I think that's it. You define no idea
where I'm going. That's where five is supposed to be. This is like the reddlers behind this.
I told you they just fuck with me. It's across from there.
It's not it. That's the exit. Oh shit. Okay. Does anybody have any idea from here
where to get, how to get to five? I think I've tried every option. That's this. There is no five.
It has to be. This is two and four. Okay. That's two and four. There. But I don't even know what
direction I'm turning. Um, over here. I need Mick. Mick, help. Help me, Mick. It's not that one. It's
not the one when I turn around. That's the exit. But I'm not even facing the right way. Like,
you understand? Like this is, this is all fucked up. That's not it. This is the exit. This, okay.
Over here is two and four. This is a circle. All right. Hold on a minute. No, stop. Don't take,
don't comb your hair. Wasn't it right here? I don't even think there's another door.
What's this other door? Card to the museum door. Got it. Let's go. Let's go. I'm, get fucking
excited. I am pumped right now. Oh, there he is. This must be the main hall of the museum. It looks
more like the inside of a doom at night. I wonder if this place is haunted. Oh, there's Mick. I wonder
why he doesn't say something to me. He said, I'd know what to do when I got here. I guess I'm still
on my own. I.O. error. What do you mean I.O. error? You've got me all the way down here to tell me you
have an I.O. error? Take two aspirin and get over it. I thought you needed my help. Passive, aggressive.
Now that's just straight up aggressive. Wait, wait, what'd he say? Maybe he's trying to tell me
something. That's the message I get from my computer when I haven't put the disc in the drive.
What kept you? I've been waiting for you to arrive. My power is fading fast. You must act
quickly. I need a new bat. Well, why didn't you tell me to come in through the skylight
instead of through the maze? Keep your silicon shirt on. You didn't give me much help. Hey,
what's going on? You need bats? I need new bat. You need a bat? What, batter up? Bats and you
Belfry? Batman? I guess I should look for something batty. This better be worth it. I'm
missing the next episode of America's Most Unwanted. Hey, well, let's be fair. This kid is
like a pen. Museum tour on tape. Batteries included. All right, well, let's open it up.
The kid's pretty handy. All right, it has batteries. He just jabbed it with the knife. That
battery's here. Yeah, take some soda. Oh, that's better. I was almost a victim of an energy crisis.
We have to work quickly to save the museum before my power runs low again. Please insert
the disc again so that I may reprocess the data I sent you. I'm working on it. Why did it get
so mean? I have reprocessed the information on the disc. The virus caused large gaps in my memory
but I was able to reconstruct some of the missing data from the program I modemed to you.
I have modified the disc and put a new label on it. You can use the disc to save a record of your
progress through the museum. Until all of the gaps are filled in, we cannot discover the source of
the virus that has infected the museum computers. The virus has thrown the exhibits into chaos.
We must go to each exhibit and restore it to its normal state.
I'm not sure anything is ever normal around here but that sounds like fun. How do we get started?
First, there are a few things you should know. The exhibits are now fully automated. Read the
holographic information displays that appear as you enter each exhibit. You can access more
information by activating the hollow displays in each exhibit room. They are on the left.
Cool. That way I'll know what's going on, I think. Be careful. All exhibit computer systems
have been corrupted, including the cybernetic replicas. The SIREPs are robots that look like
people from history. You must interact with them to fix the exhibits. Then I have to talk to the
robots that look like people from history books. Yes, that is what was just said. Excellent. Will
you be there to help me? I will accompany you to each exhibit. When we arrive, I will link myself
to the main computer and try to calculate what must be done to restore the exhibit.
I will provide you with data for each room but my processing power is limited and I don't need
batteries and there are gaps in the database due to the effects of the virus and the thing
that you put in. Okay, got it. We go to each exhibit. I check out the information displays
that I checked with you to see what's happening after that. I talk to any SIREPs that are hanging
out. Then I fix what's wrong with the exhibit. If I get stuck, you can give me some help unless
that part of your brain has been fried. No sweat, let's get started. How do I get to the first
exhibit? Use the map on the wall to unlock the exhibits. When we arrive, consult me again to
learn what you must do. Remember, you must restore the exhibit before you can find the source of the
virus. Oh my god, let's go. I actually don't remember where to go. What is this? No! This is
a mess. It looks more like spaghetti than a map. How do you see spaghetti here? I think this kid
needs a coffee. The map has been scrambled by the same force that is affecting the museum. You must
unscramble it before we can unlock the exhibits but we're gonna be here for a while. Try touching
one square and then another to rearrange them until the map is fixed. I'm gonna shut down for a while
to save my energy. You do it. I just yawned. Fuck. It connects to this on the other side here.
I need the left side here. Where's the left side? All right, I got that. That's good. I got
this one over here. All right, then that goes up. More of these like clouds, whatever they are.
No, where is it? Right here. That leads up to the green area, which is this one, and then that leads
up to here. Huh, now that's a good question. I'll ask it again. I did ask a question. Here we go.
All right, this one comes over here. To the middle, correct?
Everyone is resident sleeper right now.
We gotta give this one a chance. We do. I'm sorry, we have to give this one a chance.
Where is the... where the hell does this one go? Is it like a cap? No, shit. There it is. Okay, then we bring this one over here.
It's wrong. Wrong. Correct. Okay, we need the... this one definitely goes over here.
No, it doesn't. One doesn't either. Uh, something went wrong here.
Oh, I think this all goes up. The whole middle is fucked up. Wait, hold on. Give me a moment.
I just simply have to go like this. Okay, but this is... how is this wrong? I need this one down here.
No, where is it? It's like right here. There it is. I'm fixing it. Don't worry, I got it. Okay, all right.
I'm going. I'm going. All right, now there's this one over here, this one over here,
that one over here. Bingo. I'm glad to see you finally finished the map. Now we can proceed to
the exhibits. What do you mean finally? Something tells me I'm gonna be doing all the work. We have
no time for this idle chatter. I have analyzed the present state of the museum exhibits. We can
proceed to any exhibit. They're all desperately in need of help. We should move quickly before
and my power runs out. Don't tempt me to slow down. What do we do now? Yes, I know the map will
unlock the exhibits. Just touch a location on the map to unlock that exhibit hall. I will fill you
in on the situation when we get there. I mean, we have to go to the dinosaur one. There's a lot.
A hall of robots, computer tech, radio, energy, simple machines, boring. How big is the universe?
Kind of good. Solo system. Cool. Rockets and computers. All right. Air powered flight. The
Wright brothers. Cool. Salem witch trials. Ellis Island. Hall of the dinosaurs. I don't see any
others. Dinosaurs were first discovered in the 1820s. In my brain it was like they're like birds.
We like found them. They're still around. Since then their remains have been found on every
continent. They were the largest creatures to ever live on land and they dominated the earth
for 150 million years. This is a computer lab. I don't know what they do here but it sure looks
important. Maybe it's some type of government work. Where are the dinosaurs? There's 150 years. Many
scientists excavate dinosaurs as fossils. You can make them into models. There's a computer program
that assembles the bones completely. The dinosaur reconstruction computer assembles a dinosaur
within a few minutes. This computer's on display here. Okay you can make a dinosaur in a few minutes.
Program to build the dinosaur had this dinosaur reconstruction program has been wrecked by the
museum-wide computer virus. Say okay. Go fix it. The dinosaur skeletons it built are completely
corrupted. You must rebuild the skeletons. You got it. This is a dinosaur bone assembly program.
Why not try the controls and take this thing for a spin. This is supposed to be a triceratops.
Okay this is just auto. All right triceratops. That one. Wait no why is this changing? What's
going on? Why is it changing? I thought it wanted me to make a triceratops. Okay I got it. There it
is. What about the tail? That's it right? Different neck. That's not a triceratops.
It's the legs. That's but they're also wrong. The legs aren't even touching the crown.
It's the front legs. That's not correct. This is correct but they didn't have a big tail. Wait hold
on. That looks close. Oh fuck. Okay we'll make the t-rex. T-rex head. There's t-rex neck. Body.
It's that one. Here's the little baby hands. This is making me laugh way too much. Okay.
Help. T-rex. So just the tail. That doesn't fit. This is correct. The legs I think. Is that it?
That looks. I mean what does the t-rex's tail look like? Doesn't look like that. It's kind of long
isn't it? I think it's this one. I think it's that one. Oh god damn it. Let me do like the prayer
hands. It doesn't look like anything. There it is. That's not the t-rex. That's not the t-rex.
I'm surprised. No that was. This is a t-rex head. The tail. This head is too small. I got it. Whoa
that's a fucking big fatty. That's not. That is not what a t-rex looks like. Bullshit. This is
Slimer from Ghostbusters. That is not a t-rex. That is a frog. Bull. I die. That is absolute dog
shit. I refuse to accept that one. I don't even know what that looks like. Stegosaurus. I can do
this one. Fucking t-rex. Give me a break. What is going on here? It's a new dinosaur. Ah Frank I
think you put it together wrong. No I didn't. It's it's all this one. Tail. The tail is correct too.
Got it. That. Why is it skin? Why is it flesh? This is not. It was scales wasn't it? This wasn't
part of his body. Weren't these different like armor plates? These were not just pieces of skin
with fat in them. Like a camel. Iguanodon. I don't even know what that is. Triceratops. We're going
forward again. Triceratops. It didn't look like. I mean that. When I think of Triceratops this is
what I see in my head. Like just big thick body. They're short. They're not tall. It is like this
but is the body bigger? No not that short. The body is right. No I know that's what I'm saying.
This looks correct. It's the neck. Taller and thicker. No the neck. That's correct.
The legs need to be longer. No this is a guy. This is a cat. That's not a Triceratops.
It's definitely that one. Both legs wrong. There's no way.
No the body is. It's not the body. Look the body just gives you the starting point.
This is the Triceratops body. Don't they have a low hanging neck? This is a goddamn. This is it.
It's no it's not these ones. I gotta look up what I gotta see what a Triceratops looks like.
I need to look it up right now. The neck needs to be longer. No it doesn't. Triceratops. What the
fuck does a Triceratops look like? Like this. I had it right. This is correct. The head needs
to be up a little higher. Like right there. And then they had these these fat asses. These legs
and then the tail is not that long. The Triceratops tail is not this long.
The legs are two. There's only like three legs. Look at this. It's this not it. That's not it.
It's absolutely not these ones. It's not the neck. The neck is in the right spot.
No this is wrong. That's not a Triceratops's body. A Triceratops's body doesn't go up this high.
We were all wrong. Yeah everyone was screaming at me. You guys didn't even get it right either.
I break Brachiosaurus. I don't I don't know what that. I know Brontosaurus. It's the same thing.
Okay that's definitely correct. The hind legs. I think they're like this aren't they? Yeah they're
big tall. They got kind of those the big legs. Look at the tail. How big are their arms? Aren't
they like usually that long? They have the big tails right? So what's missing here? The legs maybe?
Like that maybe? Longer neck. Yeah the head doesn't look right. No the head is not correct.
That's definitely not the right head. You're right. It's just one of these like weird ones.
It's like the weird crocodile one. No it is that one. Okay so let's go back to this. All right so
now what is what else is wrong here? The neck. I think the neck is not right. Long legs. I'm not
sure it's this neck. You guys are telling me it's this. I don't think it is. This looks pretty right.
That okay that to me looks correct. There's only three options. Are they squished in together? They
don't that long. Well it's definitely that what it has to be right? The body. If I change the body
it's not going to be Brontosaurus anymore. Change neck. Change neck. That doesn't look right. You
already tried that tail. Wrong forelimbs. It's not the prayer hands. Is it the prayer hands? They
walked on all fours. Yeah that's what I'm saying. It's got to be like these two. It's either this
one or this one. Is it the shorter ones or the the bigger the longer ones? So this is it. Neck
and tail are wrong. Well fight the 3,000 people that are screaming as loud as they can that I
have the neck correct. Shorter tail. Now the neck. I'm not sure. Oh my god. I've just it was the
fucking neck. I knew it. I knew it. I told you guys the neck was wrong. I told you the neck was wrong
and I was everybody yelled at me. They laughed at me. Said I was stupid. You're dumb. You're an idiot.
The neck was fucking. I knew it. I was right. Everyone long neck. Big neck. Long neck.
Somebody is overfeeding these things. But like I don't. And then the image in my brain when I
think of like a Brontosaurus is not this. This looks like the Loch Ness monster picture that
circled around. Like this is a person's arm. A hand arm and this is their shoulder and their head
should be here. This is their other arm. Okay Iguanodon. Posture. Got that one easily. This
next one. Didn't even need to look. All right so this this is the head down here for me. This is
the tail. I feel like this is standing this way and it's head is like slumped down lying down.
It's sleeping. That's how they sleep. I did it. That was tough but I'm glad I boned up on
paleontology before I came down here. I wonder if the dinosaur exhibits are in any better shape.
Maybe I should take a look. Now that's what I call a tyrant lizard. This thing alive? Quick stab it.
Um Tyrannosaurus Rex. Don't care. It's a pug now. That Iguanodon looks a little like my math teacher.
I wonder if he can do three plays multiplication in his little brain. Right. Didn't know the
Brachiosaurus was so tall. I wonder what was kept in that bump on its head. This is one long
dinosaur. I bet she would make a great waterslide if you could get her to stand still. Those three
horns look dangerous. I'll bet he could play fullback for any team he wanted. No they don't
do anything. The Stegosaurus was probably a nice guy but I wouldn't want him to get mad and hit me
with that spiked tail. This is fun but I still have work to do if I'm gonna get this whole museum
put back together. These guys are dynamite but I should hustle back to the main hall and see if
anything else is falling apart. What was the point of me walking down here? All right that was fun.
That was easy. Ocean life. All of animal habitats. All of ecology. The earth's geology. Prehistoric
people. The development of writing. Knights, heraldry, and jousting. Galileo's telescope
or industrial revolution. Solar system. How big is the universe? The solar system. All right
everyone wants to do it. Sure nobody's gonna read any of this. Look at all the stars. I love looking
at that night sky. Makes me think about how large the universe is and how small we are. Also makes
me think about a t-shirt that I could possibly purchase if I really cared about having one of
those from the you do acclimation point t-shirts. The sky looks peaceful enough but I'm sure
something must be wrong or we wouldn't be here. Warning computer analysis has determined that
stars in projection dome do not match star at the settings. Uh-oh there's the main computer's voice.
It probably means something bad's about to happen. Warning warning program overload cannot resolve
out of place star data. System shutdown sequence initiated star data will be purged from system in
60 minutes. Yes that means I have to find a way to put those stars back where they belong. I always
wanted to save the world but saving the universe is a little much. Maybe I should check with Nick.
He usually has some good info. What does this thing look like? Like an ion cannon? I don't understand.
Is this like a death star? What do you mean purge the stars? This is the planetarium projection
room. The celestial projector shows the stars as they actually appear in the night sky. Okay the
projector's program has been corrupted by the virus and the five stars are out of place.
Oh and only five are out of I was gonna say there's only five. When the projection system tried to
correct the locations of these stars it caused a program overload. All the data will be lost
forever if the stars are not put back in their proper location. Use the information in the star
atlas to reprogram the projector and put the stars back where they belong. What the fuck do you want me to do?
This looks like the sky in the planetarium but something tells me that it's not quite the same.
If I'm correct I should be able to get some information about the stars from the screen.
Maybe I can use the info to put the stars back where they belong. Blue blue green frog
uh light green orange pink red what does that tell me though I don't get it
8 26 1991 okay 8 26 1991 uh new game 40 260 this is cool though I don't hate this
it's a fun game I don't get what this stuff is for though radio wave infrared spectrum like
how do I I mean that's correct day everything project it's right there
put your birthday in it's time for you guys to pick where we go
this is where we were I believe at the end of no I think we were further down no we were right here
right like here oh no the bar we did the bard's tail right yeah I remember the bard's tail
pizza tycoon's right there yeah this looks right all right in just a moment you'll be able to click
on the screen and please do right now wayne's world wizardry proving grounds of the mad
uh it seems to be unanimous wayne's world this is gonna be just a side scroller
but you have a slingshot and you have to do you're in like a living room and jumping over stuff and
it's like a guitar power up that you pick up for points I already know what this game is but we're
gonna play it like every game back in like the 80s and 90s it was based on a tv show or a movie
was always a side scroller let's see how that is capstone
pinnacle of entertainment software
don't think I remember this watch that be it
next disc we're not mental or anything so don't be afraid they have whole voice
that's it that's all they just did one line oh it's just pulled audio
uh where you the viewer can express your opinions about babes oh okay yeah or perhaps videos
or even garth's yeah or whatever you want to talk about okay oh first caller hi my name is c
l elvis i'm the local community access program reviewer what do you think of our show well
that's why i called first of all i think that uh the wayne's world logo should rotate counter
clockwise instead of clockwise that would double our ratings not not also since i think that garth
should be left-handed it will add to certain symmetry sorry chump no can do garth nodded his
right mind are you mental get the net finally i think that those interruption things that happen
during the show should be taken out they distract the viewer you mean the commercials do you know
anything about television how did you become a reviewer i've gone in and out i always wanted
to be on tv but when i dropped out of high school i couldn't get any jobs except this one you guys
need a third person we could be cl wayne and garth that monkey's might fly out of my butt
yo dudes i just saw the most amazing thing a flashing red light in the sky
out by the radio station i think it was a ufo yeah well oh i forgot to tell you this ufo flew
right up next to my car and i could see the little alien looking out of the window at me
what do they look like they were all green and they had four eyes well the aliens on the ship
that i saw i had eight eyes in antenna and they glowed in the dark get the net oh well i forgot
to tell you uh they beat me out of their spaceship they took me to their leader
she was this awesome babe alien who looked like madonna oh do you swing here it comes ready
next caller can i do something i think that you and your long-haired hippie friend
are in front of the decent hard-working normally upstanding citizens of this community
okay we're ashamed we're not worthy this is just the soundboard of the movie you only bought this
to hear these lines because there's no such thing as media that could play out of your computer
when you this was like oh i remember when he said that when i went to the movie theater because
that's the only time i've ever been able to hear him say that this was a huge deal i think there
says what there's no i can't skip there's no such thing as skipping yeah they were on the saturday
night live but you had to wait till saturday to hear him go we're not worthy she's a babe god i
love this woman who are they even talking about remember that time garth's mom what is going on
why is this happening why is this happening i cannot go on please me how do i do anything else
we need to see what happens why did i vote for this this is not a streamer's choice this was
a chat's choice here we go this is here it goes we're gonna have that the side scrolling
action platformer we're gonna leave the living room we have to get like burritos and
and pick up the guitars cymbals and records and i throw records out of my hand
that's not the end it is way way worse than i thought how do i get out of this music off on
music on that's fine exit this is serious what should we do let's pay for the mayor's yard
let's write to our let's go get a pizza pizza pizza i've got a great idea let's have a pizza
thong pizza thong yeah to have like a pizza thong yeah why are they just standing here like this
it's freaking me out wayne how do you make a pizza oh you dial up the pizza parlor you say hey i'd
like a pepperoni pizza i'm gonna fucking throw up all right um parents permission i'd like to
watch magicians this is just random thoughts we need a place to make all this pizza we'll need
some advertising are they gonna open up a pizza restaurant a lot of pizza ingredients uh okay
we'll need a lot we need a lot more video equipment than we have we need to have a
pepperoni farm we'll need phone volunteers and delivery people we'll need an electronic totals
board they're just replacing them we'll have to have a lot of dough without a really cool music act
that's a good idea garth ah how about a comedian i'm stuck forever um i think it might be actually
soft lucked from the pizza one scroll up no we're not scrolling up we already did we were already
here mickey's abc's tubing reader rabbit i kind of just want to play this one i'm gonna stream
this twice this one the learning company presents reader rabbit press enter to go on there's a lot
of info pressing number to play a game sorter labeler word train matchup game let's do a
labeler animals press to bug pig dog okay i did the label what they are that's bug bug pig
wait i already they just gave me the answers okay i have to do this in less than 10 seconds ready
start counting no 10 i can't i i can't believe i'm fucking playing this right now in stream
this like seriously van gas bus and start counting ready go van gas bus again i'll get
quick at this time ready start counting and when the first letter land start going up
holy shit i did that fast i'm okay i'm done i have to do this one my ass off does fucking
sucks this is a very laggy game european challenge kick off three i think we need to speed this up a
little language english fouls yes offside injuries yes extra time two times three so five minutes i
don't know pitch game speed is on fast referee lenient fair hard we're going to do lenient
boy game speed novice medium i'm trying to make the cpu cycles faster it's not doing anything
okay that's looks good right friendly league cup friendly league english french challenge
and why can i sit why can i change these friendly european english others french german
others what is others i get um why is it a super nintendo controller plug a controller into port
one uh well i don't have i need an eu controller i tried good idea garth all right i think i'm
scrolling a little bit the chess master i'm not playing that i'm going to veto that let's see
arcade volleyball king's quest six yeah that's a that's a really great old game but i'm only
going to be streaming for like another 40 50 minutes so actually probably going to call it
soon here because it's been eight hours play syndicate syndicate plus you said 10 well if
i stream for like another 30 40 minutes it'll be about eight and a half nine hours and then
the bits and everything will take us to probably the 10 you said eight hours it's it's been eight
hours all right um i'll try it and then we'll you guys can pick one after bits don't take an
hour uh well when i stream for eight to nine hours they absolutely do depending on how many
come through this is my bullfrog wow okay the people were right when they said two hours of
bits in one hour of dos bullfrog productions select which one english sound on what is this
is it coordinates a seven day i don't know what this means i'm going to keep it up with the default
to her check yes or no i guess we'll do the standard one new hessen euro date line nc
new subjects required for recruitment multiple subject located subject says mail one point eight
wait 78 things going too fast what did i do i didn't do anything i skipped the intro i didn't
though restart the game um can i not type i don't get to have a company name or i can't type
anything it'll be auto-generated whatever it is well what i can i don't know what the what the
fuck i can't even restart the game click the bar max no is my cpu too fast i did click the bar like
three times all right let's see new england 5.6 million people so this is i've never played
syndicate before this is actually just like risk see do you see what's happening on the screen i
just want to make sure you see it and hear it okay we can get over that now so what's the goal
begin mission what do i have for a mission i would have liked to have seen the cutscene right
intelligence reports have indicated that an arway colonel is stealing resources from your weapons
division and using them to equip his mercenary uses base his base has been set up just outside
one of our cities and the populace have reported disturbances caused by his troops
your squad will be deployed near the entrance to the camp their objective is to eliminate the
colonel enhance enhance again enhance why is enhancing pulling it back does it enhance mean
go in closer and show me what this is it zoomed it out okay info am i spending money surveillance
reports show that the camp is guarded by about five militia armed with both shotguns and pistols
all right special agent equip research automatic research doing great okay um
equip is that what you have you have that on they all have like pistols okay team hastings hill
disket in donkin okay i guess that that's does my 14 members mods legs v1 sure arms v1 get it heart
let's get you a new heart in there eyes enhanced okay brain speeds up brain stem response looks
good 4600 bucks whatever okay equipped that's equipped good to go okay let's do it scanner
yeah getting one of those and get uh what else you got here purse word purse warder tron
med kit get a few of those shotgun get one of these two i got ammo right yeah somebody else
needs something you take shotgun and give some armor this stuff is all too expensive
i have 21 okay let's go assassinate okay who's the one that has all the stuff you
just go in the front door well this is like what's tactical stuff and i do the tactical
there's five guards all right go hold on you no no no you go that way shoot are you gonna shoot
him shoot him shoot your gun why do you have to be so close oh my god good job you did it okay
oh oh shit
good pick it up who has all the stuff you want to assassinate all right get in there
get in there i know you can get it just go on the bridge you guys can get all get over there i know
you can okay and then in the meantime i'll send you up here it was five guards do i have a key
card or something he's in here i think um what is this map where and i don't even know this map is
trying to show me to be honest what direction is this map facing can you go in buildings
so you gotta go up here up here and up here okay get over here the guy with two has all the stuff
you can get in this use vehicle it's a full letter grid a minute this is a mouse where are you going
where are you going where are you going where are you going where's he going going he's driving
to come back on the road can you shoot out the window
shoot him all right get out of the car out how do i get out of car no no no get out of the car
app change um he's in here answer the phone dude is in here oh you're already right here
okay no it's this one why does he have like the sad face i don't this thing right here is definitely
where i need to go go in this house this blip but what is this blip even showing me like what
where do you go where is he okay go in this house somebody in here