Hello, good afternoon, good morning, good evening, good afternoon, how, wherever you are.
Hey, in case I don't see you, good afternoon, good evening, and good night.
He took so long to TP back. Uh, a lot of people are not gonna know what you're talking about by that.
We had an extensive pre-stream chat earlier, talking extensively about the idea of, uh,
of having a teleport power. This is why you don't want to miss the pre-stream chats.
You're gonna wink? Already? Right now? All right, hold on. Redeem that in just a second. I'm not ready.
Hold on, I'm actually not ready to do that. That wasn't scammed. I just did it.
Keep your cam on. I love, love, love, love your haircut. No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Does it really have to be 75,000 Pepehands? Well, yeah, otherwise the whole stream would be
winks and I'm like, I don't want to do that. I might just, oh, god damn it, I bumped you.
I might get rid of winks in like a month or two. I don't know. I might like delete winks
and we might change it to something else. Hello? There's always going to be a 75,000 point tier,
but I might change it to like something. I don't know. We got to freshen it up a little bit.
I'm saving it for the net. We'll just save it then. I don't know. Every few months,
we'll make the 75,000 point thing be something different. That's the idea. Anyways, we're going
to try to finish Out of Wilds today. If you missed it, we just, I started it yesterday. It's
got me interested. It's a really fun, interesting game. And I think it's, I think we got another
like six to seven hours in the game. We should be able to do it. And I was here. I was going to
start in like 45 minutes, but I'm here and I'm ready. I've eaten. I had two, that's right,
two baby food pouches. That's not a lie. Those of you that want advice. Hey, I got any advice to
like, how do you get like streaming advice, right? Hey, I'm starting a channel. What's, what, what,
what do I do? Baby food pouches. I'm serious. It's incredibly fast. It keeps you going. It's
a quick snack you can have in the middle. Like I go downstairs and pee. And during those breaks,
sometimes I'll just grab one of those little baby food like on the go packs and just there it goes.
It's like apple, bananas and strawberries. It's got like a little bit of protein. That's
that's not bad. Here's your streamer advice. Like, man, when I want to do like these five,
six, seven plus hour long broadcasts, I did. There you go. Get baby food packets and eat them
when you take a break. That's not that weird. It's just a, that's a, that's like one of those
secret tips that no streamers will tell you. All streamers eat baby food. They just don't want you
to know. Okay. Let's be clear. You're regressing a little, but we're going to finish Outer Wilds
tonight or try to. And then tomorrow I will probably have my Xbox 360 hard drive. We're
going to do Tony Hawk's underground. And the next day Diablo two hardcore and maybe Assur's
wrath DLC. Maybe it depends on how much I play Diablo two. I also have trying this. I've got this
thing on today. I've got this back and rib and stomach brace on today. Trying to take it. It
feels pretty good. Actually. I actually feel pretty good. It's wrapped around. Show it. I mean,
I don't think I really can. Hold on. Can you see it's like wrapped around my shoulders?
I have to like, I guess it's probably worth addressing right now because people are just
going to think I'm wearing a backpack. You see, dude, why are you wearing a backpack right now?
Uh, because I'm going to school. Okay. There you go. It's on here. It wraps around. It pulls me
back. It, there's one, there's like a thing that goes around my stomach too. He's an, an omega
gamer. Why do you look like a different guy? What? Why do you look like a different guy?
Hold on. What do you mean? I look like a different guy? No, I don't. Why do you look like a different
guy? It's, it's me, right? Is this me? No, it's because like the light and the shadows and stuff.
This, this eye over here is like fully in shadow and it's like fucking up your vision.
Why do you look like a different guy? Hold on. Let me, let, hold on. Let me, let me quell your
fears here. Okay. Here you go. This is what you were used to. Am I, am I a different guy today?
That's better. That's better. Okay. That's better. Now you're, now you're the guy that was here
yesterday. The colors in your room changed. It could be anybody. I got a lot of looks too,
by the way. People that say, oh man, you look different today. I got like, I, I could probably
be like four or five different people. I really could. Anyways, out of wilds. Let's go. What's
the last thing we did? You're, this, this streamer is delusional. What, what, how, how am I delusional?
What did I say? Dude, quick comet jump joke. No. Oh, okay. I was unraveling the mystery.
This is the best fucking game, mate. Best fucking game. I mean, it's pretty good. It's really, I,
I have to hold, I don't, I, I'm interested in the story. Okay. Those of you that didn't see
yesterday and you liked this game and you're like, well, what the hell has he done so far?
This, this is what I've done so far. Uh, I was going to go, where was I going to go first?
A hanging city. No. Found a cave with an anglerfish fossil inside, but the opening is only big enough
for my scout. All right. This part of the escape pods and shit, the comet. No, no, no, no. I want
to do this. The, the Nomai crafted warp cores at the black hole forge. All right. Where's the black
hole forge? Is it in the black hole? We also didn't even find this person. Al says Gabro went to
Giants deep to try to learn more about the Nomai statue. All right. I kind of have to, this is
like a tutorial quest. I kind of have to do that. All right. We're going to go try to find that guy
on Giants deep. You going to work? See you in four hours. See you in four hours. Hopefully you
don't miss the first sun joke of the night. Don't worry. You won't. Okay. Let's go up Giants deep.
I want, wait, is he going to miss the first joke or the first sun joke? Well, he's going to miss
the first room of the evening and that's more arguably way more important. Oh, sun crash joke
incoming. Here it comes. All right. Slow down. Slow down. This, I get my, this is what people
were saying last time. They're like, dude, please don't fly 300 meters a second into planets.
I know, but I just, I know, but look, it's not even moving. Space doesn't make any sense. Look,
I'm not even moving right now. You're going too slow. What, what, okay. What would you guys say
is a safe speed to go towards a planet? 150, 200 meters. Well, what, what is like the, what's like
the, I could get a speeding ticket. What's the, don't go over like sex 65 70s. You're going to
get into speeding ticket. What would it be? 300 250. All right. So this is a safe speed. Yeah.
That's that. This, this seems normal. Let's try to find this guy. Speeding ticket is 800 meters a
second near constellation. Okay. Well that's good to know. That's my skincare routine. Uh, hold on.
I even, okay, we're good. Uh, my skincare routine is in shower, close eyes, push face into running
water from shower head and squint and close my eyes and then rub my face. And then when I get out,
more importantly, I moisturize every day. That's the thing. That's a problem. A lot of people have,
they'll say like, Hey, I got any skincare tips. Yeah. Moisturize your face. Moisturize your face
every day. What is over here? Have I been over here? Yeah, I did this already. All right. I did
that already. Is there another spot to go? What's this one? Uh, did I do this yet? I think I did.
Yep. I climbed up there. That's where the, where else have I not been on this island?
Oops. Gabbro. Hold on. Wait, what is this? In the water? Is he in the water? I think he might be in
the water. Can the ship go in the water? Yeah, I can. All right. The ship can go in the water.
Uh, am I going forward? Am I in the water? Okay. That was weird. I don't think I can move in the
water. All right. Gabbro is definitely down here somewhere. I'm just going to skim the water and
find him. He's playing some kind of flute or something. Wait, there we go. There he is.
Hold on. Did you buy this on the Epic store? Uh, I think that's the only place you can get it.
There he is. All right. Found him. All right. I'm going to do this tutorial quest.
Oh fuck. Slow down. Oh my God. Tilt. Tilt. Tilt. Tilt. Tilt. Tilt. Tilt. Tilt. Tilt. Tilt.
You ever place a land up here? Imagine looking over like up over your shoulder right now.
All right. Is there, there's no landing pad here. Oh wait, I can go this way.
All right. There's a spot I can climb up there. All right. Fuck it. Let's go.
We're safe. Kind of. Here we go. Unidentified signal nearby.
Is he up? There's ghost and shit in here. That's the ghost. Yep. All right. Hold on.
Wait, he was right there. I didn't know that that was somebody in that. I didn't know somebody was
in that. I didn't have my flashlight on and the water was on my face. All right. Let's go.
Nice. It's you. Good to see you made it in here in one piece. The first solo launch is a doozy,
isn't it? They don't freak out or anything, but lately I keep like dying repeatedly. I don't wait.
You're dying too? You're, you're dying too. What about you? Have you died lately? No, it's me too.
We're in a time loop. Time has been behaving unusually lately. Yeah, time loop makes sense.
Cool. You're taking this pretty well. Right back at you. Personally, I like the new experiences
and I've never been in a time loop before. I mean, I don't think I've been in a time loop
for this one. It looks like you and I are the only ones who can tell that time's gone all weird.
I tried radioing Hornfels and asking if they died too, but they thought I was being metaphorical.
He's not as concerned about this as he could be. What if he's going to land and smash his head on
a rock? He's going to land and smash his head on this rock. Or should I tell him to stop playing
the flute? Have you ever watched a cyclone for so long it started to hypnotize you? I'm telling you,
they'll put you in a trance if you stare at them too long. How's space treating you? I found
something. What'd you find? I reached inside the Statue Island. So the Nomai created those head
statues to record memories, huh? Yeah, I could see the Nomai doing that. Not sure for what for,
but it seems like their sort of thing. You think the statues are recording our memories? I'm just
holding my eyes open underwater too. My eye's probably burning. You think the statues are
recording our memories then, because I remember that one on the bleach beach looked at me funny.
That must be my memory friend. I found something. I found what happened to the orbital probe cannon.
That's the cannon breaking apart at the start of each time loop, for real?
Did you figure out why? Too much power. Kind of scary how much that sounds like something
Slate or Feldspar would do. I'm pretty surprised the Nomai built something that actually broke.
Come to think of it, broke might be the wrong word, because it looks like the orbital probe
cannon is still firing successfully at the beginning of each loop. So why just you and I
are having a time loop? All right, well give me a tip. Something you might like. At the start of
every time loop, I keep seeing a bright flash in the sky at the start of every loop. Something must
be happening up there in orbit around the planet. What else? What else? Have you been to the Statue
Island? That's what I've been calling it. Seeing as it's the island where I found the glowing
Nomai statue. Get it? I was on the beach on Statue Island when the whole glowy business happened.
By the way, it's a nice beach for that kind of thing. I give it a solid seven out of ten
on the Gabriel relaxation skill. If you like checking out Statue Island, it's the one with
two islands connected by a natural rock arch. Pretty good, isn't it? Well, mostly connected,
isn't it? The way you'll see. Your ship. Definitely on this planet somewhere. I mean,
unless a cyclone came by, toss it into space. That would be pretty nuts.
Hope it's not a lone one. We kind of already had that info, but at least I found Gabro.
Hold on. I have to adjust my fucking body belt. There we go. That's better. All right, cool.
Geo incoming. All right, so I know. Let me go put this in just to have it done.
Here we are. Get this away. We've completed it. So Gabro goes this way and this goes. All right,
cool. So this has been completed now. We have a full connection to this brain, but this is
almost all done. This whole side is almost done. Unless there's something, nothing's connecting
from here. This is almost completed over here. Okay. What have I not found over here? Sixth
location. Right. I remember I was all fucked up on that. I don't know. Does he have any more info
for me? What do you got? What are you doing out here? Well, what are any of us doing? Really?
No, I'm just kidding. I'm out here exploring the solar system. I'll tell you what. Really
room to think. It's a quiet and peaceful out here. My ADHD is satisfied. He's usually quiet.
Sometimes a cyclone comes by and lifts my island. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. How's space treating you? Where
should I explore? What's up with this planet? I know, right? That was just Yoshi. Oh, you mean
like tell you more about it. I got you. Well, Giants Deep is a massive, mostly water. No surprises
there. There's a strong current a ways beneath the surface. Oh, I got to go into the surface. I
got to go into the... All right. I know where I'm going. I tried everything I could think to get
past that current and neither idea worked. The land masses I've found. All right. Cool. I didn't
skip the lore. It skipped it for me. It deleted me from the conversation. Trying to like take his
spot. Screen. Okay. Oh, what's up with this planet? Let's see it again. Let's try everything. As for
land masses. Yeah. Yeah. You've seen the cyclones. Yeah. They're hard to miss. They'll toss up
everything in path. Islands included. You get picked up trying to land in water. It's not going
to kill you. Okay. Beautiful. The ships don't fucking... I have to get this out of the water.
What did that do for me? But there was... Oh, yep. Okay. The ocean depths. The Nomai on the construction
here saw something sink beneath the underwater current. All right. I'm going for it. Let's see
if I can go down there. There's something under the water. Exit ship to repair. Oh, wait. Hold on.
Is this one of those shards in here? Remember? Like here. Look. There's a quantum fluctuation
down in the middle of the earth here. In earth. You know what I'm talking about. This way.
There it is. Okay. It's inside the center. Can I just try to swim? All right. I'm going. You know,
I'm going for it. I'm just going to go for it. You know, you got to... What the hell is that?
You got to go for it. I'm just going to... I'm going for it. You know what I'm saying?
Why am I stuck? Okay. Do I have a fuel? Look. I'm dead anyways. Okay. Here we go.
Sink to the bottom. Okay. So this is the current. Wait. I was inside of this thing.
I was inside of that. Remember like the electricity? I was inside of this.
I was in there. I was inside of that. Okay. Hold on. How do I get in there? What's up here?
Ship's gone. It's all right. I get a new one every day. Is this in the cyclone?
Dude, this thing is inside the cyclone. Oh, in? I don't think I can get in here.
The current's too strong. I'm trying to go underneath it. I can't like push my body down.
Let's see. Why the shipment? I couldn't... The ship sunk all the way to the bottom of the ocean. So
why the shipment? I can't move the ship down under water. I thought. I tried to do that earlier.
Did it not? I thought it didn't work. Let's go get the ship. Wait. Am I just sinking?
It's so hard to tell even if I'm moving or not. I guess I'm going down. Am I? What? This is going
further away. I'm going to go... I'm going to try to get the ship. Check the tornadoes. Yeah. I mean I
I know. I know. I'm just saying like it's besides that lower left indicator. It's like kind of
hard to know even what direction I'm facing. Where the fuck is this thing going? Can I like
turn this thing off? That's probably what's doing it. The ship is just gone. It just keeps going
further and further away. The ship is now leaving. It's like trying to get away from me. The sun's
about to explode. All I did was talk to the fucking guy on the beach. Which way is the
current going? Where is it going? Hard to see. This way? Forward? Am I moving with the current
right now? I don't know. I guess. I mean I look at the globe. I'm moving. I guess I'm moving.
Well, whatever. I'm going to see if I can go in there with the ship.
The sun's about to explode, so it doesn't matter. Hello? Where the hell? Where did I just go?
Through one of the tornadoes, I guess? And then out of the planet? This is a black hole?
That was weird. Well, I'm just going to try this again. The ship is now leaving.
Well, the only new info I got was that I got to go into the bottom of that planet.
Dude, please stop the supernova joke. I can't, man. It gets laughs every time.
You guys, if something's working, you got to keep doing it. Okay. Let me see if there's
anything else I could do. Black hole forge. I still haven't done the sun station, which was
in... Remember I freaked out yesterday? The high energy lab in the canyon at Ember Twins equator.
I still haven't done that. White hole station. Strange warp dog just... Yeah, yeah, yeah. And then
high energy lab in the canyon at the Ember Twins equator. I feel like I've tried to go find that
five times and every time I get distracted and go, what's this over there? I'm going to try that.
In the canyon. There's a lab in the canyon. I'm going to try that. It's the moon. Let's
make progress now. Progress, progress, progress, progress. You have to remember the rule of the
sixth location. I don't even know what the rule is. I don't think I figured that out yet.
All right. Don't get a speeding ticket. In the canyon. There's a lab in the canyon.
Okay. Where like the cream and the cookie goes, that's the canyon, right? Make sure I like,
I get this figured out. Apparently going too fast again. I'm fine. So it's... Just get out.
Hello? What's going on? Where am I? Why do I only see white spots? I couldn't move. I couldn't
fucking move. Did I get out right when the dust storm landed on top of the ship? Hold on. I got
out of the... I got out of the tank when the sand was touching across the ship.
Got buried in sand like Minecraft. Okay. Again, I went too fast. You know what my biggest problem
with me in this game is? Traveling to each... Like traveling from here to a... Like where's my
teleport? I can only teleport to die and teleport back here. Why can I not die and teleport back
somewhere else? Where's my memory stone? Like I just want to go where I want to go and not fly.
Space. What is this? A space game? Immersion. What is this? Space or something? Let's try this again.
All right. I'm going to coast in, captain. Right into the fucking creamy center. That's where all
the good stuff is. What are you going to wink? That was fake? Fuck. Whatever. I don't see
what could be a lab. You know what I'm saying? Like what's this secret lab? Oh fuck. Watch it.
Watch it. Watch it. Watch out. Watch out for the giant death Minecraft trap.
I'm just gonna land and I'll figure it out. Okay. I got turned around there
because down is up and up is down right now. Let's see if we can get out. Okay. Here we are.
The canyon. Lab. Secret lab in the canyon. I've been in here. It's not there though.
This is... Is it... Did I just find it? Did I just find it? I think I just found it.
This is like a weird staircase. I think I found it. This is it?
Secret lab? No. I've already been here. I think. Right? Haven't I?
Holy fucking pog stairs. I think I've been here already. There's this weird thing here.
It seems like I could teleport from that. What's that? Okay. There's like a little bridge here.
All right. Wait. Wait for the Minecraft reefer to get the fuck out of the way.
What's this? Have I been in here? No, I haven't. Found the secret lab.
This door will need to remain closed for some time. I and I are running an experiment based
on the extraordinary findings from the white hole station. Remy and I will be running this
experiment until one of us, specifically me, can prove the other wrong. So although it's inconvenient,
the lab currently can only be accessed by the path from the sunless city.
The lab can only be accessed by the path from the sunless city. Inviting sand inside would
disrupt our setup and could have enormous consequences. If you realize this, it's an
extremely... But the door must remain closed. An update. The high energy lab is now being
used to design the Ash Twin project. If you're here to help or even just to observe, be sure
to use the sunless city path to the lab. Info. Bingo. High energy lab. Bingo. There's our dark
souls shortcut that we can open eventually. All right. Sunless city. Where's that? I gotta
go look that. I gotta go look that up on my little thing. And I gotta get in there. All right. Sunless
city. I need my ship. I don't know where I am. I've been there once, but I don't know where that is.
Ow. I just broke my teeth. Wait. Ow. I need one of those little block things. Is there one of
those lying around? I don't see one. Slapstick in space. I don't see one lying... I have to carry
one over here? All right. Well, I got that info. I love getting fucking info. This is a space game.
Dumb. Wait, what? Sunless city. Oh shit. This is the sunless city. You live right here. Ghost.
I just broke... What did I just do? What? No, I wanted to read that. What did that sign say?
Read it quick. Well, I can still can. Crash site caves. Uh, I can't go in here. Sunless city. How
do I get in here? How do you clear out a ghost? How do you clear a ghost? I have to go in here.
There's like 10 in here. Okay, that looks like it's going down, not up. How do I go this way?
And like the other side? I've been in the sunless city before. Yeah, but not this direction.
It seems like a way I can get in from here. You were in the sunless city before. Yeah, I just
don't remember where or how I got in there. Uh, I'm gonna die if I don't go to my ship.
It's hard to remember every location I've been to when all you do in this game is
find new locations. It was fine. How do I repair the ship from outside? Do I have to be outside the
ship? Do I have to do anything? Do I have to repair it? Or is it just repair it?
My reactor core is like broken, isn't it? All right, let me go back over there.
Let me just take... Let me browse. I just want to browse this canyon. It's just window shopping.
Is there anything else I didn't do here? Like, what the hell is this? It's like that bridge.
What's happening? Did I get stuck on? All right, hold on. Tilt this way. Was this where I was before?
It's inside. You're gonna navigate inside the caves and shit, right? I think it is in here.
Get out. If I remember, this is one of the ways to get in here. We got... Yeah, yeah, yeah. Okay,
I remember this. So is it up? Is it up or maybe... I don't know. Let me try going up.
Have I been here? This is where... Okay, this is the quantum cactus place. I think I've been here
already. Yeah, yeah, yeah. I've seen this before. There's a rock in the cave here. Like, bed cave.
Yeah, I've seen this already. This is like, please, if you can help. My... Somebody's missing. Yep.
All right. Hi. Can I go down here? I mean, that's like a Mortal Kombat stage. I don't... No,
that's death. I can't go down there. But this bridge, it's back there. Let me just check if
nothing is over there. No, no, no. I'm gonna go... I'm gonna go deeper into the cave.
I might be out of time, though. Sand is coming. Sand is arising. All right. Okay, bring it back.
Come on, quantum. It wasn't this one. It was one more. In. Oh, one more. I gotta find this entrance
from here. How much boxes do I have? Yeah, friends find any sign. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Okay, let's go.
So, now I'm in the cave system. It's just a question of where the hell do I get through
the Sunless City? What is this? No. Damn it. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. The nougat.
All right. I missed. Okay, good. Let's go up. Looking for... Before the music starts to play
and I run out of oxygen, I have to find this entrance to the Sunless City. It's not here.
I don't think it's here. Damn it. I'm reading chat. Let me try this one more time.
I'm in the rock. Oh, crack. Crack. Crack. Dude, I'm just browsing around Twitch and I'm
looking for a guy that's on crack every day. Am I in the right place? Yep. Yeah, I've already
been in here. This rock only goes to three places. We've already done this part. Unless it's like I
can't get out of here, right? Is this... I was here already. This is the place with the text,
the original one. One, two, three, one. Wait. How curious. This rock took me to a new location.
I wonder why this happened. Curious but also alarming. This new cave appears to lack an
entrance or exit. Wait, no. I was already here. I already did this. How many locations are there
actually? Okay, come on. Quantum. Come on. Quantum. Quantum. Quantum. Quantum. Quick. Quantum. Quick.
Quantum. Quick. Quantum. Quick. Quantum. I'm going out on my own terms. I'm just going to open one
eye and just wait and look straight in the air. This is just an old 80s movie. I can see the
laser beam coming. Is it going to kill me? Right in the eye. Where do I die from first? Oxygen or
crushed head? What do I do? Tyler wants to interview you. What do you mean interview?
All right, let's go. What do you want to know? What do you want to know? What do you got?
It all started when I was eight. I saw a movie for the first time and I was like,
that's what I want to do. That's what I'm thinking of. It was Ghostbusters 1.
That's the Valve, the Valve News Network. Oh, shit. Oh, I don't know why for a second I thought you
talked about like somebody in chat named Tyler wanted to interview me right now. Like, hey,
I want to interview you. Okay. Yeah, when you want to. Yeah, let's do it. That sounds fun.
What do you want to interview me about? Please have it be what my favorite fucking restaurant
in Vegas is. Yeah, I'll do that. Sounds fun. Just really important though. I only do 22
minute interviews. I'm a very busy man. Ego fucking maniac. No, I do whatever. Hit me up on a.
All right, you know what? Here, hit up one of the mods so I can get your like contact info
through like discord and we'll talk. No, no shitty jokes aside. Sounds like fun. I still
can't fucking do this. All right. This is more to explore in the ash twin towers.
All right, I'm gonna. But I already know that this is somewhere
half from the sunless city. I need to get to the sunless city. I don't know how to get to the sunless
city. Sun station. No, I'm not going for sun station again. That's an embarrassment.
You will be embarrassed for me. You know, people go like, oh, what's that thing when you're like
embarrassed for somebody else? It's not you doing it. That's what you're going to have.
I don't want to do that. What's it called? Like shot? What's it called? No, no, no. It's called
something. It actually has like, it has like a scientific name. Schadenfreude. Schadenfreude.
Yes, but that's not it. That's laughing at somebody else's expense. No, that's wrong. It has,
it has a name. It's Franscham. Franscham. Yeah, there you go. Somebody got it. It's like, it's
like Franscham, right? Franscham. Franscham. How do I say? No, that's, that's actually correct.
You actually have that correct. It's like Franscham. Yes. People are spelling it. However
you say it. That's, that's actually what it's called. I didn't make that up. I didn't make that
up. That's the term. I knew there was a term for it. I don't know how to pronounce it. It's German.
Yeah. I think I said it kind of close. Made it up. I'm going a thousand miles per hour.
This happens when I'm arguing about something and I'm holding the left stick up.
It's not Imperial. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. It's all I know. Okay. You can make fun of me all
you want, but it's, it's what I know. I'm going to drive into the sun. First sun joke of the night.
Here it comes. Everyone's been waiting for it. Here it is. The first laugh out loud. He went
into the sun joke to explore the tower on the ashtray. First dark wood trap. Yeah. Coming up.
Okay. There's more to explore on this like right here, for instance,
but in hot 25 meters per second, five meters per second landing activated. Perfect landing.
Get out, get out. You stupid. All right. What do we got? We have this big power. I was going
to say 5g, but it's very easy joke to make and people would probably not think it was funny. So
somebody else is going to say it in the chat. I know they are. Get on top of it. Well, uh, okay.
Oh, quantum reading. Wait, this church cave shard, distress beacon. Wait, escape pod two.
I already did that. Okay. Whatever. Can I get anywhere else here looking for, I need to explore
this tower again while this time. Watch out. This is how it's made, how they make a Snickers bar.
Yep. Don't minus two that one. That was a solid reference to like 20 minutes ago. How,
I can't believe I'm getting minused here. I can't fucking believe it.
I got a tough, tough crowd tonight. I need to, I need a reader reader. I need one of those wall
readers. There's a wall reader. I need a wall reader. Wait, is there a reader in here?
I think this door is sealed up. It is. I gotta get here another way. What about the bottom here?
All right, here we go. I have a reader here. Have I read this one? Sometimes,
past, since I checked in with you, Pi, how are you an idea of progressing at the sun station?
So, my plan will either fail explosively or succeed explosively.
Why, you know, I don't find that funny. Hypothesis time spent away from the station
would be beneficial to you both. I'm immensely interested in testing your hypothesis. Yeah,
that at least we can agree on. I'm curious. Remy thinks I'm Remy thinks I'm a gas.
I don't recall requesting that you monitor this conversation.
Why is this so loud? Why is the sand so loud in this room in particular? I don't see what state
of matter you're you are has to do with this. And I don't recall supporting the sun station's
construction. But here we are. I did have some new info there. All right, with my take this out.
See what this one says. All right, what's this? Friends visiting from the hanging city. We are
planning the ash twin project at the high energy lab on Ember twins equator. Yes.
I became lost on Ember twin. My gratitude that Remy found me but the high energy lab is the
building with the large solar panels. I'm surprised I didn't see it. I already went in it though.
Imagine our otherwise immensely clever Konoi would lose his own head if it weren't for
automatically impossible. I already went into the higher energy lab didn't I? Two large solar panels.
Wait a minute. Are these quantum cactuses? All right, is this like a flappy bird experiment here?
Can I get in here? Can I float in there? Oh, fuck it is. It actually is. It actually is.
No, no, no. Patch it. Patch it. Patch it. Come on. No. I thought you guys are bullshitting me.
Oh, come on. I can't believe that you actually can do that. Wow. All right. I didn't I didn't
know it was that far. Shit. Okay. What is up there? Now I need to know what's up there.
Now I need to know what's up there. Damn it. I can't believe I didn't get up there.
Oh, that's so sad. What's inside that? I don't know. That's what I need to know. I'm going back.
Shit. Why did Omega Low get removed? Did it? What do you mean Omega Low? Oh, you're doing the thing
where everyone now has to write it because that's so stupid. Everyone's gonna write it now. Wait,
why did Omega Low get removed? And everyone's like, wait, did it? Let me check.
I gotta check. That's the oldest trick in the book, too. Where am I going? Just use autopilot.
It's the safest way as long as there's no sun. Autopilot's going a little fast.
I'm not doing this. Let me get back. Let's go. Come on. Oh, what the fuck?
Good branding. Did I miss anything else on this? What? Oh, shit. Is there nothing else on this
planet that I can't see? Sweat check? Not at all, actually. Zero. I'm good to go. I went,
remember I did this and I went, oh. And then I went this way. Something over here. What is this?
Is this like buried? This is probably a ship or something. It's coming out. Oh, the more the sand
drops, the surface goes down right. Okay, that's interesting. I didn't know that was happening.
It took him 10 hours to notice that. That's like the second time I've been on this planet.
Yeah, it took me 10 hours to notice. I've been here twice. I'm almost out of fuel.
Uh, give me, give me, I'm give, watch out, don't get in there. Now it's on the other planet. Fuck,
come on, man. Come back to me. Why does it happen to me all the time? Oh, well. Just don't use that
much fuel. Jump over to it. No. There ain't shit on this whole planet. Look at all the ground I've
covered on the map. There's nothing even here. It's because, it's because I have to wait, so I
can't, I should, I shouldn't, I should never come here immediately. Because the sand is too high.
I can't do anything. Let's just ski around the planet. But not too far. Okay, here we go.
Going over here. Okay, here we are again. Back at the North Pole. All right, let's go this way.
Save the fuel. Well, I mean, this, this whole run is just a wash anyways. Not if you're good.
All right, here we go. So right in the equator is where this is.
Is this where the cactus trap is? What is this? Oh, this shit's getting revealed now too. Wait,
can I, can I go in this window? I can. All right, so is there anything up here that I need to
look at? What's up here? Have I been up here? No, I've been here, yeah. This is where that is.
Fuel's almost gone. All right, so how long have I been walking around on this planet?
So don't ever come here unless it's been at least like five to ten minutes.
All right, here's the cactus room. No fuel for the cactus room. Well, where is this on the map?
I know that there's no fuel here. Somebody left it in the corner. Oh, we're dead. So it might as
well just end it. All right, that's right in the equator. I'm going to land the ship there after
I do something else in like 10 minutes because that's how long it takes for that building to
show. I'm going to go back to what I was doing before. Back into the canyon. Try to find this
sunless city. Sunless city. Yes, the Ashtron project was planned at the high energy lab,
a building with large solar panels on Emperor Twin's equator. Yes,
it can only be accessed by a path from the sunless city. Do a third cactus in a row. Let's go. No,
I'm not going to do that. I've been to the city once already. I just don't remember. It was just
in game time. I just don't remember. I had there was that sign that I saw to
mark it on the map. Rhinoceros beetle brain. That's a very, that's incredibly specific animal.
Why a rhinoceros beetle? That's very specific. Let's go. So I'm looking for,
what am I looking for again? Not there. Up here, right? Is that staircase?
That's there. No, please put me back in. Put me back in quick. Put me back in quick. Put me back
in quick. Put me back in. Oh my God. No. Why couldn't I go back in? Oh my fuck. I'm so mad
right now. You have no idea. You have no idea. I'm so fucking mad. Why couldn't I come back? Why
wouldn't it put me back in? Why wouldn't it put me back in? Fuck. I'm so mad. I can't believe it.
No suit. No suit. One. Cactus two. Sun zero. We're on a roll tonight. We're on a roll,
ladies and gentlemen. A roll, I tell you. God damn it. What a pain in the ass.
Put the suit on. Why can't I just permanently be in the suit? And I tried, I instantly fucking knew
and I tried. Instantly. Instantly. Within an instant to get back in. It didn't work.
I can't, apparently you have to have the suit on to get beamed up. God. Sun zero. Oh, I'm so mad.
All right. Settle down. Settle down. I'm just gonna go back to that thing. I'm so angry.
Like, I'm not even, I'm not comedy angry right now. I'm like, pissed off angry. You know, there's
like comedy angry and there's like fucking, I'm like mad. I think I crossed the comedy
anger threshold right now. Okay. Put your stupid suit on. I love how I could, I have to put the
suit on, but I can't take the suit off. Like in space. Just, why can't I just rip the helmet off?
I got it on. So this is, this is the lab, right? Can I get anywhere from here? I don't know. Did
I fully explore this place? Eight pod two. Yeah. Let's get pod three. We already looked at this.
We did already see this. Just making sure I don't miss anything. We've already seen this. Okay.
Ah, enormous cavern. Yup. Long shelter. Wait, hold on. Shelter site. Where's the big scary thing?
I have to investigate that. It was this way. No, this is the oxygen place. Wait, do I have
to go through this again? Where's the monster? Okay. It's this one, right? Yeah. Right. Okay.
This can be investigated more. I can drop down from somewhere into here. All right. Let's go.
Found a shortcut hole. I already did. Did I find the shortcut hole already? Wait, very early on.
I did. What? You found a shortcut yesterday out here. Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no. No. Yeah. Out
here. You are. No, you're right. I did out. Yeah. I think I know what that is. I think it's out
around here, isn't it? It's somewhere like out here. Didn't I, I poked my head out or something.
It's like, it was like digging up in Minecraft. Where was it? I distinctly remember that happening
for some reason. I don't remember where it was though. Oh, what the hell was that? I don't
remember. I just really don't. There's so much information in this game. I have no idea where
that is. Let me refuel. Ugh. I do remember though, like poking my head out somewhere
or being like, oh, here I am. I think it's not like right around here or something, right?
I don't, I have no idea. Not a single clue. It's like a shortcut. I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know. Don't look at the VOD. Okay. It's right there.
But where do I go from? I'm going to pull my fucking. I can't wait. This is, didn't I open this?
This is not it. That's not it. I didn't open that. No. Damn it. Let me try going this way.
Be down here. What's that? Where's the sand? No. Wait. Big bits came in. Oh shit. They did.
Daddy Umbra gave 10,000 bits. Thanks for the a hundred dollars. And is this like a,
what is it? E-mode? What is this E-mode? PJ salt. I thought that was a toilet.
Uh, thanks for the 10,000 bits, dude. Uh, they say my socks were hard to put on today. Thanks a lot,
Jeremy. Did you just get out of the shower and then try to put your socks on? What a mistake that
was. That was the biggest mistake. You gotta be more careful. But thanks for the a hundred dollars.
That's a shitload of money. Thanks for the fucking massive, massive money drop.
Putting on socks while your feet are wet is impossible. And then we just had five community
subs too from Super Bruce. Thank you, Super Bruce. I've no idea. Tell me where to go. I don't care.
Like literally tell me where to go. I'm never going to find this. You know I won't.
I will never find this. He doesn't care. I mean, I'm not, I'm not going to find,
I'm not going to remember where this is. You got like 10 planets, 60 locations on each planet.
That's 600 locations. And then you got like on each 600 locations, you got 20 dialogue options.
We're talking about like 12,000 places in my brain. I don't know where they are.
Okay. Go to the gravity cannon. Is that even on this planet? Is the gravity cannon even on this
planet? Let me go with my ship. Let me go to the ship. Let me go to the ship. You're already out
of time. So it's the gravity cannon. Where's that fucking gravity cannon? That's the thing.
That's like the broken thing. Yeah. I think I know what it looks like. I just don't know where it is.
Okay. There it is. So this, this, this, the Dark Souls shortcut was here.
The shortcut was here. I never would have found this. No way. Not in a thousand years.
I never would have remembered it. You just saved like at least an hour or two of this stream.
Thank you guys. Another hundred dollars from Daddy Umbra. 10,000 more bits.
$200 total down in bits from Daddy Umbra. Jerma, make a joke or I'll send more.
What? Make a joke or I'll send more. Why don't I just be quiet? You just told
me if I don't say anything that's worth it, then you'll have more money.
Well, make it so you don't spend any more money. I don't even have a joke right now.
I don't have anything to say. I'm desperately trying to find this city.
What's this? This is the, okay, I remember this is the quantum cactus.
No quantum cactus here. Wait, can I close this? Damn it. Is it further down? Is it all the way down?
No, this dude is crazy. Above the door. Like, you mean up there? Like not even going in the cannon?
It's above the door to like up here. I never would have found this. Never. Never would have found it.
Never would have found it. All right, remember where this is. How do I mark this? Found it last
stream. Yeah, and that's fine. But I've also found a lot of other things last stream. Yeah,
I need like a team of 10 people to be all have a different planet in their brain. I got to hire
people to remember what happened on each planet. You're the Brittle Hollow Guy. Oh, wait, hold on.
This is important. There's no ghost over there. Ghost right there though. Okay, I'm going to go
that way. What? All right, now let's go there. Okay, made it. Yeah, this fills with sand.
This is already filling with sand. Just remember what that was. Big cannon right above the door.
Yeah, okay, I can come here later. I'm gonna come here immediately, go right to the cannon,
go right in. You got to get here insanely fast. Yeah, I will. Now I remember where this is.
It's not gonna take me 100 years to get here. Just I'm gonna break my fucking neck on the ceiling.
The sand and the neck breaking is the loudest sounds in the whole game. Daddy Umbra again,
you're at $250 worth of bits. 25,000 bits. Derma, do you love us? I love the end. I love this whole
community. I think everybody's great. Well, I love each individual, every single individual one of
you. Now that I cannot say. I don't know you individually. I know you collectively as a group.
I don't know. It could be a serial killer watching right now. You know, I can't make that kind of
statement. All right, let's do it. I got the suit on. I know where I'm going. One of you could be
embezzling millions of dollars into like offshore bank accounts or something. Like I can't say that
through donations. All right, let's get in there quick. But no, I love this community.
I love this place. I love this space here. I think it's a lot of fun. I think it's great.
All right. Where's that cannon? Where's that cannon? Where's the cannon? Cannon, cannon,
cannon, cannon, cannon, cannon, cannon, cannon, cannon, cannon, cannon, where's that cannon?
What's that? I've ever seen that. No, focus. Here we go. Nice. Nice, dude. Nice. Okay, let's go.
Gee, I'm so fucking nervous right now. God. Shake, shake around a little bit.
Move. Ah, fuck. Okay. No, fuck. I'm okay. Go down here. Ah, okay. Slow down. All right,
we got we have some info anglerfish overlook district stepping stone district high energy
lab trailhead eye shrine district knowledge should we build the sun station to power the astron
project are there other ways to generate this level of power theoretically yes practically
no i can't imagine discovering them in our lifetimes i understand this proposal is unsettling
but the sun station must be built we have to complete the project i almost can't comprehend
this is being suggested seriously the purpose of the sun station goes against every standard
we hold ourselves to and everything we believe in as a species i know what happens in the game
i figured out the story unsurprisingly i disagree we're pushing a possible new technology further
than ever before they tap into the sun with the sun station and they do this fucking weird they're
trying to make a new energy source or they're trying to go forward in time or backwards in
time and they use the power from the sun which makes the sun supernova putting into a time
that's the sun explodes because they tapped into it i get it if we fail and probably the
we would question destroy ourselves in our life here potential annihilation of an entire star
system is too severe we shouldn't build the sun station but if you were going to build one where
would it be your failure is a poor reason not to try i believe if we're cautious the sun station
will work look i'm deeply honored i comprehend your position if we aren't all but certain
it will not cause destruction once we built it then i won't support the station's use
all right now what these are oh wait what's down here
high energy lab yeah all right hold on all right sand's coming sand's coming sand's coming let's
go i can teleport okay i'm gonna come back here every day what else is in here i follow the trail
i guess i guess we're gonna follow this um okay can't do that um can i was i too did i take too
long is there a place i can jump through oh shit hold on wait wait wait wait wait wait wait i might
die is gonna crush my head this is gonna crush my head can i actually do this i'm gonna try all right
if it's a failure don't matter i'm gonna teleport back anyways come on hurry up does this actually
go over the lip what ceiling is far away okay now i'm gonna go one two three go really really
really keep going what what no what hold on wait go this way oh no go go go quick oh
oh i thought i did it where the hell am i oh my goodness where am i going uh keep following this
trail oh wait what's over here don't go in it yet three minutes till oxygen explodes what but
this stuff over here is there anything over here all right not worth it i'm going up huh what where
am i going where am i going um oh oh go go go why into that oh all right i did it i think i did it
or something oh shit i did it okay i made it what do i do what's this thing what's that do
what are these are these special these special buttons warp core warp core warp core how many
different warp cores are there is there a secret this gotta be like a hold on this is probably
gonna be like i open a door or something come on like this guy i've got i have to be able to open
a door break this glass can i shatter the glass read record show nomai arriving at the warp
receiver umbrella hollow very slightly poor departing on the white house station i mean
i are devising an experiment to test if this is real phenomena or simply machine error initial
things first our experiment setup will first pair a small black hole core with a small white
hole core to mimic the setup on the white hole station clown brain setup will first pair a small
black hole with a small white hole it is possible for an object to exit a white hole before entering
the corresponding black hole in theory what we want to try to reproduce is a negative amount
of time elapsing between something entering the black hole and exiting the white hole at its
destination what the fuck are you talking about man an update our experiment here reproduced the
anomaly in arrival and departure times but pi is unconvinced but it's more than an equipment error
i hope to strengthen the effect to render it visible to the unaided eyes for that end we
decided to try adding more energy i imagine the sunless city's energy supply should prove sufficient
all available energy has been rerouted from the way to have room to our experiment rami and i are
about to run a new test hypothesis confirmed hypothesis confirmed i saw it i saw it hypothesis
confirmed is this a germa stream we just said the same thing four times in a row this is beyond
extraordinary this changes everything what a beautiful day for the intersection of abstract
theory and practical application of note rami yarrow requests that we let him know before we
reroute energy to the experiment hypothesis train i'd hate to leave him in the dark new info okay
now the question is oh there's a press this button what did i just do we're at full power
oh man there's more the southern observatory is asking if creating a 22 minute interval is
possible that is to have something arrive 22 minutes before it is actually sent through the
warp that's just enough time for germa to do an interview we've learned the negative interval
of time between departure and arrival can be increased by adding more energy to the warp core
problematically the energy required to extend the interval increases at an exponential rate
creating a 22 minute long interval is possible but we can't are currently unable to generate
the necessary energy the energy is currently unavailable you say you're a gas pie i mean i
believe it would be necessary to invent a new method of producing energy a thrilling but enormous
undertaking we would also require advanced warp technology able to handle such energy
anyway we're getting we're getting to you know you watch the first six episodes of the anime
and you go wow this is actually pretty interesting shit i this is cool and then you're at like the
middle 10 episodes of the anime and it just kind of goes off the rails in your head and they add a
bunch of shit and i don't like season two turns it upside down oh wait hold on i said the word anime
i forgot sorry about that my pun was unintended ramiya so i believe it's you who's uh error form
all right don't ever say the word anime someone will be very angry with you
it's like it's like just an automatic reaction you could be eating a bowl of macaroni and cheese
and if you hear the word anime some of you guys it's like how dare you the ashtron project will
be one of our biggest undertakings metaphorically and physically to build it we need a way to travel
quickly between ash twin and each location that holds crucial project materials you just got
punched in the stomach uh i can't laugh that hard because it's hurting me but that's funny
give that guy a fucking goal i wish i could give gold stars twitch has the vip system but that's
like kind of too much i just i want like a temporary a temporary like that i can put on someone
that only lasts like 30 minutes because if you vip somebody's like oh that's a very important
person for the stream you don't like remove the vip i want a system where i can like place a
dunce cap on them raya and be like you just you said i like what you said it's like a 10 minute
thing dunce cap and then their text is kind of is lit up for like five minutes that would be kind
of fun that's like what channel points is but without me giving it to you the time is frozen
right yeah the ashtron project will be one of our biggest undertakings yeah we need to travel
quickly between ash twin and each location that holds crucial project materials this is the sixth
location what if we used warp towers like the one we have on the white hole station to connect each
planet directly to ash twin folk root and i can begin work on this immediately in the black hole
forge where is it each tower on ash twin will warp to a different planet each tower on ash twin will
warp to a different planet we can design each tower to visually reflect its warp destination
okay the giant's deep tower for instance could resemble a cyclone and we could add trees to the
timber hearth tower yeah so it's like a sham it's their towers they're not even they're not planets
they're towers you don't get you don't travel to the fucking i mean they add they added trees in it
to make you think that wait did i do this one yet oh wait wait wait what is this six here one two
three four five hell all right i just opened it this better be open from now on this door will need
to remain closed for some time behind you lab is now being used to design the twa or project
your area you use the sound of the city we got it yeah we got it now what am i supposed to do in
here wait where is this on the map so i don't i can actually remember where the hell this is
it's okay it's where the big tower is the big um like paper mache tower kind of up uh
uh right above the equator and the northern side okay let's go down here so uh what we got
what can i do turn this on okay black hole white hole black hole white hole oh black hole white
hole okay close it up wait what's that what we're looking at okay that's what all right that was
weird what about uh two black holes about white hole black hole what does it do okay so what about
black hole and nothing black hole nothing is there what am i supposed to do so if you go into a
black hole you come out of the white hole what do two white holes do anything okay do i is this do
i need to do anything about this yeah okay so you go in you come out right okay is there anything
i'm supposed to do in here put it back in put it back in put it back in put it back in
you destroyed the fabric of spacetime this is a joe credit sequence right you got the kazoo ending
no i don't want the kazoo ending i want the real one the one that people talk about that's
i don't want the kazoo ending no i can load it right i can load the save and do it
what the fuck did that just say load previous save thank god did i learn all that info what's
what's the previous i didn't learn anything no i did okay i saved it high energy lab and then ash
wind tower designs ash twin tower designs okay so that's now that connects to here
statue island connects to here high energy lab connects to here black hole forge don't know where
it is we've almost what is this probe tracking module what the fuck looks like the modules
underwater oh the thing that shoots out of that ship in the very beginning is the tracking module
which lands on giants deep which is what's in the center of giants deep interesting
what else have i not done here southern observatory i signal locator on brittle hollow
hole there is a path beneath the surface that leads to the observatory the trailhead starts
at brittle hollow's equator bribeck says you can't get into the observatory from the surface
but there's probably a path to it beneath the crust somewhere there's a door to the
observatory on the surface but it's broken brittle hollow path in the equator let's go boys and girls
let's go i can't believe i got the kazoo ending brittle hollow equator brittle hollow into the
equator let's go bye please can we get hyped i turned off hype trains that don't exist anymore
on this channel dude you ready to get scammed i can't even turn it on i think this i think
the broadcast has to be off before i can turn it on all right we need to get to the equator
there's a path leading to this observatory going a little too fast all right let's land
walk out there i only don't it because i want to see hype trains i want to refund
look we could just pretend that it's on right now okay so there's a path on this equator okay
ready train stop i'm not seeing i'm not seeing any hype you know we're not even at level zero
all right well two people just got banned so uh that's like that's like two dollars
all right two people got banned so that's all right hype it up freeze detected is this it
now this is the uh no this is it this is it the trees are moving the trees are moving the tree
everything's moving yep yep yep yep yep yep yep yep yep yep need to go to the equator gotta go
to the equator go to the equator equator equator when you find a path on the equator
here wait a minute can i get in from here the door is broken right is the door even down here
all right hold on this goes this i remember this part confused me this was very confusing to me
up let's try and see what's up here dude what do you give me a break i might be going this fast
there's uh what's his name over there bribeck for sure wait he welcomed in this place above
you stands the tower quantum knowledge if you are making your first pilgrimage to the quantum
moon ascend these stairs and obtain the last of the knowledge you need for your journey
really the final clue the final hint no no that didn't do shit i'm trying to willy wonka my way
over there hold on what does this say crossroads all right turn it on all right look at this look
at this sonic the hedgehog level three map give me a break i'm not gonna how am i gonna figure this
out i'm just whatever i'm just gonna go in hang on left bring it right bring it we're going left
oh we're oh oh what happened hello move i just got hit in the head by a rock
oh no what did i get hit in the head what the fuck is that what is that grab it what
i'm so confused what is that why is this what's this floating here for
oh no this is okay this is the thing this is the thing yeah this is this place oh shit
yeah yeah turn it on how do i turn this thing on dude stop doing quantum crack how do i turn
this on you like press a and it you put you where is it something i have to do
yep yep you stand on the war platform on the floor and wait until the tower aligns with its
corresponding astro body brittle hollow look up while the station's rotating you see the
alignment happens when the astro body's directly ahead yeah didn't i oh right i forgot i need to
do this like turn the damn thing on let's go all right where's my ship quantum crack quantum crack
oh crack that may or may not exist oh i felt that one okay let's go try this shit again
um don't do that please game all right where is that special place to go down
sounds gonna explode yeah i know it is i learned some more stuff though didn't i
this way can i wait can i that's too dangerous what is this have i been over this way before
yep this is that rock that disappearing rock i feel like i don't want to go do all this because
i'm gonna run out of time i'm just gonna run out of time this has to be so dark whatever let's go
pick something and stick with it i already i did i picked it i'm trying to figure out how to get
to this place in brittle hollow all right give me this thing check this out this doesn't want
move now this thing's not quantum i thought it was i can't take a photo of it because i'm observing
it when it's on the photo oh whatever this is where i was last time i don't know where the hell
am i even trying to get to down there all right no falling rock right not this time good all right
no gigantic falling crater good i have a minute but where am i going down there and then to the
left back where power no this is just wrapped around and i kind of yeah no i'm above the black
hole there he is all right switch this up a little bit where am i trying to get to um to the left
right now what uh what is what is this even for i have to be all right wait hey whoa it's falling
all the way in i go with it all right well then his higher side is gone now do i have to be flying
with that thing when what about down there what is that uh this shit's upside down i don't know
i really don't know can i flip this thing somehow and turn it upside down i gotta turn this whole
thing upside down how do i turn this upside down i'm gonna turn this upside down does this exist
over here too let me observe all right hold on a second hold on a second that thing's moving
no i'm moving now it's me that's moving it's me that's moving what hold on this whole thing
came apart can i stand on this okay wait now wait what's this doing here what is this thing doing
here hold on wait wait wait hold on wait wait wait wait wait turn off the light turn lights off turn
lights off turn lights off wait wait what does it say beneath your feet lies the tower of knowledge
can i go into this wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait is this stop stop stop stop stop stop stop stop stop stop stop stop stop slow down um
okay this is wait a minute that's the tower right there this is the tower of knowledge i was when i
already up there wait i this is the tower of knowledge this is the tower hold on can i go and
how much fuel do i have holy shit you gotta be fucking kidding me get up there it is it's the it's
the this is the actual tower it's the thing all right i get it i get it i get it no i'm so bad at
controlling flying around how high do i have to go all the way what's that over there no no no no go
all the way to the top pre-detected the fucking sun's gonna blow up let's just do quick read
something read welcome so your arrival here means you've completed your profession as even you're
ready to try quantum moon on your pilgrimage quantum moon will carry you just as it carried
me and many of my clan before me in the moon's sixth and most secret location and where is it
you'll be aided in your pilgrimage by the shrine our clan built in the quantum moon but remember
this is the final route to explore the sixth location the shrine must be on the moon's north
pole be curious on your journey what about this one what do i do with this the north pole has to
be on the north pole i already read this is there another one okay so wait what's this one i didn't
read one piece of text just one piece of text one piece of text let's say if you're here then
you mean that you made it too close oh shit all right the sixth location is you found the secret
of the sixth location the north pole of the quantum moon helps if you use at least two
percent of your brain this is a game about not knowing a single fucking thing about anything
just use your brain it's a mystery where you wake up every 20 minutes we've already determined
there's like 1200 different locations if that guy had dunce cap i really want how do i get twitch to
like make a dunce cap and that's not a bad thing that's a good thing that's that's like a term of
like that's for us that's we like that here power of quantum knowledge the sixth location
okay the quantum moon sometimes disappears possibly to an unknown sixth location many
know my went on a pilgrimage during which the quantum mood carried them to its sixth and most
secret location to explore the sixth location the shrine on the moon must be on the moon's north
pole let's go let's get to the moon hey it had a job interview and i got the job nice
there's good work oh yeah you do that job as best as you can make that fucking money all right
quantum flow where's the quantum what do you call that oh it disappeared make those bits make those
bits here was the singing moon come on so am i am i about to get to the here's the secret of the game
well that'd be interesting it is ready there literally right there dude come on it says i'm
going to the secret location i'm going very fast but it's very far away so we just got to
get this thing on the moon on the north pole so i have to make it disappear and reappear till
it's on the north pole and then open up the fucking elevator he doesn't understand velocity no i just
want to get there i just want to go to this location as fast as possible okay moon i'm ready
onto moon secret got to take a damn photo autopilot i can't autopilot to a thing that
doesn't exist okay here we are i first i i killed that guy again keep killing this guy all right
north pole let's get it on the north pole i'm floating i'm floating so much all right is it
on the north pole where is this thing it's okay it's on the south pole north pole there it is
okay it is now on the north is that the north pole watch this shit close that fucking door north
pole okay now i'm gonna take a picture of this all right close it okay here we go
sixth location ah what's going on secret sixth location here it is oh fuck it's gone um uh what's
even here uh that looks like a that's a suction cup is this like it is a suction cup over here
there's a person why am i getting um castle griffin steed vibes right now okay hello
soleno who are you we don't i can't do that i don't know what that means pick up identity stone
pick up you stone pick up eye of the universe stone pick up quantum moon stone pick up me stone
pick up explain stone how many powers do i get all right i want uh explain stone
insert explain stone oh explain uh explain me i imagine your purpose here is the same as mine
to learn about and to find the eye of the universe i'm unsure how you arrived here however perhaps
you came from another star system as my clan originally did that wasn't very good explanation
uh do do i have like three wishes or something how long do i get to do this for
explain uh explain the eye of the universe please there is fundamental uncertainty throughout the
universe normally this uncertainty is only observable on a very small scale as one approaches
the eye however that uncertainty grows enormously the quantum moon probably exhibits macroscopic
quantum behavior because of its proximity to the eye shards that broke off from the quantum moon
have a similar effect as i imagine you've seen elsewhere in this star system yeah i've seen them
conscious observation forces a quantum object to collapse to a single possibility
but what would happen if a conscious observer somehow entered the eye itself over time this
has become my clan's greatest question all right uh more more more stuff explain um explain you
explain you i need nine i need to explain you i am on my first pilgrimage to the quantum moon
all know my and my clan make this journey when we come of age even though the eye cannot be reached
from here the quantum moon remains special to us as it carries us nearer to the eye than any other
place we know i've journeyed here to be close to the eye while the eye is obscured from our site
we can see the quantum moon's reflection of the eye in the sky above us all right and explain
uh explain the quantum moon too let's get all info we can he keeps taking a selfie of us
all right have you encountered a quantum shard on another planet the shard looks the same as
the quantum moon surface does now while at the eye from this we can reasonably infer the quantum
moon's natural status as we see it now and that the eye is its primary location even the quantum
moon is the eye's moon it's likely that any characteristics the moon exhibits are also
exhibited by the eye itself quantum moon and its shards for instance are quantum
thus the eye is likely also quantum quantum eyes quantum moon's eyes the eye of the quantum moon
quantum existence in fact this moon is probably quantum because its proximity to the eye made it
quantum the same way the areas surrounding quantum shards that landed on other planets
eventually became quantum so many quantum so the eye is making this quantum okay quantum within a
quantum got it shards that land on other planets eventually became quantum too okay identify we
have explained everything so now let's identify me who the hell am i i've never met one of your
kind before it's an honor to speak with you i particularly admire your four eyes okay there
are many questions i would ask if i could comprehend your language you have my gratitude for understanding
mine chip log update i have four eyes but i don't know uh on a moon this is the quantum moon
where we both are standing despite also orbiting other celestial bodies the quantum moon is the eye
of the universe's moon all right identify identify identify you like what's your name oh you already
told me i am solenum anomai my clan arrived in this star system before my birth and we now call
it home what about identify the eye of the universe he's gonna be like i don't know what that is
because well that's what i'm looking for we are orbiting the eye of the universe now although we
cannot see it only the quantum moon's reflection of it the eye is older than the universe itself
and my clan believes it dwells in an extremely distant orbit around this star system wait i can
watch you and eye of universe
many of my clan have believed the eye called to us for a particular purpose i gotta keep track of
these when i was a child i used to believe the eye was maleficent they have lured my clan to the
star system only to vanish from them so completely but i don't fear the eye anymore in fact it became
my fondest hope to see the eye itself someday but i fear this may be beyond my reach you may
think i'm strange but i have a hypothesis that i may not be entirely alive perhaps my journey has
reached its end you and okay we're doing you's now you and quantum moon like many of my clan
before me i journeyed here to see the quantum moon's reflection of the eye this is the closest
to any of us have come to seeing the eye itself you and me you may think i'm strange but i have
a hypothesis that be oh yes we already know that you are you and me want to go to dinner later
what do you think you and me we do not have much connection you and i oh okay that's all right
still this encounter feels special i hope you won't mind if i think you as a friend
that's okay all right yeah fine that's all right okay you and moon quantum friend zone
you did i do them all you and explain no i did i did them all you and me you and the eye did i do
them all this guy's probably so sick of writing this shit he's like all right man like how many
times you want to write the same thing okay now let's do me okay me and i suppose you could reach
the eye of the universe would you try to enter it what do you imagine the effects of a conscious
observer might be um i don't know i just feel like whoa quantum moon and me is this your first
time on the quantum moon it's my first time if you've come here looking for answers i hope you
find them okay me and you me and moon me and i didn't okay what else have you not done moon and
i right moon identify explain these are the two tenets of nomai philosophy to seek out and to
understand is our way of living now we got to do uh moon and we got have i done them all
moon and i i've done them all i think yeah i've done them all oh all right now how do i tell
this person like goodbye now what do we do uh i just walk by him all right what is there what
else shall i explore a little bit more i think i should explore a little
bit
is that the was that the guy wait didn't i you killed him i took a photo of him i took a photo
of him and killed him all right now this is here but i quantum murdered him he wasn't supposed to
be alive in this universe is her oh i quantum killed her should i go i think i got to go back
and process this in the ship i need to process this info we didn't learn anything yes we did we
learned that the moon is the eyes moon and it's an eye to go in where's that ship come on where's
the ship spawn the ship already i've been here before watching these guys i'm about to stand
on the clock wait this is maybe oh this is your ship this is your ship i found your ship i'm ready
to leave what what is that it sucked into the black hole i um what's over here hold on there's
something over i don't think i've been over here what is this the big bits came in daddy umbra
another hundred dollars from daddy umbra thank you daddy umbra again for your insane contributions
you're fucking hundreds of dollars wait did i just quantum lock myself in wait i have some
shit here they say but seriously want to give back for all the years of entertainment
and happiness you've given me and so many others keep being you you're an amazing person
thank you daddy umbra happy you think that way thanks daddy because i said daddy umbra
all right sun's coming in let me uh no but just fly to the sun who cares the sun hungers yeah i
got a lot of info that i have to process it's probably the sun the eye of the universe is
probably just the sun right that's probably what it is if i were to take a wild guess
i'd say this this quantum moon is the sun's moon suns don't have moons this is a video game though
it could okay so i i've learned too much and now a threat to the cosmic balance of the world right
how do i use this info one of these times i'm not going to wake up
all right ship time let's dump some knowledge all right sixth location is it quantum moon is the
eye of the universe's moon at this location the quantum moon becomes a reflection of the eye
the eye is likely the source of all macroscopic quantum phenomena in the solar system
i still have a quantum signal on giant steve it's at the bottom of the ocean though i can't get in
there the ash twin the nomai plan to construct technology capable of producing a 22 minute
negative time interval on ash twin i gotta get in here black hole forward i don't know how to
get in there either on ash twin still i don't know what that is ocean depths nomai on construction
yard saw something sink beneath the underwater current which they previously thought was
impossible something sunk beneath the current what the hell was it this huge nomai city just
north of bribex campsite subsurface energy readings the shuttle's equipment heard strange
energy readings coming from somewhere beneath the surface two of the nomai located a fissure
in the ice on the interloper sunward side they descended inside to investigate fissure in the ice
on the interloper sunward side let's go sounds like a lead hey look it's coming over now
fissure in the ice on the sun side that would be this side right side i'm currently going to
we gotta go down is that it right there is that it right in the middle right in the middle of the
ice cream cone what i thought the sun was farther away than that you and me both
we both thought that exact same thing classic sun joke ah i love this streamer
i had autopilot on too as far as anything i was gonna be
fucking bionic boomer adjustment that's complete what
sitting here adjusting my like back brace and shit oh no i didn't do that whatever i
uh i didn't even have the fucking controller in my hand you could even hear the straps moving
with two hands fucking autopilot i'm just gonna do it myself suicidal autopilot
okay let's coast bring it down like 300 don't plot a course through the sun
i have okay if you use google maps to drive somewhere it doesn't drive you in a straight
line through buildings why would it not the gps not be that sophisticated with space traveling
all right right there right it's the one right in the middle it's right there up in there
all right let's get on it where is this fissure in the ice how are we doing it's a maze it's
not really a maze but it might need to melt okay here we go it's gonna melt the fuck was that
what was that what was that what is that what was that was that like was that a snot bubble
coming out of my mouth what was that what are these things melt here it comes shit easy ghost
matter ghost matter there i can't go down this tunnel there's ghost shit in there oh man ghost
nearby where i'm receiving much stronger energy readings now that we're beneath the crust
whatever it must whatever it is it must lie somewhere below closer to the comet center
i'm starting to think it's more dangerous than we realized
all right can you hear us yes but your voices are faint i fear we will lose communication entirely
if you continue any deeper keep the shuttle warm for us clary will return the moment we
identify the source of the energy readings i understand but be cautious both of you
i think it's a ghost maze back up back up can i go just blow right through it
i was sliding i couldn't go anywhere i couldn't even go back i was sliding forward well i couldn't
just shot the probe but instead i don't know why i was panicking with the auto mode okay let's do
that again she's got to be that far away now don't do autopilot i'm gonna drive right into the sun
like why was i not i thought i was controlling it safe no get up first links
i've got to cut it off you're already about to cross the sun here i want to be on the other side
though autopilot what are you doing it's traveling kind of too fast i need to get in closer
there why slow down what the fuck is going on slow down slow the fuck down autopilot just
fucking almost screwed me what are you doing landed all right get in get in the fissure
let's do this again all right cool this time i'm gonna try to not get killed by the ghost matter
hola yo soy auto germa auto hello okay so i'm just curious what is it what else is down here
launch mode interesting that just dumps you out there that doesn't do anything this one is bogus
too what about this one okay what about this one yeah okay what about this one correct that one
is correct is that a curiosity what about this one the one i already did okay it's this one this
is the right one hey what's going on all right here we go there's two ways to go okay right
right we're good okay that's a that's a big cave with it's still going it was like hovering down
there how do i get down here up there oh be careful all right we got two what's this one go
there um um ghost detected nearby where is this all right it's the don't go down the left oh my
god are you fucking kidding me you're telling me that i have to do i have to shoot and let me
just do hold on wait this this might not be as which one was it was right right then left
and right oh oh it's already moving right that right then left and right i can't slow down
oh yes i can i'm good and left it's left it's left right and then hold on is it left
a good view what the fuck i go up oh my god i don't know which way which one of these
not this one not this one is it this one which one is it and then right then left
this is backwards i don't know where the fuck this is even going up there did i make it um
i'm still the dead person down here holy shit wait i need my i need my thing i need i need to take
photos can i read this the spirit the spherical stone casing here seems to be the source of the
energy readings no rather the source of what's within the stone i'm detecting some form exotic
matter there's a lot to read for floating around the stone is muting our energy readings they
should be 10 times what we're seeing at least hi i don't think we want this matter interacting
with us as far as i can tell direct contact with it would almost be fatal don't touch it
i've never encountered anything like this casing but it's all that's protecting us from what's
inside we're still of this matter is disturbingly volatile hi whatever the matter inside this stone
casing is it's more than just profoundly unstable it's under tons of pressure look at this density
scan i've never seen anything this is tightly compacted before this is orders of magnitude
worse than i'd imagined if this stone were to rupture the lethal matter within would rapidly
expand completely blanketing the star system almost instantaneously and the pressure is still
building as the comet approaches this star system return to the shuttle right now the rest of our
friends need to know they're in terrible danger leave your equipment and run what are you doing
pie the more we know about this alien matter the better our chances of survival i will learn what
i can hear go warn the others maybe they can construct shelter somehow now go don't touch it
but that's death so i've made it there's nothing else down here touch it touch it touch i'm gonna
touch it what's going on what's happening uh this doesn't do anything okay it's inside of this
i can't i'm i'm dead this is causing the ghosts what the fuck is this that's where i came from
okay well let's put it in the computer so that's the that's the source of the ghost matter i'm
it's green is that what's causing the explosion is that i don't know put it in the computer
ruptured core found two missing members of the nomai shuttle crewed near a large ruptured stone
looks like it exploded from the inside nomai traced the storage strange energy readings to
a spherical stone casing filled with some form of exotic matter they determined the exotic matter
was both lethal and under extreme pressure if the stone were to rupture the exotic matter within
would rapidly expand completely blanketing the solar system almost so this is the explosion
this is what's blowing up but the sun blows up that's not what happens okay yeah we well this
is completed kind of it already blew up yeah so all right still have to do this still need to do
this 22 minute course point sir for the ash twin finish reading what this this
there are three nomai aboard the shuttle one of them stayed behind to keep the shuttle warm
while the other two explored the interloper sorry the nomai who stayed behind lost contact with
the other two after they descended below the interloper's surface okay yeah i pulled the
their their ship nomai landed on the interloper not long after its arrival in the solar system
all right i'm gonna i'm gonna head back to ash twin and see if i can figure out how to do any
of this shit at ash twin give it a go now the question is what do i do that's the ultimate
question of the game ash twin it's the sand one felt to figure out that that sun station right
there how do i gotta get on that i have to get on the sun station too somehow i don't know how
would i do so i need to find this thing on ash twin this usb storage tower thing remember
how do i get in there you just go i know right i had it in me all along i just had to go
why are you guys doing rhythm heaven all right see if i can find something to do here
land okay find something to do here there's a tower the place to go i don't really have much
info besides one of the poles maybe there's this big tower here now i wonder the more the sand
drops is there going to be something else under here i don't think i've waited to see it's still
dropping yeah i'm just gonna wait this is gonna reveal some giant satellite
i didn't do it again did i where did it even go why does it have to keep happening i don't get it
don't you have suction cups on the bottom of your fucking ship by now okay so this is that but here
is okay here we go i've never waited this long what else is on is it keep going is there more
is that it no it's still going it is still going jesus how big is this thing like this
probably way it's something i can get in the middle or something let's see i'm gonna wait this out
hold on let me just let auto out bear back yeah he wanted to leave the room so how much further
like i have a question a question does does the planet run out of sand to a point where it's
just a core and there's nothing here i've never waited that long this just jumps all
sand over here and then this becomes empty oh this is a giant 22 minute hourglass
oh it takes 22 minutes and it's just it's just a timer but they called it the hourglass twins
before yeah but i didn't realize that it was dumping all the sand and it was a 22 minute
the 20 you die in 22 minutes why is it 22 minutes i knew that it was like oh the sand goes from here
to there but but what's the point of why is this why is this 22 minutes of sand i'm gonna die out
here with my ship oh right it's fucking gone this thing is huge i wonder if this is an entrance is
it just an entrance what else has been revealed and this shit is getting bigger i've already seen
this i can't really see now i've already been up there and over here there's one on both sides
there's one on a north and a south pole they're just huge antennas is it oxygen in here
yeah can i walk in it or anything is there oxygen in here somewhere hmm i'm really i want to see
what's at the very bottom your ship is right over there it's not it's over there what else before i
die coming like rocky oh fuck wait a minute what's this what is that what's this what's this what's
this oh i thought that was part of the uh never mind the oxygen here oxygen oxygen wake up
so all right every memory recorded by a nomai statue is translated to a corresponding storage
version within ash twin okay ash twin you can't do anything on it until like 15 minutes have gone
by to go in the towers that hold those masks i could do this i still haven't figured this out
either i'm gonna do the hanging city or i'm gonna try to go to the bottom of the ocean i have this
as well i was trying to get here but i got to the fucking quantum moon thing ocean depths nomai
on the construction you saw something sink beneath the underwater current which they previous
thought was impossible well what's sunk there try just dive in going 5 000 miles per hour
i'm just gonna drive straight to the planet as fast as i can and go and go into the water
or should i try to drop something in there i wonder if i should i drop something dump something in
there throw something in there i don't know tornado the tornado throws everything in the air but
well i don't know if it'll throw the center in the air i wonder if i can tell i remember seeing
inside of that room from one of those disk things i don't think i can go in there with the ship and
dive that far i don't think it's gonna work i'm just gonna end up dying and have to redo flying
across the galaxy again okay what else is even here that i've seen done that all right i have
a question i have a question can i fly into the super tornado okay what if i fly straight down
into the super tornado where is it let's do it i just did it i just did it i just did it i'm in
the fucking middle of tornado i did it i can't believe that worked i actually cannot believe
that that just worked found it this is like an elevator
okay i can't fly up there the shard is inside of that though it's gotta be something i can
clearly go and walk it just walk it don't even who cares about an elevator let's go
now this is the last shard right pieces he welcomed in this place this tower shares with
all who asked the knowledge needed to make his or her first quantum journey
i feel like i'm coming here a little late this would be my probably 30th quantum journey so far
oh let's go up enter this place without friends however these are lessons to learn for yourself
okay keep going up oh can i keep going up i should i'm going in the middle just want to make sure i
don't miss anything all right i'm gonna go down this is gonna kill me seek the wandering arch i
know this shit all right before we get into this what we're gonna i gotta pee i gotta pee real bad
i will take our actual first real break of the night i'll be right back pee time all right i
feel refreshed ow all right follow the wandering arch it's a quantum arch guaranteed
it is all right so i gotta take a photo of it oh you can't see sorry all the wandering arch so
i should just take a picture of it right okay go in my mic is not muted i'm right here i'm just
gonna go in uh unidentified signal i found you where are you going from here there it is all
right so what does this do for me in the grand scheme of things it just completes the story or
something i guess what's this observing a quantum object observe an image of a quantum object these
are the same observing a quantum object observing an image of a coin yes this is this is teaching
us the thing that i accidentally figured out because of the moon this is where you're supposed
to learn this that's fucking funny oh there it is i i figured it out i did it good thing i learned
how to do this what is that oh i can walk on this wall hold on i gotta take a photo of it
all right read the tutorial stones i mean i i kind of already know how this works the arch
and the crystal do not naturally meet i'll just get it on there and then freeze it hey hey quantum
quantum quantum quantum quantum quantum quantum this is the last one but we made it harder
oh shit i don't know what i'm gonna do about this i have to rock climb with this okay i didn't mean
to do that did i just die build the quantum helicopter sounds coming wait what is going on
why are these not moving now i don't want this one to move now i want this one to move
right all the cameras watching them both there we go okay now you stay there now you stay here
okay bring it up this way there you go you stay here and uh that's it congratulations
you've been given the power tutorial we offer our congratulations you've learned the rule of
quantum imaging take this knowledge with you on the remainder of your quantum pilgrimage
remember the other quantum shards have other lessons to teach oh oh the shards are tutorials
right the shards are just tutorials that's the purpose our curiosity goes with are you on
your journey you walk in the footsteps of those who come before you and your path guides you those
will follow later sure thanks a lot at least we completed it and that's how we fall down
congrats on beating the tutorial thanks well let me go put this in the ship because
now i gotta figure out how to go to the bottom of the ocean get it in the computer
uh all tutorials have been completed actually all right this is done
pilgrimage to the quantum moon was a deeply significant journey for the nomai
they built a shrine on the moon to aid in the pilgrimage to its sixth location remember this
final rule yeah yeah yeah so he did all this so what remains these two uh this one's pretty much
done this over here but i don't need this i don't think do i because the big ticket is right here
i could do the ocean depth thing but i signal locator probe tracking one of the orbital probe
cannons three modules the probe tracking nodule is receiving data from the launched probe any
nomai onboard the probe tracking nodule will be the first to see the coordinates of the eye of the
universe a nomai computer reports the probe tracking module is missing i saw the probe tracking
module through a nomai projection pool it looks like the module is underwater
i can see purple electricity outside that's down here how do i get down there let's get up here
i think what do i want to go what the hell is that what is this what is that where's the
observatory where's the observatory southern observatory and the ocean current discovery
brittle hollows south pole the path beneath the surface at least i tried to do this before and
no i did this but then i got turned we did the moon thing we met that god that the
there was somebody there brittle hollow brittle hollows equator i got distracted okay brittle
hollows equator i feel like i'm getting close i feel like i'm getting what wait what is i what
is this i need i what is this what is that what is this thing have i even gone over here yet
it's white oh that's the white hole station all right let's go uh the sun's gonna blow up i did
all that i might as well just die yeah this sun's going yeah i'm running to the sun i i i have
probably like five minutes it's not enough time i can't even drive into the sun correctly hourglass
planet oh shit you are absolutely right you could that's true by this point it's it's gonna be like
yeah there'd be nothing there let's go no but we might no no it's over there's no way i'm gonna
get that fast enough just burn up with the sun who cares it's kind of cool though just die
i don't think being able to land and get out and do anything in 30 seconds is gonna work
looks cool all right brittle hollow equator
you don't know the ship has a landing mode i've used it like 100 times
all right brittle hollow behind me turn is it behind me
yeah what wait what the hell is it behind sun where is brutal hollow
i'm getting so turned around it's right there what what's going on
sun why can i not see it i'm gonna go in the sun i'm gonna go into the sun
no no no i refuse i fucking refuse i refuse to go into the sun i refuse to do it for like a 10th
time i refuse i refuse to do it no can't fuck out of here why can i not see this thing am i
losing my goddamn mind what am i going backwards what direction am i facing where are the planets
where are any planets what where did i go oh my god it out here i don't even know how i got this
way i'm but i went out into the skybox i think i was so don't fly into the sun please do not
autopilot sun me god waiter there's also a hanging city thing here too which is right above where
that guy rybeck is figure it out i guess okay now we attempt to find the thing i was trying to find
before is that cannon oh come on the hell is that holy shit wait i've never seen this before i've
never seen this before i've never seen this before what is this thing activate the gravity
cannon have i been here i've never been here before shuttle is currently rusting at the quantum
no i have yes i have wait it was it there's like three of these if it's like there's a couple of
these have i been to this one in particular though all right i'm gonna fire the cannon
bye i don't know i'm not sure where you're gonna go but hold on a minute wait at the very beginning
of the game the very beginning of the game somebody gets fired out on one of these cannons
what ship is it okay well bring it back cool all right shoot it again interesting
the crossroads yeah they've been over there where does this go southern observatory all right i
can't get in here can i and i get into the southern observatory from here that image is
psychological warfare i i'm not gonna click a link right now i'm busy i can't i have you have a
controller in my hand i'm gonna i'm just let's see what's over here i guess am i gonna make it
am i gonna make it across this is putting me where's this putting me why am i this is back
over here oh this is so confusing um i don't even know what i'm what i'm even looking for right now
actual wink southern observatory i can't even switch this now there's only one way i can go i
guess over here come from platform to platform wait what's that have i been over there
wait a minute hold on wait wait wait wait wait try jump i don't know if i can make that
black hole is there but can i make that that jump and then go into this
okay then this leads into this weird blue thing wait is that it i think that's it don't you fucking
dare kill me don't you dare kill me it almost did it almost just dropped on my head i need oxygen
but now where i don't know where to go why i can't even i like to squint to see actually
i'm like having trouble i can't i can't do this i can't do it i can't do it puke inducing i don't
think i can do it i can't do this i can't do it you can you can yes you can i can't i can't do it
jump okay one two and then to there i just i don't i don't i don't know what direction i'm supposed to
i'm just gonna try i don't know where i'm going but i'm gonna try and then jump into there
i made it this is inside the fucking circle i made it inside the bubble don't watch that
don't that's it looks like a fall hold on slow down what's in here a lot of info in here
lots of info when my dad and i were lifting orbital probe cannon components into orbit for
assembly and one somehow sank down beneath the current savva convinced me not to try to recreate
the phenomenon myself using the other cannon parts we're very curious to know what happened how could
something pass through the current my gratitude for your interesting question this is exciting
spire constructed a model of giants deep here at the brittle hollow southern observatory
and it reveals how an object might sink below the current you know i'm unable to grasp the
answer by looking through the projection pool if i visit the observatory would you kindly explain
you don't mind the trek beneath the surface to the south pole i'd be delighted to see you
the trailhead starts at brittle hollows equator right no you should have seen it we thought it
was impossible for any canon components to sink even partial below current but i sank straight
to the core all right i've seen this already this is the construction yard scam wink now i know i
can smell a scam from a mile away don't worry okay let's just keep going put tongue in there
stick tongue out savva's construction yard has been using the cyclones on giants deep to lift
orbitable probe cannon parts into orbit one component was pushed down past the current that
usually prevents anything from sinking by and are crafting a model to determine why this happened
an update it's now clear there are two different types of cyclone
one most cyclones on giants deep rotate clockwise these are the cyclones to savva typically use it
to send components into orbit there also exists a rarer type of cyclone that spins the opposite
direction pushes objects beneath the water and below the current my gratitude spire can always
showing me your handy work i'm intrigued by this secondary type of cyclone but was it really
necessary to build a model to tell me that the model will be useful as we continue monitoring
giants deep also i very much wanted to make a model for different kinds of cyclones one pushes
you down sit on your nose oh yeah where go up here and see if there's anything else
there's a lot of shit up here what is this uh teleporters let's see what have we learned
thus far in our search for the eye of the universe suppose the eye doesn't wish to be found
savva how can you suggest that the eye's signal called out to summon us to this star system
i'm aware i grew up hearing the eye's story if we're no closer to finding it than you were
when you first arrived here those of us on the vessel originally followed the eye's signal to
this star system but we were unable to warp to the eye itself the locator we built on the atl rock
and the new more sensitive locator we built here were both unable to detect any trace of the eye's
signal the eye has stopped emitting its signal it's an impersonator based on our knowledge of
the quantum moon we believe the eye is in orbit around this star system's sun this would mean
the eye is located within a finite range what is all this how should our methods change as we
continue our search for the eye of the universe we know what the eye looks like thanks to the
quantum moon so what if we try to find the eye visually instead let's send out a probe
alo's idea is covered but we have no idea where the eye is in relation to here the probability
of launching a probe in the correct direction would be absurdly small i believe i have a solution
for that problem have you spoken with rami and pi about the technology they're developing
we need to build a probe launching mechanism to cover those long distances quickly and in an
orbit around a celestial body would circumvent the need to escape gravity's pull giant steve
would be a good choice it's furthest from the sun so we'll provide the best angles for launch
and it's moonless except when the quantum moon is visiting yes let's build the cannon in orbit
around giant steve we couldn't find the eye signal using two different devices built for
this exact purpose we should discontinue this search method couldn't figure it out
this whole this whole thing is all fucked up we're gonna zoom out we're gonna be like inside of a
pupil of a baby you know what i mean it's probably something like that whatever what does this do
this do okay well that's where all the that's where everything is so that one is all right
let's get the whole thing out oh it's an atom i figured it out this is the quantum moons location
it could be anywhere it could be anywhere look at all these different orbiting paths
all right i've done it i've did everything in the observatory now i have to go down a
cyclone down to the bottom of the ocean what's down here can i go in there no where does this
lead mary i did it to put the ship down yeah we already saw this and he was like i don't know why
i can't get in here all right that's done i wish that was my ship god damn it it's not
not now we got to go to don't die um maybe i should just die
yeah just die i know where to go now yeah it's going to be a baby's eyes are going to open and
it's not it's not going to be a video game it's going to zoom out of a in real life video of an
actual baby it's going to zoom out of their closed eye and they're going to open their eye and it's
going to be right when they were born and inside of their eye you can see all the planets and shit
loaded into the computer tornado situation southern observatory so this is um this is complete
the only thing that's missing is the ocean depths which i now know how to do
i just have to this looks pretty clean there's only really the ash twin project is the main thing
and this probe i'm sure i'll unlock these two and then we only have a few things down here and
that's it isn't it okay all right guys deep let's get sucked into a an actual tornado
time to get sucked in i pay left he's on the tutorial galaxy
all right find me one of these things okay they all spin in one direction one's not
spinning in the same direction see if we can find it now should i go in there with the ship
i think i'm gonna go in there with the ship so what direction you're both spinning
you're both going that's going the other direction which one of these is going the
other direction found it in the back there you are you're not going in the same direction
go ahead and throw us down sir here we go okay we oh there it is now now what i don't want to
touch this i feel like i shouldn't touch this it's electricity in water why would i want to touch it
i'm going in you can't i can't go in um wait hold on i remember i remember i remember inside
of a jellyfish you are protected from electricity one of the only fucking things i remember
all right i need a jellyfish is that the only one that's here or is there one closer in here
this one over there can i get this thing to have to kill it all right i'm gonna drive into it and
kill it okay is it dead i think i killed it it's still electrified how do you kill it inside of
this if you're inside of a jellyfish you won't get electrocuted how do i get in there what the
fuck oh my chest you can explode underwater what i don't like my ship exploded underwater
i can't touch the jellyfish how do i get inside the jellyfish then what did that guy say he said
oh yeah it tastes horrible but what was his actual okay yeah i found that but he had like
where's like the log i see something i don't know view entries no no it's the other one
this one okay it doesn't help me i'll try it again if i climb in it though won't that just
electrocute me when i touch it see what happens they'll haven't done anything really bad
let's go yeah it in my brain do i have to hit the jellyfish in the head
where there's no electricity or get out of the ship and stand on its head i'll try climbing in
i'll get out of the ship and i'll try to climb inside but there's nothing to climb in it's closed
it's like closed up there's nothing like i can go in where is it i can't climb electricity no you can't
i'm gonna take another look down there i'm gonna go to the bottom
let's see the fish let's go all the way to the bottom i don't think this ship is gonna
explode or anything but is there is there a bottom just this is not just sitting on the
bottom of the ocean it's down here okay i don't let me see all right we got jellyfish jellyfish
going in jellyfish going in that one goes in oh he's going in for a dunk all right uh wait
i swim through that that's me can i swim into that when he's done why is it it's leaving that
trail it's leaving that red spot it has to be can't be for no reason this i think the ship is too big
to do that isn't it let me get full fuel and oxygen everything i got 20 minutes don't worry
i should be able to swim through that after they go in hold on i got an idea why do i think i can't
touch the jellyfish because i if they're electrified and i bounced off i'm trying
this even if it doesn't work i don't care i'm just trying to why don't you just touch the jellyfish
what's wrong with you why can't what do you why do you think you can't that didn't fucking work
damn it now the ship got all the way back to the surface why all right we're gonna try to swim
inside am i in it am i in all right i'll give you one reason why this is i don't like this
because how is this this is not electrified is everything else is but like in under here isn't
we in i can't see anything are we in i don't even know if we're in oh we're in we're in right all
right get out holy shit okay i'm in what's up and what's down my flashlight doesn't work in here
what is that thing that's an eye and i go in it why my flashlight not work what's this this is
the can okay this is i'm gonna go in this way it's the eye of the universe holy shit i'm flying
around all right hold on i don't want it wants to come in my room i gotta get out hold on okay
hello dog hello i tell he's good he's on his pillow he's chilling on his pillow
well whatever but how do i do this i have no audio all right so here we are new content new content
is this the probe so wait a minute is this anything in here no i know you're reading show
auto i i can't the camera's like to i'll show them later i promise i gotta get through this
i have exciting news the ash twin project is always prepared to receive the probe data
from the orbital probe cannon liar oh no i can't i got like documents all over the ground
i got hold on i've got hold on i've got documents all over the ground i swear to god
there's documents everywhere and i have like insanely personal info i got so many
fucking documents everywhere they're surrounding me what is this another document
fancy desk with documents on the floor you don't understand my my fancy desk in quotes for what
you're saying is there's three monitors okay i'm gonna show i don't wait i'm gonna get he's all
he's all the way across the room hold on fucking documents everywhere i accidentally show one of
these documents i'm gonna be so mad no we got more documents over here i can't
i think the room's covered in documents i swear god i think i think i've cleared the room of all
documents ready for your close-up auto here we go
hard decision to do this hold on wait i see a stray document
documents we're good i was looking at me like what the hell are you doing i was you can't see
i can see a document guys i can't fucking move because one inch to your right is a bank document
i'm good there you go that's my special dog i saw it no you didn't clean your room i just it's just
a bank document i'm good there you go that's my special dog i saw it no you didn't clean your room
clean your room it's just documents it's not like it's like shitty diapers or something it's fine
all right here we go i'm exciting news the astron project is almost prepared to receive the probe
remy is adding some finishing touches here but she'll be finished soon are you are you in the
orbital probe cannon well we are the probe tracking module is ready to record each launches flight
trajectory and will automatically transmit all relevant data to you on other appendage i'm now
worried about this canon structural integrity and its cruise moral integrity once the probe
determines the location of the eye of the universe i'll send an alert directly to you and remy
we already saw this but let's do this let's go into the quicksand and okay this is the eye of
the universe like whatever this is this is the eye of the universe what else is in here imagine
privet the probe tracking module will be the first to know the coordinates of the eye of the universe
you'll be the first to see them i am honored and terrified you won't ask the orbit of a
probe cannon to use so much power that it breaks will you fret not my nervous friend we only need
to fire the probe once who minds if it compromises the canon structural integrity i think we read
this one i would mind malo i would mind because we won't be capable of receiving our probes data if
the probe tracking module is destroyed so where's the data where's the data is that very explodes
oh whoa whoa no no no no this way where you going over here okay so here comes the data spear
uh day pot has redeemed bernie sanders okay the 34 000 points okay retrieving data from probe 9406
visualizing current trajectory of probe 9406 with data all right that's what the sixth location
looks like retrieving previous launch data from ash twin for probes launch 9406
deep space anomaly matching all known criteria for the eye of the universe
bird of universe found by probe 9354 somebody found it retrieving stored coordinates from ash twin
displaying coordinates for the eye of the universe screenshot it okay it's c or like an l
uh l a well what was that just blew by whatever i'll know i guess somebody will remember it
oops okay so i got i got the i got the coordinates for the eye of the universe
i have the coordinates for the eye of the universe i got it it's i did it let's go all right can you
stop doing that for me all right if you could stop doing that it'd be very nice okay all right
i i know the location of the eye of the universe anything else down here that i need to look at or
see i don't think there's anything else in here the tree i think i think i got everything i needed
i'm not sure there's anything else to do it's just this weird tree core all right let's go
let's just get electrocuted to death i could have swam through the whole time
i already tried that yeah okay out is okay i guess all right where's my ship
doing over here
all right let's deposit this data let's see we get probe tracking module all this has been
revealed i have the coordinates of the eye of the universe there's only one or two real outliers
here and it's this shit at ash twin project and black hole forge and then the hanging city and
then this anglerfish fossil you don't have any more info on this go to ash twin by this point
most of the sand will be gone right so i can kind of explore hold on a second
oh i forgot the big gravity in this after that i forgot the gravity the huge gravity in this planet
yeah i can't get the ship i can't get back in the ship now no longer have access to the
getting sucked away by the current i'm trying to jump i'm trying to fucking die
i can't even die correctly just throw me in the air and let me just go die somewhere
thank god the fucking sun's about to explode i can't even go forward please just throw me here
why are you not throwing what i'm standing inside of this tornado why am i not going up
you can't suck me up that's the down that's the own that's the down one it's the down one of
course it is blow up so i can please i wish i could delete that water effect
we need a good view i don't know if there is a good view there's kind of a view there it comes
been a while to get here well i did learn a lot so that's good progress when you're gonna do nancy
drew i don't do like an hour please note do not hold any of these terms accountable for germa
he's not going to do these things okay i want to go to the ash twin yep i think that's what i would
like to do i still haven't figured out what this thing even does or why it exists i just know it's
here you lied about fl studio yeah i did i'll take that one i did eye of the universe the twin
project thing land on it let's go all right now i'm just gonna make sure that i have enough
remember you still as confused as me about this game i have a very basic understanding of what's
going on but an incredibly basic understanding of what's going on there's this group of alien
people who wanted to find the eye of the universe and it wiped them out and they may have wiped out
everything here which also wiped us out the ship oh no the ship's gonna get grabbed no the ship's
gonna get grabbed by this this happens to me every time oh come on why i'm going for it
we're going so fast just get on the beam okay we're good okay good heel
okay good very good very good excellent hey we burnt some time hey i wonder if that
uh sand plant it's a little lower than it was before this time make sure it's not in the
trajectory of the sand it'd be very nice if you did that and get over there oh i'm not gonna land
on the equator again i'm not gonna land on the equator waiting for it to come by this is where
i want to be i don't care just crash don't land on a fucking equator okay right here is good
let's see what happens two on either side of this planet when this goes to zero it triggers the
event when all the sand is gone it triggers the event to bring me back to life with the cactus
jump no you're not dead i will be this whole this is where the masks are stored which is where i
you store the memories of the last person just control my breathing just hang out for a little
bit do i try cactus jump all right i'll try cactus jump no no i'm not gonna do that
there's this which i still don't know exactly what this is for let's get a look at it
i know some some ancient town i don't know cactus was this person here before is it cactus
all right i gotta be careful this is in the trajectory this is in the trajectory of
i can't get in no yeah i gotta put the ship all right it's starting to let me get in the ship
get the hell out of here here it comes all right what this has got to be some entrance
pumpkin smasher pumpkin smasher just gave a hundred dollars another ten thousand bit donation to
stream ridiculous you guys are crazy giving that much money but holy fuck thank you
10 000 bits huge bits they say hey jerma show your beautiful face for the rest of the stream
and i'm not gonna do that i don't do face game unless i'm playing a horror game or i'm
showing my nose i'll also want you to rest easy and know that your rent's gonna be paid this month
so your upload you can upload more content or if a wink gets redeemed so i could oh so i can upload
more well i like i can make some more streams that's fun but thanks to the huge amount of
fucking money i'll give you a look i'll give you a wink what is this this is new whatever this is
this is new i haven't seen this before oh shit a document leaked pumpkin smasher just gave 150
more dolls pumpkin smasher 15 000 more bits thanks for the wink here's some more thanks
the huge money pumpkin smasher for the love of god that's a lot of money thank you billionaires
in chat double wink all right where am i going what's going on hey hey hey hey i tried to put
back around am i ever gonna have enough am i ever gonna be able to sit here for 20 minutes to have
this planet become an actual thing i can see or something going to happen to me within the 20
fucking minutes i have to do this sleep at a campfire you can't afk it's too bad
uh okay i'm gonna go here i'm gonna sleep at a campfire and then we're gonna try this again
yeah no there's a campfire on that uh with the dude playing the guitar there's a npc up here
and he has a camp right doesn't he has a camp yeah that is a fire that much i know at least
just use the sun as a campfire yeah why don't i why can't i just i can't just close my eyes
right here and just wake up in six hours i guess i could that's just sleeping i could do that but
i'm piloting a ship i don't think i'd want to do that go to the campfire let's sleep and then
let's try to figure out stay down please am i am i landed i'm staying no fuck with the fuck up i'm
not going i'm no no this thing's gonna take off again i'm on the equator no i'm not doing
that for the fucking 10th time i knew i saw you see i saw you i knew it i'm not fucking this up
again nope no no no no no no not gonna happen uh i almost did it again yeah yeah at least i saw
the train coming down the track this time all right now i just want to find that person let's
just pull up the crazy over here left bumper tilt dude i wish i could fly this ship with my eyes
where is this guy like i wish i could just i could turn my head and fly rather than like hold left
bumper tilt right stick left stick no i want you but i want to i want to use my fucking eyes and
the head i want to tilt my head what guy there's a guy here where's the guy this is the wrong
planet he's on the other planet is there actually no campfire here there is no campfire here he's on
ember oh motherfucker really i think there's a guy in the sand yeah i yeah there's not a guy in the
sand it's all right he's right here how much time passes when you do this that was off five six seven
wait wait wait wait wait are these minutes or second hold on is it i was gonna say holy shit
that's going fast what should i do 10 minutes okay that's about two i'm gonna do more do another
like three or four three just sleep until the supernova happens that would be so bad
i chart oh it's you i have a question for you i found something i found uh right isn't this time
supposed to freeze i don't know that much of what's out there okay question for you um where should
i explore i haven't left this lake bed have you seen the old shipwreck on ember's twin southern
hemisphere oh yeah i think i've already done that i don't have time for this i found something i
found uh the quantum moon everyone loves a good mystery all right i don't have time for this i
literally don't have time to talk to you bye goodbye all right i'm going back but i looked
over and saw that the satellite part had barely even gotten uh breached
so here we go so there is all kinds of shit in here now which one what do i go to this or here
i'm not sure what i should do first what are you doing
okay what do i do what should i do first something over with the satellite things
it's still going but one of those other buildings to go in what under here look anything under here
yet really this tower anything else on the surface level on this one it's still going though
dark don't please stop stop stop look at all this shit but this there's nothing down here
um just i just wanted to see what was beneath the sand okay i think this is stop
still going not still going i can go in here the door opened in here
there's an opening who cares this brings me to the top where i have no idea where it was before
i've already been up here this is the bridge this shit is coming in it's coming in right now it's
gonna it's gonna do the same thing i did last time does this eventually get something at the base
something deep buried in here no idea i've already been up top here we go yeah i've been up top
before here's the entrance is dropping anymore it still is is there anything else in the bottom of
this chip is gone well i mean we have like three minutes before it ends i'm not leaving this planet
all right so this is now what happens if i is there only and i have to go up the middle
but haven't i already been up here yeah i've already been up here
this doesn't do anything for me well now i'm gonna be able to see everything
what the fuck is down there all right it's just like the meatball i'm just i'm this is the meatball
core okay right in here i already went in here i have absolutely no idea what's going on
like the sun's about to explode gotta go in the cactus tower there's no more sand before
in here right in here and walk up this now i can walk down this done this already though
what the fuck is this what is this bro what is that hey hey hey hey no no what have i
get in there here's the first delivery warp fresh from the black hole forge
ash 209 i've been here before i think once yeah i've been here once you go to meet at the station
i've been here once yeah i didn't learn anything so there's other buildings that are on that equator
how many more there keep going with the same ones everything just kind of blends together
let me look at the notes all right uh yes they did they want to know if a 22 minute negative
time and if it was possible they can clue yeah yeah yeah yeah designs for each of the towers
and ashton's equator each tower warps through a different planet these towers are done to
visually reflect its warp destination yeah but all right i'm gonna go back and i'm just gonna
ride the equator right cactus tower again maybe all right so you know the problem is is this planet
always starts just just a circle so it's it it's not like everything gradually comes out of the
ground let me try to get to the cat i don't remember where the cactus from is is it one of
the equator ones it was part of the equator wasn't it so it's both the poles of these giant
huge satellite things i'm not on the equator right good all right so where what where's that
cactus where's the cactus one on the equator too fast this is all right let's go get in all right
this is literally right in the middle on the equator and okay i know what it looks like it's
good it's a weird like star shape i can't get in there yet i need an entrance besides the entrance
gonna be on cactus run hard mode there it is open come on hurry up is it broken this fucking thing's
broken i can't it's right here that's not it's gonna cross over on me all right it is immediately
to the right cactus room go through the cactuses be careful go oh shit wait what's that do i didn't
do anything what's this what's that what's this somebody said look up at the ground
how do you look up at the ground i knew we were gonna fucking pour it into the sun station i knew
it i told you i told you guys i knew it but when i freaked out and started screaming about this game
and i was like there's no fucking way i have to do this there's no way i have to fucking port i knew
it 81 000 years ago no user commands received for 10 minutes all systems entering sleep six
minutes 40 seconds increased solar activity detected sun station hull integrity approaching
critical levels closing emergency doors opens the emergency door um i didn't want to do that
i didn't want to do that no no no no i didn't think i didn't know that was i didn't know opening
the fucking door oh my god i'm gonna be i'm gonna scream opening the door and walking forward it was
a trap you have to actually float into the other room that's so finicky and so annoying to do that
holy shit i'd rather drive there with my ship do it then i don't get any new info oh at least i know
how to what to do now it's cactus rooming fuck me i'm so close to learning the secret
why am i going so what's going whoa whoa whoa i'll tell you i'll tell you use it star wars it star
wars it i'm fine can you please where am i in the equator so okay here's just a car wash
there's just a car wash we're fine give me off the equator all right in two
i'm not back on the equator i'm not back on the equator i moved away from the equator
oh my god okay let's get back to the cactus tower and i gotta float into this
you want to chill by the camp nope i don't i'm not i'm staying right here
this is where i'm gonna be this is my this is my spot this is where i'm gonna be for a little while
yep this is where i'm gonna be hates bits wait hold on what's going on we had five thousand
bits from freak out uh more than that we had uh like a hundred dollars from freak out and more
of these weird code i don't even know what this is oh this is the code this is the code guy this is
the code guy i don't i have no idea what the hell this is i i don't know why you keep doing this
but uh no don't don't put those codes in chat please i don't know what they are i can't condone
them if i have no idea what the hell they are no no no no no i i don't know what they are i don't
know they are this is a bunch i don't know what they were it's a bunch of codes thanks for the
huge amount of fucking money jesus but i don't know what these codes are man why am i paused
because i'm reading a bit donation from the codemaster they'll say hey jerry i've been
watching you for a few years after being with my girlfriend for a while now i decided i was
comfortable enough to introduce her to your streams however this was not what she wanted what she did
want was to sleep with one of my high school friends behind my back oh shit i've been single
for three years now i've decided that now is the time to get back in the dating scene but i just
wanted to ask you what are what what what's going on what what why is it already freaking out all
right thanks for the huge amount of money i don't know what to do when we got like a thousand like
launch codes and then everyone i'm reading a donation everyone's saying stop reading
and i'm like i what the i don't know what the fuck is happening this is just a shit load of money
by the by the way if you haven't seen if you've if you by the way if you haven't seen your one
anime i recommend welcome to the nh i don't know what this is i'm done i don't know what this is
that's a good anime oh this is real this is a real thing all right this is real it's a real
anime okay this is anime all right this is not like porn launch codes okay uh welcome to the nhk well
the art style isn't great it deals with issues rampant in our society it's cool there's such
as drug abuse depression social anxiety okay it's only 24 episodes it should be something you can
watch without burning out that's cool launching porn in t-minus 22 minutes he's not gonna watch
it let's be honest all right you mess thank you for these fucking you but i gotta ask all right
can can you not do any more cool codes you're freaking me out with the codes i'll be real
honest with you this this like weird like monster spam of like code links is freaking me out a
little although i do appreciate your ridiculous amount of money that's a hundred dollars from
freak out no don't if you post if you post them you're gonna get dropped don't do it i'm telling
you if you post those codes you're gonna get dropped by one of the mods it's gonna happen
you're gonna get dropped for like probably like 20 you're gonna get like a 30 minute don't do it
i'm just telling you i'm just trying to be real with you germ is so gullible i don't know what
the hell i'm what do you want me to do somebody drops a hundred bucks in bits and i'm gonna i'm
gonna read what they say and then it's like well oh my i can't believe you read that why has the
game devolved well it's because i'm waiting to do cactus run again to fly into the station
this is my fault this is my own fault somebody just redeemed a wink in the middle of all this
all right other side cactus run and then we're going up and i'm gonna i'm gonna i didn't i couldn't
see i'm not gonna just walk out immediately i'm sorry i don't know why i thought there was like
a door wait we're gonna one more uh uh big straw suck thing you wasted it what let's do it same
deal and then i'm just gonna i'm so bad with free floating i'm gonna have this gonna take like 10
attempts son of a god damn it son of a god damn it no fucking way no way no way not a chance no way
no way i'm sitting in my car i guess now for days if i suffocate i'm gonna be really this is
not i can't it's not trees that's not a real tree where's the station please hurry up i'm gonna run
out of oxygen all right where is is it just right there straight ahead all right i'm just gonna go
straight out this is way harder than it looks that's i can't climb up i have to jump press
left left triggers to go down is the right trigger is the one that's for a and right
trigger is the thrusters just say you hate this game already oh that's so funny
i messed up like a tricky sequence twice oh so it's like dude just like admit you
fucking hate this game like i mean come on man slow down i'm so close to the end of the game
like seriously it's in the sun station you pick up a block of wood and you stick it in your mouth
and read it all right i can't go full tilt here if only he knew how to control no it's not that
all right and i had like two minutes of oxygen remaining too so like all this stuff is going in
my if i don't get it this time it's not gonna happen i'm just gonna be i'm gonna be completely
completely honest with you he flew the off no i jumped i jumped out and my character started
turning i didn't press any buttons he just started going like this i didn't press anything it just
started moving on its own that's the point just don't touch anything so just just walk out and
don't even just put the controller down is that for real skip time yeah i'm going to the other
planet no no why would i that's a that's a one guy comment why would i listen to that all right
let's go sleep where's the campfire there he is
dude i'm fucking just gonna land on this motherfucker what do i care
can i use your fire please to go to bed thank you magical golden fucking goose egg i'm gonna try i
gotta get it this time i know it's gonna be hard for me to do i know it is come on i'm telling you
man you don't move i'm telling you you don't move what
why am i being told man to not move by people telling you man just don't move i i think i
missed the opportunity wait hold on did i did i sleep too long wait a minute say goodbye to the
ship i slept too long didn't i yeah not that one what the hell is that what am i doing um trying
to find that it's the other tower wait i went past it did i wait is it that one it's this one
right here fuck it is this one what's too late i was i was too late anyways i wouldn't have been
able to do it anyways five fucking gaming moments of 2020 there it is write that one down all right
get the fuck out of here that's not impressive i know it's not impressive all right do i listen
to the one guy and just hold a while i go forward and that's it walk off and don't move oh don't say
that just hold a walk out and hold a don't press anything match velocity station can't be targeted
just don't press any buttons i'm not gonna press anything but what about you were wrong you were
wrong no i got it okay i got it okay i made it mission science compels us to explore the sun
can't we change this i don't enjoy working in view of such a morbid mission statement
but it's accurate we're going to create a supernova for the purpose of scientific progress
that's our mission the mission is to decide if such an irresponsible feat is even possible so
they did it here's a better one mission determine if it's possible to prompt the sun to explode why
why do they want the sun to why are you doing this you lack a sense of humor at least i don't
lack a sense of ethics kindly refrain from going supernova on me before the sun does
oh you're dead why the masks little go-karts wait are they like bugs is this like a person lying
down with like weird beetle people or is that just like a storage unit i don't know i don't know i
saw a guy wearing one of these all right let's go let's go in i could go up but let's go down
first wait that's the sun is down there sun's down there the sun is in there let's go up
uh this happened to me what is going on what i didn't run out of time
ran out of time the supernova didn't happen the sun was expand well i'm trying to like explore
okay on the back of the game's cereal box it's like explore everything and look at stuff and read
stuff i had to go down well how am i okay how am i supposed to know i was supposed to go down
first i want there was a way to go up all right i don't have that info we're gonna do it again
there's a setting that pauses time while reading why is that not enabled automatically
it is it is it is it's on all right let me do this again i just i i i turned around like five
fucking times where the hell am i going i have to do this should we use the you i go i'm gonna use
the fire yeah what was that don't do that don't do what are you talking about wait what are you
why is everybody goes don't do that what was that noise what do you mean what noise are you talking
that noise not you oh i was like what like there's a noise in my room slow it down
okay we're on the equator i'm on the equator every time am i yes i am move it out of the way
right here should be good like right here please would stop rolling the fuck around
use the campfire at the start yo signal boost this shit yeah retweet it everybody retweet it
where is it retweet at the campfire how's it not popped up yet all right you guys see any good
movies stand here no i have to go into the sun i have to float over there again and you saw how
horrendous that was i have to do that again i was so hoping i was never gonna have to do that ever
fucking again and i have to do it again match velocity i can't because you have to have something
to target to match the velocity i will match the velocity of the sun and fly right into it
okay here we go passes through and then we go don't touch anything that's what i did last time
it was a disaster and i ended up just freaking out and fixing it let's go okay one two three
three that's bullshit you're right that's ridiculous just just ridiculous just ridiculous
oh i have to do the jump all right i'll get it you're gonna be falling to the sun for fun
elbert said stop saying that um i'm gonna say why did it not work okay left trigger right trigger
right trigger left trigger right trigger and then go down here we go go down what's in here
uh read star has reached out end of natural life cycle now approaching red giant stage warning
evacuate sun station approximate time until sun station is destroyed by expanding star four
minutes nine seconds approximate time until star's death 15 minutes and 39 seconds i need a disc what
happened to the sun station not fire it fired yarrow but it failed the sun barely responded
there were infinitesimally small surface level changes but they were barely visible even to the
third eye the sun station is useless it will never and could never cause the sun to explode
i don't know what comes next my friends i suppose we must start over but i'm unsure how to start
over don't i do it uh return to ash twin first my friend perhaps a change of task would help
aspire notice to comet approaching this star system that we'd like to investigate
hi i hurt for you my friends we all know how hard you both work i can only offer my compassion how
are you how is it idea we're well yarrow or as well as can be expected given the circumstances
though disappointed may have disagreed with exploding the sun but i never wish the device
would fail and hope their terrible work was finished i mean that wait hold on these are all
people standing around me these are all people standing around a circle and they're all standing
around me is that it is there anything else i can do in here uh we're gonna die run run
what did they even do for me i just they tried to explode the sun with the sun station and then
the comet they wanted to use the comet instead so the comet is what's making the sun explode
but why how the sun station done the sun was designed the sun station is going to make the
sun go supernova the nomai fired the sun station but it had no effect on the sun they concluded
the sun station can never cause the sun to go supernova the failure of the sun station the nomai
took a break to investigate the newly arrived comet according to a nomai computer our sun has
reached the end of its natural life cycle okay i still don't get what i do how what do i do about
this ash twin project all the memories are recorded through a storage unit within ash twin
there's also this coal forge in the hanging city what course the black hole forage there's a huge
nomai city just the north all right i'm gonna try this i'm gonna do this so this is right above
ribex campsite i'm gonna find ribex we're gonna do this tomorrow let's just crash and die
try to get out you're gonna fall into the fun for son elbertson
right going back to diablo 2 yeah on saturday saturday is going to be diablo 2
hardcore we're going to try to kill diablo we need to go to uh it's uh ribex campsite is in
the what is it the hollow what's it called riddle something you act like diablo is the end but we
know this in act five um yeah i know that too i have to beat diablo though i have to kill diablo
first tomorrow's tony hawke underground the xbox 360 hard drive has come in and it's saturday's
diablo 2 hardcore and depending on how how depending on how poorly that goes
probably finished sir is wrath too bilateral itch just gave five tons of fucking money tonight
huge five five thousand five thousand ten thousand ten thousand ten thousand ten thousand bits you
guys are fucking going nuts thanks guys seriously that's a shitload of money i like to imagine the
god of this game is watching just like what the fuck is this guy doing and what and they are just
blowing it up every time they're just they're doing it they're just like you know every 20
minutes see if we can figure out where i am i'm gonna find the eye of the universe see if you
can find me good luck all right we're gonna find uh right there but thank you phylactery
five thousand bits like he's like in the core but i gotta go yeah i gotta go down that weird
there's a spot i can sneak in there it is all right let's go down almighty god in chat
good god human dev in chat cool hey dude um why did uh not we can ask questions about the game
why did you give us fingernails what was the point of that he's over there i can't just how
do i get over there reliably how do i get over there reliably without just jumping and dying
i could go down here but how far does it bring me i'm not gonna jump where does this bring me
he's right there right there all right i think i can actually jump from here and land in there
no i don't ah okay it's above ryback right so ryback is there the hanging city is here like up
here i'm gonna okay i'm gonna turn up here so what like this way like up there or right there
how do i get over there how do i get the ridge like go that way i know i'm looking at the funnel
but like i just i want to make sure i'm doing this right okay and then this way did you did you guys
just more huge bits hayden clip fell 10 000 in kxc 50 at the same exact time have fun space cowboy
thank you guys both of you god that's a shitload of money thank you all of you that's too much
hanging city co-op bits something like that oh well that was deeply unpleasant i made it this
far though i guess that's the part to focus on and not how i'll eventually have to get back up that
path wow this place sure is something looks like the hanging city is north from here and east is
a gravity cannon i definitely want to see that another thing i'm detecting oxygen from somewhere
below which is good since i uh used up a lot of my supply screaming during the trip from the surface
as i stop driving heaving i'm gonna head further down below so i can refill my tank
what's this say gravity cannon yep let's check it out let's check it out hanging city
i don't want to use any fuel or anything i'm scared to use fuel i'm not gonna get hit in the
head with that boulder am i school district melt water district eye shrine district
black hole forge district i need air i'm what black hole forge i need air somewhere
we're gonna get it there you go
oh
okay i guess i plugged it in hold on this text here the ashtron project requires a powerful
highly advanced warp core how should we obtain it we could craft a new advanced warp core inspired
by the vessel's warp core abandoning the vessel's warp core and its casing means losing valuable
knowledge this is true however its knowledge we have little hope for covering it would be best
to relearn i think i'd very much like to craft such a powerful core more relevantly i believe
the black hole forge crew and i could recreate the basic design is the safest path for our plan
is the safest path the best best one or our goal is worth the risk is it though we've tried for so
long to find something that i and others now believe might be possible to find what are they
doing here now can i just be honest what the hell are they doing here i can find the eye we
would find the eye why because we have to why do you have to because that's what we do why
that's what we do if we do that's what i've been yeah the greatest challenge here i think is we
don't have to design for such a powerful core or any of the original craft is the vessel's core
no but what was apprentice to annona who created the original design and a black hole forge is
adept at crafting simpler cores i believe i can be of use here the vessel's warp core was created
before my time but unknown explained many of his designs to me but didn't we we got it right from
the horse's mouth already we talked to one of these people and i was like what are you doing
you just do okay why do you want to find the eye because we do i want to know why i need to know
why i can't wait to know why it's i'm gonna be told why and it's gonna be a huge like wow
i can't wait you've already they already told you yeah because they just wanted they just wanted
know as much as they possibly can they just they strive for knowledge right that's all it was
they're just curious you heard the term don't fly too close to the sun it seems like they did like
a hundred times this would require a return to dark bramble loom my father said many good know
my perished there retrieve the warp core from the vessel retrieve the warp core from dark bramble
my mentor and his old mentor once discovered and studied an anglerfish fossil on ember twin
i saw that once i studied an anglerfish fossil using that knowledge we could avoid the anglerfish
entirely i remember that anglerfish fossil we used to play in fossil fossil fish cave when we were
children that's that's fossil let's say that five times fast fossil fish cave fossil fish cave
what meloria and i have learned is that and that fossil would theoretically help us evade the
anglerfish but our hypothesis was never tested on a live specimen vessels warp core is broken
at best we call those present when the vessel crash said it was it's the same lethal injuries
there's no guaranteed reward for the risk perhaps we could still repair it my grandmother my
my grandmother told me there was a little time to assess the nature or extent of the damage
guys that's a liar even if it no longer functions the old core could be a valuable blueprint
provided we're able to transport it back here all right how often do i who cares let's keep going
up any more of those uh any more of those memory sticks for some reason you can't walk over that
i feel strange trying to recreate and known as warp core without him at times it still feels
strange to no longer be his very young apprentice for the black hole forge to be in my care and not
his this will always feel strange even though my time with him was short i miss my old mentor
the chance to try to have the chance to try is thrilling but i don't want to disappoint everyone
i think i can do this probably but what if excitement has clouded my assessment of my
own abilities was i wrong and volunteering to build it i was born in the star system and
never saw and known as warp core with my own three eyes i only know what he taught me they have three
eyes what if i've bitten off a larger portion than i can consume still all i can give is my best and
as anona would say should my best prove insufficient and we will find another way to achieve what's
needed i have clary and rude in the forge and i have my clan i'm not alone on the button to turn
on going up we are up very high mother fucker there's a distress beacon down there i'll have
to read that out later all right we made it to this kind of snowy area to go that way but wait is
there anything over here not really almost out of fuel which is not good running water all right
remember where this is this is right to the right south of the north pole and it's a little river
that you can go in all right cool a little shortcut um i'm gonna go back in here though
wait go all the way back down all right let me see let me find where's that distress beacon
down there there's more stuff i could do over here wasn't there
fortune controls uh yeah they go up and around up on like this surface let's go
there was like two other there were two or three other places to go
can i just go this way i guess i mean i i'd use the black hole thing
where's the black hole district isn't that just in it i'm going this way whatever i'm just gonna
explore uh i don't i don't seem to lead anywhere what does this go keep going not really what is
over here the sun's gonna blow up any second we have probably three minutes before the things
gonna start doing them on the music everybody is dead you're all dead everyone's dead everybody
did they supernova themselves oh yeah they commented themselves i get info to read yeah
some somebody uh somebody touched this thing that they weren't supposed to touch let's just see what
this is he welcomed in this place this shrine is a space to reflect on what brought us to the star
system to signal from the eye we observe the eye signal in our travels and followed it here to
find its source what we know is this the source of the signal which we have chosen to call the
eye of the universe is older than the universe itself the rest we have yet to learn enter and
open your mind to its possibilities what is the eye of the universe here we go it's gonna tell us
the eye is the source of the signal that brought us here suppose the eye is a more advanced being
pose the eye is older than this universe so imagine how much it could teach us perhaps it
is a cosmic library what is the eye's signal suppose the eye wishes to communicate the signal
is the eye's voice it speaks a language we don't yet know or maybe the signal is the eyes attempted
expressing itself the signal is a call where we the intended where were the intended audience
from the signal we were able to determine the eyes approximate age for lack of age and how can
the eye be older than the universe itself suppose it's a relic from a previous universe
the early universe was unimaginably hot and dense if anything existed before it would have been
destroyed suppose the universe is older than previously assumed okay uh universe old eye
knowledge good work guys what is this thing let's go up a little forward on something
what do you have to say i no longer believe as i did as a child on ember twin that the eye of the
universe wishes to harm us but it may not want to be found either what else do you have to say
the terrible circumstances of our arrival here were almost certainly exactly that circumstance
we saw her earlier i suspect imagining we are special to the eye in some ways wishful thinking
the eye might have called out to any sentient species or it might not have been calling out
at all and that my ancestors heard the eye's signal holds no great meaning this wouldn't be
so bad in fact the eye may not have wishes at all we have no evidence supporting this
it didn't call out to chat it didn't call out to you guys no sorry it wasn't calling to you
all right have we learned most of what we've learned so far have we learned everything we
need to know here hey asshole with the eye okay let's go back i think i've read most of the
things i can read here i missed please grab the ledge grab i'm going to the fucking black hole
i'm going to the black hole i'm going to the fucking black hole i tried to skip it i just
wanted to go so i wanted to go and get out and wait what the hell are you doing out here
wait what the hell are you doing out here this is a scripted part of the movie why are you doing
this hanging city the vessel oh the vessels warp core broke when the ship crashed in dark bramble
the vessel where we almost completed this one escape pod two warp core broke when the ship
crashed in dark bramble to dark bramble we go it sounds about to blow up but you know
these things things about to blow up i want to see the supernova it's gonna take too long no let's go
we did learn a lot but where i have to get into that ash twin database thing i have the key
i have the coordinates for the eye of the universe what am i what do i do with them
go to the vessel did just open up vessel no i debated how to obtain the powerful highly
advanced warp core when i traveled to the solar system in pursuit of a signal from something
older than the universe itself the vessel so we need to go to dark bramble and find this vessel
anglerfish no mine learned how to evade anglerfish by studying an anglerfish fossil they found on
ember twin let's go for it dark bramble it's been a while since i've been here actually
it's been it's been probably eight seven or eight in-game hours since i've been here dark
bramble and we're looking for a vessel a ship ship ship ship some kind of ship i'm gonna say
distress beacon yep yep yep there it is good impression of storage wars no that would that
would be a little different that would be yeah what the fuck is that it's a signal there it is
all right how do i get in there reliably right there there it is all right get in on the ship
all right fuck it let's get in there all right just get out i can swim right our escape pod
crashed as we tried to flee this place destroying our movement and communication capabilities in
the process we've held out as long as we could here but this pod supply of breathable air is
nearly depleted and the anglerfish attack more and more frequently the best chance at survival
is to return to the vessel to either repair the damage or more probably wait rescue second is
the message finished the vessel's beacon is already growing fainter it'll be gone in a matter of
hours we need to leave here isn't this is not the vessel all right escape pod three
this shit ain't the vessel well maybe i'll get some info where the hell it is
escape pod three vessel has been mortally injured emergency sequence activated awaiting departure
from vessel now launching escape pod three multiple collisions have altered pods trajectory
significant damage to pod detected navigation error life support error propulsion error
error scanning external environment scan complete gravity not detected breathable
air not detected multiple life forms detected do not exit pod i know what the vessel is the
vessel okay the vessel is the thing that explodes when you wake up there's a new problem our
equipment is detecting two distinct beacons from the vessel but it's impossible for the vessel to
be in two different locations at the same time i agree but the beacons are exactly identical to
each other perhaps if i had more time we're nearly out of time already din the vessel's
beacon is quickly fading soon will be gone and we'll be lost we will follow the beacon whose
source is nearest to us suppose that beacon is false we likely don't have enough air to reach
the farther of the two beacons did the decision is made for us we'll leave a trail of lights as
we go there's still a chance someone could hear our escape pods distress signal okay don't open
this yet i want to read this emergency escape hatch wait no we gotta go we gotta follow these
lights give me the ship give me in the ship okay all the lights going that way i'm just
into the computer escape pod three escape pod three survivors another beacon didn't say there
was another beacon that's what is this is this a ship holy fuck they're all dead okay hold on
what are they what are they doing over here ready who come here searching for us we followed one of
the two beacons from the vessel to this place but now can go no further it's almost too faint to
hear now but the vessel's beacon is still faintly emitting from within this thorny seed yet the
opening is too small for even a single gnomai to fit through it so our escape pod couldn't have
flown through here i don't understand how this could be possible but this gruesome place seems
able to manipulate space itself maybe this was our undoing so to be close to the location of the
vessel and still go so far is difficult worse the vessel's beacon is dying soon we'll be unable to
hear it there's nothing we can do now but try to perhaps find a way inside or at least attempt to
comprehend why this happened my dearest hope is that the other escape pods were able to reach
relative sits the fucking thing that's on the home planet that's the thing that's on the home
planet the vessel is the thing on the home planet box box thanks for the raid just i missed it sorry
thank you box box for the huge raid welcome everybody we're currently in the second half of
uh i almost said keep talking and nobody explodes but that's kind of that makes that's
you could describe this as well i would do wilds okay here we go i know what to do let's do it
hey stop the way of ruin my immersion
hold on do it again that's where it is he's gonna follow the thing all right we don't need
anything else here go back in the ship let's get the hell out here follow that beacon follow that
beacon right red duplicate signal it's in the red oh hi guys okay go go go faster
will he smash his head on something uh so two of them show up i'm not sure uh we have to get by
them is there a way i can kill them or something i learned a lot fossils they turn into fossils but
how okay my grave survivors from escape pod three follow one of the two vessel beacons to a small
dark bramble seed but they could go no further they could hear the vessels beacon from i'm sorry
stupid fucking mike the opening was too small yeah yeah yeah studying an angler fish fossil
they found on ember twin shit ah i gotta go to the ember twin thing to find out how to evade them
is it like just is it light is an angler fish fossil on ember twin go to ember twin and find it
ember twin let's go there's a fossil of one of these on ember twin hopefully it's on the surface
but didn't i know i've seen it it's in that cave how do i get in that cave i never found out a guy
is it was way to like drop down is way to drop i think i can drop somewhere i just don't remember
i know it's in that like that cave system i gotta go down there and look but i can't get there from
there it's over here above the door where the cannon is here it is all right so theoretically
here get out of this thing here right no no no no where is it it's like in the rocks up here
why does it have to be so fucking dark why is it to be so dark unbelievable this is a space game
okay this is where it is not here what the fuck excuse me i was holding a
okay now how do i get there from here it's gotta be away wait i i didn't even touch this shit
i didn't even touch this stuff did i angler fish oh huh angler fish observation tarot deck
yeah how does this no wait very old specimen what we might learn if we could examine it
for both grades and luckily this dry plant is hard yeah i don't know i've already looked in here
i need to get like in i want to get in the observation deck i want to get in the room
i need to get inside of there clearly this hole is too small for it to have fit through
there's another entrance to this cave if there is coleus and i will find it we can't leave valley
below of course there is okay now why can there never be just a front door in this game
every door is blocked you have to go in a back cave door we need to find a way inside quickly
because when i returned here there was uh children playing in the specimen
there's another way in whatever gotta go here comes sand that was too fast
what's this one stepping stone district there's so much shit here turn them all on
um high energy lab trailhead what's this one eye shrine district over there let's do one
at a time here can you give me like a three second window before it becomes available to touch again
running out of time
we're meeting in the fossil fish cave to play the game if you're too big to climb through the
angler fish overlook hole you'll have to go the long way but it isn't far go to the stepping
stone cave and then up and into the fossil fish cave i tried to get to the fossil fish through the
stepping stone cave but i couldn't find the entrance where is it remember to feed the fossil
fish first if you go to the angler fish overlook and throw a light into his mouth he'll show you
the way what rocket can't fit through the angler fish overlook hole anymore because they grew
bigger he's taller than levi now who cares it's still i'm still the tallest i'm gonna do one final
break i'm gonna take auto out and pee and we'll do our last break and hopefully i can get this
game done in the next hour or so i'll be right back what are you guys fighting why are you guys
fighting why is everybody fighting hey no food fights no food fights please all right stepping
stone cave the entrance is feed the fossil fish from light into his mouth stepping stone cave
okay well the sand is filling up i gotta gotta what is this stepping stone cave i keep having
these eureka reveal moments in my brain and i say them as i see them although i didn't put the light
down wait did i shit is it still there all right thank god thank god my my idiot brain actually
just left it there oh children doing this why were children doing this sand sand am i supposed
to use the sand how much higher can i go that's not correct that's not correct it's not correct
it's okay it's just sand how do i get up here the fuck do i just i mean the light he has the
light going your way the stairs i just was on the stairs all this wasn't i just on them oh i was
following the scout thing over there i only have three minutes of air what the hell is all this
are we playing the fossil fish game tonight i fed the fossil fish a new lantern if you go to the
stepping stone cave the entrance to the fossil fish cave is easy to see now gratitude solenum
good to see you're small enough to climb in through the hole at the angler fish overlook
i'm still small enough you won't be for long mom and dad are tall so you and i will be tall too
must be nice uh i just keep going keep going all the stairs no this is not right that's not right
stepping stone cave i was i think it's over uh all right it's we're like filled up we're like
filled up with sand at this point do i have time to do it do i actually have time to do it
i have time okay well what is it up here i don't remember the doors every single door here is it's
all the same it's blending together in my brain it's all the same architecture where's it's right
there i i this is broken there it's in here it's not i don't have any oxygen either i'm dead how
to die yeah well now i'm gonna go here exactly immediately did i just better get it no uh i'm
gonna do this i'm just so disoriented down here the cave is just like the same color on either
side and this like it's just everything melts together in the same pot of same exact image in
my brain i have this one light in the middle and like the same color on either side of my brain
right there oh quickly quickly learn the secret learn the secret quickly whoever was
whoever was it when we ended last time is the anglerfish pickle rule change the anglerfish
now has to wear a blindfold the rest of us line up against one wall when the anglerfish says go
the little fish sneak across to the other side the anglerfish catches you you're eaten last little
fish to be caught is the new anglerfish the old anglerfish gives the new anglerfish the blindfold
and becomes a little fish why are we changing it it's too hard if you can't see anything
aunt pie says real anglerfish are blind but you have to wear a blindfold the rule stands
it's okay if younger kids don't wear the blindfold when they're at it
the rest of us will still wear it for scientific accuracy and make the game even
all right so the blind so that what just to go quietly is there anything while i'm still frozen
here is it any those kids dead holy shit okay what about what's up something up here
i made it what oh come on really okay i got i learned what i wanted to learn anglerfish are
blind so i'm assuming i just have to be very quiet when they show up
so we'll just just turn off the engine just don't move like if they're blind then they
can hear so they they're gonna i just have to just not move don't make any sounds when
they're around okay so let's test that hypothesis and let's head back to the bramble to that ship
for that uh beacon see if we can kind of coast slowly by them
um okay go in the sun if i keep this trajectory all right take up the stress beacon escape pod
three and we go that correct all right this should be i'm gonna be quiet is there any is
how do i be quiet in this thing it's like a big ship with fire and um how do i be quiet
i wonder if i just if i just don't move but then how do i kind of turn the ship
it's at the i wonder what's the range of them being able to see or hear me
okay uh is it just the red one should i just go towards the red one that's just it right
i don't have to do this whole thing all over again do i all right somebody's hears me i'm just i'm
not moving where's he go to the left okay he's right next to me is there one right next to me
to the right all right there he is can i move oh my god i don't know what i don't know the timing
he was still i thought he was past me the booster is low enough for one bar they won't hear you
can i look around hold on let me i could like get out hold on this took me like five or six
five tries i believe i don't know i'm trying to figure it out this is where i gave up
oh really damn i feel like i want to go fast though like tiptoeing around okay that one
when you go in the red dot and there's two of them and they go hey don't move there right but i feel
i feel like if i the slower i am like i'd rather just go in quicker and and i'm looking at chat and
talking and i'm gonna crash into this and we're gonna have to do the whole fucking thing over again
a philosophy joke let's be supportive for a change germa you got this don't fuck it up
it's not really supportive that's more like putting pressure on me you should have said hey you got
this no not don't fuck it up i wonder where it is i'm just gonna go fast the faster i went last time
i got through two like just go the last two times i've made it through here i've gone fast is there
a way to how do i look do i have to unbuckle see like i'm just i just got the fuck in here
and now is when i just don't fucking move um but wait wait wait wait wait hold on a second
so how do i i'm gonna bump into his his tendril i'm gonna touch him i'm gonna touch him you can
direct it wait i have to go don't boost i can move i'm gonna touch him i'm gonna touch him
oh how did i not touch him i i'm shocked and i can't believe i didn't touch him
okay almost there floor it i'm not gonna floor it wait okay what is it is it another thing to go in
is another bramble or is it a vessel is it the vessel i can't see what that is what is that
it just flew by me what is this i'm not gonna floor it i'm not gonna floor it no flooring it
there's a bunch of eggs am i the sperm i'm the sperm i knew it this is about making a baby the
baby's eyes are gonna open it's gonna be a baby okay so what is this what am i doing with this
am i gonna crash into this what is this eggs what i did i did i pass something hold on do i have a
beacon i can't break them he didn't scout the vessel pick a hole and go omega lull
you see people saying i missed a person here i don't see anything that's really weird whatever
it is like a dna strand so where the vessel is go find that all right it's gonna pick a hole
wait what are you talking about what are you guys talking about i don't have the scout anywhere
guys i shot the scout at that i i that that's not i shot the scout onto this
that's i didn't do the thing i did before the scout i didn't have the scout i didn't do the
thing i didn't go back and shoot it through the thing you did a hole now just one of these
fucking things just shoot it into one of these i think i think it has hit i think i just hit
i think i just hit a fish well wake up if you want to wake already what about right here
not on that one it's not that one so what i had to have gone back to where they all were dead and
shot it in there to be able to find where the vessel is i can still find it i mean good luck
i have to just pick the random one that's correct i'm gonna hit this damn it so so this was so this
was the fake signal right then they said there was two signals i think i just have to die then
don't i i have to just like floor it and just die because i don't know i have no idea which
one's the right one just like this like it doesn't mean he's not there let's have to leave
there's no distress beacon in here i'm just gonna go in one
whatever i don't have the the signal like i have to go get the signal and shoot it into the thing
so i know where it is i might be screwed here yeah i should have done that first i just for some
reason i thought because i don't know i thought i listened to one guy in chat that said just fly
to the red light you're fine you can't even get me somebody said you don't have to do that just
fly to the red light and i was like oh okay you must know what you're talking about all right go
to escape pod three shoot into the thing go follow the beacon follow the scout that's where i need to
go now it's time for hard mode no let's go go to the grave fire the thing in sneak past all the
guards and follow the right beacon should have done that i was gonna do that too i was going to
i'm actually glad it's an emote only but i can't get fake advice i wonder what seriously the
percentage of actual real advice is in twitch chats or if people are just saying just typing
random shit they're just like i don't fucking tell them i'm just gonna see if i can get them to do
this hey yeah dude uh you you press a three times when you get to the when you get to the grave is
he gonna do that and they hear they hear this and they're like oh my god what a fucking idiot
let's go fast i know everyone hates this and so do i but i have to go fast i have to
grave i thought that was a fish it's just a log it's just a strange looking log okay here we go
is that a fish or is that a log okay here we go there it is hire the scout in and then follow
the lights god you're gonna make me fucking throw up what are you it won't go in it won't this shit
won't follow the lights i did wait no i just have to go to the no i already have it it's already
there why why did they say all the lights oh no that was we did that already okay yeah i got
the yeah yeah that was like that i did it in reverse duplicate signal let's go here we go
just get me in get out of this okay can we get like the star trek ship to get the fuck out of
my way it's not that way it's down there i'm gonna bump this right have we that's be very
clear that i'm not gonna bump this shit all right there's the scout wait where's the error duplicate
scout is that is this still good we're good right i'm going so slow but i can't press a button
there are the frog eggs there are all the new tadpoles that are going to come out that's fine
we just go past it is it safe to use thrusters right now is it safe to use thrusters
no i can hear somebody i just did it a little bit okay don't do it anymore
oh sorry just floor it try floor it try floor it
oh all right so we've got 600 meters we're almost there this is the vessel are those things still
here what do i do get out and fly in it with my body is there a broken entrance or something
their window broken like over here okay get in here entrance over here this looks like torn up
can i go in there underneath because the door this is just like a underneath and underneath dude
what kind of fucked up ship do you fly here what is this fucking thing this this is a lawnmower
this is not even a ship where how do i get in here you're fucking weed whack a ship i well how
where do i go take it off emote only give me the answer i don't care get out of this thing before
it explodes no what at the very top my god this is so disorienting i want to throw up
right here this gameplay makes me want to puke in fact i probably should go puke wait it's not
right here there's a giant hole right here oh you dickhead game it was this the whole time this is
no entrance here this is nothing here to go in oh you gotta be fucking kidding me it's that
white ass background i was gonna go there first but i was like oh no there's like there's nothing
there all right what do you got in here what can i read in here turn this on power it up this thing
all right we're gonna put power somewhere i don't know what that did i guess i don't know i'm gonna
go travel up here although there's a button to press over there but i'm not gonna press it yet
it's probably info up here there is why can i just chew on fucking like gravity gum like they do in
mars attacks this is escal's vessel something went badly wrong during our warp and our vessel
is mortally wounded we needed help as quickly as possible our vessel appears to have has it
fused with the local environment somehow there are vines that are now part of the vessel it's
been torn apart from the inside itself we're abandoning our vessel any nomai clans or space
flight capable species receiving this message i employ you we need your help well you're all
dead is this broken can anyone hear me hello our vessel's dying sorry i only have 20 minutes to
figure this out any nomai clans is best i can hear this message clear the universe is dying
there are fewer and fewer resources and safe places within space now so my clan and i believe
the best option is for all our clans to stay together if you can reach the glooming galaxy
we found that black rocks suns are fairly stable and life in this star system is thriving we live
in relative safety well if you prefer you to continue exploring alone know you will be on
your own hannah we're making our way to you there's a lot of writing on this one they took
the whole board it's good to hear from you romey we'll watch your vessel we'll watch for your
vessel has anyone heard from neem his clan was on its way to our vessel but they never arrived and
he hasn't sent any messages i'm beginning to worry that is unsettling it reminds me of that old myth
my grandfather used to tell the disappearance of escal remember hearing that story as a child
one day escal's vessel simply stopped responding the other clan searched and searched but found
no trace it was as if their missing friends had warped out of existence that's no myth friends
escal's clan existed and their story was real what a curious event to have passed into myth our
ancestors ancestors were told that story when they were young are you sure it's true
fucking goddamn gravity man i swear to god it was a very long time ago but yes my clan's ancestors
searched for escal's clan for a long time but in the end none of them were none of them were ever
seen again i hope you aren't comparing escal's story to my clan's vessel all right wrap it off
guys it got much more board space time to wrap it up neem my friend we feared you were gone
people gonna start writing on the edge like a little bit like oh fuck i can't fit it
not yet we aren't but nearly we found trouble during our warp see blame this idiot
that took this much space right like two or three people took up way too much space here
we found trouble during our warp the triple suns of the bright spark star system exploded
and it was only a lucky coincidence we weren't caught in the blast we'll meet you soon
i'm relieved your clan is safe neem it's good to hear your words any vessels nearby remember
to be extremely cautious of potentially unstable stars because yeah blame the guy with the big
bald ass handwriting you didn't have to have a board this big i press the button warp core
uh i don't think this thing's broken what the hell is this i have to turn on all the the karen
stones i know the word i know the word i know the word i know the word i know the word i know the
word i know the word i know the word i have to spell out the coordinates okay it's it's like an l
right just stop moving like this it's like a weird l sit still i'm holding a this is definitely how
you spell out those coordinates it's gonna be really hard to do um i don't i don't know what
they are it's like c yeah i don't i don't know exactly what it looks like warp core is broken
well is this a warp am i am i warping right now i don't even i probably know this could be the
fucking microwave i don't have that info i'm not gonna be able to do this regardless but this is
i get this is where i have to put that in yes the three it's three one two okay i mean can i
can i place it in here is that like what i'm supposed to do yeah i'm dead anyways all right
well i found it is there anything else i can see before i die warp core has to go here i don't have
a warp core i have a broken warp core can i take my ship's warp core do i have a warp core
oh time's up anyways is there anything else like over here i just dead person there
i'm going down the hallways i'm all closed goodbye just die i have zero health zero h02 whatever
okay so i found the vessel there's a broken warp core and that's where you input the coordinates
i need a warp core i have to go back there with a warp core see what i learned he's definitely not
gonna finish this tonight really is that much more to do i have the core i just really no way
you're really close no way though oh here we go there's the vessel activated reset
pillar on the vessel's bridge there appears to be some sort of input device
they tried to call for help but the vessel's outgoing message did you know there's a problem
there the vessel can still hear incoming messages from other nomi vessels the remaining nomi
clans are regrouping in response to the impending death of the universe right how am i still not
done black hole forge found a switch in the meldwater district that raises and lowers the
forge the black hole forge district is the highest district in the hanging city
no my name poke plan to create a new advanced warp core in the black hole forge no my crafted
warp cores of black hole forge before delivering them to ash twin that's where we're gonna get one
all right let's mark it i need where is it it's the brittle brittle bramble whatever it's called
shard uh black hole forge all right can i um i mark this spend it below the hand i
had to go to the hanging city i guess i can mark the hanging city let's go have i been to the
sixth location yes i did that a very very long time ago i did that a long long time like four
or five hours ago yeah remember that shortcut to the hanging city you know what yep where is it
i don't remember just tell me i'm your friend you can tell me these things just tell me i'm
your friend i'm your friend near the north pole we're friends here and it was the river water
right you and i you and i friend you can tell me where that shortcut north pole river you never
been to any of my birthday parties yes i have i was in a costume i didn't want to give away my
identity so i was i came in a costume all right we need the north pole uh it's like the place
so there's a river flowing through it where is it over here where's that river right here somewhere
i think let's get out this is the south pole opposite side um oh you were the stripper
so you ordering a costumed stripper how does that make any sense
close enough
okay it's like right here right there's water right here somewhere
there's that water there it is okay let's go back down let's go to the that city i think
i just blew up right behind me is that hole
where the hell is it is it on the it's not on the other side is it the whole other side completely
isn't a lot of fuel for this shit too okay all right now we need to go to the forge which is
actually sure to be honest it's up isn't it city the top most level i already read all this
is there an elevator or something i can fly i can get on over here all the way up there
can i get up there i gotta do the controls first oh wait yeah those are down here aren't there
all right press the button there it goes i get on that while moving i'm not gonna use any more
fuel so now i have to go up up here up up up all the way up can i let me try this one first
this way maybe i go all the way up up up up up that's as far as i can go
i'll be even further from here to there another way to get here this way yes this looks right
this looks kind of correct
you'll know how do i it is wrong but oh there's what is that thing
that's a teleporter isn't it where was there a teleporter
wait i think maybe i can jump and look at it where was the teleporter that goes to here
it's this white and purple looking place is it over here there's a thing here
what the hell is a teleporter is it on a different planet there's a couple of teleporters
do i actually have to go and teleport from a different planet to here why can't i just fly
hey uh i've been streaming for too long for this what is that what is up here there's something
else i did everything here where have i seen that cube before i remember standing on it and
and where is it where is it where is it where is it where is it i'm searching my brain right
now where is that platform i have to look at brittle ramble when it comes by where is it
ash twin we're gonna go to ash
are you going to ash twin yeah that's true how is this not exploded i was trying to just delete
this and do it again and sleep in a campfire why are you still here explode already
explode thank you what just get out and repair it
no no i'm starting over i'm starting over again i think i'm stuck what do you mean isn't it where's
the eject button there's no eject button i'm almost out now if this thing is stuck back here
i'm gonna burn myself to death in the fire i don't know i don't know what the campfire is
i have no idea this will kill me don't worry why is it so hard to die i'm trying to die
what's in there here comes kazoo ending too all right how long what like a minute two minutes
how long is too long for me to get to the planet one minute two minutes probably two
i'm gonna say like two i'm gonna take about three minutes or so to get there okay we are going to
ash twin we're going to desperately try to find the teleporter to that place teleport to it
he didn't do the black hole forge thing i'm not i'm gonna be out of time then like i shouldn't
have slept in the fucking campfire then why did i sleep at the campfire let me just see if this
works i'm gonna go into the sun i just need a warp core and i can end the what do you
that almost seems impossible that was that was impossible what just happened i have no idea what
i don't know use autopilot autopilot flies you into the sun it just puts you in a straight line
to wherever you're going and just goes straight into the sun all right i'm gonna how fast can i
do this north pole do the controls teleport these are the real gaming hours
why is the atmosphere yet sir am i allowed to turn sir this is a wendy's
so we need to be in north pole i don't is this the north pole it's not we need the north pole
so here it is this side of the other side it's the other side it's the other side
side other side is it right there is it right there it's right there that's right okay
turn on the controls and then come back up here all right so how how do i reliably get back up here
just go back up that way how hard is it this way this way this way okay then down here
all right right here turn this shit on going up right okay controls are on let's get back up here
back up right let's go now we head to the ash quinn find that teleporter stand on
one let's go move let's go all right it's on the equator but which one it's on the equator it's
one of those towers on the equator just gotta find the one that has the at white background
so this is i'm on the this is the equator here i don't see any towers yet don't get hit by the
thing here all right this one here is it this one here it's here somewhere
oh looks like a sun all right not this one what about another one what about this
way what's this one what's this one's shape like does it even have one in it wait this is the
it's not this one it's not this one it's not this one this is the um this is this plan wait no this
this is this planet right cuz this is the two pillars let me see now this ain't it
watch the ground you're gonna see the ground it's not white wrong it needs to be white
another one okay here it looks like it's coming for me sun shaped tower that's this tower
then there's this five towers right what's this one that shape like a circle might be
this one they all teleport to a different place arm of three well there's oxygen here
thank god there's don't get too cocky here was the last one it's here there should be
two more one here wait just wait for this to go by so I can have but I can uninterrupt
yeah here's another one this is another tower hey what's this one this one is this is just a
spot but wait a minute that's uh this is we need the sand to go down this is not brutal hollow
though this is like the spike shit it's got to be this one it has to be this one is the sun again
now this is the Sun I did a full circle were there only four towers did I miss one
now the sands come in here isn't it I'll drop it that fucking sand
all right let's go okay brutal hollow wasn't it that's not brutal hollow
oh here's our first delivery one warp core fresh and black hole core
sands going up I'm upside down right all right this is it I gotta wait for I gotta wait brutal
hollow has to be in view hey look at what happened departure time 800 time arrival 800 with a little
one return warp status charged step onto warp platform when ready black hole forge
oh okay there it is all right give me my warp core let's just get in here whoops any just
looking for writing let's go back there's the thing I plugged in it's two I want how much time
do I have I'm not sure I have enough time Larry and rude kindly tune the alignments on each black
hole core as I finish them schematic on the floor shows which warp tower aligns with which astro
body right speed future deliveries to ash twin I've tuned the first black hole core to activate
when it's a warp tower aligns with brutal hollow before anyone comments yes I am aware this reduces
the distance between yarrow and me schematic shows the six towers on ash twin are being tuned
only five alignments a mistake no that's correct for these alignments we've decided to treat the
hourglass twins as a single astral body right if it helps you can imagine the hourglass twins
is aligning with themselves have you seen flox's tower designs in the high energy lab on in between
they clarify each tower is a warp destination yeah we gotta figure that out all right we need
a warp core projection stone alignment one the sun alignment two hourglass yep alignment three
timber hearth yeah yep mm-hmm alignment five giants deep alignment for brittle hollow so
yeah they just correspond yep yep yep okay a little bit more writing here where am I taking
this first black hole core and where am I taking the remaining cores once they're ready
all the warp towers are being constructed on ash twins black hole cores will go there
my gratitude in that case poke larry I'm leaving for delivery I'll send yarrow your regards
look I returned to the ford shortly I'm going to catch up to root and help them deliver the
first core to ash twin just make sure yarrow receives it of course the white hole cores are
for the six warp receivers each warp tower leads to a different planet so that will be a greater
pain in your cervical spine that was on ash twin so it's just on ash twin somewhere delivered
someplace I need to find okay let's use the stone and go read I have good news yarrow the advanced
warp core is ready to be installed at the heart of the ash twin project I'm intrigued love everyone
on ash twin is excited to see it no it isn't is everything well at the forge don't worry love
poke is only nervous core is extraordinary and her design work is beautifully clever
the core's durability could still be improved I need more time ignore her yarrow the core is
finished and if my sister tells you otherwise then she will be finished as well killing your sister
what again this thing they're one looking at me why do they why are there two heads
um okay so now I know that the core is on ash twin I need teleport to ash twin
but I think I did everything I needed to do up there it's okay there was nothing else for me
to do up there there's no core up there it was it was on ash twin yeah I could have been way
more upset about that all right now let's break our legs and our spine
I'm trying to like scrape my face on that come on just die come on let me catch one of these
how have I not been hit by any straight power or something okay got a bunch of new info what have
I not done I don't have very many more connections ash twin is one of the only things that's a
question mark let's see where we're at now I call forge ash twin that leads to here ash twin
our designs yeah it's just ash twin so far the vessel has something to explore the ash twin as
well an advanced warp core was successfully forged and for installation at the heart of
the ash twin project like in the heart inside of ash twin at the very very middle
but just have to wait till the thing goes to zero and just go in the middle
let's try it I'm just I'm gonna just explore and see if I can ash twin I gotta get to the
heart of the ash twin too fast already I think I saved it how do I get to the heart of the ash
twin mine the equator yep always on equator okay so I have to get to the core of this
how is this still aligned I just flew 5 000 feet to the left it's not we're gonna rank
wink redemption um do I just wait till it gets to the very bottom the sand and just stay here
and just try to go right to the core right to where like the tootsie roll pop thing is
that's real this is real wait this is real wait this is real there's only one
for there's only one warp I know what I have to do there's one warp of both of these planets
I gotta warp from that one this one or vice versa I gotta work from this one into that one
let me give that a try I work in I work into myself so if there's the two tower one and I
warp into it like the fucking name of the goddamn game is called the two tower project of course
it's going to be the one that's the two the twin the twin tower one go into the twin tower one
teleport and there it is the ash twin project you'll see let me let me look let me see let me go
read it while we wait for this the sand to get out of here look ash twin ash twin towers design
now I got it that's I'm gonna teleport to myself wait for the sand all right there's the sun
looking for the is it this way or the other way let's see
there's the sun behind me tribes of scent where are they is it still taking too much time
where these are the towers come on here we go there are the two towers now I need to wait for
the sand to get down here and I'm going to teleport look at this there's a teleport thing here
and there is not one here I gotta stand right here I'm gonna wait until the sand goes over me
and I'm gonna teleport through into the sand in the yellow
oh not here I'm talking about one down under the glass speaking of which I gotta get the
fuck out of the way enough now for me to go okay so wait there's another one there's two
but this is broken wait is it gonna line am I gonna see it am I gonna see it I might see it
when is it gonna happen that it hasn't happened the ship is gone now wait here it comes here it
comes here it is I ow what these are all the faces 10 minutes 40 seconds receive data from previous
cycles masks receiving data from probe tracking module giant steep memory statue timber hearth
memory statue 12 minutes until end of cycle transmission I need a thing today we finished
the excavation of the ash twin here in this space we carved we will craft our most ambitious
project yet the ash twin project powerful enough to send information back in time how far we've
come since our experiments at the high energy lab I still can hardly believe Ramy's hypothesis was
true we've also finished relocating all subterranean plants we met while digging
we'll need to keep our eyes on how significantly we've altered the environment here
oak just sent the warp core for the final tower to us from the black hole forge now ash twin can
be connected with giants deep the cassava is working with havens to craft the orbital probe
cannon and with blocks of sculpting the memory statues hypothesis it was not by accident the
core of our warp tower was the last to be forged cores could have been forged faster
saba had interrupted my work less frequently to ask for updates the important point is we are
all connected through the ash twin now we made the internet is what they're saying and also that
i'm no longer needed for mediating your disagreements our friends on giant steep tested the orbital probe
cannon today malo tells me the cannon is doing well and that havens advocates more launch power
if anyone can coax the maximum power from a device havens can then if anyone can go to device into
exploding that too is likely havens perhaps i should check in with the oracle probe cannon crew
in the interest of safety would help to remind havens that malo his love will be one of the
nomi on board the cannon or is malo part of the problem
fox and dad's finished the memory statues today and they are truly remarkable
when the ash twin project succeeds or in the event that it fails the memory statues will activate
allowing us to gather more data before we shut down the project
high-end idea i've worked hard on the sun station and it is at last is complete everything goes as
planned the structure will prompt the sun's explosion which will in turn supply the power
the ash twin project requires my boomer belt activated okay when i press by their mental
fortitude this was the project's most difficult task in more ways than one we're nearly ready
to activate the ash twin project here is what will happen first the sun station will receive
the order to fire at the sun prompting it to explode using the energy from the resulting
ash twin project will send the order for the orbital probe cannon to fire back in time by
22 minutes exactly 22 minutes after these orders are received the sun station will again trigger
the supernova to send the probe data from this cannon's launch back in time in total each
cycle created by the ash twin project will last precisely 22 minutes we can end this cycle it
will these words are difficult to write the sun station did not work suppose we redesign the sun
station to generate power of that magnitude a supernova is still our only viable option
this is easier expressed than accomplished you can wait for the sun to explode on its natural
timeline if you prefer idea but you'll need to find some way to halt our aging process
i believe we can still find a way to create a supernova my friend don't lose hope
however this is the closest we have ever been the ash twin projects theoretically sound
we were only unable to power it perhaps there is another way final drawing we are halting our
research into creating a supernova for this moment comet has newly arrived in this solar system we're
anxious to explore it it's been a very long time since we last explored somewhere new
so we're excited to welcome this comet imagine what knowledge might be gained there
oh my god there's a lot of stones install the masks inside the ash twin project blocks
they look beautiful although i feel like i'm being observed it's comforting to know the statues will
not pair until the project succeeds otherwise i imagine the experience would be hard to endure
i read this already daily they only need to activate once the project succeeds as a safety
measure however the statues will also activate in the event of equipment failure they will why is
that if anything goes wrong with the astron the statues and the mass will make us aware of the
situation and enable us to fix it otherwise it would be possible for us to remain permanently
unaware of the problem i hadn't thought of that what a profoundly hurtful fate
we're trying to be trying to fix it okay it's just it's it's the total recap this ore should
be the last we'll need for the ash twin project it's exciting news can i offer an extra set of
this final check delighted to help be grateful if you would the more eyes the better
once we finish the shell that seals off the core we'll check to ensure there are no longer any
physical entrances ramie and i will be checking the interior and then the exterior for cracks our
final safety check mr lore wall where i think i've seen the rest of these almost prepared to
receive the probe data yeah we've seen these yep yep yep i'm looking for the eye of the universe
like i got these old i have good news the advanced warp core is ready to be installed
to the heart of the ash twin project is where i am no it isn't yes it is everything well to forge
don't worry yeah we read this like five minutes ago okay we're good artificial gravity control
um wonderful i activate first wait that's what hold on this is the teleporter to over there
turn on this wait we're flying around you're about to access the core while the ash twin
project is active removing the core will disable the ash twin project what there it is i got it
okay now we have to we gotta leave now i have the core i've got it i've got the core to power the
ship let's go where's the ship i gotta go put this in the core i don't know where to put it
i don't know where to put it in my ship all right it's going in my ship i can't i can't get to where
this needs to go fast enough i can't get to where it needs to go fast enough but wait hold on wait
the project isn't going buckle up there's no supernova don't fly into the fucking sun don't
fly into the fucking sun the fuck just hit me okay now i gotta go um um i have to fly to dark
ramble wait why is everything getting sucked into the sun throw it into the sun no what throw
the core into the sun where's dark ramble this music is driving me crazy okay i need to shoot
the um i need to shoot the thing into the beacon to get to the vessel so i can get there right
i have to shoot the beacon into the thing i'm going 15 trillion miles per hour
oh my god oh my god just don't get in no okay i need to mark the distress signal on my
on my i'm gonna mark the distress signal on my thing yep where's the vessel uh the the this here
okay all right we're good wait no i don't i found it already i already found it i found it already
uh the fish are still here though so i can still die from a fish if i die from a fish
i'm gonna be really mad if i crash into something and explode i'm gonna be really mad
what are the symbols i gotta look at my notes but here's the thing i have all the time in the world
i could just coast for like three hours that's what i'm gonna do oh you motherfucker
what's going on did i hear something why did it explode i disabled the project yeah so it
couldn't blow up let's just go get it and let's get the fuck let's go do i have it what if i still
had it in my inventory all right let's get it so we get it we get the hell out of here get in the
ship go go go go speaking of go all right we're gonna try this one again fucking just crash into
it you dumbass i have to time i have to i have to speed up time anyways so you know what just
just do it i fucking have to speed up sleep
what it takes to fucking destroy a goddamn ship i won't i'll never know
i have to make i have to sit at the fire the fireplace like three four minutes i gotta sit
at the fireplace so that i don't stand around for five minutes ten minutes i thought i had all the
world emote only we can't help him but we can't hurt him either i'm gonna do four minutes i also
want to look at what the symbols are because i'm not gonna have very much time i didn't do
anything a zit just popped on my forehead i didn't do anything i didn't touch it one more for all
time's sake no no i wanted a marshmallow get me out of here what are the symbols no fuck it no all
right just just go to the planet we could just look up teleport to that weird place grab the
core park the ship in a safe spot get the hell to the bramble and go by the way there were two
errors there was an error in error it's it's the red one then the white one right you can help me
out on this i don't care help me please i'm so close there's a wink all right this is not the
right one oh get me in there this is a blindfold run um yeah pretty tough it's the broken one
come on get me in before the whole cycle goes through i've got to grab this
okay here we go got to grab that warp port
why is it not happening this time um why did it not happen
why did it not happen i didn't jump i didn't jump i got what what okay sir but honest to god
what happened to myself do i have to bump my head and then fall back down
sand pulled you off of it well how are you supposed to stay on this how are you supposed
to stand still sand's gonna do this every time i even reach it from here
i like to throw myself into space it's kind of but it's not gonna help
please just do this okay that's i missed the cycle i'm losing a lot of time here too though
and now i have to wait oh god damn it i have to reset the whole thing can i get in there and do
it right now just the sand went up more well here we go so i i have to stand in this here so i don't
get sucked up and then go just go like this wait under the lip here that's that's come on
that that is a like dot dot dot come dot dot dot on you know like come on this is gonna stop me
am i in the right spot stand on the blue i no stand under the thing okay here we go
one two three are you sure you want to proceed yes windows fucking authorization bullshit
okay okay okay
what the fuck is happening i turned on autopilot started reading a book let's go wait wait wait
what hold on can i teleport to dark dark teleport dark bramble try teleport dark bramble no okay
and we've confirmed we've confirmed it's red first and then white right just red no white then red
my god i'm going really fast i'm sorry i have to fucking look at chat i tell you it's that's
fucking stressful is it red white then red please tell me the truth please tell me the truth don't
lie to me i'm not now all the marker that's what i'm saying there's two markers red okay i'm going
to listen to fucking six of you no why is the end of the game like this
uh i can't even go fast in there because the angler fish are in there and now i have to do
this all over again i can't i got a checkpoint with this fucking stupid thing in my hand
i didn't use a campfire thank god germa doesn't have a real job why because it's late yes oh
let me go over here let me assess you as a person so it is in the video game out of wild it seems
that you have you didn't go quickly to the red dot fast enough for me to i'm sorry gonna have
to dock you a few points a second restaurant waiter i can't believe it yeah i just i couldn't
i couldn't believe it yeah no no no i was going over your i was going over your resume guy that
drives a bus and uh how come you didn't see the there was more writing that was on the wall there
that you didn't you didn't look at i'm upset by this therefore you can no longer drive a bus
oh yeah wrong fucking planet i can't even drive a bus all right i'm gonna try this one more time
and i'm gonna youtube the ending it's been almost nine and a half hours don't you dare what does it
really matter if i youtube the last eight minutes of the game i'm gonna i'm youtubeing it i'm gonna
youtube it i can't believe i have to fly through bramble place again i'm youtubeing it i'm gonna
youtube.com slash fucking no you know i'm just gonna open up the wikipedia page of this game and
just read the end and one sentence am i still on the equator yes oh my god i just want to be done
this is is it far enough
please man i just can i fucking just shut the warp core i can't even go wait no god exists god
exists it's gonna fall back down to us where am i fuck me man i have i need that ship to fly to the
bramble place you still didn't watch like a deer in headlights yeah because i'm at the end of the
tunnel and the tunnel has no oxygen in it and i have to go through it and hold my breath and
fucking just try i'm trying it one more time just read game boomers instead i'm at the final part
of the game this is actually the end of the whole game this is the it i just have to do this i just
have to wait for the stupid fucking god damn it i'm going to bed somebody said that they didn't
have campfires before a patch how many times have they patched the end of this game three times
they've patched this game four times for the end of the game this is gonna be the one
he hates us he hates this game he hates everything no it's just it's just having to
fly through the bramble place again and get eaten by a fucking monster kind of sucks you're not
gonna actually kill me again all right is autopilot gonna kill me here autopilot was going really
really fast and it was gonna go right into the sun all right can i not make it like 30 for 30
landing right on the equator that would be great if i that would be fantastic get me the fuck out
of this boat all right now i got another minute or two it's the one after the sun
uh who's your favorite girl from what love lied i don't i don't know what that is i'm gonna say
i'm gonna just say um all right let's get it first try let's get the hell out of this
and then put this thing in and then i also need to type in the code so what's the code
don't worry about the code i have to write this code down don't i which one's broken come on
where's the mechanic where i can smash my fucking head into the wall and have
10 minutes go by okay let's go so have we confirmed red then white then red or white then red then
white because there's two fake ones yes i know put it on all right come on let's go technically
either will work the white one avoids the fish okay here we go where's my ship where is it
far away right here okay coordinates set them set them here we go this is the one
we're going white first and then i'm going to try to float gracefully into red going too slow
the one time that i'm going too slow we're going red first and then we're going to gracefully
float into you guys told me let's go just i'm not looking at chat no more chatting no more
chatting no more chatting no more chatting no more chat for me oh my fucking god i gotta make
it a good shot red but there's a fucking there could be a fish right there there's a fish
next to me or something there's a fish i can't move there's a fish don't pump them i have to
bump anybody don't pump anybody okay there's the vessel 1.2 kilometers that way don't fucking
floor it no how much time do i have anybody have any ideas like 10 seconds 30 like 10 minutes
one minute five minutes floor it i can't floor it i can't floor i can't flour it there's everywhere
i don't know where to go i can't floor it i'm going too slow i can't floor it i can't
or you're a coward floor it i motherfuck i can't floor it you're gonna run out of time i'm gonna
i have to move a little bit is it safe here fish here fish here fish pull the fish here nope
No fish here, there's no fish here.
Floor it, floor it, floor it.
Get in, get in, and just go and type in the code.
What's the code?
Am I in it?
I'm like tilted.
No, no, no, no, wrong way, wrong way.
There it is, there it is.
Ah!
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Put it in, put it in, put it in, put it in, put it in,
put it in, put it in, put it in, put it in, put it in,
put it in, put it in, put it in, put it in, put it in.
Okay, slow down, whoa, Betsy.
Slow down, put it in.
I can't see you.
Now is not the time for the, you would have to,
what the fuck is going on right now?
Is there any?
Quartets.
Okay, quartets, R.
Is that it?
That's it, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah?
How do I say yes?
How do I accept?
Put it in the bottom left.
Go down to the, then to the right.
This next one is, oh my God, here, here, here, here.
Here, confirm.
Last one is all fucked up.
Last one's all fucked up.
Let me get it right.
Bottom left corner, bottom left corner.
Up, around the whole thing, down.
Looks like we made it, excellent job.
You finally found the core,
meaning the eye of the universe.
I might not have time, I don't care about jokes.
I might actually not have time for this.
How are this?
What is that?
That's the sun.
Oh, it's those rocks, it's the quantum rocks.
Why is this thing making human noises?
What are you doing?
Oxygen refueling.
Ah, I'm doing that, you're trying to block me.
Okay, there's an opening up here.
What?
Go down the toilet?
Can I stand on this?
Connection lost.
Um, fuck.
I just jump in it?
Wait.
Imagine if I died.
I would fucking laugh so hard.
I think I can climb that.
Hold on, I can get there from here.
Oh, oh, it goes upside down.
Me and my custom switch remote.
One of my Joy-Cons, the right Joy-Con.
Brought it this far.
Wink, we're literally at the fucking big reveals.
Child's Adventures was founded by Feldspar,
Goss and Slade and Hornfels to explore
the solar system at the end of the universe.
The Nomai never got to see it for themselves,
but thanks to their efforts and technology,
a hearthene was able to reach the eye of the universe.
At the end of its lifespan,
our sun collapsed on its own gravity
and then exploded in a violent supernova.
You're really fucking ruining this ending, aren't you?
The Nomai who came to our solar system
were following a signal from the eye of the universe.
It perished when the interloper arrived,
bringing with it the deadly substance
we call the ghost matter
that flooded the entire solar system
almost instantly and without warning.
Missed the plaque.
Of all the life forms who will perish
in the oncoming death of the universe,
we will miss the anglerfish the least.
I mean, fairly rude.
Hornfels observations.
This is incredible.
At first I thought the points of light
in this image were stars, but they're not.
They're galaxies.
And this image covers just a tiny patch of the whole sky,
which means the universe contains
at least a thousand times more galaxies
than we previously thought.
I think I need to sit down.
This is odd.
According to my redshift calculations,
every single galaxy in this image is moving away from us.
In fact, the farther away a galaxy is,
the faster it appears to be moving away.
Almost as if the entire universe is expanding.
But that's true.
Was everything closer together in the past?
And how far back can we extrapolate?
Did the universe have a beginning?
Ow!
I'm just in a forest now.
That's pretty, yeah.
I was planning, I hear somebody playing something.
What's over there?
It's a blue.
When do I get to go home?
This is a dinosaur track.
A quantum campfire?
Did I just spit that into my helmet?
Hi, Phil, whatever your name is.
Esker, do you hear music?
Did I be hearing music?
Is somebody in here?
Gather, I have a banjo.
I guess I'm gonna bring it back to you.
You can have this.
You're here.
It's not quite time yet.
I'm pretty sure we'll need the others for this next part.
We'll need, you know, everyone.
Don't rush, take your time.
It might not even exist here.
All right, I'm gonna fucking quantum yeet
these motherfuckers out of here in a second.
Here we go.
Hi, can I die here?
Can I die here?
I don't get it.
Why am I gathering all these random people?
Feldspar, Hatchling, you found me.
Nice to have company around a campfire, isn't it?
Go on, get the others.
Wouldn't you want them?
I wouldn't want them to miss it out.
What the fuck did I just get?
It was Santa Claus.
Stars are beautiful, weren't they?
Even if our star is what ultimately killed us.
I'll wait here, remember them while you gather everybody.
What are you guys looking at?
Okay, you're building a skeleton ladder.
What did you gather?
Mask, zoo.
Hypothesis, everyone must be here.
Once they arrive, I believe we'll be ready.
I'm gonna go to the other side of the ladder.
Glad you remembered me.
Collecting all my friends.
Quiet shade across old bark in the ancient glade.
It's always dark.
Okay, is that everybody?
That's everybody.
There ain't nobody else.
What do you say, time buddy?
Ready to start the music?
Yeah, this should be cool.
Get it going, play.
Conscious observers enter the eye.
I wonder what happens now.
Is it time to find out?
Not yet.
They all play together.
They've been playing the same songs in random places,
but it all matches up.
Into the fire.
Really burning.
Let's find out.
This song is new to me, but I'm honored to be a part of it.
You made a fucking party balloon.
I believe we've reached the end of our journey.
All that remains is to collapse
the innumerable possibilities before us.
Your curiosity friend, let's find out.
Cut a little close, don't you think?
Well, it worked out all right in the end, I suppose.
I hope there are beasties in the next one.
How long has it been since I got to make music
with everyone around Campfire?
I'm really happy we're all here.
Yet if it's over now, I had a good time learning,
but I think the rules are about to change.
I learned a lot by the end of everything.
Past is the past now, but that's okay.
It's never really gone completely.
Future is always built on the past,
even if we won't get to see it.
Still, it's time for something new.
Time for something new.
We're just going into the light, apparently.
Okay, so we went, we blew up,
restarted the universe, rebirthed the whole universe.
We just made a new, yeah, just make a new one.
That was pretty crazy ending sequence.
That was kind of all over the place.
That was really good.
You wanted to YouTube it.
No, I just didn't wanna fucking keep failing.
How would I have ever YouTubed that?
We would have watched somebody else stream the game.
What are your first impressions?
I love time travel.
That's a really cool concept.
I feel like this is one of those games
that I'm gonna wanna go read the Reddit or the Wikipedia
and just kind of reprocess everything
and have people tell me how cool everything is.
There's still things I didn't do, yeah.
I can see why people say this is one
of their favorite games last year.
I can understand it.
Makes sense.
Pretty unique.
No, I only got frustrated at like two parts.
The sand taking a long time was always,
no, that started frustrating me a little bit.
Hates the sand.
This was a college project.
Was this actually a college project?
Wait, what?
No, there's like 500 people on this game.
It's not a college.
I thought like, wait, did an entire college make this?
Every student apparently had something to do with it.
Started as a college project.
That was really, really cool.
I'm glad I experienced it.
You were so angry, you had a zit pop on its own.
Explain the story.
Sure.
There was this civilization of people
that wanted to find as much knowledge as they possibly could.
They came, well, while they were doing research
and they ended up on this galaxy,
they figured out that, uh-oh, this sun's going to explode.
This sun's gonna supernova and we're all dead.
We gotta find a way to try to,
we gotta make a way to stop it.
So they get together and they have a bunch of people
that are working on projects.
And then one of those people figures out,
dude, there's a comet here that's killing everybody.
And they all die from the comet.
And then you come in and you have to pick up the pieces
and solve the mystery that they left behind
as to why this super omega wrong.
Well, here's why this game's kind of hard to understand.
Because there's no one, two, three, four, or five
sequences or anything like that,
you can get this game's story like two, six, one, three, five.
So you can, wait, 14.3 billion years later.
I mean, you're also telling me to explain
an incredibly complicated, complex,
intertwining time travel story after 10 plus hours
sitting on a live stream talking to you guys.
I'm a little fried.
What was that that flew by?
That's you overshooting the planet.
That was the best joke of the whole night
and I had nothing to do with it.
All right, that's it.
Out of Wilds in the books in the bag.
All right, let's give it a letter grade.
Think here, this is gonna be tricky.
It's gonna be tricky.
I don't think this is an A plus.
Nope, I don't think so.
I'm not sure this is an A either.
I don't think this is a, I don't think this is a B.
A plus, I don't think so.
No, no, I'm not talking about going down.
Like, oh, I don't think there's just a C.
It's a C minus, no, no, no.
That's not, I'm saying I don't,
you're misconstruing what I'm saying.
I'm gonna give it a B plus.
I'm gonna give this an 89.
Could've been a 90, could've been 89.
What would I dock points for?
You don't have to care what other things.
Give us your own score, 89.
What am I comparing it to?
I don't know.
Well, if you have a 10, you have a 10 point skill.
10 is the best game I've ever played in my life.
10 is the best thing you've ever done in your life.
A 10 out of 10.
Metacritic gave this an 85.
Yeah, but that's from a million different places.
89 out of 100 is,
I tell everybody I know that this was worth playing
and you should play it and it was great.
But for me, when you climb into like the 90s,
like 90, 91, 92, 93,
like for instance, last year,
this came out last year.
Resident Evil 2 for me was like a 95.
So an 89, that's very close.
Being my favorite game that came out last year.
Imagine being so dumb that you compare this
to Resident Evil 2.
What?
I didn't, wait, when did I say,
you know my favorite part is the zombies?
I said Resident Evil 2 was a 95 for me
and that was my favorite game of last year.
So a game that came out last year as well that's an 89
is pretty damn close to my favorite game
that came out last year is what I'm trying to say.
What's a 10 out of 10?
Team Fortress 2.
And this game was not as good as TF2.
Oh, fuck.
Okay, I can only be a dick for so long
before I have to fucking stop.
All right, so that was very, very good.
I am happy I played it.
It was a great recommendation.
I'm glad I played it.
It was very good.
Where's Bloodborne on that scale?
98.
Bloodborne is in 98.
It's only two basis points,
two points are taken off because it's 30 FPS.
If that game is 60 FPS, it's 100.
All right, we're gonna be doing Tony Hawk tomorrow,
Tony Hawk Underground.
Should be a lot of fun.
That was Outer Wilds.
It was a very, very nice game.
So good in fact that it was an 89.
It was a B plus slash A minus.
That means it was very fucking good.
Don't even try it, Jeremy.
You can't do that.
What would you give Simpsons hit and run?
Oh, that's easy.
Probably a four or five.
Somewhere like a 4.8 out of 100.
No, out of 10.
No, 48 out of 100.
Ooh, the vibrations.
You guys are killing me.
What would I give Jump King?
I don't think you can even rate Jump King.
Jump King is like going and riding a ride at Disneyland.
You know what I mean?
It's not like I feel like I can't even rate that game.
Like you ride a ride at Disney and you're like,
oh, I've rid that ride.
I guess cool.
I can't score that game.
You just jump into walls and scream.
Like I can't even score it.
That was an experience.
It wasn't really a video game that I'm going to play.
I experienced that game.
I wouldn't even call it a video game.
I would call it just like a simulation
for your brain to get angry.
It's not even a game.
What would I give Mario Tennis?
A six.
What do I give Cuphead?
87, too short.
Kana zero.
70, 80, no.
79, too short.
Any more?
No more heroes.
No more heroes on Wii or no more heroes the way I played it.
The way I played it on both.
A Wii, it's like a seven one or like a six eight
because the game runs like shit.
It's like a solid like 78 or like 79 the way that I played it.
I would give it, I would give it up now.
No, it deserves an 80.
It does.
It deserves like an 80s flat, just like a B minus.
Nancy Drew.
All right, we're done.
We're not doing this anymore.
I'm going, I'm going to leave.
But if I had to give Nancy Drew a score, 95, 94?
Yeah, 94.
And then, okay, good night.
All the Drew crew, good night.
We'll see you later.
Okay, now that they probably clicked the X
because a lot of them just definitely were leaving.
It's like a six.
No, it's like a four and a half.
We got to keep the Drew crew going though.
We can't just tell them that there's the game
that they love is a six.
Although, yes, you can.
Yes, you can, Jeremy.
I do it all the time.
Rating stuff.
I give it a nine.
All right, let's do the bits.
See you tomorrow for Tony Hawk if you're leaving.
Let's get through this.
Bob Boy, thanks for the 1500 bits.
Thank you, Bob Boy.
Half-Life series free until the release of Half-Life Alex.
And you claim to play Half-Life Alex the day it comes out.
Plus the developers of Half-Life Alex
recommending you play Half-Life series
to get a grip on the story.
Will you play the Half-Life series?
I've played Half-Life one already.
I've played Half-Life two.
I know the story.
I already know this stuff.
Tell us the story.
No, I'm not gonna rifle off all the story beats
for Half-Life one and two.
Somebody might not have played it yet.
Doesn't know.
You're a scientist and you push a crystal into,
you're working on a project.
You're a scientist working on a project
and you're trying to reach to find out as much as you can
because you're curious.
And something about the sun is gonna explode.
The sun is gonna explode.
In Half-Life, that's what they know for certain.
So Gordon and a few others get together
and they try to figure out a way
to make the supernova not happen.
They end up dying.
And then you play as the gameplay character
who they named the G-Man.
You walk around, you get a stick,
you get a red crowbar.
It's a great, it's a really great game.
And then there are these bugs
that fucking drink your brain and shit.
I know what they are.
They called, what are they called?
The ambassadors or something.
They, I know what I'm talking about.
What a great story.
Dude, just like, just explain the story to me.
All right, let's keep going.
No, I'm not gonna play Half-Life on stream.
I'm not gonna do it.
LMMan, thanks for the thousand bits.
Dermot, you are the son of sons.
Thank you.
Thanks for the thousand bits.
LMMan again, Dermot, you're the best.
You're the only streamer I donate to.
I hope these bits will feed your rats.
Thanks for the 500 bits and the thousand bits.
I will feed my rats that I eventually might own.
Thank you though.
Thank you SuperBruce for the five community subs
fitting 300 bits.
I just remembered you said you were gonna rename
phylactery lich to phylactery 50.
How the fuck did you not think of phylactery rich?
That's pretty good too.
That's also pretty good too.
Attack of the Hank, thanks for five subs.
Daddy Umbra gave 350 plus dollars tonight in bits.
35,000 bits.
Thank you, Daddy Umbra.
Ridiculous, insane amounts of money.
Kazzy, five community subs.
Thank you, Kazzy.
Taylix, thanks for the 500 bits.
I dropped out of college a few months ago
and I feel like shit.
Can I get some words of encouragement?
He is the founder of this game's development team.
Masioka was an actor for the TV show Heroes.
It's fucking awesome.
Well, the only thing I can really say to you is
college is not for everybody.
And hopefully, it seems that you may have
figured out that already.
But you don't necessarily have to.
You don't have to do that.
And I know a lot of people think that college
is kind of like the end of the world,
like the end all be all, like you have to do this.
But there's a lot of different things you can try.
You can do trades.
You can...
I know like some people study foreign languages
and they teach, they teach English.
You can do that.
Trades pay a lot of fucking money.
They really do.
Some of my closest friends in my whole life
are in the trades.
And they do really, really, really fucking well.
So I really hope you don't think that
potentially being out of college is
something that should be a huge, huge, huge problem.
It's just not for everybody.
It just isn't.
Go to streamer school.
Well, that's not real.
Yeah, it's about finding something that works for you.
Find something that works for you.
You might not need to go to school for it.
Well, I mean, a typical four year college.
So I wouldn't worry too much about it.
Plus, you can always try again later.
If you really want to study something in college,
you can try it again another time.
I don't know how old you are, but if you're still young,
some people, it doesn't matter.
Some people go to college in their 30s.
And that's fine.
That's all right.
I wish you the best though.
Thanks for the 500 bits.
If you're a raw host, thanks for the 500 bits.
Hey German, I just want to thank you for being there for me.
I've been watching you for over seven years now.
Since then I finished two schools,
got through a lot of stuff and with all your help.
Right now I'm being challenged more than ever.
So here I am seeking happiness with you.
Thank you for everything you have done for me over the years.
It's a very long time to be watching this channel.
I sometimes I assume people will watch it
and kind of get bored after a few months or like a year
and then be like, all right, that was cool for a while.
But some of you guys have stuck around
for a insanely long time,
almost 10 years for a lot of you guys.
And that's crazy.
I'm shocked, I'm happy.
And I can't even tell you how I'm glad you still think
this is a fun place to still be.
And any of your challenges going on right now,
Veraus, I hope you get through them.
Take it slow, stay focused, and do you.
Help, I'm stuck here.
Don't worry, I'll take care of that.
Unmod, demod, purge, ban, remove founder.
Can I be a mod?
Nah, sorry.
We also had Squishington, thanks for the 300 bits.
Love you, German, thanks for always making my day better.
Thanks for making my day better
because you hanging out here allows me
to continue to do this and allows me
to make enough monetary compensation
to do something like this for a living, which is ridiculous.
So thank you for sitting here and watching this
because you're making my day better, immensely.
He's in it for the fucking money.
That's true.
Without people watching, without people here,
and I don't know, I don't, who knows how long
I would have been able to do it.
Remember, I'm starting to get a little older
and I'm not so sure, you know,
let's say rewind the clock 10 years.
If my YouTube channel didn't really start gaining viewership
when it did, I'm not sure I would have spent
too much more time on it.
Maybe after like a couple of years,
like two or three, four years, maybe it'd be like,
all right, I'm getting, I'm starting to be,
I'm gonna be 30, so I'm gonna try to figure something out.
You know what I'm saying?
So people being here, people watching,
and the views and the subscriptions on YouTube, I mean,
and into Twitch, that's,
you've allowed me to continue to do this.
You've allowed me to make fun what I do for work.
You know what I mean?
Trying to just have as much fun as I can
with as many people as possible.
You've done, that's what you have done.
Don't ever forget that.
It's like I said, the closer that I was moving
into like my early 30s, it's, you know,
I'm like, all right, what do I wanna do now?
And that still might happen.
I don't have a crystal ball.
I don't know how long Twitch and being
an online content creator or in quotes,
an online entertainment influencer in any quote.
I don't know.
I don't know what the future holds.
So I'm trying to keep an open mind about it
and just kind of go with the flow and see what happens.
Somebody was saying, hey, about the college thing.
Like Taylix said about the college thing.
I mean, I might be in my early 40s and be like,
all right, now what am I doing now?
You got plenty of time.
Produces, I screwed up your name again.
And I'm probably gonna get corrected for it.
But it was Produces Asen and I know it's wrong.
I already know it's wrong.
Thanks for the six community subs a little earlier.
Hawkwing, thanks for 500 bits, Producesen, there it is.
Thank you Hawkwing for the 500 bits.
Jerma, why do you hate this game?
It makes me sad, it's my favorite game.
Why do you hate me?
What?
Jerma, why do you hate this game?
It makes me sad, it's my favorite game.
Why do you hate me?
When did I say I hate this game?
I just gave it an 89.
That's a hater grade.
Wait, hold on.
Am I under the assumption that any game that's under a 90
is a game that the person hated?
Isn't that reserved for a three?
I would give The Surge a three.
I would give, I mean, that's,
so you're talking about going from a three to an 8.9.
Giving The Surge a three is generous.
Future Gamer, thanks for the 250.
Will you also be doing the Get Well Soon card
during the Diablo stream?
I talked about it earlier, yesterday I think,
and in the pre-stream chat as well,
but I'm gonna do the card alone.
I'd rather experience that by myself.
I feel like that's more appropriate for me.
It lets me sit there and take it in by myself.
So I will not be doing it on stream.
Almost midnight Pacific.
Yeah, I mean, this is a long one.
I knew I wanted to get it done tonight.
We'll be back tomorrow afternoon, Tony Hawk.
Dark Soul, thanks for the 250.
Any anticipated VR stuff or is that still off the table?
I also now get why you only did four to five hour streams
because boy, does this motion sickness just lie inside you
and come on instantly.
Yeah, being in that VR headset
and broadcasting is, it just, it takes a lot out of you.
Any VR stuff?
Kinda, yeah.
Besides Half-Life Alex, obviously.
It's not that Walking Dead game came out.
It kinda looks cool.
Boneworks looks awesome.
I really wanna play it.
There's at least two or three titles that I know
that I wanna play.
Tarisov, thanks for the 400 bits.
Appreciate it.
Let's get the credits rolling.
We're nearing the end here.
We'll bump you, just make sure.
We hand that guy.
Hold on, let me just get it on the screen.
It should be there.
In three, two, one.
There it is.
Thanks to all the subs.
The oil that continues to move the machine.
Appreciate it.
Thank you guys for letting me do what I do.
I know maybe not every stream is your favorite.
Maybe not every stream is my favorite, right?
Some streams are my favorite thing in the world.
Some streams are your favorite things in the world.
But at the end of the day, thanks for letting me do this.
No, not this one.
Not this one.
This was fun.
These last two streams,
I've had a lot of fun playing this fucking game.
I'm just saying in general.
In general.
We have a game in 89.
But all of a sudden, he's talking about Asura's wrath.
God damn it.
All right, let me be real with you.
This is the end of the stream.
Half the audience is gone.
Let me just be real with you guys.
People fucking did not like that game.
Can we be completely real here?
People were not happy that I was playing that game.
People were like, like losing their minds.
But we're probably gonna finish it.
If this time after Diablo II, I'm gonna try to play it.
So again, you know, some of your streams
might not be your favorite streams or your favorite games.
But thanks for continuing to come back
and continuing to talk and continuing to hang out
and still having fun as I am.
We had a box box raid earlier for a shitload of people.
I don't know if you're still here.
Some of you guys might still be here.
Thanks box box.
You're awesome.
Thank you.
Really appreciate that.
Big Applewood, 500 bits.
No message.
A Skedongler gave a thousand bits, $10.
Today we were all told to write down the name
of someone who we look up to
and put it up on the board at my school.
I racked my brain for a while
and you always ended up on the top of my list.
We were then told to find a way to thank that person.
So here I am.
I honestly think you're the most selfless human being.
I want to grow up to be as humble and kind as you.
You're such an inspiring dude.
Hope you know.
Love you, Jare Bear.
We tease you because we love you.
That's something I never thought I would ever hear
anybody say when I was, you know, like 16.
Knowing that that happened is just,
I hope you being influenced positively.
Regardless of talking shit, fucking around, making jokes.
However you view these streams,
I really hope that you take something good from here.
Something.
And not everything has to be super duper positive
and perfect and fantastic and oh my God, it's so good.
Everything's perfect, everything's positive.
But at the end of the day,
I really hope you look back on this and you go like,
oh, that was like actually a really kind of fun time.
I met some people, met some friends.
It was a place to hang out.
It was something to watch, something to think was fun, right?
Like I hope at the end of the day, you do think that.
I never want to be somebody you look back on
and be like, yeah, that sucked.
That guy sucks.
That community was dumb.
So I'm happy that people are not doing that.
And they're sharing stories like this.
Thank you so much for the $10.
Means a lot, it really does.
Hey, Greco Twitch, thanks for a thousand bits.
No message, just a thousand bits.
Just $10 deposited into my twitch.tv bank account.
Bonjour Tristan, thanks for the 500 bits.
Hey Jerma, I just wanted to share an idea.
I often watch your streams and VODs while cooking.
I'm thinking it'd be funny
if you did a follow along cooking vid
for a really hard dish.
Then we could all share our results together
in the sub or something.
Anyways, just a thought and thanks for the streams.
Whenever I watch your videos, I pog my pants.
Oh, that's, thank you.
There's cooking stuff that's starting to be worked on.
It's just kind of weird.
We'll see.
Zero giblets, thanks for the 500 bits.
Hey Jerma, I haven't given anything in a while,
so I figured I should show some love.
Keep on keeping on.
Oh, and when you address my message in chat,
among the many others,
it's like the lucky maiden in the crowd
whose favor the night chooses.
Thanks.
Thank you.
I appreciate it.
Hey Gondolaine, thanks for the 250.
Hey Jerbo, it's been a year
since your famous 700,000 game stream.
I think it's about time you give us a prequel stream,
where you stream the games that started it all.
These are a collection of really shitty games
and these are unique,
unlike the 700,000 games by Viva Media.
It'd be worthy for a fuckface shovelware stream.
This is called 555 Games, XP Championship Edition.
All right, fine, yeah, I'll buy it.
I'll buy it right now.
All right, yeah, sounds good.
Hopefully there's a super frog in it.
I'll see you guys tomorrow for Tony Hawk.
Take care, buddy.
Two more bits to do.
I know it's another late one.
We've done a few late long streams this week,
but remember, I'm not gonna be here
for almost a full week next week.
So I'm happy to do four or five
of these long streams in a row.
Cornflake, thanks for the 500 bits.
Small brain streamer, you just don't get it.
I get it.
I have read countless explanations on Reddit.
I am, that's it, they trailed off.
There's nothing there.
Hey, all the chemists, thanks for the 500 bits.
I dare you to read the Reddit summary on stream.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Somebody might have clicked on the stream
and not played the game and they just get like a TLDR
and the whole game's ruined.
Cap'n spurt dick, thanks for the 500 bits.
I said the dick part of that, so emphasized.
It's been almost 11 hours.
Give me just a little slack.
They just say Jeremy.
Jeremy who?
Jeremy me?
Or Jeremy you?
See you guys tomorrow, have a good night.
Tony Hawk's Underground tomorrow, have a good night.