Hello, it's Traveler. I got you. What the hell is your character? What's your name? What is your name?
You look like Elmo. Don't do that. I'm gonna die now. Yeah, I'm gonna bleed to death now. Did you slice him?
Yeah, he sliced me. I'm dead. I'm just looking at the screen right now. It's just 19, 18, 17, 16.
Hold on, I can do something. Hold on, hold on. I have a... You better hurry up, whatever the hell
you're gonna do. You! Oh, you're a zombie? Well, hello zombie. I've got pocket knife. All right,
let's also save all the looting and stuff for when we actually meet up. We just get like a melee
weapon. I broke my leg by the way. I was climbing, I climbed up this ladder to try to find like just
like a weapon and I slid down and broke my like femur. So I'm gonna have like a bro, a handsaw.
Good, here we go. Come on! I've got legitimately like 30 zombies on me. Yeah, there's so many.
Get away from me, back! Back, you vile spawn of Satan! These guys are gonna kill me. Why does the
handsaw suck? Holy shit, this item is terrible! I'm dead. Well, you're trying to kill zombies
with a saw. What do you expect? I think I'm at pizza again. Oh, there's a lot of zombies here.
Yeah, just be careful. It's out, it's out, it's out. No gas. Oh, that one does not have any gas.
I'm at pizza again. All right, well you are currently getting swarmed. Yeah, no joke.
Don't die. I haven't got hit yet. Oh, that's a fast one. That's a fast one. He's fast.
Where's the katana man? Yeah, you have to run to me. I'm running to you. Just kill the fast one
behind me. That's it. Just backpedal, backpedal while you do it. Okay, I don't think I want to
do that. Oh, sledgehammer. All right guys, we finally met up three friends. What do you guys
want to do? What the hell? Is that a door? The shield stay on your side. Your arms are just
coming through. Hey, dude, it took us seriously like an hour and 15 minutes to find each other.
Do not just to start attacking. Are there no headlights on this car? Oh, there we go. All
right, let's do it. If you turn around, you can see Jarvan sitting in the back. That's funny.
I'm going to sit in the back with him. He looks lonely. All right, I have no idea where I'm going,
by the way. Sit back here with me. Hey, is there a military base? No, I did not mean to do that.
I didn't mean to do that. Did you hit him? I'm not going to tell you what happened,
because I don't want this to turn bad, so no. I'm trying to do it. How do I hit you?
You can't. Only I can, apparently. All right, let's go. You can shoot out of the windows.
How? If you have guns. I don't know. Can I shoot him in the back seat? Don't even tell me.
Seriously, don't. Don't even seriously. Hey! Oh, you killed me.
Why? I didn't think I was going to instantly kill you. I'm crying right now.
I really didn't think that was going to instantly kill you. Instantly. Dude, I thought it was just
going to be like when I hit him, it was just like boop. A zombie. Oh, no. Whoa. Whoa.
What the hell, dude? He wasn't even in here. What happened? He's dead now. I almost died.
Snuck up on him when I was looting. I took some vitamins. Did they give you help?
No. Oh, I guess maybe they do. Hey, Jeremy, get out of that building real quick. That car's
about to explode. What car? No, that car. What are you grunting for? There's so many zombies.
You better get out of that car. I'm out. It's going to blow you up. You're still too close,
probably. Can you kill this guy? I only have 35%. There's bandages in here. There's vitamins
in here. All right, let's get them. They've trapped me. No, I can't get in there. Don't worry. I got
you. I got you. Jeez. Punch him. Punch him. Punch him. There's an island with a helicopter down
there. Oh, you're in the island with the downed helicopter? That's what I've been saying. Wait,
let me look through my binoculars. I see him. I'm so glad we found him. Italics, land ho. Whoa.
All right, you guys don't do it. I think I found food and I think I'm holding it in my hand now.
But I think I want to eat it. You're going to give that food to me? I'm at 18%. I want to put
that back down to zero. I have 85%. You're dropping that food. Put that food down. Put it down.
Come on. I will catch up to you. We got a runner. I'm at 90. I can't believe you ate that food.
He dropped it. He dropped it. It's on the ground.