Hello, hello. How you doing? Welcome, everybody. A little late. Maybe a few minutes.
Vinny and I want to make sure that we could get in the game together. Multiplayer. We did. We are good
to go. Welcome to another stream. Give you the game plan today. Part one of the game. Bro, you fell
off. What? What are you talking about? All right. How did I even read that? That was impossible to
read. But yeah, today we're going to be doing some sponsored segment of the stream. This part here is
sponsored by EA. We're playing Wild Hearts. Looks pretty damn fun. Vinny and I. Vinny is joining us
today too. Hashtag ad. Should be fun. Do you read messages that have resident sleeper in it?
Every single one of them. And it hurts every single time. Yeah. After this, we're going to be moving to
the that last hero nostalgia. Should be a fun night. Looking forward to it. If you don't know
what Wild Hearts is, it's in that monster hunting kind of monster hunter world where it's kind of
a monster hunting strategy action game. So if you liked Monster Hunter, you probably would like this
too. That world of this type of hunting game. We're going to do face cam today. If you're good,
I will turn face cam on if you're good. Everybody's like, oh shit, everybody be good.
Everybody be really good today. Everybody has to be so good because then we're going to see his face.
I also like, okay, I need to like turn my face cam on at some point just to prove that I'm
I'm not like covered in bandages or something, right? Like I've seen the concerns and let me
tell you, no, I, I'm, I'm fine. I'm not bald. I heard the theory that, oh, I know why he doesn't
have the face cam on anymore. It's because he's bald and he went bald and he doesn't want to show
us. Nope. We're good. But yeah, thank you EA for sponsoring the stream. Let's get started. Wild Hearts.
Vinny, how are you? Like, oh, I forgot to unmute. Hey, hey, hey, hey, how are you? I'm good. Um,
we were talking about mitochondria. Really? Yeah. What about mitochondria? It's just cool.
So, um, so, so yes. Uh, how are you? I'm good.
All right. We need to get, we need to bring people up to speed of what happened.
We did the tutorial already. We wanted to get right into the goddamn game. You understand?
So we have not picked weapons. I know there are weapons. I think we're still in the tutorial.
Yeah. I think that's correct. We just looks like, yeah, we just like rescued someone and we just
set up camp and this is the earliest we could play online together. So we're not sure where this is
going to go. But, um, at the moment, I guess we both have long katanas and that's how we will kill
this rat. And oh, you, spoiler. Oh, right. Sorry. A rat broke through this and you didn't get to see
it. So we have to go hunt this rat. It was actually really cool. Very sad you didn't see it. This game
has, um, like a kind of a weird game play mechanic too, where you can like conjure like crates. Have
you done, like, did you see that? Yeah. Yeah. You could, you can make, right. Watch this.
Yeah. All right. Check this out. Yeah. I have to stand up first. Ready? Yeah. All right. Now
watch this. Where'd you go? I don't even know where you went. Oh, wow. That's amazing.
Wow. Oh, sorry. I did it. I just like freaked out. You can like jump off. You build stuff. You can
jump. It seems pretty fun. Yeah. It's like, um, breath of the fork knife.
Something like that. Yeah. We've got to kill, but you know, it looks really cool because I like the
rat. I almost don't want to kill it, but this is kind of the intro monster camp. All right.
Vinny, are you ready? Yeah. Yeah. Let's do this.
What is this? Have you? Rage tail. Get him. Okay. I'm trying. I'm, I'm, I'm pressing the wrong
buttons. Did you ever like play a game a lot and then get used to those buttons and then have to
get used to a whole new set of buttons? Yeah. And your brain doesn't know how to like. Oh,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Ready? Uh, use your, uh, your, hold on. Ready? All right. That's
actually pretty cool. We do it. Uh, I don't think I did a very good job, but I heard some
weird noises. Yeah. You can, you can jump off these crates. That does a lot of damage. You can,
you can lock on to, you probably figured this out already, but yeah. How high can you put the
crate? Three at the moment. Maybe there's like a, oh, there's just like fucking everywhere. Can
you get the tail? Like, can we, can we do that? I wonder. I hope so. Cause you played other similar
such unnamed monster games. Yeah. Monster Hunter has that in it too. Does the monster
hunter have that? Yeah. Wait, you gotta get the flowers. And if you, you get low on health,
press up, I think on the D pad to heal. I wonder if that's consumable. What is like the rat's tail
or. No, no, no. Like the heels. Oh, it is. It is. Yeah. There's like, can you eat the tail?
Yeah. That's what I thought. No, you can. I'm going to die. There's like, there's like these
healing plants. Here we go. E3 can play commentary. I got your back chef. I've got you back. Stacking
crates. Crates now quick to a barrel roll. Oh, there's crates over here. Yeah. There you go.
Oh, sick. I just did a hundred damage. Get it. Now it's now it's time. Now it's time.
Right ahead. Now it's time. Now it's time. I think you can charge swings too. Oh, you can.
What do you do? Do you do ranged or do you do like melee? In let's say generic monster game
where you hunt said monsters, whatever it may be called, I usually go for the switch axe.
I like, I'm a ranged Andy. I like the range stuff. Okay. Yeah. I'm John switch axe then
because I liked ranged in, which one was it? Monster hunter three you, I think it was. And I
did like bow and arrow, but now I do a switch jacks and charge blade. I'm actually curious how
many weapons are in the game. Yeah. I'm kind of, I'm also curious to see if there's anything similar
to the switch acts. Cause that's like, all right, I got to stop doing that. It was like big chunky
weapons. Do I have any heels left? I think I'm out of, you know, I got, I got one more.
You can always like, I think you can also grab more from the environment. Oh, right. Right. Right.
Cool. There's like several just chilling. God damn it. Wrong button. We're going to use the,
the crates more. Yeah, they do. They did a hundred damage earlier from the crates.
Are you fat rolling? I'm fat rolling. Is there such a thing? I will say chat, like the gameplay,
the mechanics of the gameplay feel solid. Yeah. It actually does feel pretty polished in regards
to like hitting the monster in the face. So almost dead. Cool. If you need more healing,
there's like, uh, against the trees, there's like green bulbs. Oh, wait, I only have four more of
these. Uh, you have to collect like dust. There you go. Right there. I get it. These ones. Oh,
yeah. There we go. I don't know how much crafting is a focus of the game. Vinny Vinny. What are you
doing? Oh, oh, sorry. I just got carried away for a second. Yeah. We already made our characters
before I started the stream. Yeah. I barely, I spent three minutes making the character. I
didn't work too hard on it. There's like default plus like three edits. I was good with that.
It's very angry with things bouncing around on its, on its ball. There we go. Oh, there we go.
What'd you just do? Oh, I jumped off the crate. Did a hundred damage. I can't wait to make
by the way Vinny and Jerma were born in the same year. Are we literally 1985? Yeah. Yeah.
Some chat member. Oh shit. Yeah. I didn't know we were that. Yeah. That's cool. Yeah. What,
what month are you? You just had a birthday, right? Uh, no, I'm September. Oh, okay. Boy,
time goes quick. Doesn't it? Time does. I really feel like that's the case though.
2023 feels like it started like a week ago. It's fucked up. Yeah. It's crazy. And like there's
already been like a ton of games to play. I don't even have like time in my life to play this many
video games. All right. Drag over here. I got to land that at least once. I'm doing it again.
Like why did it tail? Oh, there you go. Oh, did you get it? We got it. Nice. I wonder where's the
weak point? I would see the head bulb, big bulb. I'm going for the tail. I've been going for the
tail. I've been trying to get that thing off. Watch out. No big swing. That was a very gamer
watch out of you. I want to see the weapons. I want to get to, I want to, I, I'm very curious.
Yeah, me too. There's actually, this is, this, uh, if you have no weapon on,
you can do like a dash slide is pretty helpful. Oh yeah.
Durham, I think dead. I think we got it. It's like, no, no. Oh, it's still alive. Mad.
It's extra bad. It could spawn a tree. It just got like, do you ever get so angry that you
conjured a tree? I like the fact that you can ride on the ball. That's weird. Maybe it hurts.
I mean, usually it does. Oh my God. I have no Jesus. Oh, I'm unconscious. Yeah. Just
mash, mash buttons. Wait, did you drop something? Someone said, someone said, what the fuck is going
on? Hey, grab, grab. Hey, Dre. Oh, here's an item. Rage tail thing. Just I think you cut it off.
Oh, okay. Okay. Get your head in the game. I know. I know. What does it look like?
We're just a couple of dudes hunting a giant like angry rat.
Those cubes, you just do so much more damage. Yeah, you do. All right. Right in the head.
There you go. Oh, wait, wait, wait. Finish it. Do you want me to do it? You can do it. Yeah,
you do it. Look at your face. I forgot he looks like this. Now stay down. That's it. Why am I
saying this to you? What's the chef cooking up this time? See, that's how you do it.
Why am I saying that stuff? Now stay down. That's it then. There you go.
Let me increase the volume of Jeremy because you can conjure. Wait, can you make,
can we make like a bunch of like, would you like a bunch of like Minecraft piston stuff? Hold on a
minute. Kind of looks like it. This thing's going crazy. Yeah, it just propels you forward.
All right. That's crates. You can, you can jump up. Oh, I gotta get my car. I didn't even get the
car. Is there a car? I think we just got it. Did you get that screen? Did you get a game? Oh,
you did a completed screen with all the. Oh, okay. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. But I didn't see this
stuff because I was, I was looking at the chat. All right. Now we got to make sure the woman back
safe is the woman back at camp is safe. Oh, we have to go back to camp. Yeah. So I see it. It's
the, yeah. The icon. Yeah. It's really, it's convenient when you're a streamer and you can
just blame chat whenever you don't see something. It's like, no, I was looking at chat. You're going
on here. We said I unironically want this game. Yeah. I mean, it seems pretty fun. I like how
everything has to be like, sorry. Everything has some layer of irony on the internet. So it's like,
it's good to clarify just in case, like, you never know when, when there's irony on the internet.
Some people don't use CAPAs. How's performance been? Performance has been pretty good for me.
There's a little bit of slowdown on some of the new loading areas, but at least from what you're
seeing here so far, it's, it seems pretty good. How about you? Yeah. It hasn't, it hasn't been too
bad. I'll tell you what it earlier in the tutorial, I had a couple of spots. There's,
I think there's a big patch on the way to, which that will be nice, but I turned down like one or
two settings and it's been mostly okay. I feel like once it loads a new area, you just run kind
of smooth, but yeah, like, you know, it's a new game. I'm moving, I'm moving around a lot. I mean,
I, I don't seem to have that many issues. Not saying that people don't have issues, right?
So I guess we talk to her. I do have to admit, I skipped a third of the cutscenes. So I kind of know
what's happening. Oh, I skipped all of them. Oh no, because we were like, oh, let's get,
we've got to get in a game together. Let's test the multiplayer.
Mm hmm.
I have like an idea of what's going on. That's my character. Yeah. You look kind of cool.
I guess I was like default, default, default, change one thing. Oh, you did default everything.
Okay. So big monster. Oh, you can see, you can see all of our Tetris pieces.
By the way, your placement of your blocks is fucking awful.
Spread them out a little more moron.
I have to, who? He only came with me because I insisted. Wait.
Well, you can see when I skipped the dialogue. Yeah. Oh, wait, can I, are you skipping her now?
A little bit. Oh, it's a monster. Oh, I just turned the audio off.
Okay. So she's a blacksmith and she can help us get weapons. So we're going to,
we're going to get weapons now, I think. Also, I do have to bring this up because this is,
this is a good feature. You and I are just in the game together. Yeah. You and we don't, I,
I don't, let's see what happens here, but I, we're not, it's not like, oh, we have to join
this lobby and then that lobby. I think we're just in the game permanently. Okay. So, oh yeah,
there, I see you. I see the chef, but I'm like, oh, I have to return to you. So wait, you're not
escorting this person. So, okay. That's interesting. You were at camp while I was doing the cut scene.
Yeah. Wow. So maybe it just puts me at the camp when you're, if a cut scene is activated.
Okay. Hold on. Open your info screen and select. Oh, there's a map. Okay. Turn your face came on.
I told you, if you're good, I'll turn it on. Don't threaten them with a good time. Okay. Here we go.
So you have like a tree, types of Karakuri. You can use the kimono orbs that you obtain by hunting
kimono to awaken new types of Karakuri or strengthen Karakuri you've already awakened.
Knowledge of certain Karakuri cannot be awakened using kimono orbs. Instead, you need a flash of
inspiration in the midst of hunting particular kimono or some other hunting success to unlock
such Karakuri secrets and conjure them for the first time. So there's like a tree. Okay. So this
is the one we've been using. It's massive. If you scroll all the way down, like hold X and scroll
all the way down, it's insane. Oh my God. What is going on? What? I thought that was, it wasn't
repeating. That's a lot of whatever that is. I guess cause this game, it looks like this game's
feature or one of its features to set itself apart is that you can like actually build your camp the
way you want to. Oh yeah. Okay. Cool. So yo, that's a lot. Sugoi.
Make what? Make what? I didn't hear it. Oh, sorry. I think she said bow. Oh, she's gonna take apart
the Katana. Time to choose your weapon. I know I want to switch X. If there's no switch X,
then I'll take the biggest dumbest object I can use. Forging. Have a weapon forged.
Oh man. This is like, look at this. Oh, here they are. Well, we can't get all of them right now.
It's like, I think, I think you have to do some stuff. All right. But what do I want? Katana?
Nodachi, bow, maul, bladed, wagasa. What is that? An umbrella. Yeah. It's an umbrella.
What do you think? What are you into? I'll let you choose first and then I'll just,
I'll choose second because I'm just happy to be here.
I'm just happy to be here. Vinny, you are, you are, you're the best. Thanks man. Well,
I mean, thank you for, you know, getting me the game and stuff. Appreciate it. Vinny's a good dude.
All right. So what do you, I think, should I do the, I usually would probably, I'd go maul.
Either maul or bow. I mean, I'll just, I'll probably do the Nodachi then because it's like a big sword.
I want to be like Cloud from Final Fantasy 7. Maybe I should do. What do I want to do? What
are you guys saying? Wagasa or maul? Can we get a pole? I'll do either one. Looks like you can
already upgrade it too. Once you get your first one, like you have the choice of like the weapon
tree because we killed that rat now and we could use the rats like bones and gore and like organs
and spleen and stuff. Umbrella now, umbrella now. You know what? All right. I'll do, I'll do the
Wagasa. Chat, this is a tough choice. I don't, I don't know which one I want to go. Oh yeah,
we already can do this. All right. Critical master or savage. I don't know what savage is.
Oh goodness. Okay. I don't, this is, this is a lot of options. Yeah, it's, it's skill details. So
savage increases attack. You can press Y. Critical master boosts the chance of critical strike. So
I'm going to go for my critical sword. I don't have the materials to do the other one. So I
think we're both going to do the critical one. Okay. Although you could wait and go,
you could go this other path. There's that left path too. Hey, I want to. Okay. I might as well do
more damage. Okay. I got big sword and then armor too. I don't know if we can make armor.
So yeah, they all have their own individual trees. That's cool. Yeah. I mean, it's nice visually.
I'm going to get, um, the gauntlets. I think this is just teaching us how to do this. Yeah. Very
cool. All right. Let me see your weapon. Ooh. Can you charge it? Big energy. Like I can just like
unleash energy. Wait, I got, I have a hop. That's cool. Umbrella is amazing. Can you,
what happens when you hold a ZR or R2? Like I like spin it. I think it's a block or like a parry.
Okay. Can I charge, let me see if I can charge this. It is a parry. All right. That's cool.
The problem with the problem with me is I keep trying to press R and R2 to attack. Yeah. All the
Elden Ring, all the, every, all the from software games. Yeah. All right. We, um, oh, make a plan
for the hunt around the campfire. You want to make a plan? Yeah. I unlocked something else though.
See if I can figure that out. I unlocked a, um, so we got a drying rack for food. Let's make some
steaks. And I also got a hunting tower that uses celestial thread to seek out kimono in the
wilderness. Sends out pulses from the turret to use as echoes that return the chart. Okay. So we
can find monsters. Okay. So we, when you sit down at the campfire is when you decide on what you
want to do next. Okay. From the map, you can take on quests or travel instantly to camps and other
places out in the wilderness. Quests come about when the people of Minato make requests of you
and your hunting skills. And when there's a kimono thread that needs it. So we can kind of
port around. Some can be taken as many times as you like, right? Okay. So I think there's like
story missions. There's other missions, but I think we can just do it from together from the
campfire. So yeah, I see, I see more rage tales, but, um, I don't know. It's up to you. What do
you want to, you want to go for another rage tale or do you want to, I don't know how we find like
new monsters. I think we can do rage tale again if we want to, but, um, we talked to her for another
one. Yeah. You want to do it? Yeah, let's do it. Actually you might have to do it because you're
the host. Oh, that's right. Okay. So wait, what happens when you, um, do you watch this or you're
just like running around looking at nothing? No, I can see, I can see what you're doing.
Oh, okay. Okay. There's a weapon later in the game that's basically the charge blade
switch axe thing you're looking for. Sick.
The monster design is actually very good.
It looks like they put like truthfully, they put a lot of like budget into making things look cool.
Someone said crisis looks better. What do you know about my brother in crisis? That is a 20
year old game. Somebody just said, what do you know about design? I don't know. I just think
the games, I just play games. I don't know. All right. Saps scourge. So we're going after the
step. Are we, are we prepared? Huh? Um, yeah, I feel like the preparation is, is less than we
would expect maybe, but let me talk to her again. Yeah, it's, I'm ready to rock and roll.
Yeah, we can, we can just start fighting like, do we have to remove these or are they just all
permanently here? They're just still here. Oh yeah. Why are they still here? I think they're
permanent. You have to be very, maybe you can take them down. Do you have enough healing like juice?
Um, wait, if you conjure a hunting tower, you'll be able to detect kimono in the surrounding area.
Yeah, I got one of those in the tower. I, I, I did one of those. That's, uh,
Oh, and I think it wants us to make it. Oh, I can catch the snake. I just caught a snake.
Can't fire. Where's hunting tower? Wait, do you see the enemy?
All right. So the game is telling us to go down the tree in your Karakuri tree and unlock the
hunting tower. It's like a radar. Okay. Cause I, I have the monster on my, uh,
UI. I can see it for the wall too. All right. Um, did you see that little fella? Where?
This little fella here. Oh, I see a friend. Hunter aids. You can enhance them at campfires.
I think those are like cats. Did you collect them? Yeah. I think you, you collect them and then you
can use them to like tank hits from giant rats so that you don't, you don't die. And they do
something like that. Make changes to them. Okay. Cool. I think we have to upgrade our menu at least
down to the tower. How did you know how to do that? In your menu, go to the Karakuri menu.
It's like to the right and then hunting tower. What does this actually do? Field Forge. Um,
Oh, I think we can build stuff out in the wilderness. Okay. That's cool. We can build a
tower here. Yeah. So I guess this, um, seek out kimono in the wilderness. It sounds out pulses
from the turret and uses the echoes that returned to chart the lay of the land. And look, I say,
I think it's like, you can get map reveal with it. Yeah. I, I built one at base and, um,
I'll build another one here and see if this does anything, but it's already in operation. It says,
Oh, there it is. Okay. Yeah. I don't know. So I think, I think this just kind of sits on the map.
Maybe it beeps when, uh, it detects something nearby. Oh, we just follow the thread. If you
hold L two, it just like shows you like a path to the enemy. I got full heels. Okay. There it is.
Is this on iPad? Um, no, it's not. What the fuck is that? Look up. There's two of them. Oh gosh.
Why is there two? Why? Okay. Well, these days monster games need to have at least two.
All right, let's go. Oh boy. I wonder how the parry work. It said we can request assistance.
I guess we could just get like randos to jump in. I'm imagining it's probably that.
All right. I'm going to build a spring and see what this is.
I hope that other thing doesn't. The other thing is still over there. It's hiding.
Oh boy. Are you dead? No, almost. I'm just healing. What are we thinking? What are we thinking?
I'm just going to put shit everywhere. Head empty. All right. I might be like annoying,
but whatever. No, no, no. I'm trying. I do it. You put everything everywhere.
I just did like 150 damage or more to this thing.
Ooh. All right. That's funny. Use a spring to dodge. Oh, you put these around to not get.
Okay. I get it. I get it. I get it. So you put them in places where you know you can dodge.
Trying to charge my attack. Yeah. Oh, some of the sack blue.
It's fine. I do like a weird dive. I would go straight down on the crown of my head.
I kind of float in the air. Also. Yeah, dude. The amount of damage you do from a tower is insane.
It's unbelievable. It's so good. All right. I figured out how this thing works.
You want to be in the air. Wait, is it gone? Wait, wait. I think you might've,
I think you, you cut something off over here. Did I? Okay. Hang on.
Zap Scourge Amber. I just picked up a weird thing that allows me to build more stuff. I think.
I don't know. Hold R T and X to build your meter faster and then release R T for a charged attacks
as a chat member. Helpful help. Today we have helpful chat members. Like I didn't, I didn't know.
So wait, where did, where did that monster go? All right. We got a marker. Yeah. We got a marker.
There's a rage tail behind us, but yeah, let's just mark it. Oh no. Oh, that's a turtle. I chat.
I get it. You're trying to get me to say the forbidden words. I'm not going to say them
just like wiped his eyes. Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, look, look, look. Yes. What? This is one of those
friends. Oh, okay. I'll grab one. Okay. We need the bear at the camp logic to train and see all the
combos you can do. Interesting. That's, that's the way you work it. That's the way you go for it.
Put down some of those, those tools and just bounce off them and jump in the air and stuff.
Okay. Oh, it rolls around. Oh, I got to collect that. Wrong thing.
Dude. Yeah. You fly in the air. I like that. This weapon is actually pretty fun.
More stuff rolls around, comes around. I guess so. Yeah. That's sort of fun too.
What's the thing around it on his left leg? Like a blue thing? Uh, I don't know.
It's like a wonderful spot. Yeah, that's weird. I don't know what that is. Damn it. Things.
I want to try the parry. I'm going to try a parry. Let's see what happens.
Wait, is that a specific to your weapon? Oh, it is. It is. I think so. I wonder how it works.
Wait, I think we did enough damage. It's running. All right. Use springs quick.
I mean, I mean, they help a little bit. We are just fucking up this whole area though.
These are going to be here forever. Yeah. Oh, this beautiful area. We like,
this is a comment on industrialization, this game. I used all of my breads.
I know there's more. It's like some of the trees maybe. Oh, you can slide too.
Chat member, I swear you've typed that like 18 times since I started.
Look out for the snake. Look at this guy. This guy's just trying to hang. No.
I need to save the snake so bad. Okay. Thank God. That's like the most concerning thing
of the whole game for me so far. What's wrong with me? Oh, oh God. Oh, I got out just in time.
I'm out. I gotta get more. He loves animals. Yeah. As I kill one right here. Yeah.
And forests. We love the forests. You keep chopping down the trees like that. Oh,
shoot some sticky. All right. You, I sappy substance. Oh, where is he? Okay. Oh, I'm
going to use yours. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It really does. So it's insane. Like I, and I combo with
it. Like I ended up doing like a hundred hits. I love the elbow drop that I can do with this thing.
Okay. I just got really knocked off. Oh, Vinny, I might die. I'm going to die. I'm trying to help.
I'm trying to get attention. Dodge chef. Oh, okay. Okay. Okay. I just went back into the fire.
Oh, he's angry Vinny. Oh boy. Yeah. It's dropping like, like,
Oh, whatever this is. Oh, sap scourge. That's right. That's the name. Whoa, whoa, whoa. Look at
this. Hold on. Can you climb this? I'm going off the top rope. Oh my God. It's eating me.
It's a tree. It's a tree and it's eating me. How does it have a mouth?
Where you be? Where are you? Sorry. Sorry to make all these weird noises. No, it's all right. No,
I'm good. It's just this, this enemy is literally like a tree creature. I didn't even realize that
until just now. It's taken down the whole forest. It's so sappy. Jesus. Shit. I missed you climb
freeze. Not like you can climb the crates. I don't think those are like made. Those crates were made
for climbing. That's just what they'll do. Yeah. Same here. I'm sorry. I keep missing it and it's
so cool. Great egg commentary. Okay. I feel like we're in the last phase here. We have to be. It's
angry. We've been hitting it. There we go. We've been sapped upon several times by now. Oh,
Oh, under leveled. Oh, he is eating me too. Here we go. It's good damage on now.
I'm trying to see. I know there's like other attacks that you can combo. Like I'm seeing in
the top right. Oh, that's hot dog. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go. Massive damage. Absolutely
massive damage for me. Get that shit. Get up there. Drop the crates. Get up the crate.
You did 40 DPS. I'm doing fine. Jay is saying that my graphics look better than your graphics.
You do. I don't know. You have to show little bro. Germa your settings as a chat member.
What are your settings? Um, I don't know. I have most things on high. I got rid of ambient
inclusion and motion blur and everything else is on high. It looks apparent chat saying it like
my graphics is good. My graphics are not good. All right. I don't know. Look better. You have
a better GPU than me though. I do. Yeah, you do look better. We don't get time for this. We
got to hunt the monster. Yeah, we got to. That's right. Oh, there's a little fella here. I don't
know if we can catch it. I caught it. The same graphics are wicked crisp. Why am I not crisp?
I didn't apply them. Is that chat member from Boston? Did you actually say wicked growing up?
Like was that like a regional thing? Because we did not have that in New York. All the time.
No one was saying wicked when I was growing up. Like when Ocarina of Time came out, no one was
saying it was a wicked cool game in New York. That was actually a thing Germa that you were
saying wicked. I said wicked all the time. Yeah. Did you ever hear of like herbs? Do you know like
when someone's a herb? That I don't. I don't know. Okay. Is that what you. I think a little
little bit of that or if someone's a skel, do you know skel? Skel? No. Yeah. Like if they're on like
a fellow of ill repute is a skel. We got we've got a weird we've got like an asparagus dragon over
here. Yeah. Let's do it. Why is this here? Let's get rolled over. I love I'm fighting just like
the random shitty enemy and it's an intense fight and you're over there fighting the real monster.
I'm trying it. Oh, you got it. You actually got the tail. You could do it. It's real. Climb it.
Climb. Oh shit. I'm on his back. Oh, you can do that. I'm on his back. What do I do? I don't
know. Press buttons. All right. I'm still fine. Come on Vinny. Kill it. I don't know. How do I
thrust? Oh, those hits. I hope there's no damage meter because you're probably doing 80% of all
the damage. I don't think so, man. I'm doing okay. But there are moments where I just don't get any
hits for like a minute. There's no health bar. There usually isn't in these games. Yeah. No,
you just have to like if the monster is like limping or if the monster seems tired or weak,
that's how you know you're almost done. Definitely on this there. We have to be. You need to parry
to do real damage with this weapon. All right. I'll learn it after this. Finish what? Oh, wait.
This thing's still alive. That was kind of sad. Oh, oh no. Shit. I'm going to try to parry.
Oh, I'm dead. Okay. I don't think I can get you back. I think I can get. I'm going to see.
Be careful. Oh, it's eating me alive. Oh my God. Bro, why? No, no, no. I'm sapped up. I'm
saying this about killing monsters. I'm sitting there going like, oh no.
Let's see. I think I can rescue. I can rescue you. Oh my goodness. You were just in time.
Died to sap scourge omega low. I'm fine. Don't know the combos. If I would be so much more
effective with this weapon. If I knew the combos, I've got to figure out the parry. That's how you
get this to work. Yeah. For yours, that would probably be amazing. Even angrier. We are at
anger levels. Never seen before. Stay alive. Keep going. That's sap off of us.
Ungar max. That's right. That's Barrett's limit break in final fantasy. Ungar max.
Kill, kill, kill, kill, kill. Did you ever hear about that? What was it?
There was a mistranslation of Barrett's limit break in final fantasy seven.
And they called it Ungar max when it should have been anger max. We won. I was like a little kid.
I was like, what's Ungar max? Yeah, they just mistranslated it. Hey, I got the final blow.
All right. Ungar. New word every day. Flying vine. Karakuri awaken. Oh, that's me. Yeah. So
one of the big selling points of this game is the fact that you can put, I mean, we're doing these
things, but there are a ton of these tools. You can like put like zip lines around. You could,
I think it's pretty handy to make like almost like a little fort in the monster fight area.
Like at night. Well, during the day too. Okay. During the day too. Good. Good.
Your gamma is too high. I'm a regular hunter. If you say so. Can I turn my gamma down?
Turn down your gamma. My gamma is like so high. Is that why the graphics is different? I think
that's probably what's going on. Yeah. You mean that explains it. She roped me to doing her dirty
work for turn on ambient occlusion. It breaks the shaders. If it's off. Okay. Oh, all right.
Mine are off too. I'll turn mine back on then. Weird. You made camp teacher in that case lead
the way much as I like the idea of a statue in my honor. I don't want to keep it. So this takes
place in medieval Japan. Yeah, that's right. I was thinking or like some very, I mean there's
monsters. So look at this. You, you awaken the flying vine dragon. Hold on a minute.
Did you see that? Yeah. Let's see if we can make it. Instruct your own network of corridors
through the wilderness. Yeah. That's what I'm saying. I think we're, I think everything is
permanent. We're supposed to make essentially our own permanent resources to travel around.
Let's see if we can do it. Let me do this real quick. The tail is, I think I carved the tail
already chat. Like there would be like a green stink around it if I didn't. And I'm pretty sure
I got that. Oh, that does look better. Oh, you know what? Here, let me turn the ambient occlusion
on. Oh, it's a thousand times better. Wow. Okay. Yeah. They weren't kidding. Yeah. This actually
looks like this is great. I had my, I had my gamma up like way too high. All right, cool.
I'm trying to build the thing, the flying vine thing. Yeah. Cause we're in a cave. We can't
let's, let's get out of this cave and see what happens. Oh, I got one. You did it. Yep. This
should help. Oh, wait. Oh, I didn't, I made the wrong thing. Wait, did I make the wrong thing?
Maybe. I made like, I made like a fucking, like a trebuchet. Oh, wait. No, I think that's it.
It's the one all the way to the right, right? Why are you not holding A? Wait. Oh, whoa, whoa,
whoa. I get it. Oops. I blew it. You got to hold A. Oh, I blew it big time. I get it.
Okay. You have to aim the thing and shoot it. I thought it was that we connected together.
Let me try it. Okay. Wait, how do I yeet myself? Oh, you jump and you hold right bumper.
You hold right? Um, RBA. I re I press that chat. I press that. It's literally tells you.
I know it tells me, but it's not working. RB. Oh, I was pressing LB. Dude, that thing's going
like two feet. It's fine. Do you want, oh, you're all the way over there. Let me get to you real
quick. No, there's nothing over here. It's fine. I mean, all right. That was, all right. That's
cool. It's, it's cool, but it didn't, I didn't really build an effective one. We need to,
okay. The next Mossberry fight, we have to build a little base around it. Okay. You can teleport
to camp from the maps as a chat member. Oh, you can. You can. Oh, you can. It's useful.
Only hosts can do that. Wait, no, no, no. Okay. I'm good. I'm gone. Oh, there you are. Okay. Here.
I'm going to build one of these. The dragon pit isn't powerful enough. Oh, we need more like
capacity to build extra stuff. I think I am going to become so compulsive with this because these
things are permanent. Hunter with death stranding. There's elements of both. You're sure. What's up,
Jeremy? I was going to say the, if everything is permanent, I feel like there's a lot of people
that are going to make insane travel basis. Like you're going to be able to go anywhere.
Some of you that get this game and just build networks. Yeah. I'm curious like the insane
networks people are going to build with all the stuff unlocked. I'd be preserved in amber right
now. Exposed for all to see. You paint a green picture. It really was fortunate. You're right.
Did you see this one in battle? We are face cam imminent by the way. I want to make sure
everyone's aware. I know creating out of thin air like that. That's a skill I simply have to learn.
Good. We've, we were good. We've been good. I'd like to get back to me.
No, I'm not turning. I don't know. Oh no. Yeah. No, don't wait. Not, you know, not you. No,
no. My, my chat's like, you should do it too. Vin. I'm like, I don't care how good the chat's been.
I've been, uh, lazy for that. I've been streaming with it off, uh, with it off recently.
It's just, it's nice because I could sit back in my chair and I can just look like shit.
I know not have like light lights on. Like I can stream in the dark and damage my eyes. It's fun.
I like it. I was using a game boy camera for a while and you like, that was actually my,
were you actually doing that? Not a real one, but I found a way to make it work.
Oh, that's so funny. It was cool. What was that? Oh, I thought he, I thought he farted.
Suburban Sasquatch.
Probably haven't eaten a thing since we were, I was looking over at the chat and I just said,
okay, so we're going to eat because that guy's stomach was growling and we have food.
All right. There we go. It's all real.
That's a very interesting way to sit. Let's not linger here any longer.
Good. It's, it's, it's good on the spine.
Mm hmm. It's a nice permanent spine damage.
Fuck. Yeah.
That's fun. Oh, wait, what's this chat members? Oh, hang on. I just tabbed out by accident. Chat
member. Can you repeat that about the audio thing? You have to break the dragon vines you place to
make more. And two, if you change your audio settings to 5.1, your FPS gets doubled. Really?
5.1. Huh. All right. I'll try. Let's try it.
You'll have to do this scouting alone. Please slow you down.
So you say go to audio? My FPS are good. I don't like,
I haven't had, I've had stutters a little bit, but nothing terrible.
No. Put on it, put it on 5.1, 7.1?
Yeah. Okay. 7.1, 5.1. We'll give it a shot.
Someone mentioned the audio thing in critical's chat too. All right, we'll see.
That actually like kind of, that actually kind of worked.
I mean, it was, it was fine before, but wait a minute. Oh, this is the training thing.
Did you fight the bear? No, not yet. I'm going to do that. Oh, that's what this is. Yeah.
Okay. Bunging comet from reverse lunge. So you go wham, then you go wham.
DRG has a similar bug. It's with internal EQ. Okay. Interesting. So once I could charge this,
like faster, what was the charge button? I just did 795 damage.
What? Not a second. I was, we were, I was doing like three damages swing.
You just did 700 damage. Yeah. Yeah. I did a full charge
with the sword and I got that much damage. What? Okay. That's, that's interesting.
Oh, I see. Okay. With this weapon, I can charge and attack while I'm charging and then unleash
a 700 damage attack. Crazy. Absolutely insane damage.
Come under attack while in parry stance. Hold on.
I want to bring one of these little fellas with me. Is that working? Do I have to time it? Like
press LT next to the bear. Oh, deficient materials.
I need to parry it. Isn't that, it's not working. Parry successfully for big spin dance.
Oh, okay. So it's not, wait a minute. All right. It's not the top of the weapon. It's, I get it.
So during a box, you're right. Where are you? Yeah, I'm fine. I'm just equipping stuff in a box.
So you parry, parry, parry, parry, parry, build up your gauge and then you've got ultra damage.
This is hard. This is, this is tricky. You probably chose like the most technical weapon
like by accident. This is now your thing. Okay. So during parry counter attack,
I'm not caught up with this one. I think I have to use them all. I have to use them all.
Oh shit. All right. Wait, wait, wait. I got a full gauge.
Vinny, why are you fondling that poor ball? Don't, do not incite ball fondler.
Do not like summon him. Whatever you do. Okay. I think I'm getting it down. Now how much damage
does it do? Nice. All right. Oh wow. I'm doing so much more damage to swing now. Mid dodge attack.
Nice. Okay. Oh, this really does just teach you all your combos. That's awesome. Yeah. All right. Oh
my God, dude. I was swinging and hitting the back of the bark on the back of that last enemy's back
and was doing one damage to swing. I'm doing like a hundred damage now.
Nice. I wonder if I was so useless in that last fight. Okay. Mount spring, then mid leap.
Great based attack. There's a lot of travel attacks. It seems like. Yeah. I just got to get
the parry down. Mount spring and then X mid leap. Wait, you can mount a spring. Oh, I see what it
means. Okay. So you have to like spring into the enemy and then attack. Cool. So I'm imagining that
chat helped me out here. When my gauge is higher, I do more damage. Obviously. I mean, obviously.
Nah. Cool. Yeah. Now it's like we both know how to play the game now. Yeah. So that's good.
You both got it down. Yeah. What about these little guys? Yeah. So I just upgraded that little dude.
I don't know what it does exactly, but you know, you can like, I think you can carry more stuff
for crates. That seemed to be like what happened. You lose the gauge very quick when taking damage
or not fighting anyone. Attack form? Jerma, there's food too, but you can, you can draw your meat
and then it'll like give you attack and health bonuses and stuff. I just learned.
Ooh, let's do it. Find out what creature made the roar. Ooh. Okay. Dry ingredients. Oh, this is what
you're talking about. Jerma, is this woman stuck in a box for you too? Whenever, whenever you're
over there. Um, I'll check it out in a sec. Yeah. Yeah. No rush. Cubed meat. I'm just drying a bunch
of meat. Luigi, I'm stuck in a little box. It's me, Mario. I need you to get me out of here.
I'm just drying meat. Mario, Mario, what are you doing in the box? I'm in the box too.
What are you doing in there? Get out of there. That's dangerous. Someone just said you're
embarrassing us. I mean, I'm embarrassing myself, not, not you, chat. No, no, no. I, I don't think
you, I did. You don't get embarrassed here. Do you understand the things that I've said? Yeah,
I know. I know. Yeah. Don't worry. We are all collectively weird here. Don't worry. Yes. That's,
that's fair. All right. Let's make, hold on. Let's make one of those. I'm going to make one of these
things and you're going to see how cool it is. Ready? Yeah. Check this shit out. Now, before you
do that, the Jerma, I have a, there's a sign over here that you can place. It was, it's, there's a
weird message on it. Really? Yeah. Yeah. Check this out. It's weird. Like I just read it. I was
like, how, how did that sign get there? Like, why does it say that this one? Let me investigate.
Hold on. Yeah. Right here. Yeah. All right. You want to go hunt a monster now? Really? Really?
I want to sponsor stream Vinny. All right. We need to make that a, speaking of sponsor,
thank you EA for sponsoring the stream. The game is out right now. It is wild hearts.
You can get it on PlayStation five, Xbox series X and series S as well as PC.
Those are the best times to possibly do that. If you're into the monster hunting
kind of lifestyle, this is potentially the game for you. Weirdly enough, that switching audio
thing actually increased my performance by quite a bit. I mean, I would say that what I'm looking at
right now, yeah, I would call, I would call it beautiful. Like a marginal difference. Yeah.
Really? During my sponsored stream? Really? Unbelievable. Oh my God. Vinny killed him.
I had to, had to. All right. So we wait. Oh shit. I forgot about, I, my, I wasted stuff.
All right. You ready Vinny? Check this out. Yeah. We're going to make this happen here.
Okay. I don't have enough resources. You need to make one. Make what? Oh, we need to tear that
down. Hold on. Come back over here. I'm just getting smacked by a goat, by a fantasy goat.
Hang on. Let's just take care of this. All right. I think we can only make a certain amount of
objects in. Correct. Yeah. Yes. So if we have too many, we should probably remove some, right?
Can I do that? So how do I? You can dismantle from the menu, I think. Oh wait. I don't know.
How do we do that? Cause it says, uh, dragon pit isn't powerful enough and see dragon pit capacity.
We're at kind of minus 13 right now for that or two old L one and press up. Oh, dismantle. There
it is. Yep. You press, you press the right stick in. I found another sign. It's weird. Another one.
Well, you got another sign. Let me see what's on it. No, no, no, no. You're no, you're good. You're
good. Not during your sponsored stream. Check this out. We are going to make a zip line from here to
there to the, to the mountain. Okay. Cause my zip line is placed in a very inconvenient area and I
think I'd have to go over to it and dismantle it. Okay. We have so much shit everywhere. I can't
feel it. Looks like we're walking. Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait. What if we, um, touch the dragon pit
here? Do you have a small mist crystal by chance? Do you still want to eat shit? No, no, no, no,
don't do that. Um, German over here. Can you, can you touch this dragon pit? Cause if you do that,
we can then build more stuff in this area. Only hosts can do that. Goddammit. Can you do it?
I can't because I'm missing a small mist crystal. Wait, maybe I have one. Small mist crystal.
Wait, this might be it right here. No, that's crystal ore. I have a shitload of them. Can I
give them to you? Open your crafting and hit right stick and you can dismantle the boxes.
All right. So if you do that, oh, wrong button. So if you do that right. Uh, and then you can make
it huge so you can just get rid of everything. All right. That's the least you can do that.
Wait, how do you dismiss? Oh, nice. Okay. Can you, can you, can you build the thing now? The,
the zip line? Like I'm really, I cannot really dedicate it to the zip line. I didn't know.
I cannot build it. I can build this other stuff though. So we only have, okay. So we have two
of that capacity on the top row. I think I honestly, I'm going to be honest with you. I
think I built like four of them when we were testing it. They're all in that place. I wonder
if I can do it from the, do we have to go dismantle them? Get rid of the poop sign. Someone said for
me to get rid of the poop sign. Okay. Or you might have to go back to the old one. All right. Let me
get rid of the poop sign. We'll try then. Oh, I got a small mist crystal. Hang on. I think that's
exactly what I needed. We need more leaps and purge. You can now conjure more dragon Karakuri
here. So now I think we can do it. Maybe. I think it's not quite. I think you only have two out of
a larger capacity. You don't have enough resources. All right. We just need to get resources. Let's,
let's try to get our way over there then a long way. We need one more. All right. Oh wait. No,
I can do it now. I can do it. Oh, you can. All right. Nice. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. So now if you put
it here, can you just aim it to the top of that cliff and can we just ride it up? Yeah. I'm going
to try. There you go. So how do we make the zipline part? You know, you get on top of it and you fire
it wherever you want. I think it's a left trigger to activate it and then you aim it and you're
trying to get it there. And look at that. Oh my God. We did it. Why are you faster than me? You
shouldn't be faster than me. I don't know. That's not fair. I got on it first. I think I'm starting
to understand. So there is a, okay, so there's an object limit and me placing the poop sign
meant that we couldn't place other objects. I think that's what happened. All right. Use your
sense. Make sure there's nothing here. Where the hell are we? There's a document in here.
We went, where do we go? There's a lot of stuff here. Oh, this way. Oh, look. There it is. There
are all of our stupid things that we placed. You can see them? I can see them on the mini map,
like on the actual map map. Yeah. Well, it's all right. Like on the, on the map, like if you press
select, yeah, you can see where we, yeah, I see them. That's funny though that they're permanent.
All right. So now where is this monster? Find out what the creature made the roar.
I think if you hold your senses, we were being guided in this direction.
Do the roar. I landed on the ground with such force.
Jeremy, you're going to like the view up here. Okay. Good. Oh my God. Oh, we got a Pat raid.
What's up, Pat? Thank you. That was so violent. I want to be there too. It's not fair. You will be.
You will be. Warthog. We'll crush it. I mean, crush it. We will. How come,
why are people so afraid to have somebody with a funny voice as the main character?
Like Yoda? Yeah. I mean, just like, how come the main character in video games can't,
you know, talk like this? Why not? That's why we need more Muppet games.
True. Seriously, like Muppet Treasure Island was a great game and everyone had that voice.
Someone in my chat wrote, because cringe culture.
Cringe? I don't know. Funny voices is great. I made a career out of it.
Actually, you know what people, that would get annoying. Yeah. After a while. I mean,
but Mario has a funny voice. Someone just said, and like he goes, the whole game and we just get
used to it. But Mario is not, Mario, you know, going like, yahoo. He's not going like, yahoo.
And by the way, let us talk about current political landscape. Like it doesn't really,
it doesn't really talk that way. Luigi does that. Luigi's like, oh Mario, we're going to yeet that
meat. You know, I actually really, I like that voice. I don't think I would have a problem with
that voice. I wouldn't either, you know, we're going to make it the pasta, the pizza.
Snow covers summer pastures. I like that voice.
So if we let that Kingdust think this is its patch. I don't suppose.
Charles Martinet actually talked to people, like as Mario, like he can hold like full
conversations with people as Mario. What an absolute saint of a person, by the way.
Yeah. He's a champ. He's awesome. I met him once and he was like, it was a long convention.
Really? He was signing for days and days and days,
like all three days. And I met him at the very end of a day. We were both tired,
but he was way tired. You could hear his voice was just tired and he was still doing the voices
for me while he was signing my photo. He was like, wahoo. It's me, Mario. And he just signed and
drew pictures all over it. And he was so nice to me. And I was like, Charles, thank you. You just,
you just made my day. You just made my month. Really sweet guy.
All right. We can use the tower search. Oh, that's what this does. All right. So if it's
in the area, if you put down one of these towers, that's how it's being illuminated
through the walls. And if we use flying, it's as flying vine, we can do surprise attacks.
Yeah. No, he just seems like a really, really swell guy.
Yeah. He's good. Good, good lad. So how do you want to handle this? You want to do a zipline?
Do we have enough points to do it? I'm going to see if we can make one, but I see a little
Jerma. Yeah. Jerma, can you get over here? Yep. All right. Nevermind. You know what?
Probably wouldn't be good for your sponsorship. But, but here, can you, can you follow, follow me?
That was pretty fucking cool. I'm not going to lie. Okay. All right. I'm just,
Hey, name me, name me another game where you could do something like that.
Good point. I can't write the second. Good point. Someone said Sonic 06.
That was pretty pog to me. Skyrim. All right. All right. Yeah. Well, we can zipline that dude.
Let's do it. Let's, let's go for it. All right. Hang on. Let me see if I can do
a zipline. Can I just jump? I cannot. I don't have enough resources.
We, unfortunately we might need to go and like dismantle these like useless.
I made two or three of them in the same place. Let's see. Dragon pit isn't powerful enough.
Oh, hang on, hang on. Before we give up, let me look for, there's, there's a thing.
There's an item you can get and then you can increase the, the amount of stuff you can place.
Yeah. Those little pits with the purple, with the dragon pits. I think we need more of them.
There's one down here. Is that the one we already got? So there's one over here,
but I can't upgrade it because I don't have the material for it. Yeah. The collision.
I don't know what's going on. Look, I'm looking. Is this actually an open world game? Can you just
climb that stuff in the distance? I think that's accurate. I'm pretty sure it's just like a big
open map. I think that's accurate. I think we can just kind of go up pretty much anywhere we want.
Or maybe it's different areas that load up. You can even go into the sky. Oh, I found, oh wait
now I found a core stone. Um, I mean, I guess we could just go down there and kill the thing.
Is there, I wonder if we can like dismantle things in the, on the map or something.
We could just go down there. Can you dismantle things from the, from the map?
Let's just, I'm going to, let's head down there. All right. Just don't fall too far. Oh, I'm alive.
I'm good. That hurt a lot, but I'm good. Huh. I didn't take any damage from that.
It's probably a, all right. That he's like right here. All right. Everything we learned,
everything we trained. It's time to kill this thing. Okay. Wait, dismantle this shit.
Oh, so, so you, uh, here's how you do it. Um, right stick. So, so go into the thing and then
right stick, click in and then you can dismantle. I think we, it has to, oh, here's another one of
these. Activate this thing. We need extra materials. Were you able to activate it? No.
No, the host has to. Okay. That's so weird that only I can do it. I guess it is my game world,
right? Following your game world, but yeah, I think that's probably why we sneak over. Yeah.
I don't have the materials. Someone said I have both yours and German streams open at once.
That's a good lead. That's pretty, that's pretty cool. Yeah. Are you ready? Yeah. Let's, let's put
some shit around the area. You know what I mean? Like I'm going to put a spring over here, like
maybe have springs all around so we can kind of keep the monster the same, you know, put springs
around boxes. I got springs. Okay. Got a bunch of springs. Okay. All right. Are we, are we ready?
I'm going to aggro. Whoa, it's Roar just knocked me back. This is a two star monster. Are we in
trouble here? We could seek assistance. I guess that's like health from randos. Shit, he almost
killed me in one hit. We're going to go hog wild. I got to get this parry down. Oh my God. And here
we shit. Yeah, this is a problem. This thing is huge. It's very big. Look at the eyes. All of my
tactics. There's so many eyes. Oh yeah. Oh God. It's got a lot of eyes. Oh, I don't like that.
That's so weird. Back legs. Back legs seem to be vulnerable. That one did. It's a tree out of the
way. We're good. Don't chat. Don't worry. We're going to put the squeeze on this hog. What? Unleash
unleash a little bit. Got a little bit. Oh, there it is. I got one. Careful. This weapon is definitely
for like for a master. It's not me. Yeah. I mean, I'm even struggling with this big sword.
So I was dammit. There you go. I did some damage there. If you knew the monster patterns. Yeah.
I think this thing is higher level than us, but we'll pay. How do you enjoy monster hunter?
I've played a lot of monster hunter. Try three you for world rise. Sorry to just list my
credentials, but no, it's true. I played a lot, but I don't get like I play like 100 hours of
each game. And then I just after that I'm good. And that's like no small amount for me. Gamer
resume. Exactly. I got it. I'm going to try to get a Perry. It's like a whack. Nope. All right.
That's a long swing. That's a very long swing. I might have to go mall. I might have to start
some materials. Don't forget you can attack and charge. Oh no, I know. But then the hog attacks
me. And then I end up kind of like losing the combo. He's running LB. What's going on right now?
Wait, what? What did I just do? What did you blow? What the fuck did I just do? What did you do?
Holy shit. I don't know. I had I went like instinct mode and I made a bulwark, a bulwark
fusion. Cowra Courage is flashed into existence. I think that's the play for this one.
Bulwarks can fend off charging kimono use a fusion of how two rows of free crates.
All right. Oh, you're down. Yeah. Perry, you can. Oh my God.
I tried. I think we're dead. No, no, no. You got this. No, I'm dead. All right.
I think this thing is this thing is a little more difficult. So we have three tries, it seems. So
retreat. Yeah, we have to retreat and then I think run back. Oh, I'm gonna grab some of this water.
Revival point. Yes, definitely do get. Hold on. Do we have your meat dry? It dried. I got it. I
don't know what else to do with it. Oh, I did. I don't think I tried it properly. I'm going to try
to let me try the other weapon. How do you eat the meat? Do you know? Or was it like auto eat
meat? I don't think I'm going to go this way. You should upgrade your gear. I don't know if I can
right now. Like we don't have enough materials to really upgrade gear left on D pad to eat meat.
Oh, it is that. OK. All right. Let me let me just real quick. I just want to mess around with the
mall. This thing is OK. While you do that, I'm going to do. Oh my God, it's huge. It's got like
a small handle, too. I feel like this would be hard to handle. All right. Let me try it.
Have you heard about stream squad? It makes it easier for people to watch your stream when
you're playing with friends. No, I didn't know about that really. Jumping smash. Nice.
You're trying to fight one of if not the last boss of the map. You skipped all the one star fights
as a chat member. I don't know how true that is, but it feels true. That felt hard.
All right. This is this is way cooler. Stended mall held. You went straight to Ganon. Yeah,
pretty much. There's also another Rage Tale. Oh, you can see. OK, because the towers we build
have like radius of like where the monsters are. So, yeah, we. So wait, this is a little explosion.
Is that what it does to this boss? You switch to Minato map. The NPCs are looking for its entire
village. Oh, yeah, it's a telescoping handle. X, R, T, X, R, T, X, R, T, X, R, T. Come to work.
Here. You know what? You do that and I'm going to deconstruct all this crap that I built.
There we go. Jesus. I suggest doing this boss since you pick up side quests at the village
after this boss. I mean, if we can, we're going to try. You got to get this down. So it's like you
smash, then you press right trigger, then you press it again, right trigger and you press it again.
Instant extend power smash. All right, that one's way cooler.
Yeah, I'm just going to go resource gathering while Jerma is learning the hammer.
Feel like I'm going to like it. All right, I think I'm ready. So what else do we have?
We've got King Tusk. We've got King Tusk and that rat again, which could be good to upgrade our
stuff. But I mean, it's up to you. Do you want to go for the rat and then come back to the King Tusk?
Yeah, let's let's do some resource gathering. Let's actually I'm going to go destroy all this
shit that I made over here. OK, I'll be back in two seconds. Yeah, take your time. I found the rat,
so I'll just be there. I'm going to go delete that stuff because it's just it's sucking up resources.
It's the fastest way to get there. I think fast travel only works to camp, but yeah,
we'd have to like make a bunch of ziplines. It's definitely worth me going and getting rid of them.
But I think that's only per area, like I'm almost positive it's a per area thing.
And then like you can just go to a new area and build more, but you need to upgrade the limit.
Chat members, can you confirm this? I think that's accurate. It seems like it's accurate.
Something just screamed at me. I don't know what it was. Oh, I found a new ball. New ball just
dropped almost there. You need your pits upgraded. That sounds weird when you type it like that,
but I know what you're talking about. Oh my God, I fell. This is probably a better way to do this,
but it's going to be more mindful of it. Dude, can you seriously climb this? Oh, what am I doing? I
have boxes can help. Yeah, that's right. We just had the same issue and I had to build boxes the
same time you did. I'm going to get a different area of the map. All right. Bounce, bounce, please.
Bounce, please. It doesn't rock and whatever. I think we talked about this, but you're not going
to Boston for PAX, right? I am not. OK, right. I think we did talk about that. Sorry. Yeah,
I haven't really been to very many conventions or meetups or anything like that in a while.
Yeah. I'm going to kill this frog. What about TwitchCon in Vegas? Says someone. I mean, that's
here. Yeah, that's close to you. I considered that one. I haven't been to the West Coast or
the Middle Coast very much at all ever. The problem I have with that is last year it was
the same time as Comic Con. And I like I like going to New York Comic Con. So I just went there
instead. I'm going the right way. I think I am. Yeah, I'm picking up a bunch of resources to just
anything I can find. Yeah, me too. Like I already found another upgrade area. Vinny, there's no
coast in the middle. Yeah, it's just a bunch of fields. But like if you go south, there's like
the Gulf of Mexico. No, I got a snail. Oh, that's the Gulf Coast. All right. I'm almost there.
Don't fall, please. Why did I not make the thing? I'm good. How do I get up here?
Vinny, wrong direction. Well, how do you know where I'm going? I don't know where I'm going.
Actually, I'm looking for a rat. Have you seen a rat anywhere? I am. Where is the rat? Oh,
I found the rat. Oh, you're right. The pink icon. Oh, shit. All right. I'm coming in a minute.
I'm going to teleport back to the camp and I'll meet you there. Crystals. All right. Where are
they? They're like behind me. I hope I'm going the right way. Yeah, this is definitely the right way.
I have initiated rat fight. I am about to initiate the one we just did. Hold on. No,
let me just delete this stuff. Don't fight me. Please don't hurt me. I just want to get. Oh,
all right. Here's one. Here they are. Good, good, good, good. Oh, get off me. All right.
I think this one's not mine. Isn't it, though? Can you not deconstruct it? Oh, yeah. There we
go. All right. Did that free anything up? Can you look at your menu? Uh, it might. But again,
I think it's since it's per area, I think it's it should be OK. Wherever wherever I am, I think
is different. I'm not sure. But it might also be a limit on like the zip lines. Like, I don't know
I don't know how this game works. I don't know. I it definitely is per area because I just deleted
them in there still there. It's definitely. All right. I'm coming to you. Yeah, I'm wailing on
the rat. It's going great. I can figure out how you got there. How did you get over there?
Oh, I got to go this way. You take a bite out of a bar of soap on screen. No. What? It's kind of
unhinged. Why? Why? Why are people like, oh, yeah, yeah, that'd be so awesome if you did that.
Oh, man, I hope you eat soap on it. Why would I eat soap for no reason? No, it's a good bit,
streamer. Trust me. Actually, I've eaten soap at least three times before I got here today.
All right. I need to go back to the road. You're going to kill that thing before I even get there.
Chat, I won't even face cam. What makes you think I'm going to eat soap?
And then it's to the left, right? OK, here we go. I was so close to unleashing my fury upon this rat.
Am I going the right way? As long as I get the finishing blow, that's all I care about.
You know what I noticed? You don't have to sharpen your weapons.
No. That is a great thing to not have to do. I get why that's in the other series,
but it's kind of nice to just fight and not think about it. OK, I'm still trying to find you.
I think I can go this way. I can't eat anything at the moment.
No, I see your name. I see the chef. OK, I'm coming. I'm coming. I'm coming. I'm coming.
OK, good. Good. Good. I'm almost there. I'm 200 miles away. I'm almost there. Oh, no. Oh,
no, no, no, rat. Don't don't do it. I'm getting there. Can you see me?
I think I can see. Was that you? I see you. I see you. All right. What's up? Yeah. Help me
fight this rat. And then like we can use rat materials to further upgrade our weapons.
It's going to be fucking awesome. Oh, there's a ball here. Oh, germ germ ball ball ball to be
friend. Oh, I got one. All right. Rat. I like this town. Pretty cool. Looks good.
How do we get over there? OK, now that was way more damage than I've ever done. Nice.
And unleash the fucking fury upon the rat. Oh, my God. 500 damage.
I think it's kind of like trapped in here, too. Might be. Right in the head.
Oh, man. Did it run out? I lost it. I lost the charge. I think there's a material here. Yep.
Got it. Cool. I'm enjoying this, actually. I think it's pretty good.
Yeah, I think just learning how to how the mechanics work, I think are important.
Yeah, like they're going for the like the box stuff. I get what they're doing. Like the same
way in like rise, you can like use your bug to like go to the sky and then do an attack.
This you just build boxes like it's once you figure out the combos and dodging, it makes sense.
All right. This thing is inside of this room now. You know what? Yeah, fuck it. Let's you know,
speaking of that. Oh, that would have been so awesome. You all know what I actually landed.
Why is there a little possum down here? See that little possum friend? I think this might be
the same species. I don't know. It looks like a little fella. Oh, again. Again. Stop running.
It's dead. Fucking dead now. Oh, that felt good. It's all about using the springs and stuff.
Yeah, I got to start building more springs. Let's see. Oh, nice.
Oh, do it, please. Again. Oh, man. I had so many opportunities. I just screwed up. Yeah,
I'm not doing the combos very well. It's like this swing. It's right trigger. Swing, right trigger.
Swing, right trigger. This little fella part of your vocabulary now. That's been a part of
my vocabulary for like the past decade. That's like a Carl Pilkington thing that I've just like
said for years. Get some monkey news up in here. Little monkey news. Little fella.
A hundred damage. Very mad. Very dead, I think. Very dead. Very dead. Nice.
Carve it. Yeah, I always have a problem in monster hunting games like this,
because I don't know what to play with. I always go, no, no, something else.
Then I change and I have to relearn the whole thing. And then I go, no, something else.
And I have to relearn the whole thing. Ah, something else. You end up sticking with something,
though. Yeah, like I said, I have like my two, but even then I forget like which one I'm using.
And then I'm like, oh, I'm pressing the wrong buttons. Sorry, I couldn't escape. I couldn't
go anywhere. Good. That was a good sneeze. It was like a powerful sneeze. I like got out of the
chair. All right. Maybe we should make some armor. Yes. I like that idea. I'm going to teleport back
to camp, I think. Vinnie, your duck sneeze. Yeah, I do a duck sneeze. People like that.
I just sound like a duck when I sneeze. I'm like, people like, do you do that in public?
And my answer is I fucking try not to. Wait, we discovered it. We discovered one.
Target kimono discovered. Oh, I see. OK. So I wonder, do you see these grayed out things?
Yeah, those are camps or the dragon thing. Yeah, I think those are the ones that I've upgraded
the pits. So we got to like, yeah, if we go to those and upgrade them, we can place more garbage.
Yeah. Oh, I can actually do it from here. Really? Yeah. Yeah, I just upgraded one.
You have to like actually see it first and then you can upgrade it. Paddle scoop. Oh,
this is an automatic fish catcher. Let me see if I can upgrade something. Upgraded. I got a new
thing. It's like, oh, OK, I can do this. It's an ornamental lantern. I think I'm going this way.
Oh, Jerma, collect this food when you get a chance. The dried out food. And if you press
left on the D pad, you can use it before we fight and it'll give you a boost.
There's also inherited skills here. I'm like putting that on. Interesting. What do you mean?
Where's that? When you go into your weapon upgrades, you can kind of take inherited
skills from the thing you just had. OK, that's interesting. This thing's way cooler. My magma
hammer. Nice. I need one more Rage Tale thing and then I can get the better sword. Damn it.
All right. I think I got this combo down. Bang, whack, bang, whack, and then wham.
Which one's bang and which one's whack? Bang is X, whack is right trigger. OK.
Health boost. Oh, this armor has a health boost. Are you going to play anything else today or just
this? I think in a little bit I'll play something else. Maybe we'll see. Dark and darker ended,
right? Yes, it did. I needed that to end because my productivity was dipping anyway. I'll wait
like another month and a half and I'll be happy with that. That's fine. We could go kill that
sap scourge again if you want to. Which one's that? That's the fire one that was burning
like the whole forest down. Oh, the sap scourge. Gotcha. Yeah, yeah. We could do that. We could
just go like explore and find things to hunt. I'm fine with that too. You know what? We could go
like here, like that blue icon or the purple one and we can build a tower and just see what's out
there. I'm into it. Let's go. Why did I not do that? Wild hearts. I feel like I'm going to be
way happier with this weapon. Where's our thing that we placed? We got like a... I destroyed a
couple of things. Do you want to just kind of explore? Yeah, maybe we'll explore it and we'll
find... we'll go this way and maybe and then we'll just like... We'll probably run into something.
Yeah, we'll run into something. I'll build a tower. Have you told Jerma about your pet owl yet?
What is this pet owl stuff that people keep... What are you talking about? You got a pet owl?
No. It's the owl's name. Flanko from the New York Zoo. Oh, right. Yeah, because there was an owl
that escaped from the Central Park Zoo and he's just chilling in Central Park and like eating rats.
What? Yeah. I can't wait to just magma smash. Not fair. I'm heavier than you.
I'm heavier than you. Not fair. Oh, we went... Oh, we can go up and around, I guess.
Vinny, tell him about the female owl plan. All right. Well, Jeremy, I don't know if you're
interested in this information, but in order to catch the owl... No. No? All right.
No. No, I'm just fucking around. What is it? Oh, ball here. Ball. Ball. In order to catch the owl,
they're putting a female owl of the same species in like a little like cage and they're just going
to like dangle it in front of the owl and hope it goes into the cage. What? I'm not even kidding.
Like that's how they're going to catch the owl. That's the plan. Yeah, that's the plan.
Uh-huh. What kind of plan is that? That's a good one. Hopefully it works. I hope they catch that
owl. I read that and I was like, wait, no, that can't be real. That's like Bugs Bunny shit. I was
going to say that that's some like Looney Tunes level of... I guess it's just put this here and
hope it works. If it goes for it. That's it. I like the slide. All right. So we are down here.
Maybe put a beacon up over here somewhere. Um, let us... What's that? Um, what's that creature
over there? I think that's the King Tusk again. Yeah. Okay. Let's go this way and we'll place one.
I'm just picking up every single thing I see. Oh, this is the one I made earlier.
This is the useless one. Oh, yeah, that's right. Tom literally did that to Jerry. Oh, the plan.
Yeah. Oh, we can upgrade this. Okay. You can now conjure more dragon something, something here.
Okay. Oh, yeah, we know. Yeah, we can. Oh, wow. That's way more. We had like two before. It's 59
now. Holy shit. That's so much better. It's good. Um, we can go. Let's see. Yeah, let's, let's go
over this way. I'm going to build a tower and we'll, uh, we'll see if there's any monsters
chilling. Has it got a squirrel? It's always monster hunter, but what about monster chilling?
Like, like, why can't I just hang out? I think that's what we're doing right now.
All right. Let's see if we can find something. Uh, I can't build it because it,
your dragon pit isn't powerful enough. Let me, you know what? Let me just head back this way and see.
I think we're like out of the zone. If you look at the map, see the map,
maybe we have to be in those zones. I think that makes sense. Yeah. Let me, let me get closer to
this. If you sneak up on wild animals, you can pet them and get free resources. Oh, you actually
can pet the animals. You can? What? You just like changed Jerma's life. Thanks chat member.
I want to do that. Uh, no, I can't place this here. It still says the dragon pit isn't powerful
enough. It's weird. All right. We can just go kill that pig. That's why I want to keep exploring up
here. Let's go up here and then we'll loop around and if we don't see anything, we'll kill a pig.
Yeah. I think the, the issue is that because you're the host, it's technically your game.
So I can't interact with those. It's just so, so weird. I get it, but it's also really weird
and not, not really anything in here. Nothing that I saw. Oh, there's a cool rock break.
Yeah. There's rocks to break. Yeah. Um, this game, please. You are so close to getting it.
You are. Just keep up the good behavior. Jerma chat. Keep up the good behavior.
I think we got a lot more damage too. I, I'm, I now I'm not doing like four damage total,
the whole encounter. Cool. So I'm down. I mean, we can loop back around this way and try to get
to the hog again. Down for that. Uh, where did you go? You're there. What percentage still face cam
you're at like 92%. Your other towers are overlapping. Well, that would make sense.
This is a cool looking area. Yeah, this is cool. Yeah. I think,
I think the chat member is right though. Like I built too many towers too close and,
Oh, yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Can you pet the snail? Wait, I need to see if this is real.
It's real. Holy shit. I just pet this weird tree creature of, of whom it's family. We've
probably killed a couple of times. How do you do it? So you press the dodge button while standing
still to crouch and like go stealth. And then when you get close to the creature and then you
just pet them, it'll show you the button. I think I accidentally angered this thing.
I hit it right in the fucking head. Yeah. It's too late to pet it. It's angry. I mean,
I guess that's angry. It looks angry. Well, it's angry at me, not you. All right. All right.
All right. Oh, I feel so bad. I have to leave. It's just this weird little hop.
Listen, don't look, don't look, Jerma. I got this. Oh, what is he doing? What are you doing?
Vinny, quick question. What's your favorite oil? Don't answer that. That's somebody from yesterday.
What? I mean, you can answer it. I'm curious. Okay. A light olive oil to cook with or are
you talking about like like essential oils? Because I like like lemongrass. It was a very,
it was a very vague question yesterday and I gave pretty similar answers. So
are you ready for the pig? Yeah, I'm ready. We're prepared. We're upgraded. Wait, I suppose.
I wanted to pet that. Okay. It's not going to aggro until we attack it. Okay. I'm sorry. I was
just collecting a ball. We've had the big monster. That'd be kind of funny. Yeah. Your chat is
bleeding into mine because now they're saying honest to goodness. Let's hunt like they're just
they're just like, I think we focus people saying focus on one of the legs. Let's focus on the back
left leg. Okay. It's a good idea. Sure. All right. I'm gonna I'm gonna engage in three, two, one.
Let's go loud. My goodness. 120 damage dude. I was so useless up until about 15 seconds ago.
Nice. Nice. Nice. Get that damage. Nice. Wait, build the build the bulwark. Oh, I built it.
Don't walk up. Okay, that was weird. It fucking worked. It did. I have a bulwark over here. No,
yeah, I do. Oh, I'm over here. Get him to run into this. Come and get me. Pumped his head.
Oh, what? Get that damage. Get the tail. 400 damage. One, two. God damn it. That would have
been awesome. Yeah, same. I also at the exact same time missed my big attack. All right.
At least we're doing damage and we know how to like play the game and stuff.
Vinny, have you noticed that this hog has jiggle physics in its ass? Mods. Mods.
Please remove this delinquents. Where did he go? I don't know. He's gone. I don't see him on the
map. Oh, wait. No. Yeah. He's at the blue. Go to the blue. There it is. All right. Re-engaging.
Bulwarking. Bulwark up. It kind of. Oh, it worked. I think maybe. I'm not sure. Big hit. Nice worked.
Two hundred and twenty two damage. Nice. Sick. Four eighty. Four forty eight.
Kimono weakness has become apparent in battle. Oh, I see. I see. I see. You can steal. Four
hundred damage. Karakuri threat from. Those blue areas are their weak points and you can
steal threat from them. Oh, grab onto with R, B and A. Then you can extract thread.
Oh, that was pretty cool. He's got like horns now. These things like he's got like antlers.
Like I'm on top of the thing now. That's weird. So wait, wait, wait, wait. So I can get on and
then I can extract. Wait, wait. If you do that, you might be. I think you're distracting. Oh,
you get like a massive abundance of materials. You exceed your limit so you can build like
massive towers. Speaking of that. Oh, should I have no more. I got no more juice.
Healing juice right over there. There's the flower right there. 164. Not bad. How did I
do the spin attack before? I forget. I kind of remember how I did that. These are two. Yep.
Oh, my God. I am dead. I can help you. Maybe I thought I was out of the range.
Oh, my. Dude, what did you just do? I just did the bulwark. I'm going to be able to rescue you,
I think. He just bounced around. One. Wow. MVP. I was a VIP. But you know what? That works, too.
Oh, my God. I can't see shit. No. All right. It's almost dead. OK. I wasted a bulwark,
but that's fine. Isn't it so crazy that oil like gives us energy? This weird goop gives us energy.
Why is this dude in my chat? I don't know. I'm sorry. I apologize.
Is this what was happening yesterday for you as well? Yeah, I think everybody got on this oil
thing and I was like, OK, feel free to permanently ban that guy. No, it's OK. I understand. He just
likes the wonders of oil, I guess. Like it it propels vehicles and like you can cook with it
and use it like on like skin like use it. I get it. Like, I understand. I'm kind of like team oil now.
Yes, Jerm. Oh, no, I was making so I was going hmm. Every time I touched one of these things,
it really used these ziplines, but we're just like, let's run instead.
In that game against the storm, I choose oil as my first boon chat. So that's weird. Ready?
Yeah. Fast travel time. Let's go for it. Check it out. Bang. Nice. Please don't tell me you cook
food with crude oil. Yeah, we so fucked up like you run out of oil. It's like,
all right, I'll just grab it for my car, I guess. Oh, that hurt. I got to get on one of those crates.
Oh, work. Do your biggest combo. Biggest combo. Unleash it now. Oh, no, that was an awful noise.
But yeah, I'm dead. Awful noise. I didn't hear anything. I think you peaked so much that I
didn't hear you. I have an idea. Oh, my God. Stop. I don't have enough valiant effort.
Run, run, run. I'm dead. I'm dead. Fuck. No, I'm sorry. I tried to dodge. I didn't know where he was
going to land. Okay. Oh, the hunt ended in failure. Shit. Oh, because each of us were like,
we each have one life out of three. And I keep forgetting that there's no iFrames. I'm like,
oh, just wait for the iFrames. Sorry. Hey, hey, hey, this is a tough one. It's tough.
You know, Jeremy, we forgot to eat. I don't know why I keep calling you by your full name,
but we forgot to eat food. It's weird because my name is Dave. I don't know why you keep saying
that. Yeah, I could call you like Jer or something like Jerry. They call you Jerry. You could call
me David, which is my name. David. I don't have to keep calling me. All this time. I didn't know
that. I'm going to talk to you. I'll talk to you after the stream. Okay. You know, it's funny
because for a long time, people were like, hello, Vinny. Is your real name Vinny? I'm like, yeah,
no, that's it. I took some defense food. All right. That went a lot better, even though I
kind of blew it at the end, but it's okay. Well, what about armor? We might have, let's take a look.
We could look at all this stuff we can make. I already, I already built a bunch of armor.
Oh, I didn't. Yeah. So I was like able to tank like a couple more hits to the face.
This is okay. I can make one of these. Is Vinny short for Dave? Yes, it is. Actually, it's a lot
of fire damage. I'm losing from these. These are the days I know. I know these are the daves. I know
it hurt. I'm just going to make the just the regular gear better than what I had on. I don't
think I want to be able to recover health for you. Chat. Do I have to bring these balls with me or
do they just like do this automatically? I pray for you. We're at 97% face cam turning on. You
know, close. No, they've been good. Give me one second. They've been good. I'll turn it on.
One sec. I'm actually going to open your stream to see if you do it. Like, I feel like it's a bit
incoming, but I don't know. What's up? Nothing. No, it's like, I'm not like joking or anything.
I'm just turning it on for a minute. So here you go. I'm look, I'm normal. Oh, yeah, there is
normal, normal Jeremy. I'm just normal. Everyone was like, Hey, what's wrong with you? Man, I wish
I had. I wish I had that kind of balls. Oh, wait, I do in game. The once every eight weeks
face cam. There was a point where people saw my face once a year. Like that was like pretty much
like for just some weird special occasion thing. I like that. It was fine. All right. I've eaten.
I'm ready. Let me do one more thing real quick, because I want to get this down. Well,
ah, hmm. Okay. That's jumping splash. I want to get it down. For a while. I thought V-dub was an
actual different person chat member. That is a different person. V-dub is a different human
being entirely thousand damage. But why was it doing that? What the hell? Okay. I think I get it.
I get it. I get it. I'm going to try the bow for a minute. I want to see what that's like.
Good idea. How about the timing? You got to go like swing and swing now, then swing.
Line it up. I feel like I'm going to use this combo a lot. Arrow switch.
This is pretty cool. Shoot. I'll tell you where the higher landed.
Is it one single shot? Or do you do more than one? You can do a couple of different things.
But I think, huh, is there like a switch? I see. So when you charge, you can like
shoot the area you just shot and it does more damage and they explode the other arrows.
Like, yeah, the arrows get stuck in there and then you can make them explode.
It's weird. It's that seems like an omega shot. Oh my gosh. Climb crate and then
RT mid jump. I feel like jumping off of the crates with the hammer seems like that's the way to do
it. I'm going to only attack by jumping off and just hitting Y. Heavy attack. It's just too good.
It's just too good. You know what I mean? Yeah. Yeah. I mean, if you find the weapon that works
for you, honestly, the sword was also kind of broken. So it's pretty happy about that.
All right. But I think this bow is pretty amazing. I'm going to try this.
I'm going to try this. Do you want to try the King Tusk again? I think we had it.
Yeah, we had it. Let's just eat like a good hearty meal before we attack the King Tusk.
Yeah, I had some defense food. It was pretty sick.
Jerma, do you like grilled cheese? Oh, yeah, I love grilled cheese,
especially when I drop it on the ground and eat it.
Wait, that's an actual thing that's happened? Somebody said that, right?
No, I just pulled that out of the air, dude. Like, you didn't have to tell me that embarrassing
moment. I was literally just asking about grilled cheese, like from my no one said that.
Sure. Yeah, I swear. What do you mean you ate it off the ground? Like David Hasselhoff?
No. OK, in my pre stream chat today, I said that I was mess. I was joking around. I said that I
ate a grilled cheese off the ground. And I thought that's because people talk to you about oil.
I'm just thinking like, oh, they're going over to your stream and bringing up my shit that I do.
I shit you not. I was just thinking about grilled cheese today because I watched like a recipe like
Gordon Ramsay just like actually butchered grilled cheese with some like weird recipe.
And I was just asking. Wait, is it the one where he he puts it like in a weird kettle like like a
fireplace? Yeah. He's like, OK, we're going to use the saffron. Beautiful. There's like apples on it.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, we're going to use this expensive cheese that doesn't even
melt delicious. Best grilled cheese, Vinny. Let's go ahead and discuss.
OK, I can tell you, but you tell me first, what's yours?
So how about we both write it down and then say it at the same time out loud?
OK, I don't need to write mine down, but. Yeah, why would we need to write it down? OK, so you go
first. OK, it's cheddar in the bread, white bread, just simple. And then you can also put butter on
the pan and then put cheddar on the other side. And then you can crisp the cheddar in the pan
on the butter. And like so you have crispy grilled cheese with melty grilled cheese in the middle.
It's amazing. Now, that sounds amazing.
I'm going to tell you something. Have you ever have you ever used mayo instead of butter?
No, like to cook on the pan or just in there. Mayo on the outside instead of on, you know,
do you like butter the like the sides, right? Like you said, you put butter on one side or
do you put butter in the pan or do you butter the bread and then put it on?
I butter the pan and then I put the grilled cheese in there
because it helps the cheese not stick to the pan.
Well, I'm into the cheddar. I would say I would add a little bit of Gruyere if I were you.
Yeah, that's what Gordon Ramsay was doing. Yeah, I don't know about that, buddy.
If I can't say the cheese name easily, then I'm not sure I'm going to edit.
I've never even eaten Gruyere. I don't even know what it looks like.
OK, good. All right. Ready to go fight this big warthog?
Yeah, I don't know where it is, though. Cheddar is good. I like Swiss, too.
I just like love Swiss. Monster is my favorite cheese.
Probably I've talked about this on stream. I love monster cheese and people.
What do you mean? Monster cheese? Are you milking monsters to get it?
I'm like, no, no, the male thing is for real. All right.
It makes it really nice and great. Wait, let me hold on. Can I let me pet?
You scared it, I think. Oh, here. Try that one. Try that one.
Mayo outside of bread is life changing. Vinesauce.
OK, you have supporters for this mayo stuff in chat.
So I'll take you up on that. I'll give it a shot.
It's another rat. Oh, another rat.
Yeah, I think we're going to have to like I do. OK.
I do really appreciate the fact that we're just in the game and we don't have to leave.
Like, you don't have to like call me back in.
I don't feel like a summoning thing down, like we're just in the game playing.
Yeah. There's been no other screen.
It's just get in the game and stay in it. Let's just kill this thing.
Why not? It's free. It's free.
You want to? Yeah, it's free.
OK, that would be awesome if I hit it. I mean, it's good practice for the bow, at least.
Yeah, maybe get the moveset down too.
Oh, oh, yeah. It explodes the whole thing. The whole rat just exploded.
It was amazing. I want to hit this so bad.
Damn it. You can get that right in the head.
Oh, my God. OK, yeah. So, Chad, here's what you do.
You have to like shoot the rat with these explosive bolts.
They don't do a whole lot of damage, but then you can then you can make them all explode.
It's really cool here. So like that, like that.
It's fucking. That was a good stagger too.
Already got it running. Already running.
Already running. Running. Yeah, it's running.
Chasing. Running.
The game's like build a tower to chase.
Like you said before, we're just running after them.
Vinny, what is the Lunchables tier list we were promised?
I never talked about. I've never promised the Lunchables tier list.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Chad, have you had a Lunchable in your like if if you're an adult,
have you had a Lunchable recently?
Like the ham tastes like water flavored ham.
Like I don't it's so like like weirdly watered down ham.
You don't like it? No.
Wait, do you like Lunchables? Did I just insult you?
No, not that great.
OK, because when we were kids, it was amazing.
But like I had one as an adult because I was like, let me be wacky.
I'm like a wacky, quirky adult.
I'm like wacky. Like, you don't know.
So I'm going to try. I'm going to get like a Lunchable as an adult
and I'm going to try it. And it was like really disappointing.
Like the magic was just gone.
Um, the notch was good.
I ate, I ate a whole stack in one bite.
This was, um, what am I going to say, like three, four years ago?
Would not recommend for like a charity or something.
No, I just did it.
Oh, um, there is the thing about Lunchables, though, is
they're actually not that bad.
Look, it's it's very easy.
It's just look, it's just all the food groups are in there besides vegetables and fruits.
Um, right.
So meaning incredibly important, you know, um, very important, very important.
It's just not in there.
Uh, but it's, hey, if you need a snack, it's a good snack.
It's a good snack.
As a kid, though, I was like, if I eat a Lunchable, I'm good.
I'm getting all of my balanced diet.
It's fine.
But like what I do these days, if I'm craving that kind of thing,
I just get like the Hormel pepperoni and cracker meal.
Like that, that shit's good.
Yeah.
They make like kind of adult versions, don't they?
They have like adult versions and like you get like salami and like,
like you get like fancy cheese.
It's like, I like that stuff.
That was a good hit.
My mod.
Jeff just said rich people food, bro.
Bro, salami and cheese.
Yeah, I disagree.
Vinny, what's your favorite deli meat?
Oh, can I answer that for him?
Yeah.
Answer that.
Black horse ham.
It's good.
I do like that.
It's not my favorite.
Wait, what's yours?
Black horse ham.
Oh, all right.
I thought you answered for me.
Oh, like, yeah, I'm just speaking for you.
It's yours is black horse ham.
It is now.
I like deli chicken.
Yeah, I like that too.
Deli chicken slice chicken.
Yeah, it's good stuff.
I haven't had that in a while.
I like, I'm going to tell you, you know what?
Since we're talking about food, I want to tell you about a sandwich that I really like
that I found on the internet that I now get my deli guy to make for me.
I'm a huge sandwich fan, so.
All right.
Cool.
Because I love a good sandwich.
I like really good like store roast beef.
That's like my favorite.
There's like a little salt on it and it's like, like store-made, like good shit.
That's like perfect.
I'm not a huge roast beef fan, but if it's good, toasted bread, slice of fucking provolone
on it, let's get weird, right?
Love that.
Yeah, love that.
If you're ever in New York, I would take you for like the best pastrami sandwich you'd
ever have in your life.
Oh, don't say that.
I'll literally get on a plane tomorrow because I got some good things.
Yeah, I got some good places like pastrami, corned beef.
It's just unbelievable.
I'll tell you about the sandwich and maybe you'll be interested.
I don't know.
But all right.
Chicken cutlet with pepperoni on top and fresh mozzarella.
And what you do is you put that in the toaster oven for a little bit and you let the pepperoni
sweat onto the chicken, right?
You let it sweat onto the chicken and the mozzarella melts a little bit and then mustard
on both sides of the roll.
It is life-changing.
It's so good.
That sounds so there's some shit YouTube chef who said he made that drunk in college
and he said it was like the best sandwich you ever had.
So I tried it.
It's that good.
There it is.
That sounds incredible.
Good job, Jerma.
The only problem is I'm not a huge pepperoni and salami fan.
Okay, so you're not into like the salted like dry meat.
I like it.
I just I don't really love it.
That's fair.
You know what it does?
It just gives the chicken a little extra push.
Like it doesn't really you don't get as you can put as much or as little pepperoni,
but I loved it.
Are you more mustard or more mayo?
Because I think you're more of a mayo guy.
I would imagine.
I like them both, but I'm more of a mayo guy.
Okay.
Yeah, I am too.
You know what?
You know what other kind of guy I am?
Kind of guy that is enjoying this experience.
Thank you to EA for sponsoring this stream again.
If you want to check it out, it's on PlayStation 5, Xbox Series X and Series S.
Kind of a monster hunting game.
You can, you know, get materials.
Quite shit.
Pretty fun.
Thank you, EA again.
I'd like to point out that I don't have to say any of those things,
but I'm enjoying the game.
I'm enjoying it.
I got to find a time to come out to the East Coast.
Just do like an East Coast trip.
Yeah, you should.
Ross was out here not too long ago.
And I took him for a pizza.
I took him.
We had some cool, cool stuff.
Good meals and stuff.
It's fun.
Kraken was here a couple.
Kraken was here around the holidays.
And we got some some noodles and stuff.
And yeah, it was fun.
I could go for some New York pizza.
I'll tell you.
That's like my favorite style.
Well, I know the spots.
Oh, I bet you do.
What do you got in Vegas?
I love pizza in Vegas.
Dogshit.
There is like no good pizza in Vegas, unfortunately.
There's some that are okay that I've had.
Vegas is not a pizza city at all.
This one.
This is a monster we've never seen, I don't think.
So what?
We'll go to it.
We'll check it out.
So what do you what in Vegas is good that like you go for on a regular occurrence?
Pretty much any of the sit down restaurants in Vegas are some of the best in the country.
You're talking about like like steakhouse type stuff?
Steak houses, a lot of sushi places that are like 10 out of 10.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
There's a lot of like amazing Korean barbecue out here.
Dude, I love Korean barbecue.
Yeah.
You got McDonald's?
We got McDonald's.
We got McDonald's out here.
Oh, nice, dude.
All right.
Is that the same monster?
I think it is.
Why is it a question mark?
Well, there's a Sap Scourge.
This might be one we've never seen before.
It looks weird.
Oh, wait, wait, it does.
No, no, that looks like the one.
I think so, yeah.
Yeah.
Let's get it.
Okay, hang on.
Let me see if I can build a wacky thing here.
He's just like in the village, just hanging out in here.
He's just chilling.
He's literally just hanging out in here.
Ask him what his McDonald's order is.
You won't be disappointed.
It's changed over the years, though.
Why?
Was that like a weird order or?
I used to get like two McChickens, two McDoubles,
a large drink, a large fry.
It was fucking bad.
It was actually bad.
How do you eat that much?
I don't know.
I just did.
Okay.
It was bad.
Are you up here?
Are they where?
I am.
I'm ready.
All right.
You ready to take this down?
Yeah.
Let's do it.
We got resources.
Yep, I got 12.
You got enough?
Yeah, I'm ready.
Let's do it.
Okay.
As soon as we find that weak point,
I'll be able to like shoot it directly.
All right.
That was a big hit.
May have exposed some flesh.
Two.
He's exposed over on this side.
Okay.
Now, Jerma, if you grab that stuff,
you can get a ton of materials.
Really?
All right.
How do we?
I got to try to get.
The run button and then just like jump onto it.
And then you continue grabbing
and then you can get all the materials.
It's amazing.
I know.
Face cam is on.
People are going to love that one.
Clip it.
I don't care.
All right.
I'm seeing materials.
Shit.
Oh, wait.
Has he got the glowing blue spot yet or no?
I got fucking magical.
Oh, he does.
He doesn't even know.
Okay.
See if I can grab some of this too.
Did the pig just say appreciate you?
What the fuck?
No, I don't think it did.
No, it did.
I swear to God, it did.
There's no way a pig spoke English.
It did.
I just did.
It had to have smoked English.
215.
Oh, nice hit.
Nice hit.
Big hit.
No.
Oh, come on.
I landed that.
Damn it.
These wash died.
Winging around.
I was so loud.
I'm sorry, dude.
I don't hear it.
It's being.
Yeah.
Discord is like just limiting the fuck out of that.
So it's not loud at all.
Slamming the compressor, I believe we call it in the biz.
We got it running.
Not yet.
Now it is.
There it goes.
All right.
Let's catch up.
It didn't go very far.
Not really.
I appreciate it.
Yeah.
It's like you hit him.
He's like, thank you.
I appreciate it.
His mouth moved perfectly to appreciate it.
It was actually very humorous.
People are saying that you got a lot of good Mexican food in small places.
Oh, yeah.
In Korean traditional barbecue.
It seems like you have everything except like good bagels and good pizza.
I'll tell you.
Sub shops and pizza places.
Yeah.
Some there are some good breakfast places,
but that counter serve deli counter serve subs pizza.
Yeah, I live for that.
That's my favorite food.
And it's not here.
Yeah.
Well, you're an East Coast guy.
I guess you kind of grew up with that like I did.
So yeah, I love that shit.
It's very angry.
Be careful.
Wait.
That was awesome.
Get it.
Oh, that was a good one.
It didn't look like I did any damage.
So we're phase three is when it is horns light up, right?
I think so.
Nice.
Okay.
Two.
Wait, what?
What do you mean to?
Oh, shit.
I don't even know if that hurt.
That was full, though.
215.
Okay.
Now I'm getting it.
Horns coming up.
This game has critical range.
Oh, you have to be closer to do better damage with the bow.
I see.
Oh, this dude just slammed through my bulwark or work.
Let's get fucking weird.
Watch this.
Oh, never mind.
I don't have enough resources.
Shit.
That was good.
Seems pretty unhappy.
Oh, my God.
It's weak point.
Get the blue weak spot.
I do, but it doesn't.
If your crosshair is white, it won't do damage.
Oh, that makes sense.
I don't have any.
Oh, what?
What don't you have for a bulwark?
I was trying to do a bulwark.
Okay.
I got one up over here.
Get it.
Nice.
All right.
That was like 500.
I understand now, chat.
I was just too far away because this bow is amazing.
And I was wondering, like, why is this weapon so broken?
It's because you have to be kind of close.
That's why we place this shit everywhere like this.
Just to be able to hop around.
So you make a permanent route.
I get it.
And then the world just changes as you continue adding stuff.
So that way it's like...
I mean, when people were saying death stranding,
I was like, wait, what are you talking about?
Now I kind of understand.
We have a situation over here.
What's that situation?
You'll see when we turn the corner.
Oh, that of the situation.
Yeah, the sap scourge, dude.
I think it's all right.
Keep going.
Yeah, I think we could just keep moving.
Is it a better spot for it?
It was an amazing shortcut, Jerma.
Got one?
Oh, yeah.
You got to take that.
It's literally right exactly where we have to be.
Why can I not grab this?
What's wrong with me?
You hold the run button, press A, jump into it.
What's going on here?
That was weird.
It was covering my health a little bit.
All right.
Let's finish it.
They do make these big trees.
It's really weird.
Oh, damn.
I just got my ass handed to me.
Try to get back again.
It's like almost some Star Wars in this music.
Like the Force theme.
It's very good.
It's very, like, intense.
It is.
Yes.
Worth it.
Got a bulwark?
Ah, don't even need it.
I'm running out of heals.
Too far.
Oh, no, not too bad.
Still did some decent damage.
I got a bulwark up in case we need it.
I'm going to run behind it.
Oh, you got it.
You got it.
It is now time.
Right in the head.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah.
Oh, that felt so good because we lost to it the first time.
It's like even more satisfying.
You can do the final blow.
Yeah, yeah.
What happened?
That was weird.
Wait, did I just destroy our tower?
I just like, I guess I don't know.
I broke a lot of buildings.
What happened?
I don't know.
Okay.
That was fun.
All right, great.
Lyco tower destroyed, yeah.
Charge blue-green arrows for level three for volley arrows.
Can you charge level three?
I guess you can, if you're saying I can.
Why did this come out, by the way?
This come out like today.
I believe last night or midnight, maybe.
Okay, because I was wondering, like, how do people even, like, know how to do?
And now I understand.
Tattoo that logo on your head.
Did you see the land retake its original form?
By hunting the Yamaugachs, you reversed the influence of the Kemono.
Minato is but a stone's throw from here.
You saved it from being...
I don't think he said the Amogus chat.
So I wonder if that's the first sort of, like, tutorial chapter.
Because I feel like at the very...
I think it is, chat was saying.
Yeah, at the end of that, I feel like I know how to play the game.
I feel like the guy know how to play now.
Like, I get it.
The answer you seek is woven into your soul.
You need only reach out and grasp it.
As guidance, I can give you only this.
Hunt, hunt the Kemono.
You know, with brave...
For a second, I was like, what's wrong with the game?
Oh, no, that was what was wrong with me.
This is impatience, is all it is.
Whoop, whoop, whoop.
Excellent.
What's this?
Uh, I don't know.
Back in action.
That tower just, like, got destroyed again.
Wait, what?
Jerma, what's happening here?
I'm just so strong.
Literally, what the fuck?
I think...
I think it doesn't want us to lose the tower,
but the pig is lying on top of it.
Can we get the pig out of here?
How do we move the pig?
He's ruining our structures.
It doesn't take much to amuse me.
I swear to God.
How do we delete it?
I don't know.
Here, I think I know how to do it.
I'll try to delete it.
It's hog-locked.
Yeah, I think it's because we got the exact moment
when I baseball swung him into that structure,
and I think he's stuck inside of it.
That just scared the shit out of me.
And I didn't even, like, it didn't even look like it.
I didn't go like, holy shit.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, all right.
Well, that just keeps happening.
Look for dragon pits.
Let's look for dragon pits.
Over here, look.
Yeah, the pig is too big on top of everything.
Okay, so then we can do this one.
Good.
Believe it or not, that was the hog that said that.
I want to see the clip of that.
It was funny.
So I'm just getting the essence of each sentence, you know?
All right, I want to see this.
All right, Vinny, if you want to see the pig talk,
uh, open up my stream in...
Someone already linked the clip.
Oh, okay, there you go.
I gotta...
It was very humorous.
I gotta watch it in a second.
All right, I'm gonna watch it now.
Yeah, let's watch it.
Oh, my God.
Your face, too.
Did the pig just say, appreciate you?
It's fucking perfect.
It's uncanny.
It's like, perfect.
It's perfect.
I gotta show the chat because they really want to see it.
Look, and you can see, like, Jerma's reaction to it.
He's just, like, befuddled.
That was fun.
This is a...
Ooh, look at the mountain.
Okay, hang on, hang on.
That was really fucking perfect timing.
Okay, uh, look at the mountain.
There's a mountain.
Huge, right behind you.
Oh, shit.
Flying vine.
Ah, it wants us to do this.
What, like, to the mountain or to this place?
Oh, right, right.
Yeah, I almost missed it.
So now this is...
I think we're opening up the hub world or something, right?
That's what it seems like.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I think this is the big town.
Appreciate it.
I gotta watch it one more time.
Just one...
I promise one more, and that's it.
Like, it was...
It's perfect.
It's actually, like, kind of perfect.
Did the pig just say appreciate you?
It's...
I love it so much.
That's, like, my favorite moment of the whole day.
Well, we made it.
Someone just said that would be a good sub-graphic for a stream.
It's just a close-up of the pig, and I appreciate it.
Yeah, it even sounded like it came from the pig's direction, too.
Yeah.
Yeah, this is definitely, like, the hub world.
There's no bunny dongo here, chat.
There is bunny dongo junior, though.
So here's a big kicker here.
Yes.
Hold on, this is...
What are we...
What is that?
It's some kind of sack.
Is that the...
I think we carved that off of one of the monsters.
Off of a rat?
Yeah.
It's like those popping videos you see on the internet.
It's a big payout.
It's the scorn goal of the dong fish.
You weren't very good at that, apparently.
Don't talk during the movie.
Started to feel at home yet?
Well, good for you, then.
Or run.
Yeah, from Final Fantasy X.
Time to go to sleep.
Good talk.
Yeah, good talk with that dude.
Jeremiah, are you seeing your character or my character?
I see your character.
Why do they always wear these jabroni outfits,
like in these monster hunting games?
Like, I swear to God, they have the jabroniest outfits I've ever seen.
New armor can now be forged.
Let me take a look at this area.
Your home is a convenient place.
You go, all right, so here's the kicker.
This was the kicker.
This was...
Here we go.
We are still in each other's game.
I can see you were literally running around across the way.
Oh yeah, I see the chef.
Yeah, there you go.
That's a huge...
Do you have a home or is this my home only?
Be honest.
That's a big deal.
That I don't...
We don't...
Like, oh, invite me from like something
and I join this thing.
Join off me.
We're just here.
Forever.
Yeah, it's convenient.
It's nice that we haven't had any disconnects either.
It's like we're just playing the game.
Doesn't feel like in a pain in the ass.
No.
The only thing was we just had to complete the tutorial
and then that was it.
It's like 10 minutes, 15 minutes.
You're welcome.
So we have gear to craft.
He's wearing like a modern day looking mask.
What is it?
I'm gonna come find you.
Can I use this stuff here?
Oh, sick.
Oh, man.
You can make ornaments.
Okay, Vinny, I'm gonna need to do something for me.
Just stay right there.
Just turn around and look over here when I tell you.
Okay, go ahead and look.
You had the exact same idea.
I was about to do the same thing.
Yeah.
That's the...
You put this...
Oh my God, don't kill anybody.
How do I get up there though?
If I want to go up there,
I wonder if there's a way to do that.
Oh yeah, there is.
Oh, you put it in your hair.
We do have new materials from that pig, so...
Oh yeah.
I gotta find the forge.
Over by me?
Wait, what happens when you jump into the water?
Oh, you just die.
Cool.
What is that 40?
40 what?
Is that like elemental damage?
A 40 of OE.
Oh, this is...
Okay.
So that's more damage.
And so when it topples over,
I do 13% more damage if they're toppled over.
What is nimble fingered?
Oh, I can...
Yeah, I can do this now.
I can upgrade the sword.
Very cool.
Bare thread.
What does that do?
Inhibit stamina loss when Karakuri thread has run out.
Okay.
If I want to keep going down this path,
I need to kill the King Tusk probably a few more times.
You can't afford to neglect the equipment that affords you protection.
Armor mods?
Wait, wait, did I...
I'm not sure if I forged a new weapon or if I just put things...
Oh, enhance.
There's a button that says enhance.
I see.
Okay, now that's the next level.
Oh, and I can upgrade to the Creeping Vine Nodachi.
This is centered.
What does that mean?
That was like E3 gamer talk right there.
Is this centered?
Yeah, hold on.
I kind of just...
I glossed over everything it just told me.
Strong arm spirit.
It's like an evil meter.
Final blow.
Boost attack power against toppled kimono.
Boost the chance of landing critical hits for a while when Hunter's arm is activated.
I don't know what that is.
I might have just beansed it.
Is there an undo?
Oh, fuck.
No.
Used materials will be returned.
Oh, it's only a gold cost.
Yeah, that's easy.
No, I didn't blow it, chat.
It's all good.
You can get your materials back.
Oh, that's good to know.
So we need to talk to the person over...
How are you doing, by the way?
You good to...
Do you like another monster or are you good?
I can do one more fight.
Okay.
Do one more.
If you want to go kill a toppled rat or some weird slime or something.
Yeah, let's try to find the next monster.
Yeah, let's do one more.
This thing has a running fire swing.
This thing's just burning now.
Oh, that's the new thing I got.
All right, that's cool.
I get it.
So that's fire damage.
Of course it is.
Human path modification.
Kimono path modification.
Where did I shoot that thing?
There it is.
Wait a minute.
What's going on here?
We might have to climb to the roof to get on that thing that I made.
Okay.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah, I had to do that earlier.
How do you equip a different weapon?
Do you have to do that at the forge?
Change equipment.
So at that same lady, you can do change equipment.
Oh, I see.
Okay.
Someone in my chat named CostcoHotDog150, which is...
That's a great name, by the way.
Said, can you convince Jerma to drink a 40 on his stream and burp directly into his camera?
I mean, how would you convince me to do that?
I'm not going to even try.
You guys enjoying your dinner?
Not even going to try.
Oh, there's a ball over here.
No, I'm not going to drink a 40 on stream.
Have you ever done Edward 40 hands?
Do you know what that is?
Edward 40 hands.
Yeah, it's when you, like, electrical tape or duct tape two 40s to each of your hands,
and you can't, like, get rid of them until you drink them.
It's Edward 40 hands, yeah.
No, I'm not going to do that on stream.
All right, you ready to go to the new location?
Is that the new location?
I think the new location is we have to talk to this person.
Oh, I thought they were in the new location.
Yeah.
Wait, I think you have to do it, actually.
I'll do it, yeah.
Someone said, I heard you talking about Edward 40 hands, so I joined your stream instead.
That's sick.
You know what would be cool?
If everyone came to my stream and just, like, followed my stream,
that would be, like, that would be really cool.
You should do that.
And based.
Do it right now.
Even do it right.
I mean, there are almost 12,000 people here right now.
All of you better go follow.
No, no, no, no.
And you're fine right now.
You better do it right now.
What's going on?
I'll just have to get you to drink a 40 at some point, but it's fine.
It's making the bridge repairs on the old blossom trail impossible.
I'm already followed.
This is an ad for EA, but for Vinnie, I suppose so.
Wait, why can't it be both?
It can be both.
Carrie, request.
What if we talk to Toga Hime?
Is that he Hime or Hime?
I don't know how to pronounce that.
I don't know, because I'm not the host.
I can just sit here.
Wait, can I emote?
How do I do emote?
It probably is emote, right?
They're right on the D-pad.
Chat, I swear to God, I thought this was a person with no face.
Like, I thought that was their shoulders and like their head was missing.
Re-input.
OK, you are.
Dude, everybody just left your screen.
Heck!
Lots of cool and basic chat members that have just entered my channel.
Very nice.
Very cool.
I promise you, new chat members, I will not drink a 40.
I will not be on camera.
I will not eat a grilled cheese off the ground.
That seems like a little...
I don't know why you wouldn't.
Oh, no, you shouldn't.
It's not the best deal for these new viewers,
but I can make a funny noise once in a while.
Let's hear it.
What's your best funny noise besides that one?
I'll go first.
OK.
That just sounds like you ate a grilled cheese off the ground.
They are not good.
They're not being good.
Space cams should be revoked.
Show him the AI snake.
Well, there's an AI version of me like shorting out
and making like really bizarre like death throw noises.
That was a pretty funny noise.
I thought, OK, I got this.
That was really good, actually.
That was pretty good.
My name is Tinky Winky.
I'm a Teletubby.
How you doing?
Hey.
Hey, that's pretty good.
Which Teletubby is you?
I'm the one that is orange, I think.
That's actually.
Oh, my God.
We could start a TV show with these two fucking voices.
Hey, welcome to the funny kids programming show.
Yep.
You know, but on the paper when I make all the rules,
you know what I'm saying?
That's kind of like Peter Griffin.
I don't know what you're talking about, Lois.
I mean, I never even once sounded like Peter Griffin.
All right.
Vinny, you are not sponsored to play this.
But can I just commission you right now to just on my stream?
You can mute your stream.
Can you just do that but say what platforms this is on?
I don't know what platforms it's on.
It's on Xbox, X and S, PS5, and PC.
Just mute your stream until it only comes through my stream
because I have the sponsor.
OK.
So excuse me, Vinny, where could I get this if I wanted to play it?
Be happy to tell you, Jamer.
Well, it's on Xbox Series X and X.
It's also on PC and PlayStation 5.
How you doing?
He said what he said.
He already forgot.
No, I got it right.
No, you got it right.
No, that was good.
That was actually really good.
Thanks, man.
Hey, thanks.
Free, by the way.
You could have that one.
Yeah, that was that was free.
Like I said earlier, I'm just happy to be here.
I love playing games with you, dude.
It's the it's fun.
Yeah, I'm glad we started doing this more often.
Exactly.
It's exactly what I was going to say.
I appreciate you, Jerma.
Appreciate it.
All right, appreciate this.
So where are we going?
We got to kill one more monster.
Head to Spirit Island.
So I guess we have to find the exit.
Are you near the exit?
Can you like?
I don't think I can activate it.
I think you have to.
I'm very interested in this, though.
So the Costco hot dog person said you're one step closer to gaining his trust.
Like, I'm not going to have him drink a 40 for you.
Like, I can't force Jerma to do anything.
So don't like stop Costco hot dog person.
That's you're weird.
Yeah, relax.
Oh, dude, right here.
Yeah.
So here I'll depart us.
There are so many options here.
I don't even.
People are people are going to go absolutely nuts with this.
There's like dummies.
There is training dummies.
There's bulwarks.
There's there's a lot of stuff here.
Honestly, yeah, there's a there's a there's a ton of things.
This is like a trap.
Powerful leverage brings down a massive hammer with terrifying force.
A single blow can stop a kimono in its tracks and crush any horror.
So you can set up like little traps and stuff.
And this goes forever.
That's cool.
There's some this is something else to put your points into, right?
Sounds fun.
The Costco hot dogs hit different.
They are.
You know what?
I will say they're fine.
They're just cheap.
They're fine.
They're big.
There's nothing wrong with it.
No, this area is ready.
They're fine.
I like the coral.
Good source of bacteria.
That's right.
When your gut biome is in danger, just go get a Costco hot dog.
Can we swim?
Kind of like.
No, not really.
Wait, why would I be able to?
OK, never mind.
Yeah, the weapons are so huge.
They're just like weighing us to the ground.
Hi.
Ah, all right.
Would you agree that Bologna or like hot dog pancakes?
Jerma, I think we've reached the point of no return for stupidity
and I can't stop reading these chat messages.
No, go for it.
I have the choice not to read these and I can't stop myself.
Welcome to every single day of my life.
I look over and it's just somebody will just say something
that's just so just so strange that I have to address it.
Exactly.
Yeah, that's like one of the reasons Jerma and I even know each other chat
is because like our chats ended up being kind of similar
and people started noticing like just the weird like the weirdness.
Yeah, it was a meme friendship.
Yeah.
But at the same time, there is like some commonality to the to the way the chat.
I mean, I mean, we have demographics.
Vinny, I'm sure you've looked at this or there's overlap.
Yeah, I think as of two or three, four years ago,
I think you and I have shared like 30 percent of our audience together.
Something makes about like 40 percent.
It's interesting.
Weird, weird dudes the same age that make weird scenarios.
However, I will say, though, Jerma, don't get used to this, but to compliment you,
you do put a lot of effort into your bits.
I don't.
Thank you.
Yeah, you do.
I whipped cream.
Jerma, I have whipped creamed an alien.
That's that's as far as I'll go for a bit.
I'll whip cream an alien.
That's it.
Can we just talk about how pretty this area actually is?
I love this place.
I love this.
I love the beach.
This looks awesome.
This is like Chrono Cross, like one of my favorite games.
Wow.
That kind of holy shit.
You just unlocked a memory in my head.
Yeah.
That looks like I was wondering.
That game is got like some pretty areas.
Watch this.
Check this out.
Let's explore over here.
Sounds good.
Let's go up.
Why not?
Oh, you can.
You can stop mid midway.
Like you don't have to keep going.
Like you could just slow down and stuff.
I did it on purpose.
OK, we put one of those under towers.
Yeah, I could do that.
I'll throw here.
You know what?
Let me fake.
Was it the whole that gave it away?
No, it's three presentation, dude.
Dog.
I couldn't decide between dude or dog.
So I said dog.
I can put one over here.
Search.
Oh, that's right.
We had we gave Jerma a dog.
Sona.
I forgot about that.
Hey, we all got one.
Yeah, we all got one.
I don't see anything from here.
OK, I'm going to place a tower in the middle here and hope for the.
Oh, Vinnie, open your mouth.
That circle is the range of this tower.
So there is no monster in this circle.
We're going to have to keep going.
Yes.
Took me a while to figure that out.
I'll be honest.
I think I knew that, but I was not putting it into like a like active effect.
I was just like hiding the information for some reason.
But can you pet the sea animals?
You can pet the turtle.
That's cute.
Wait, he dropped it.
He gave me an item because I was nice.
Yeah, they do that when you pet them.
What about the crab?
I can even pet the crab.
I don't think they feel it like crabs wouldn't like even know what that is.
Oh, he's not very happy.
Jerma, I found like a cool pirate ship and there's like a monster on top of it.
All right.
I'm coming.
My character is going to puke.
All right.
I'm coming.
So you are all the way back there.
Yeah.
And I found a really strange looking monster.
I'm coming.
Wait, let me get some thread.
Just sounds like flipper.
Chad, you know, you hear that?
This monster conjure a torch to engulf your weapon in flames when you attack.
I think I just picked up something to do that.
Oh, wow.
Okay.
Oh, Suno Bashiri.
Are we doing this?
I'm fighting this one over here.
I don't know.
This thing is going for it.
Yeah, it's really fast and it sounds like flipper.
Yeah, this thing's quick.
It does have like a dolphin sound.
You were good.
Come back.
Vinny, that's called a dolphin.
Yeah.
No, I just wanted to be even more specific with my reference.
That's all.
What's it doing?
Oh, what the fuck?
I okay.
That was pretty ridiculous.
Oh, do it.
Damn it.
Not in the head.
Come on.
Oh, didn't hit pounders can do.
All right.
So three springs makes a pounder.
Watch this.
Oh, man.
Yeah.
Three springs on top of each other makes like a big hammer that swings down.
Ready to go.
That's amazing.
Oh, shit.
Yeah, I'm like a little too slow for this enemy right now.
Then again, you have a hammer.
So honestly, you using the springs gets a knockdown if you get it right in the head.
Shit.
I'm trying to climb up there.
Stop camping.
Oh, I'm out of materials.
Is there any materials like any threads?
You know what?
I thought maybe the weak point, but this enemy might be too small to grab thread from.
Oh, shit.
Did I get it?
No.
So fucking fast.
Shit.
I don't have any more.
Whoa, did you get it?
Now's the time.
Yeah, now's the time.
Yes.
Oh, I got the big hit.
All right, he's running.
All right, let's try to get some thread, too, because that hammer move is so good.
You can collect it from a lot of places.
Someone said they keep hearing the Splatoon disconnect sound.
It's the same thing.
It's just like a water drop with a reverb.
The threads.
Threads over here.
I found some, too.
If you hold down left trigger, you can see what gives you.
Yeah, it's like it's like spider vision.
You're going to want to see this on my way.
Yeah, it was very odd.
Oh, is this the same thing we were attacking before?
Smash it.
Oh, it is.
Yeah, it's mad.
Oh, don't die here.
What did you just make?
Pounder.
Oh, that was a pounder.
Yep.
Oh, opportunity.
Nice.
Just did like 396 damage or 68 rather.
Stay right here.
I got 250.
Oh, that would have been fucking awesome.
Whatever.
A lot of materials over here.
Jerma, if you walk into the torch, your weapon will.
Oh, oh, he put it out.
I don't know the big sack bounce.
Oh, that hurts a lot.
I am dead.
Thank God.
He ran away.
All right.
Healing, healing, healing.
Thank you.
Dammit.
Smash.
Oh, missed.
Nice.
No stun, though.
Oh, I got sacked.
Not too bad.
Oh, you got worse than I did.
Yeah, that hurt.
All right.
Seems to be out of that weird like intense mode.
Do you have any materials for this?
I got no materials.
All out.
I think we're pretty close, though.
Yeah, it should shouldn't be too much longer.
What the hell?
That was weird.
Running materials.
Yeah, there's a crystal over here.
Yep.
This is also one of those dragon things.
All right.
Is that a wooden horse?
I got full threads.
Finding a lot of these balls.
Oh, here comes trouble.
Yeah, this is a wooden horse.
Can we break it?
I don't think so.
Where did where'd our friend go?
Oh, down that way.
Very far away.
Oh, we're saying funny comedic line.
Oh, I see what you're doing.
Jerma, we're gonna we're gonna do this.
Ready?
You're talking about dropping down from
I'm dropping down from the zip line.
I think I fucked up.
Hang on.
Let me try again.
We could do that.
We could we could zip up here.
Maybe now we get this.
All right.
If we get this, there needs to be only pogs in the chat.
Okay.
So you take one up here and then jump off from here.
Maybe I'm not sure I did a good job with this.
No, we're getting close, dude.
Never mind.
It was still cool.
It's not even the same monster.
It's not?
No.
What?
Oh, this is yeah, this is like a peacock.
What the fuck is this?
Where did the monster go?
Down here?
Uh, come over here.
Did you find it?
I think it's down here.
Let's activate this.
All right.
Ready?
That's it.
Right?
Yep.
Right here.
All right.
Pogs in the chat.
No!
What?
Did you get it?
So I certainly didn't.
I just felt flat on my fucking face.
We died.
Yeah, we died.
It's all right.
That was really oh my god.
I thought that was going to do like 10,000 damage.
No, we didn't die.
We didn't die.
No, we're good.
We're good.
All right.
Oh my god.
I thought that was going to do like a hundred K.
That's sad.
All right.
I'm engaging.
Big hit.
Damn it.
Nice.
That was perfect.
No stun though.
I just got.
Wow.
He knocked me into the water.
Damn it.
That was an unbelievable amount of damage.
Oh, it's okay.
This is it.
I just always horn knocked off.
I think we did it.
Nice.
You can do the final.
No, you can do the honors.
Okay.
I want to see a hammer lodged into its cranium anyway.
Crash.
Wait, what happened?
Oh, okay.
I see.
I think the horn came off.
That's crazy.
Cool.
Glider.
Make sure you get the horn.
It's also like, yeah, we don't even have to initiate a hunt.
We just like are just hunting.
You can just kind of go wherever you want.
Yeah.
Now you can conjure gliders.
The tools, I think.
Dude, I'm in a helicopter.
All right.
That's pretty cool.
You probably figure out what you want to use for a loadout for this stuff.
I imagine.
Yeah, you probably choose when you unlock a bunch of them.
Because at some point, you're going to have a couple dozen of these, right?
So, I mean, you kind of have to choose what you want.
Wind vortex.
How did you get the glider?
What happens when you stack gliders?
I think you have it now too, no?
Do I?
Is it in that Karakuri menu or no?
Yeah, it's a A button.
Oh, so we just have it now?
Yeah.
Or you could just take one of mine.
What are the physics of this?
How does this even work?
I think it just kind of floats around.
Well, that was fun.
Are you good?
I'm done.
I'm going to go to sleep.
I'm tired.
But I actually enjoyed this more than I expected to.
Not to say it like that.
But once you start fighting and getting the mechanics, it is fun.
Mechanically, the game is sound.
And I like the monsters.
So I'm ready to go to sleep now.
Like other games like this, like in Monster Hunter or whatever,
you really do need to play for like an hour or two before it's like, oh, I get it.
OK, because after the first couple of hours, we just kind of learn what
is when you first get shown this new mechanic, it's kind of like, what the fuck is this?
What is this?
And then it's like, oh, wait.
Oh, oh, yeah, no, it's pretty much.
Yeah, it was good.
And it was just good playing playing game with your germ.
No, I enjoyed this.
Thanks for I mean, I reached out.
It was like, hey, you want to do this?
So Vinny was was cool enough to jump in.
So yeah, well, thanks for the invite.
I'm going to quit out.
And yeah, thanks, everybody.
And German chat, thank you for like bringing your unhinged chat messages
to my chat for a little bit.
That was fun.
And yeah, I'm sure we'll play more stuff in the future.
But thanks, man.
Have a good night.
Yeah, you too.
Thanks for coming up.
See you.
That was Vinny.
Fine sauce.
Awesome, dude.
Because I figured playing a game like this multiplayer is kind of more interesting anyways,
for me at least.
And that is going to conclude the sponsor part of the stream.
Like Vinny said, I'm pleasantly surprised.
Took a little bit to kind of get the feel of things, but it's really fun.
I have to imagine that there'll probably be some patches for it.
It's on everything again.
EA, thank you for sponsoring this part of the stream.
That was really, really cool.
I very much enjoyed that time.
Multiplayer was smooth in a game like this.
Like I said, that's probably the number one feature that,
I know I keep harping on it, but I keep talking about it.
That's really nice to not just be able to jump in and just play.
But yeah, thank you, EA.
That concludes this part of the stream.
We're going to move on.
I'm going to go back to last hero of nostalgia.
That was Wild Hearts, available now on pretty much every platform,
every current platform.
So I'm going to take a break.
I'll be right back.
I'm going to pee, maybe get some more water,
and we will play some more.
Be right back.