Ready? Get ready. He's gonna say it. He's gonna say it right now. Ready what?
War. War, yeah. War never changes today. War never changes. No, I don't.
Okay, skip.
Can you get that? It's probably that salesman. He comes for you every day.
Just got hit in the face by a broomstick, honey. Can you get the goddamn door?
Hey, what's going on guys? Welcome to Federal Offense with German985.
What's that? We're gonna take this guy's mail? Federal off-
He doesn't have any mail. Hold on. We're gonna find a guy with a mail in his mailbox.
Oh, fuck it. We're really gonna town now. Who cares?
Huh? Oh shit. A raider.
Get him. Get him. Get him, boy.
Don't kick my dog, you fucking bitch.
See if he had anything worth taking.
We're looking for cash. We're looking for ammunition, supplies. Or you could take off all the guys clothes.
Easy with that thing, dude. Easy with that thing, dude.
Take a look at that, boy. Diamond City. It's a beautiful area. Wonderful people.
Let's get to know some of them.
Looking for someone who's gone missing.
Gone missing? Who is he?
A baby boy. Kidnapped.
A baby boy? Really? I'm afraid.
I'm lost, pastor. I need help. Please.
Well, I don't want Nick Valentine.
Thanks. I'll go talk to him.
Take care of yourself now.
Piper, you're back.
Who's there? Gonna be a good fight.
Will you shut up?
Seriously, I'm trying to like sneak up on people and this guy's just screaming at them. Will you duck?
Wait, the hell?
You fucking idiot.
This is what happens when you scream.
When you scream about puny humans. When we're trying to be sneak attacking. What do you want me to do, dude?
Get cover.
Officer?
Nice hat.
You like my hat? Thanks.
Park the car in the yard? How about I hammer you in the heart with a haymaker?
Oh, Boston.
No funny business.
You're from Boston.
Get me out of here.
Our new arrival. I wish I was in your shoes. Getting to see our glorious city for the first time. How can I help you?
A man named Kellogg used to
Oh, what is that? I-95? Oh, that's a good fucking highway.
The history of Boston Common.
I'm interested in the history of this place.
Let us go back hundreds of years. It is the year 1775 or seven years.
Excuse me.
Gotta pick me up if you're feeling glum.
You got drugs?
Oh!
Did you say something about drugs?
That's right. All the chems you need to fill out your lifestyle.
Right.
Everyone here buys from-
Fuck you! How dare you sell drugs?
Uh, not now.
Cool. Cool.
You should think about getting a trim.
Yeah. Hey, can I have a sip of your Coca-Cola? Thanks.
Uh-huh.
Can I, uh, can I have a sip of your other Coca-Cola? Thanks.
You're using that umbrella. It might rain tomorrow. Thanks.
Don't be shy now.
Can I have the container that holds the umbrella, too? I don't think I have one.
Oh, thanks. Can I have the desk fan, too? Thanks.
Can I have all this stuff in your medicine cabinet? Thanks.
What about your safe? There's a lot of stuff in here, too.
Can I have-
This could be yours.
I'll put it back!
Just wait!
I'm gonna put it back!