Early Andy? No, right on time, Andy.
Precisely on time.
201?
Pacific time? How you doing? Well 201, okay.
So in the time it takes to go from 2 to
201 is
59 seconds, right?
So technically if I show up at 2 and
58 seconds, I'm still on time.
Well, you're gonna like, you're gonna like look over my shoulder and see when I clock in?
You know, like what if you like just forget to clock in? Well, what if you clock in?
Okay, what if you get there and you have to go to the bathroom or something?
You're like, should I get it? I could take a piss real quick. To me, okay, as your boss, right?
I'm as your boss.
You've got it, but you've got like a 10 minute window there.
And I'm talking before or after. It doesn't matter, right?
Like you've got like a 10 to 15 minute window where I don't give a shit at all.
Like you clock, did you clock in at like
208? I don't give a shit at all. I don't care. You know why I have that philosophy?
Sometimes I'm two hours late.
I'm two hours late, but you better be within 10 minutes.
That's not, no, you could show up an hour late too. All right, that's fine.
What an excuse.
I don't, I don't, punctual, punctual, I'm not punctual.
Look, shit happens every second of every day.
Oh, you got something to do it at like exactly at 2 p.m., right?
Yeah, but like what if you need gas or something? Like, oh fuck, I didn't get gas.
Just go get gas. I don't care. It's like 205, 206.
I'm not gonna look at the clock and wait for you.
Now if it's more than 30 minutes, then like I'm gonna text you and be like, is everything all right?
Within 10 to 15, 20, move it up to who cares?
What are we doing today? That's a good question because it's gonna be really fun.
Today!
We are gonna be doing a
stream, a special stream. We did this about a year and a half ago, two years ago, and we're gonna do it again.
There's been requests to bring this back.
It's a really fun time. I don't know what we're gonna get. It's a gigantic gotcha
of every single video and broadcast I've ever done. And what does that mean?
So Lazy Luke, sort of the community webmaster here,
put together this kind of randomizer of everything I've ever done a
couple of years ago, and we did it and
there's a big, I think as of now, since it's been updated.
The last year or two of streams, it has been put in here, too. So we might get something that happened like a week ago.
So what happens is
it's a little randomizer site.
You click a button and it's going to give you
a random
timestamp of a random VOD or video over the last 11 years.
And it totals out to be
something like over
4,000 hours of video, which is about 170 days.
So if you just let this go and just watch every single thing I've ever done, it would take you
170 days straight, 24 hours.
Which is weird to think about. I'm surprised there's that much even. It's weird. And we're gonna watch the whole thing.
No, we're not. There's gonna be a few rules here. You better get cracking. No, just hold on. There's rules.
You have to follow the rules.
Rule number one. Each one of these has a timer of 120 seconds. I am thinking of making that higher or lower.
I don't know. We have to kind of come to a community consensus on this here. I
get five vetoes.
Guess what?
You get five vetoes too.
Because if chat is, if chat really wants to skip something and there's a lot of people in the chat saying skip, skip, skip, skip, skip,
right? We'll take a general consensus and we'll do a poll. If you vote to veto that means we skip.
But I think two minutes is too low if vetoes are in play.
Well, that's not gonna work. Well, then I just get five vetoes. Who cares? I'm in control of this shit.
So I get five vetoes. I gotta make sure I use them correctly. Five minutes? I think five minutes is too long.
Three? Two? How long? What do you think? Five minutes is like as long as entire videos I used to make were. Three minutes?
Yeah, three is good. Three is good. That's 180 seconds.
So the last, we got a lot of Nancy Drew last time and also this reversed vetoes too, right?
If I want to stay for more than three minutes, we're staying for more than three minutes.
Also, to make this a little more interesting,
there's gonna be a bingo card of
various things that have happened over the years. You know what, let's just do this. Let's get over here.
I pressed it one time and I will watch it for two minutes, okay? I promise.
I want to show the, I want to show the board. We're gonna make it even more interesting. Okay, so here we go.
So let's change that to 180. As you see here,
a lot of these are very possible. If this shows up on the broadcast,
we obviously have to put a stamp on it, right?
Like this. And if you get bingo, if bingo, I have big rigs in the background,
I know. If you get bingo, then
I didn't really think of, I don't know, I'll give a hundred community subs. That sounds easy, right?
How about this? I'll give a hundred community subs if you get bingo. I'll give,
uh, hold on. How much should I give?
How many subs should I give? Let me, hold on. Let me, let me like, think of how like, okay, hold on a minute.
What's 250 subs? How much money is that? It's a lot, right? I can't do math in my head. It's
1200 bucks. That's 2, 2, 2, 2, 500 dollars.
1200 bucks. 1250. Okay. Alright.
If you fill the whole board, if we fill the whole board in this stream, by the way,
I have to give a time limit on this stream because if we stay here long enough,
we're gonna get every, we're gonna fill the whole board in at least three or four hours.
Horizontal row four is gonna be so easy. You think so? I don't think do it
I don't haven't done doi doi doi that look, okay
We'll go over these because I want to make sure this is really really very clear
Jack's moment is when I'm playing a game very very well has to be incredibly clear not just like oh you jumped to that
Platform correctly. No like a gamer moment where it's like, holy shit. I can't believe you just did that. Look at me
poses, you know
I don't know
You know what I'm talking about and when I put my arms in weird places hog face me know that
Rants are fine rants. You know, I just go off and start talking with something my crazy and a rant does not be bringing up
Any topic it's a rant ball joke. We all know that that's when I deliberately fall off of a cliff to make everybody laugh and write
Lul and make me you know, feel happy character voices any impression or character that I'm doing one guy is you
Otto is Otto lich. You don't need a gambling is any gambling on stream
It's I'm not gonna say that's like could that be debt oriented. No, I think that's on here, isn't it? No, yeah
That is already on here. See debt ordeal
Gambling is not debt ordeal as well
It has to be like I'm playing blackjack or I'm like gambling on the on stream
Naked is when I talk about maybe if I talk about being naked which happens a lot
drug
It's I don't think that's gonna show up because there's another two years worth of streams
It just became way less likely percentage wise that drew crew will show up
What else is a could be on here that might be you're saying an emote out loud is another one
If TF2 shows up if a wrestling video shows up or if I get scared if you get bingo
100 community subs if you fill the whole board in three hours
I'll give 250 subs as that's on you just did all I I know but I understand bingo
I know what about being high now
That's not on here a lot of community members helped with this
There's been a couple of iterations kind of just grabbed from a bunch of what people were talking about different mods community members
So thank you contributed to this. Thank you
It makes the stream that much more fun and I think we can go so can we get him maybe a link to this
You probably linked it a few three and a half hours or the deal is off. What no three hours is perfect
You know if you want to open it up and play for yourself
And if you want to open up so you can scream at me when something happens
Are you ready to go through the ages by the way to test it?
I was going back and forth with a Luke last night. I've tested it a few times and
I landed on really really kind of like cringy TF2 video
There was like a live commentary, and I like hated it, so I I'm very ready to use my five vetoes
Already I don't I have to be careful though
I have to see if I can stomach some of those older videos
Because if I can then I can save my vetoes for something very important right all right
So let's get this off make sure the timer is correct, okay?
So this is three minutes, and I did press it once already, so this is I believe a YouTube video of
On the main channel. This is the worst game. This is okay. What's good. Are you ready? I'm ready
Let's go in three face cam not yet if you're good three two one go
Oh look at how much fun. This is god damn it. That's not a voice hold on. I
It's almost a 90-degree angle. I gotta do it that doesn't count
That's not a funny. That's I do that
Sick Tony Hawk ramp that doesn't count. I'm playing on a half pipe right now. Not a character voice
That's me doing me we do like a 720
God damn it no already hold on all right funds over go through this is that I'll take game glitch is fine game
Which is mine is fucking awful truly truly a disgraceful game. I can't think of anything worse
I really can't think of a game. That's that's worse than this okay. This is not a brand no
It's not it's not a rant. This is not even a video game. Well here. He's a bridge. No good bridge
That was fun. Yeah, it was fun going over or something with no detection on it
No, it's not a rant. That's complaining. I don't know man if somebody can tell me in the comment section a game
That's worse than this. I would can either go. It's gonna be pretty tough. I can't I can't think of anything not not blow oh
No, it's okay. Oh look. There's my buddy. This is yelling. Oh, there's my friend. Hey. Hey, remember when you
You are winner. Oh, hey, don't worry guys. You are winner. We'll do random race
I want a veto already sounds like fun. No, that's not a voice. That's me going like this
That's not a voice. That's me. Just changing my voice to be like funny for a second all right. We're in like in
What what three minutes is too long? No, I didn't do any days. Why did I just win the game?
It didn't I didn't even have a chance to move what do it again. That was stupid. I don't alright. Thanks for the win
I'll take the victory. I'll have my KD go up or my win-loss go up. This is old video
What the fuck
Stop doing this. Is it how much time is in the video random race?
It's not even enough time in the video to get to the end of the time stop giving me the victory automatically
This game is trying to tell me to stop playing
ready
Yeah
Right
Hold on the the timers look at the video is gonna end all right
So we have to go over this because people are freaking out about this no that is not
I understand that this is a game glitch right, but no that doesn't count as a voice that doesn't none of that counts
Anger does not equal rant. That's correct. That's the prime of your career. I'm not cheating. I'm not sure that doesn't count all right
Let's go. Let's go here. We go ready. We're going. Oh shit. I fucked it up all right here
We go people out of here. This is the movies whatever the other timer who are these people?
Extra extra no we don't want this many extras. This is the movies part one. Are you?
Okay, that's fine. That's fine. All right
Okay, we're in the bathroom still
Somebody enter it somebody here comes the guy with the fucking axe. That's the same lady
It's a fall joke fine fine
Is it is this is it the same person yeah, it is god damn it are you fucking kidding me hold on
All right
Prop bashing object I could do free space too. I have to group these together, so I don't have to keep pressing this
She walks it only two more
That was I'm gonna hit horror shot crane shot. That's not a laughing fit. No way
We you know what a laughing fit is here. That's not a movie no
It's gonna be horror shot to now. Where's the camera during this whole thing dress set?
There's so much shit to do here. I can't wait to fucking like to spend a million years here remember playing this
This was so new. Oh god. I missed this shit
It's just weapons. I wish they would just make another one of these so bad okay
This is just the intro that's gas lighting you yeah, how do we preview all right?
Let's all right talking with you in the free camera. Okay free camera
I wish that make it redo this whole thing and make more intuitive controls
This is ready for casting
Maybe I should do those tutorials
All right, I can stomach this one. I can I just want to see what happens here ready more actors
Yeah, does not come actor. Where's our nine ten seconds?
Where the hell come on these are actors man where we going
PlayStation 2 games hey you want to come hang out you climb up here with me. That's all this is all
This is a Jax moment. I hope not I should have known no. I'm gonna get pissed at this
I remember being really mad at this shit. Okay. I thought this is horrible
Yeah, I hated this. What's the fastest way to deal with this?
And it's a really good show you putting on that. It's in vain
He just kicked his own his friend one goes down get the other now. That wasn't a voice not even close
All right guy guy you look like a middle-aged magician. I
Actually can't believe that work I cannot believe that work
Not wrestling at all. Not even close nice comedy movie
If anything, this is gonna be pissed off
What do you put what game is this? What are your games is are the entire time you've an egomaniac mug?
I don't know. I'm looking at his hypothesis
The present from my mother. It's a they cannot hurt me ever
Just wait for the do that and then they'll eventually hit each other like that
Stand in the middle and just hold our one wait, they take too long. Yeah, I bought this on my own free will
Yeah, they're identical. They're a mirror. So they're gonna run into each other
45 seconds emotion captured real twins
Why did you play this but not Yakuza I played this I played this like
25 minutes at the same time at the same dance moves. Are you fucking serious? Are you?
Giving me right now drive that was close, but it doesn't count
No, that doesn't count row knife across the map throw tomahawk. That's not a character. That's no no
That's that's me fucking montage
End of the video Tomahawk kill across the map on Newtown. Thank you very much. Thank imagine if I had Call of Duty reference
Oh here much. I'll put it into your montage funny
Montage joke. All right, like you get it fine. I like how like I'm not even like breathing
For multiplayer too much laughing instant
Just stay like that the whole time don't laugh Jeremy don't laugh
This is gonna be this part of this video where there's no laughter, right? Let's set up the joke. Don't do it
I'll just like delivering my statue. It's like the art museum
Don't do it
That's him laughing
Alrighty then let's go get a helicopter. Oh, okay. All righty. This is off. All righty then
These guys are so much fun car right now looks like you know when like your dog gets into one of your toys and
Absolutely ruins it. Yeah
One of your toys
It's like this is the most messed up car one of your toys
Oh
I'm contemplating what vetoing every YouTube one. What was that?
Just ran you over you just ran me over behind no laughing
Was driving so fast
My screen I just insta died nothing even happened
I just felt like
What what the hell was that? Nope
Not me laughing
All of you to remember if something remotely interesting just happened slow it down and play it again. No, where's my parachute?
Where's my parachute? Good. All right, so meat that thing is gonna kill a lot of people
I feel bad for whoever that lands on what's with it. It looks like it's like sad faces and shit. What am I doing?
All right, I'm parachuting down to the Empire staple thing. Is that you right there? I don't think I'm gonna laugh that way
What's up? Stealth? Oh
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. No, no, no, no, no, no, no. No, this is not happening. You're not doing that
You're not doing this. I'm not gonna be able to land on this thing. Oh, he's coming after me. That's what's going on
Stop shooting me, please
No, this is not gonna work
Works I'm gonna just fell off. All right, boo. No laughing fit in the video. That's
What are you doing? What are you doing? I win
Five seconds, you better not shoot me off at the top of this
Oh
Yes, okay, here's hitman3 Oh
Look at the level. This is this is bad. All right, we have to update the bingo board
Because we had we had something happen there. What was it? I'm gonna give you character voice, right?
Cuz I mean here comes your the rant free space actually me put free space in now. All right, so hold on
What are you guys looking for here? So rumor and wrestling that's could happen very I'll reset the timer
Don't worry. All right. Let me see how like the path of where you can find the best
Okay, rumor might not happen wrestling might not happen if you get laughing fit and you get rant
That's gonna be close. It'd be close
I really don't want to play this because this is like embarrassing because I get this is like actually like a part of this
This is a stream that I did where I was like pissed out when I turned it off
I was like, I fucking hated that stream. I fucking hated that game. Well, I love the hitman3, but this level well
I'm gonna we're gonna do it. I'm sure I veto it. I think I might veto it
I'm like actually and this is like the surge to like the surge, right? Okay. Here we go. Let's just go
Good luck. Well, let me group these together because this is gonna be a group
This is gonna get this gonna start to turn into hell if I don't do this
Okay, there we go. All right resetting timer and
Three two one. Let's go. I had to don't sell me the drugs right here. What are you stupid? I save it here
Okay, thank God. You can listen to the tone of my voice. I'm already upset about something Richard Nixon impression. Sure
I'm fine. When they're pulling the bus, I bring that snob. It's already on there. It's already on there
In joke currency fake money, not real one. I'm so predictable. It's just such a joke
Why does he drop it on the ground? You notice that so give it to me. That's not one guy. No
Should I?
You know putting syringe on here wouldn't have been a bad idea
That's what I wanted to have happen last time good silent. Somebody will hear me if I stab him
And it ended it down to did it did it did it did it did it down to that?
I'm not a drug dealer. So now I have to walk up to one of these guys and sell drugs to him
I think we're yeah, we're missing the part where I go on the rant about it being a concrete level
Okay, which one of these guys does the drugs saved see if it's you you were really high on this stream
No, I wasn't actually I was lying to you because I didn't want people to think I was a moron
I was fucking probably stone-cold sober on this dream as I said
I was like hi, so people would think I have a moron you you might like
You think that why wouldn't he he should put on like a like a ever since I started to tell you guys that I
47 never puts a voice on its character voice is already there every time you disguise. He's just like yes
I'm here the chef ready to serve you you think if he was an assassin like that
Why wouldn't you put a voice? He's a liar put a voice on
Okay, and would you like some drugs?
Why don't you just speak my normal voice this guy doesn't want any drugs
I don't think I just do I do so many voices
I'm probably so annoying to be at it with like a Thanksgiving dinner or like Christmas and shit
like at some point I've never been recorded and if I'm the most
Incredible assassin in the world. How do I nobody picked me up?
Like a microphone in an office complex being like the job is done. I just blew it. There we go. I got too close
I was talking
Not mad yet. Oh
That's right when I shot that person. What is that? That's all right. That's not a rant
Now oh
Well, I mean you have like you have like shit
No, wait, you can order run like three weeks if you want. This is wrestling god damn it. Okay, hold on
Yeah, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Okay, so that's wrestling
Of course the last three seconds of this fucking video vroom as well when it was not a room
What are you talking about got scared? You know, I've come to understand something about myself and about this stream
this is not a bingo card for
Things that have happened over the last
Eleven fucking straight years. These are things that happen every stream every single one. So
Besides big maybe TF2 and maybe special event stream. This is just not a bingo card
This is just a checklist of things that I'm gonna do every broadcast
You know, we'll put all on that. I want to watch that. I want to hold on
I want to watch this video pause the timer. That's what I want to watch. This video is two minutes long
I just want to see this part. This is one of my first t-shirt ever. I don't give up on a garment
This is the crew man t-shirt is now available. Yes. That's right glue man
protector of the innocent
offender of justice and
Warden of all that is good and kind has finally caved into marketing
It doesn't count not to deliver this shirt to you buying this shirt will take you back to moments like these
Glue man's German wrestling debut as a 22 year old newbie under the stage name G
Grossi
He made a real splash in his first match when he was nearly killed by Dogman the magical dog magician
Was considered at least partially blind each shirt does not
Get of authenticity. I forgot about this might be what one may have looked like if they did
Signed and stamped by the father of all contemporary German wrestling
George our glue man senior himself, which are mine is a true site of craftsmanship and quality and again
No, you don't get one of these how much does a t-shirt like this cost you ask not?
12,000 not 8,000 not even
5,000 tired joke to get your very own glue man t-shirt. You need only one low payment of
$20 plus shipping and handling a spill joke take pride in owning a piece of German channel history
brag to all of your friends that we
Depicted character has been deemed out loud as the worst character ever and
Useless by the individual who created him these shirts are only available for a limited time and may never be available again
Yeah, they are head over to the spring comm slash glue man to reserve one today. All links will be in the description
Yeah, they're available June 2015. Holy shit. That's a long time ago. What a lie
Well, I said they may they they weren't from 2015 to like
2019 this shirt was gone. You could not buy it. You're old. Yeah, I know welcome to how old I am
All right, you're right. Let's keep going. I just want to see that
I haven't seen that video in like six years or something. Where do we stand?
All right of rumor ends this whole thing for me. Well, not really but you know, we keep going. All right, let's go
I'm gonna start the timer back continue to go through the ages. Here we go. Oh shit. Hold on
This is just the timer settings. Oops. How did I mess this up? How did I mess this up? What the fuck? Oh, there we go
Okay
Streaming the Nintendo I got a time camera off. Yeah, it's gonna be every single character. They're just Bayonetta
I'm not on cam yet, though. It's a special event
No, it's not. This is it before
This is like 60 62. This is not a special event. They do one of these every fucking 30 days
That's not a special event
This is e3
I'm telling you if I see Glover, I swear to God
It should add a Glover. I'll stand by that
Is it if I've got damn it fine. It's a special event. It is
Yes, it's e3
all three Battletoads
Which is e3
2018 god damn it. Yeah, okay. That's not just like a Nintendo Direct. This is like e3. I
Want to what's the announcement though? I wonder please tell me that they just they just unconfirmed Luigi by putting him in an egg
eternity
It's not funny. What about this the big reveal? Who's the new character? Who did they reveal in 2018?
I'm gonna show them. They're gonna zoom in on his face
There he is
That's right. Every fighter in Super Smash Brothers history is joining about
people are gonna think I'm like
One of these weird twitch channels that just streams random like TV shows and events and stuff
Why is this channel streaming the 2018 e3
I'm not vetoing it with 60 seconds left. This is fine
Even so your starting roster may be as small as the original Nintendo 64 game
No, new characters conditions for unlocking fighters and we want to make the process interesting
So I want to know what I have to say about this though. I feel like I have a really shit take on this
Come on give us unbalanced video game
What exactly is this frame it's me watching
4000 hours of videos
You have shit takes on everything no, I don't what about what I said about peanut butter
Link dawns as champions tunic from the legend of Zelda breath of the wild
His bombs are now remotely detonated and his final smash. We're going on
Way so they still haven't fixed this because I've tried to go back to direct x9
No, no, I was gonna do these commentaries. I tried it still didn't work. I still was getting terrible frames per second
I've tried everything so
Don't leave a comment telling me to change my video drivers or something cuz I've already done it
So I come up behind this heavy get him with the backs. I'm gonna beat on this one
I don't want to talk about another tip
Look at what I have equipped right now as my disguise as a medic
I'm using the bone saw right now
You can switch what we're just holding out of the skies if you hit B while you're holding your different weapons
Too many spies walk around if they're just guys
Let's just say you're disguised as the back words if you're walking around with a syringe gun out as the medic as your disguise
People are gonna know you're a spy because what medic walks around with his syringe gun when there's no enemies around exactly
So make sure you're aware of the different items
So me and this sniper are going toe-to-toe
No, actually what happened was fucked up
Somehow you killed that guy and this revolver is really really fun to use
It's really really powerful the whole point for me coming back here was to take off the teleporter
I figured it was gonna take too long for the sapper and I was right because look at these people coming out to try
And get me I get away with my life intact and I decloak right behind this rock
Like I told you before this is fine fantastic for decloaking because look nobody seems to know or care
so I'm following this line of people and
This is where the dead ringer shines as you'll see in the next second or two here
Get this engineer get the sentry gun pull out the dead ringer guys run behind everybody
You know, you're just gonna die and use it
Don't be afraid to take something out to give some get on to every single person again
I didn't make this video like two weekends ago
Come right back. I made this video before the game. I think was free
12 years ago or something row I get this engineer
Of course, like this is gonna be outdated in medic and the heavy he was healing
Pull it out Brinson repeat again
That's the best part about the dead ringer is if you have a set route pretty much
Plan out a route you're gonna take and just do it every single time people are very very ignorant to dead ringer spies
They never check and they always lose their ground
So I get that sniper I get this scout pull the dead ringer out. We turn around
We try and do it again. Fuck this and John knows
Video I'm vetoing starting to wise up a little coffee everywhere
Dammit right behind these rocks. Oh, this sucks. Awesome. Oh fuck this video come up here
I'm jumping doesn't work so clean and right here is a totally totally horribly embarrassing things stop talking
I got a beer back. I actually have to bear back. I swear to God. I'm not kidding. I'll be right back
I'll be just one second. I guess I gotta clean this up before it stains
I'm not even muted. Whoops. All right, it's coming up. It's coming up. I just give me another minute
I think I'm okay. It's coming up. Damn it. I've been so good about keeping this area so clean
Then I dump up fucking coffee on the ground
Swinging a spy around
Mocking my past self. It's like yeah. Yeah. All right. Wait, let's go
Finish the stream hurry up. I want to play terraria. You just put me in a tab man. Oh, that's all right
Just put me in a tab. I we got to update the bingo card, which goodness. Okay, we have some new additions
TF2 this is actually filling up Jax to really because I got like three four kills in a row
All right, I guess that makes sense. Yeah
No, like okay getting three backstabs in a row is spy in 2011
I mean
Okay, this is important too. This was right after they changed the knife to be instant instead of it taking a full second to swing
That's not a Jax moment. Yeah, I disagree. I disagree right after this changed back in like 2010 2011
spy was insane for like a month or two straight because nobody was used to the fact that it took
Less than less than a second to stab somebody in the back, but I will give you the special event
Oh, no, I just have to say that by the way, this doesn't count
I'm just giving you a reference when I say something like monkey ass or like a pog jam like yeah that
This is gonna end pretty quickly. I think all right
let's put the time to get the timer back here and
Continue in three two one we move
Like five people guaranteed if he has more than a few shots and he can land them far too often
I'll see engineers standing by their sentry guns with the glowing bright shotgun
Just doing nothing
I'm gonna be I feel like if you start to heal those people and tell them over Mike
Hey, how many revenge crits do you have? Oh, I got
17 hey you want to go kill the whole team right now. It's like I'm no brainers
I have five videos right there that was me building the sentry gun and it took about 30 seconds
Maybe it's nothing happened. I didn't die
It was just really boring so I didn't didn't want to have you guys have to sit through that
But killing that sniper right there and people freak out
I've said this before in other gameplay commentaries that when you get hit by a crit
What is it you get shot in your stomach breaking record whether it's a rocket whether it's a shotgun doesn't matter
You freak out a little bit, and you go. Okay. There's crits. I gotta run by oh by the way one shot kill right there
You sound like an asshole what I mean right when you see a crit scree when a medic pops a crit scree
I don't somebody and their weapons are glowing you immediately go here comes crits
I'm gonna die the same thing can be said about somebody that has a frontier justice
That's glowing even when I'm not playing engineer
I could be playing soldier or I could be playing spy this is not if I see the glowing shotgun I go
Your aim omega low shit, and I either back up or I go for another target. That's what goes through everybody's mind
So this is the second century that's built to completion now get a few kills that spy was 90 seconds ringer
Always tell when a spy's a dead ringer when you shoot them one time from far away, and it does two damage
But it magically kills them so dead ringer spies. I do that too though everybody does that
So I got four kills on this century, and I kind of do something really really outrageous tips and
Not recommended to most people that are playing engineer because we have this one point
We only have three minutes to go and I
Destroy the century to get the crits. I'm such a greedy bastard
Bad idea. This is a good idea. Yeah, let me just destroy the century you put it immediately quick enough
You can get a century built back to complete. Oh, yeah quickly especially when I have that dispenser right there a full level three dispenser
I'm not worried about it at all right now. I'm just curious
I want to try and look around try and get some more kills soldier right in his face 180 damage remember how I said that before
180 looking around perusing seeing if I can get a shot on somebody get a kill
I miss a few times, but I get the kill on him anyways from long-range crit guys
Don't be afraid to do this if you're afraid to do this if you think you need to stand by your century at all times
And I go for life
I mean that's true, but it's not true enough where you can't go have a little bit of fun
Remember a spy is gonna try and backstab you and take out your century and all your buildings
So what happens if a spy just saps all that stuff right now the map is small enough where I'm gonna be able to get
Back to at least one or two of my buildings preferably the dispenser or maybe even the century
It's really not we're going go go go I need to like feed this guy drugs, so he doesn't die surgeon simulator almost almost
Come on all right. Where's the syringe? We are just there. Yes. I played the funny
YouTuber games when they came out yes, yes
We're good. We are good. Just need to cool it here. I'm vetoing this don't want to lose the hearts right here
Oh, you already know what this whole video is fly out the back. No, I'm video heart. We don't hurt for the time being
Okay, the doors are closed
Vito damn done Vito. I think anybody's gonna do this. I think I just wasted like two hours of my time
Would you do it? I would never do this no this video is awesome actually
Except for this guy except for this guy
Please be the only brainless motherfucker in here. That's gonna. Do this watch the shit. He's doing it follow him down. Oh
He's gonna crash into people
It's if you're alive
He's making it into the pool. I love this video was a lot fun to make it in the pool
It's safe. It works
Come on. Let's go
all joke
Yeah number two I gotta get a good view of this. It's already there though. This is too long sitting here waiting for this
Here we go. Let's see what he does. See ya
He made it he made it yeah
McLeod music
We all used it man anybody else
Anybody else
Pause it see he is about to jump off this high dive right now, and he thinks he's going in the pool
Well, what we're gonna. Do is we're going to replace
Let's replace a is evil part of this pool that he's about to dive into with you know just just like that
Let's just see what happens. Let's see how it happens to this guy. Oh, don't tell me you wouldn't do it either
Yeah, you would do the same thing. Yeah, there he goes
What where's this kid right there?
Are you serious? You're completely fine after that. I'm not hungry
He's fine. All he has to say is I'm hungry coming through
Beach hut was really good value. I'm not that hungry right now. He's shocked by his own video jumped off of a
5,000 foot platform into the ground
Got right. What are you fucking spider-man? I made this feel like nine years ago. I don't remember. Oh shit
We're at the end. That was a good one. I like that one at the timer doesn't matter for this one
Are we good? We updated? Yeah, we're up did no bingo yet
No, you'll know when it's actually rant. You'll know we won't even have to have an argument
We won't we won't even have to talk about it. It'll be so so obvious. All right, let me uh, let's go
You ready the timer reset and let's go. Okay, the end of this video the last one second. Okay, let's keep going
You're one almost done solar system, which this is a Stardew Valley stream or tonight
I'm gonna make a couple more planets. Holy shit. This is old. I can't believe I'm actually doing that by the way veto
Why these bat wings to sell for a lot? I remember correctly
Let's just go. I'm not wasting a video. I already have I've had four vetoes left
I'm gonna waste a video on this. Oh god. I don't care how boring this part of the enemies
I'm not wasting too many people down here
We have a video want to die down the well gonna have to vote for that. You have to vote for it
Geez, I hate these little dust mites to the worst. They're too erratic
The stream sucks. Hey Stardew Valley is like where I started. Okay on like streaming on twitch
Anymore food eat this I'm gonna have to go down here. It's like one of the best video games ever made
You know, it's a fishing pole
Scared the shit out of me. I thought that something happened to me
Why did I have that selected?
What a fun game. I love boring Andy. I was in tear look
You do understand it's everything we could get me sitting there
You could get like the credits of the stream and I would have to stay there like you might get like the end credits
It's of a random stream. It's very possible. But truth be told. This is the most enemies
I think I've seen in the game so far in one room. Whoa
What if we got a veto dwarf scroll to I already got dwarf scroll three
That's a worst version of the spell that I are. No, look at all these knows. I ain't going anywhere
Look at all these knows that one looks different. Is it gonna explode? You know, I mean look he's doing the he's doing the thing
That all enemies do right before they blow up this 50 seconds left where it doesn't take that long
So weird and like just looking into like a sword with telescope into the past weird
How come my voice got higher? Please be better than my broken Trident new microphone and I aged 10 years
I think the speed is cool. You know, this weird thing happens when you get older your body changes
You don't stay like 25 for your entire life. This is a stab
You you age a little your vocal cords to get a little different you get a little gravelly
You microphone settings might change. That's it. Plus two speed and second actually making me faster
I can't tell where we're going. Where we're going. You see no ink part two. This is a banger. I know that for a fact
Okay, guys, oh
This part to pasta ataliado. They all go and start like a war at the restaurant. This game is so good
We've got a corner the chef market this game this was the funnest thing I've ever done
You need to extend the time for this one because then I'll be the only restaurant
Isn't no the casino games are there but I'm not playing it's a heavily guarded fortress
This is an RTS now. Why somebody on the ground your hit man. Okay top tip this okay
This was nominated for like best dreams of the year last year, right? People loved this. I did too
Oh, they're all in. Okay. Wait, maybe we should extend. Okay, let's extend this this part
Your hit man, everybody's here Peter Baldwin
Mr. Hoffman, mr. Nolte, mr. Bingham Paul Srebling
So many people here
Madison doesn't somebody like just start attacking is all stand over here
They like burn this place down like five times. Don't they without me doing anything?
Oh who cares I
Don't think right now besides wait, I think they getting keen on this
Oh, they have a security guard there, right? How one of your staff has died
All right, who's gonna take the shot? Who's gonna make the first shot here?
I remember just being in a different room or something just hearing that through the mic
It's just like what the fuck is going on. All right. All right, mr. Jurgens. Mr. Jurgens. It's all hit men
Oh, yeah, we were taking out their restaurant chef bako is in your sights. Mr. Jurgens fire
But oh my god
How many am I putting down
Oh
I want to raise
By the way, this is like if you've never played casino, Inc
Get out. This is like one of the best games ever made. It's so fun. It's so much fun
It's the most absurd fucking game ever
No, no more hitmen stop coming in
That laughing fit like if a chef walked out that fucking door if a chef comes out that door then
Then this is owned by a trillionaire. Let me matter
Not quite
If a fucking chef opens this door
Does it happen? I don't remember. Can we extend to find out? I'm curious
Oh, no, they all just go in the elevator, right?
So many people in that elevator
Extend no, no, we're not just gonna extend this one over and over again. We have we have a hundred and seventy days
Straight 24 hour periods of videos to see so this is good. What was this guy doing? All right, we're going let's go
Let's go. Come on
I was in retaliation. It was the old guy
He took like seven shots
I'll include it. All right. All right. All right
I
Remember this place I just attacked this place
And they got back to normal and they started a fire again
Those who they didn't see this dream that this restaurant was on fire two days a week
They burnt this place down two days a week. It was
All right
He just walked in all right
So that is like this is not bingo, right? Oh, I don't think so not yet
Where's laughing fit?
Damn it. You're getting close. You're getting really close in God
Naked of rumor saying an emote out loud
Text oh one of your staff is dead. What? What are you talking about?
One of your staff is dead again
Gambling no, I have to gamble. It's not what it's not just a gambling on the screen. It's me gambling different. All right, let's go
razor death at her
Wrestling shit is gone. And here comes next already on there
Next is number 12 almost to the halfway point which what year is this? Oh German short 2k 18
That's clothesline not over-the-top ropes, but just barely into this is like the chat meme rumble right two planets in here
And remember the planets are in here just to make this more difficult for the shit memes
Remember. Yeah. All right. This is really important to remember if a planet wins
Yeah, there you go laughing about it a little bit just a small amount just eliminated German Jupiter
Who's this? Who's this gets that much easier for one of these shit memes to stay alive?
Who's the guy with the green hat and number 13? I?
Didn't say an emo who's still in it who still could be talking about no
I didn't time to leave what I say for sure. Maybe persevere through this whole thing turbo late
Oh, what the hood stay and persevere through the whole thing or could he just get eliminated by himself?
I'm gonna I'm gonna play semantics here with you and there goes German Saturn. The planets are gone
There are only I believe two more planets never mind
German getting as far up on the ropes as he can like I said previously and German late is might get it next in here
He does not
Okay, oh, that's not true. He's got a huge gross foot in his mouth. Okay stops it pre no no no no no
He's gonna reverse it now. He's spinning around hundreds ups big belly to back suplex stick around. I'm doing at the end of the stream
Somebody saved the planet pile driver that move is illegal bingo German just did a move that has been banned since 2002
You understand that's how fucked up and angry and that's just yes, right? Yeah, it's fine. It counts
Loud P coming in at 14
I'm not vetoing over. It's only 60 seconds man. I think a lot of people want to see loud peace, right?
I don't think we're gonna fill the whole board actually I could do with any of these
Except for short German and next oh these are characters
Looking oh my god
The countdown you're like face counting still is not in here bread across the right side sir bar was in here first, right?
Here comes acid base overall as possible. It's possible pretend. It's here. There's still another two hours left at least
Oh, I gotta do it fine. There's no music shit, right? I gotta do you gotta do the music again
I want to reiterate people that there goes next
That just got here or the head didn't know don't know how we're doing
This is a website that is set up to randomly play a video and a random time stamp
That was loud of every broadcast and every video I've ever done speaker in his ass
It's 40 next is going in 100 hours get it out of your system now because it's not gonna be there
We could get anything extend now comes a sensor bar at number 16. We're gone dark souls remastered part 8 bonus
This is where I need to remember again. It's you go up through the this is going to the tree
Oh, this is gonna be some massive anger water wheel. Whatever the hell it is, right? I sound really deflated here
Oh fuck you don't have the thing. This is blight town. You got it. You got a really good possibility for a rant here
I don't have the thing go this way you died to pinwheel
He holds up. He this is PvP PvP and multiplayer
Just kind of messing around in multiplayer. What?
When did I did that? Who did I PvP?
This is remastered and let me actually our souls remastered part
It's this is like the last on the bar because I know it'll be a problem
Trying to wonder where this would fit. I just know it will so all right now from here. I gotta go the origin of the sub sound
that's from Monster Rancher that is one of the sounds a monster makes and
Everyone thought it was really funny because it sounded like
Tim the tool man
Oh
That was a kind of funny. I just became the sub sound for like three four years
It's not me. No, it's not me
Wait, you guys thought that was me
See how many people can read phantoms only?
Pull them all in no
That's a sound file from Monster Rancher. I'm gonna keep going up right keep going up
We I think we're safe on this one. This is just me walking around and boring Lee filling dead air. It's perfect
You guys not get another bingo. That's how you go to get the the soul, but I don't even really want it
I'm really surprised. We have not seen an end of the screen bit reading
Why am I feet yellow because the whole character's yellow? That's kind of actually surprising
This is 12 year old let's play of Dark Souls. No, this actually is a probably two year old. Let's play of Dark Souls
This is the remastered again
Happy with our two words. I am completely lost. There's no way I'm gonna
We did that very silently. We all knew you dick. This is an old one
It's just me and like this weird hermit guy back here now
I like this video
I'm fighting through
Too bad rats is not one is it also we're wearing bandanas and look like pirates
I
Okay star you're not allowed to look
No, cuz we you're the burger judge
Customers, but I'll talk the people you got to show them to their seats
I'll lower their expectations lower their expectations cuz they're gonna probably throw up after eating one of our burgers
I wonder did it get to the party. Oh, where is it? Where's the video? That's pretty far?
Yeah, still we have to make burgers. We have to make our own delicious cheeseburgers by second rule
Start with the bun and hey, I have everyone get away from each other because we're just gonna knock into stuff
I'll take my stuff into the bathroom
My burger station is gonna be right next to the sink in the bathroom
Yeah, I'll be I'll be in the bathroom with my oh, well the cheese is completely. It's it Mike
My cheese seriously is just like a black pile. If you want a little bit
I
Texted star
Station hey get up. I need you to help me make you
Yeah, he didn't even live literally didn't even like get a glass of water
He rolled out of bed and like I just dropped my burger in the fucking say I was like, hey
Please get up and help me make this video and he's like, I don't know. Okay, and I was like, thank you. Oh my
never
Star just pretend like you didn't hear that. What are you doing back here? How are you like multiplying these bacon star?
One he like wasn't even participate. I know how to break everything. Where are you?
Dooping shit, what the hell? How did you get all this bacon eater? I'm the bacon eater who's under the ground Jeremy
You're under the ground
Under the ground, I'm gone
Where am I
Like that one that was a lot of fun. I like that one a lot. Let's bingo. Mmm
No, no, we still have just one no singing. No wait, no drew crew, which I'm happy about. Let's go
I'm not well, I'm not happy that I don't I'm just happy that it's not gonna give you another space
That's pretty cool. Oh, so again ready. Watch this. Hey booboo booboo. Look at I got like nothing in my hand. Hey ready
Crazy. He's not always insane autos not showing up on on screen yet
There is all right, you know what I'm just gonna go do like a front flip into the snow right now
Like I thought this is some big stunt
Whoa, uh-huh. I jumped over a thing. That was like five feet off the ground
Somebody help me, please. Oh, I'll tell
I'm sorry. I just made you do that. Oh
boo-boo
You'd break your back dude. Look at how young you're handsome autos
Boo-boo, I boo-boo was a great dog. Well, okay videos over. What does that leave us here?
Mmm, okay. That's also that's
Two thousand thirteen twenty thirteen. That's not a Jax moment. No, it's not. Okay
You're really looking for of rumor rumor is really the only way you can get anything again
Replay the video. No way. That's not how it works. It's only a matter of time. It is actually it's possible
There was a lot of times that happened in Vegas, but this is taking from every single arc
This is taking from Boston arc Vegas arc Vegas arc to right. All right, let's keep going
Where are we gonna go next?
Nitro
Nitro is kind of crazy
Road redemption
Nitro again, this is not my job
It's okay. I'm still alive. I can still do this. No, this is not a rumor. Let's go you son of a bitches
total carnage
Boy
Did you see how much stuff has got crashed?
Oh
Laughing fit is a free space
You know, I saw the German laughs at car crashes compilation, it's like four hours
Oh, I don't laugh at just car. Okay. I laugh it. It's the end of the video
I don't laugh. Okay. I don't just laugh at car crashes. Okay, I laugh at
Just chaos like just carnage chaos is like just anything that's absurdly happening makes me laugh
That's just the way it is anything car like crashes in a game. Oh, just like absurd on their own, right?
Where we gone? Here's a fine. This is the another movie's mouth
I think I'm gonna veto this happening with his mouth here
But whatever we're gonna send it a character creator for three minutes veto. I'm using my second veto. I have three more
go
first-rate stranglehold
I don't even remember playing this game. I got over. I don't even know what this is. Who's left one guy
Jax no, this is easy
I could have been fine
One guy nope has to be one guy in chat
Just leave go
You said one guy no, it has to be a reference to one guy in the chat. I stuck here forever
I need to like leave this building
Get me out of here. I'm stuck here forever. I can't leave this game. I'm decent. I just I have no memory of this
Why?
Please look up. I don't know. I I don't know who this is. I'm not even me playing
Dick shot purgatory. That's what we are. I can't get out
There has to be like an exit right like to the kitchen
Stupid what am I supposed to do? How do I get out of this?
Like a second running from me. I don't know. I can't tell I
Don't even know what's going on. This is never ending enemies. I need to escape. What the fuck?
I'd play the whole thing and probably how far into the okay. This is 39 minutes into it. Oh boy. This ends in 20 minutes
Get me out of here. Get me out. I just need to find the exit. He's upstairs. It has to be
Finally stream this game for an hour. I don't think I need I think I need to kill everybody
I don't think there is an exit. There's no way
This is okay, which I think I found the secret called zombie staircase
We're good, I think this is one of the Xbox 360
Screens the stairs
So whatever you guys want to see first I was like into that one, but tonight tonight tonight we have obviously
Was this late shift something else we're doing. Oh, it's like an if this is the though
This is the FMV game get this down here
All right, we're gonna play casino ink. Look. I don't know anything about this game
I saw it on Steam and I saw it actually on Amazon first and I was seeing if it was on Steam
Oh if he only knew right this game is gonna be fucking stupid, but like there are a couple of options
We have a couple of game sucks options. Oh, if he only knew so don't worry
I was talking about how that could be like and maybe it looks like it sucks and bring this up
Should be working now and here's the one problem with this
It's gonna be really hard for me to see any like bits and like right when I say that
The second I say that here comes fucking glue man
Like the second I talk about how I can't see bits all the sudden fucking glue man comes over fucking German suplex. Oh shit
That's right. I forgot about the animated bit stuff
Thank You KXE
501 and it's a lot of the bits also. Thank you to sticks renegade and you know James Big Mac
Who could forget James Big Mac? I think
KXE's went through I'm not sure sticks went through because they were gonna be another two when I'm gonna say anything
It's gonna be two minutes and some of those just pretend some of those suplexes were from you
sticks
Pretend some of those were from you
Anking subs. Yeah, thank you. Thank you guys for the 50 fucking dollars each each and
KXE says let me just get this up. Is it gonna work? Okay, it's in the chat right now
Are you kidding me? Cheer? Cheer? Cheer?
Let the bits flow lads
You're here right now mod James. No, no, we're not doing this joke tonight. No, that joke is done. What's going on James?
I'm not doing that, but KXE. Thank you so much. And also thank you sticks
Alulu just gifted five tier one crowns. I have that also
I can't show up. Sucks a shit ton of bricks. Thanks Alulu. Sometimes literally, but like you I'm also in the mission
Glad to know you're alright from it. Much love also, by the way
Phallus1916 cheered
45,000 bits. Who's talking? What? No, no, the winks are only for when they're in stream. Somebody gave like
$450 earlier
Okay, I'm gonna veto this if it doesn't get end in 10 seconds or 20 seconds
I have no idea. I didn't see it pop up or anything. Okay, everybody that was okay before this ends
Thank you. Thank you
4,500 bucks. This is this is back when I used to read things. Let's get this going. Thank you everybody. I'm not gonna extend this
No
Grub. The gum you like is coming back. Grubinsky makes the 20 community subs. Is it gum that I liked? No, we're not extending. Go
Oh, oh, although this is a really relaxing part. So I think we're fine. I think we're good
This is gonna take two minutes I can't move by oh god damn it. I'm so sorry. I'm trying to move do it again
Picked a perfect place. I just like cut them off
My hair is permanently messed up from when I smashed the coffee into the ground
From the top I
Could veto this but I'm not gonna
Go outside why it's all right, like they're gonna do it again we're gonna again as a joke
I'm not doing it. I want to hear the whole thing
Come on guys, what's with this patience?
Can you break? No, I'm good. Extended or suffer the consequences. No, no, this is not how the game works
Take a break you should go BRB. No, I'm fine. Oh, that's why you're saying
easy
Easy, don't don't let me get the spray can
Don't let me get the fucking spray can if everyone's to talk
Stop it
What the fuck is he doing? That's to get the shit out of me and I did it like fucking nitrous oxide by webcam
Holy shit. I look look I look like deranged
I look red and sweaty and what the fuck well you can't just like freaked out. I
Hundred and three not 114. I'm so glad this is not in the middle of me freaking out the bumblebee level actually wait
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Let's go. I want to see what simple does just out of curiosity
Simple what does it do? I beat the game? I think the nice bosses. We're gonna go to you. We'll go. Yes. That's true
Like is it really simple now, you know how we feel
Not really. I mean, it's pretty simple. It's fairly simple
Damn, when's the DLC for this game gonna come up?
I guess this is cold, you know, if you have to co-op with like you like little brother or something
And you're teaching somebody the game. I can understand how this would be 24
No, no, it wasn't
You want to like co-op with a friend?
mechanics
No, I can't be fantastic. I really love you. Hey
I
Beat this one. I think I have three more videos like I'm vetoing this. This is a veto. Hey guys
I'll trade you my holographic charizard for your holographic spree. No, I'm
Vetoed it's vetoed a
Holographic spree is worth like is worth like
$500,000 you're gonna try to rip me off right now
There's only one in the world, but I've got the one with Japanese text
Do you really?
Do you do you seriously have that?
Do you see you guys ever like play Pokemon trading card? Do you seriously have that card though?
Cuz I kind of want it with the Japanese text. I hope I'm still funny like ten years later
That went right into his mouth dude, are you alright? Please get me to a doctor. I'm sorry. Just chill out
I gotta pull the arrow out though. Um, hold on. Just don't talk. Get it out of me mate. Come on
I'm trying to I'm really sorry. I did that. Oh my god fucking help guys help, please
Fucking murdered this guy
Turbo, where are you? Can't get you away from the scene of the crime. It was alright. I want to see your trophy
No, oh, he's gone. It's too bad. It was it was absolutely heinous looking
It was it a sniper. Is it this boo?
Now that took a lot to do that. This was this was the old the old crew. All right, I found nobody nobody
Nobody scared the spy. I found a spy. I'm it's guaranteed that he's a spy
Just don't don't like scare him don't scare him running really slow. I think I know he's a spy
I don't know where you are
I loved this so much. Oh, you're right behind just following around a spy. That was you
How much fun you could have in team four
I'm really sorry
I'm playing shithead Natasha
Fortress 2 is every single drug ever made combined into an oral pill that you take
Oh boy, and it's and it's every single thing. It's every single drug ever made. Okay, don't do what I was gonna
Do to you you punk only 20 seconds. I'm good
What what why you just kill random crits?
What I'm so confused right now from that
Ten seconds, here we go. No, that's the death of accidental Jax. That's not a real Jax scout on the point scout on point
Scatter the black
Screw it. Oh
It's gonna get scooped up there
This is this is gonna be a ramp for sure. I remember this everyone called me an idiot
Up here, okay, then it goes that way that's going fast
This game was a lot of fun though. I like this
Ah
Smarties are great. Yeah, they're very delicious if you eat them. I wouldn't put them anywhere else
I've done this like some such a nervous habit. I remember reading the chat and people saying like can't even solve a simple puzzle like seriously
Dude, I'm like actually worried about you
Like I'm worried about you do like no, we're not fucking around and I got like pissed
I think I get actually pissed here. Hopefully doesn't happen in the next minute too. Oh, it's exhausting pretending
Scoop it already. Come on, man
Again
Come on. Where'd he go? I think I'm in the clear though. Shit. I think I fucked it up again
I think it's like another two or three minutes after this at least because I was here for like 30 minutes. Hey
Extend it
I'm just giving you a free space if I do that. All right fine
You get your reverse veto. This is number two, by the way. I'm her officially extended whole damn thing
That's your second veto and it's all it accounts for a reverse veto as well. So you only have three more of these left
Now here we go, this is once I start getting quiet I
Start talking like this
What happened? What's going on? Like what the fuck?
That's the focus whenever you hear me start to do that
That's when like, you know that I'm probably read off camera and I'm looking over here like right here and I see
Like holy shit. I did this in fucking 10 seconds actually is the one this dude's a fucking idiot
Like this dude sucks. Like how does he have this many viewers and shit? Like when I start to see that I'm just like
You start to laugh it off a little bit and then once it once you realize that you don't know what you're actually doing and
everybody else does
You start to like stamp your feet like a little baby
Go I got this is the one got it. It's not the one
What an idiot holy shit. Oh my god seeing that again was fucking so bad
But like it's a big hole to fit it in. I've holy shit. I really thought that's what you did Wow
But I come on anybody could have made that mistake
Okay, I thought the arrows we're talking about like I like you like tilt this tilt it
Well, look, you got to tilt it around and get it in the middle those old stupid toys
I thought it was like till tell there to tilt it around just get a bit in the middle. I didn't
I think I fall off here too and it escalates. Alright, I'm gonna give you another extend. I'll give you one more for free
Oh, I'll give you another one for free
Shit, I I thought it was just like oh get it in the hole
Didn't he say get it in that hole too. Can you say something like that? Like, oh make sure you get it in the hole
Can you say that?
You fell off. Yeah, I think I think at this point when I mess this up again, what's that?
Solved the puzzle it took a touch. No wait for 12 or 1 2 2 5
Or 1 2 2 5 what's going on? Oh
That's right some we did an elaborate thing where I like made people go skip around the Vaude and shit, right?
I have completely forgot about that. We did the Vaude puzzle. Oh, yeah
Why did I pull the controller out I
Specifically remember everybody hating this bit. I thought it was genius and everybody's like this sucks
Dude, who just play the game. I was putting like little clues and hints
To like get go to a specific point in the Vaude, right?
It was four hours in like in like 12 seconds or something, right and like the whole idea
Yeah, like it
Was funny as a Vaude watcher. Yeah
Screaming on here
No, it's not. We're good. Congratulations. We're good. By the way, uh, I just did that into my chair
I don't know why yeah, I got up. I put my face directly into the bottom of the chair
I don't want to scream because that's way too loud. I'm like, I got a muffle in some
Yeah, it was it was gross. I realized it it was fucking vile. I think I'm in the clear
We're not extending it again. We're good
You ate your own ass
All right, where we going? No, we're not extending you got to see at least that part. Let's go. Where is it?
Into the stars and torn into a thousand pieces
But if this spell was intended to destroy it does not you are caught three stars and held this is it
I love this game
What an amazing game come on, by the way, if nobody if you have not played sorcery, it's on everything. It's on
Ios Android steam everything. No
Jesus Christ
No, go get it and please love a god didn't work if you want a list of like, oh would work
What's your top five games of all time?
sorcery
No, no
No, at least probably like number four or three. You're just refluxed. I don't whatever. I'm drinking coffee
Whatever son of a gun. I have to go all the way back up there. I sound kind of pissed off though
Where is this? This is I can't rewind rewind rewind. Okay. Rez is the only other spell that can counter death
Yeah, but there's nothing to Rez
There are four sorcery games. I know that was what I needed to do. They're so good too. I want to scroll up
I think the fourth one's probably the worst. No rewinds. Didn't it say like oh you're held in the stars
It was correct. The fourth one has a bunch of weird shit that you have to do, right?
But like the sorcery one two and seven a lot of three are
Phenomenal spellify. It's just telling me that okay, so it was it's doc
file
tell
Zed when how long ago was this? I figured it was just gonna put me whatever
2014 no 2015
This was 2016. This is one of the first let's just I'm just going right back there and see well
No, cuz this wasn't out yet, right when I started streaming this came out a little bit further after I started
See if we can get in there 2016. Yeah, we're doing a speed run eat box. Hello. Yes. I'm a guard captain
How nice to meet you. Yeah. Yeah, yeah, make a move. What's the actual best game of all cards? Hi guys
I don't know. Yeah. All right. Bye. Bye. Bye. Bye return the salute see you later. Thank you for your
Encouraged encourage her. Yeah beat that guy up kick his ass. Nice work. Good rock. We're safe. Good rock
No, the correct answer is
team Fortress 2 Diablo 2
World of Warcraft wrath of the Lich King my body
Mario RPG run a trigger
blood-borne
sorcery
I'm like that keep going three seconds. This is a right pain in the ass not top five fan that person for at least five seconds
I never wash my hands. Let's touch some people's food now. Hey, how you doing? What can I get you miss? Yes
Hi, how you doing? I'd like a regular burger with some tomato sure some onion a little bit of lettuce a medium
Well burger, please
Thank you a little bit more onion a little bit more lettuce and can you please toast the bun, please? Thank you
Yes, yours. Absolutely, sweetheart turn stick fucking but I'll give you a toasted fucking fun. Oh my
Oh, so right
Screw up anybody's order tonight because if you do you're gonna get fired from this job that you need
So much
It's sitting right in front of you you don't know that much and you squeeze from your bottom to make sure it
Comes out to me
A fucking moment right there. All right, just want to be clear on this
Some confusion you did not want a complete head of lettuce between two pieces of bread. No
But what the fuck did you want?
I understand you're upset. It's taking a while to get your food. Everybody chill out. It is listen for a second
They're right back at you dickhead. But anyway, I am the only person working here
I know singing my boss is a cheap son of a bitch. He's not gonna hire anybody else. I'm doing the books
I'm doing the cashier and I'm doing the cooking. How fucked up is this right?
Wow, that is pretty fucked up. That's terrible. I don't like what where'd all the other workers?
Seriously, all this game has taught me is
How much it sucks to work in the restaurant business like I don't ever want to do this
I never want a restaurant job in my life because how fucking awful this is and I give two thumbs up to
Anybody that is doing a restaurant job ten years ago, and if you'll excuse me for one second
What is this yes, I would like two large cheese pizzas and I want them crispy on the bottom
Not like last time when I didn't get him crispy. You understand? Oh, I see what I'm doing
And I also want some free drinks too. Otherwise, I'm gonna complain to your boss
I
Say I get it. I see what I've done
All right, we'll do singing was that video 2013 that was a rant too. Oh
Shit that actually might be a rant could be nope
It wasn't because that was not oh shit frog attack or hours of Dean dingus. I hold on me
I gotta get this some good fucking food
No, what you doing my Wellington? No, stop it. Stop it. What you doing my Wellington? No, don't tick-tock
All right, what we got I need two more pies. What was that? What was it? You see that? What where is it?
Where is it right there? Oh, it's literally right here. Hello. Is anyone home? Sounds like somebody's inside, but I shouldn't intrude on I'll come back another time
No, they're all they're doing something weird and gross on tik-tok. What you doing? No, stop it. What you doing my Wellington stop
Don't do that. You're a detective. Yeah, and I'm I'm detectiving. Well, I people don't know what I'm doing there
That's not me doing an impression of
That's not me doing an impression. That's like that's his that's what he does on tik-tok
Tells people that's they make wellingtons and like send him like an M&M's Wellington and he goes that's what my Wellington
What are you doing? Stop Wow singing? Oh shit. You're right
I thought I was I don't know. I thought he's talking to me
I honestly thought that somebody was saying that to me like you were so you were calling me an idiot
I heard you or something. That's weird. He's stupid. Look, he's stupid
Shut up. I'm mad at him. Like I'm fucking annoyed with him right now. Is that weird?
Weird thing to say I like I'm pissed off at what I just said. I'm annoyed by that. All right
Um, right. We're gonna do what?
singing a
Rare doy doy doy is gonna have to show up here for you to get another one
I don't think you're gonna get another bingo by the way, every bingo is another hundred communities
I want it's a lost pie. I need one more. There's a huge deer in the water
Take rants off the deer in the water. Okay, that's that's fair because that was not me ranting
That was the character grandpa ranting, right? I mean one more pie the rant was
I feel like it's just five rant, but that was not necessarily me ranting
The rant has to come from turning the rant was a bit. Okay. All right. Well, let's get this off
Okay frog detective this is really fun as it was frog stick three out what I know that we're doing another one more thing
Not yet. All right. What do you want? I hear your pies. We're gonna bring the voice actor back
and
It's very simple. There's a there's like two buttons to this game
There's a punch and there's a kick and apparently there's a jump. Yeah, there is that's that's that fighter beautiful looking by the way
May you fat fuck. No, but your health is in the top left. I gotta beat this guy. I got five
He's got five. It's over. I lost is that nine by the minute video
Another really nice thing that you're probably going to realize is you know, each one of these guys
Vito has the same stupid sound when you pick anyone I just picked this guy ready listen to this
Yeah, look at how much the crowd just looks like utter shit, by the way
I don't remember any crowd being like sepia tone in my life. I hold on. I might be able to pull this out
I'm able to pull this through. I feel like we've already seen the whole video a little spin kick
I think we've seen the whole video already. This is like the tutorial. Oh
Jim it Jim it I got it. All right
That's the first time I've like ever you know that guy. So that's a good thing graduate. Why am I on a forklift?
How do you say it right match to it? You guys ready?
So match to sepia, right? Look at my health
Why did I stop with that though health sepia? That's correct. We time. Oh, that's sepia
I'm just surprised. This is a nine-minute video
Okay, I have 65 health. I'm gonna start the next fight
With six to light I'll veto this but I want to cuz that's that's fucking bullshit. Oh god. That is absolute
Complete utter crap. Look at this guy has 260 health. This game is not possible to complete
You can't complete this that actually is bullshit though. How would you ever be able to do this?
It doesn't make any sense. It doesn't I doesn't make any sense
Why that would ever be a thing every fighting game I've ever played in my whole life. This is Street Fighter one
This is a clay fighter. That's like a staple of all fighters. What? Why would you ever remove that?
Why would you ever not do that?
Everybody starts with the same health when there's a new round. Why would you remove that from this game? That's what I don't get
I don't understand that. Okay, you got it
so
Fucking stupid. I just want a guy. I want to get past the first you're a fighting game expert
But that's true though as you yeah, you started around people who made this game
All I remember is playing off the Super Nintendo and the arcade. This was in the arcades
That's why wasted on this server. I'm more than 15 seconds
See if I can do it. Is that you you the pyro? Nope. You have to nope another rare TF2 video
Oh, you're you're pathetic little grenades. Just bounce off my manly chest
Come on shoot me again didn't work. It didn't even work. Oh, I didn't know what protects me against that
I am completely protected. Yeah, that's stir. Okay. Let's see how long you stay alive at the mid fight
Okay, why was I so jaded? If I die at this mid fight?
I have to like drink the rest of my iced coffee as fast as I can
I feel like I've been jaded since I was like fucking do you know why did you say that?
Yeah, I don't think that's ever changed. It was not a good
Ten years ago, that'll hurt your head gambling on the corner either
No, I'm going I'm going up balls to the wall. This doesn't happen. I cannot die here
Oh, here's the fine. I'm like baby smoke it ever. That was a terrible jump. I
Try I still try to see the good and things I do but I'm yeah, you know, okay
No, get this pyro out of here. Yeah, I lived I don't have to drink my ice coffee as fast as I can
I'm gonna come kill you like right disciplined emotional. That's right. Absolutely. That is absolutely correct
I thought you didn't have that much health
It's okay
It's okay. I've died from like 30 Scouts
I was sitting if my warning for I have like jello vision right now
Oh, okay that that is like kind of horrible to do something to me. No, I didn't do anything
Drugs what's going on?
This is bad, you know, this is real bad. It's serious. Um, yes. All right. Hey, oh
Tell me when you respawn. What's my name guys? Can I have a comeback Tycho RC?
Are you about to give me like a hundred percent?
You got really weak eyes. Are you respawn? I am spawned. I am spawned actually I kind of do look
What is this thing? Oh, no, do it again. I walked into like a friggin resupply what is going on?
What does this thing mean? What are we talking about? Oh, that title makes sense
Just cuz I was like what the fuck is going on. Oh dear lord. Oh boy. Oh
No
Still didn't even kill him. People are gonna think I'm a legitimate hacker
Like I killed that was unbelievably bad some pyro blew the rocket back. I
Went spy cuz I was gonna try and kill you while you were like that, but dude, I died
Time within ten seconds. I'm a having that thing. All right, let's go ten seconds
I don't know. I don't know if I can trust you. Let me have it. I know I could trust you. Hmm
All right this time I promise I'll make use of it
Oracle Mordhau I thought it ticked damage on you cuz I don't play battle royale. I played a battle royale like twice. Oh
I can't believe he's not one of these streamers. It plays battle royale every day
What I can't believe you didn't know that that was the circle
I mean this guy streams battle royales 5,000 hours. I can't believe you didn't know what I didn't know
I think it was just gray. I thought it was like gonna battlefield me and turn me around
You know what it goes like
Please get back to the playing field in five seconds. There was a battle royale. I forgot there was a bit of excuses
That's not an excuse
Hey, it's Alex. I did really well. I
Was killing people I just walked out of the circle here. I don't think he's even in the call
He needs to know how many times have I called him?
You know what? I'm getting getting realization here like I'm gonna call I'm gonna call him
How many times have I called it's Alex like I'm right now like with a complaint about something
Yo, he has me muted the battle royale circle thing instantly killed me. I was doing well
I was in the last six you get like chased and you
Taleks is just the friend that like if I have something I got a fucking event about I stepped out of the circle for a second
The phones like I'm about to have the word dump soup on you
Please battle royales. Hold on. So you'd like
You strolled casually into the fog and maybe it's because I'm afraid to do that to anybody else
There are tons of people that I talked to on like a weekly basis right like a whatever do that
Can we can you cue is I don't I don't do that to other people. I
Fucking tell you something. Can you understand what's going on here? It's Alex
Party home
My my logged in probably not. Maybe I can see you are you like in the game? Oh, there we go
No, actually, I do that's like my mother to
Stixen I'll be like mom Dixon. Listen to me. You understand mom like they get you mom and she'll be like, yeah, of course. Mm-hmm
Should have got it, right?
All right. Well rants is already there at anger is already there. I don't see you in the party list here
No, no, look at me, which is weird an invite, but it's not actually like an accept invitation. No naked. Hmm
Can you join off me? He's ignoring us
Not ignoring more help what what he has no friends
By based on his true story written by to be true 2033 this is back to back. All right
Oh, do you guys remember this? Oh my god. I forgot about this stream. Oh boy
Um, I couldn't get past the tutorial in this game and I was fucking freaking out and livid. Are you okay?
No, not right now. I'm fucking angry right now. Yeah, this is bad
This actually is running against bad internet and I'm fighting against like my streaming software being a piece of shit. Ah
new game wait, no
You guys can see this right? Am I?
You guys can see this right? You're not jaded. I want to make sure that that's possible positive guy
You can see this. Okay, good. I couldn't get past the tutorial and it was pissing me off
I was playing on like the hardest difficulty because you got to play on the fucking hardest difficulty because you're on stream
You're a streamer
If you don't play on hard and everybody gonna laugh at you and like well snot rockets at you like on their screen
They're not like streaming software. I'm gonna make my own fucking internet
I'm gonna make my own streaming software my own internet in my own house
I'm gonna build my own house with my bare hands. Holy shit
Fuck this. I ain't like having somebody else have to like run my life. You know what I mean?
I'm gonna build my own house. I'm gonna put I'm gonna make my own bank. I'm gonna make my own bread
I'm gonna make my own milk
What the fuck am I talking? Can we talk about that for a second by the way?
So if you don't know I was in a snowstorm
I'm pretty bad one and
I don't know what it is with with people for some reason
What why do people buy?
bread and milk
What's the bread and milk story there? I still explain it to me you go to a grocery
Don't matter what grocery store you go to go to any grocery store before like a snowstorm or before like a hurricane or something
Especially like a snowstorm. I don't understand
You're gonna eat a bunch of bread for like a day. I
I
Wouldn't eat bread. I won't be able to eat a loaf of bread in two days
Three days four days. Why do people were you just chugging milk in your basement? Why do people buy bread and milk?
Why don't you buy like food?
What's going on there to eat where you can eat a bunch of bread? I?
Wouldn't you bet like get like a fucking a dozen chef Boyardee cans I get like a juggling bread and milk
It's nothing. It's nothing else you go to any other aisle in the grocery store, and it's full
But people are gonna just slam eat like loaves of bread and chug milk. I still didn't get it
I just don't get it like what the hell are you talking? What the hell are you doing?
Who the fuck drinks milk on like a regular basis anyways?
I'm glad we're getting away from this one my mask the thing Oh God
I could just shit my pants now. I can just buy new pants and then buy a new chair and then buy a new floor
What fuck?
That does that was next level seriously, that's just been three in a row of me just fucking furious
Phylacter is still coming in with another another ten thousand bits
The almighty dollar I gotta like it Lee. I gotta like illegal. I gotta get like I gotta move my hair. I go
He's deranged. Thank you. What am I about to do?
Holy fuck. Oh, this is nine and a half hour stream Jesus new top. Yeah, I can't even look over there. That's
This is what yeah, all right. I'm gonna be I'm vetoing this one
Free samples from Trader Joe's that's right
We're gonna go in there and go we're gonna go around the mall and
Get like the free samples from all the food court places
I want to veto this cuz I don't I'm gonna talk about like a people are subbing all again
I don't want anyone to sub. I don't sub right now. Even if it's for a job. I'm speechless
I have no idea what to say. Thanks for the fucking crazy amount of money. You guys are awesome
Yeah, this goes on for like ten minutes. I remember I'm doing it. Let's try to beat this video game
Vito, I mean, this is one of my favorite streams ever link the German mustard website. It's it's gonna be crashed
All right, where do I need to go? I gotta go plant the c4 on the hangers, which is upstairs, right?
Ban people that sub right? Which way do I go from here?
No, I think we're I think we're over it. I think it just happened like five minutes ago. And this is the post reaction, right?
I remember having one health at some point this whole game was my friend was a mess
Is he dead? I think I need him. Don't I my I had like a clenched in the door teeth
Clenched ass this entire time. I played this game this gap
Guys like dead you actually just did that. I need this guy so I'm gonna heal him
But what you hiding behind the door? All right, ten seconds. Let's go. Okay, let's keep going
Anything else in here that I can grab? I got a shave man. Look young little rift area thing
My impressions but this thing right here has to be protected and these doors over here
If you look in the top right of the screen
This door is gonna open and this door down here is gonna open as well. What's gonna happen is orcs
Hundreds and hundreds of orcs are going to pour out of those places and you have to defend them
You have to kill them all or else they're going to take that over back when so how do you do this?
Also
With your crossjournal, you can shoot it like this. It has a couple of little features, too
You can do like I don't know why we all thought that place
But the cool part about this game and why it's sort of like tower defense is because you have all these things you can put
Down so I have started to upgrade or I've already upgraded this poison spike trap and I use the
Super boom barrel, but I'm not gonna use that right now because I don't you don't
I don't
Really really interesting in this game and look at how many spells you're gonna actually end up getting two more
It's a whole lot of fun. And yes, you'll see what I'm gonna do here is beat up. I remember this game
America's funny some videos. Oh, yeah, I played this for three hours. Can you hear the fucking jewelry is tapping?
God's right. How do I dodge?
You just saw this one, right? This game is really fun. I
I want more games like this that are just fun. Don't funny. I don't care if they're like
60 plus hour experiences hundred-hour experiences
I would gladly pay 40 to 60 dollars for a game that even if I get three to six whatever four to six hours of
Enjoyment from it. I just want a game. That's fun
and then I don't have to have like a
Legend on a mini-map fuck with like 15 different keys on the legend
You know what I mean? Like oh, there's like that turn in there's like the side quest. There's the collection
There's the other collection. There is the side mission for the collection
Care I just give me a nice it's gonna be a fun game. I'll pay the money. That's a number 98 opinion
No, I can't go forward. I can't go left or right
Talk shit talk shit talk shit talk. Why are you chanting that?
Chanting in the back just like come on talk. What shit talk shit talk. All right
All right, okay. Yeah, I hear you. Okay
I think
That I think that if you throw it make a game. That's even
Two to three hours long but has some replayability and some and share ability
Think about that. You want to share this kind of shit?
Like let's say it's only like a four or five hour game
Your ability to want other people to enjoy it is another reason to why to pay the money. I
Cannot tell you the last time and I fucking mean this the last time
I paid for a triple-a game
I
Wanted somebody else to play it too. I like wanted to share it with somebody. Nope
Give me a deal has not happened in a very very long time
You play some of these triple-a games that are like 60 bucks and you just want to forget they existed
You mean you enjoy them for like a couple hours and you forget they exist
I want to be able to tell everybody about this shit
Like remember Stardew Valley you remember like telling everybody how fun Stardew Valley was and you've got a fucking play
You've got to play it that doesn't happen
$60 is worth it to me if I can share it with people. We actually class shorts there. That's a reddit take
Just maybe stub my toe. I just stub my toe right here and that's your fault
And I want you banned for at least 10 seconds. I can probably try to what is this game?
Clone drone in the dangers. Oh, I'm over this. This is actually kind of fun. I think I was playing with people in the chat
Wasn't I?
It's like a lightsaber robot game watch out for the train
Wanting to connect with other people is the least reddit take Oh
Spikes. Oh, he died. I just got dunked on. Holy shit. That was bad
All right. Now, I know what I'm doing. I get that was I got slammed dunked on I'm going with a hammer here
Probably should have an armor, but I got I got another chance here. Where is he up there games for me?
Are all about being able to like wanted a chase game to play them to show them to people
That was one of the reasons for like the original YouTube channel
We actually are doing the chase game. I wanted to show people something because I thought it was really cool fun
Like I really liked it
If I can't be confident to tell you how much I want to like share an experience with you or like tell you that
You should try something
All right. Here we go
No jammer and armor see if we can't seal the deal here
Oh, he might see what you want to show people how to backstab as a spy
Well, cuz spy was the little my favorite thing in the world. That was like my favorite thing ever
You're on his reddit take. Holy shit. That was sick
This game looks good
This game actually looks pretty fun
Smog yeah gets smogged. Good game, dude. Seriously. That was a ton of fun
Let's be the last one that we're gonna take a piss break and come back and we'll do challenge mode
Spinning wheel of death say it like you haven't played it before you're forced to fight on the one level
I don't know. I forget everything. Yes. I don't remember anything that I ever do ever
That's why these streams are so weird to me. We just did it for like 45 minutes and it was it was just fucking mess
I don't remember saying any of these words
What's this game called? This game is?
Clone drone in the danger zone. I gotta go in aggressive
I think we're gonna get into the BRB though after this next one unless I beat away with the game here
For this experiment to work. We've got to win three times did once not more a lot of TF2 and do it again. Oh
Wow, I can't do that shit anymore
Got ya, is it gonna be a second win? It's gonna be a second win. I
This is win number two and I don't even need to make an edit. I don't think
because
That was like two seconds. So we can just keep talking about like I don't know the weather
Jack's now it's got a dead sunny outright overcast right now. It ain't bad edit Andy. It ain't very good last from the past
What is this about? Well, I know how to I know how to play territory control. Don't worry. I've played it before about hydro
Let's do it again. Oh, it is hydro like two minutes
Let's get at the third victory on hydro and then I can go eat like a banana, right?
I think I had to do this on my server because nobody played this so like why not right?
Why wouldn't you eat a bunch of bananas if you bought why there's this many people in this one tunnel? That's right
This is like we're gonna win. Did we get a bingo? You got one
I'll show you the updated card. I didn't do it. I didn't do anything. I didn't do it looking for a rumor still looking for
ejects moment
naked
Played hydro. I mean some people do it again
Third time's a charm. Let's go. You've only been naked three times. I've been no no edits
We're not doing any editing right now. I want to I want to see for myself. I've been naked
four or five hundred times on screen
I've been naked probably okay, how many how many streams have I ever done a thousand
I've streamed about a thousand times
I've been naked seven or eight hundred of those times
I'm just not on camera
Well, not naked like with no clothes on but like no shirt or like shirt and you know, I'm not
Right now things are just happening. I'm gonna get myself in trouble. I need to shut up and we're gonna win quiet. Yeah
Stand up right now. You did it. No
All right, we got to the end of this video. I'm gonna pause it
I'm gonna take a VRB. I'm gonna go pee
Why you do it?
Why would I ever turn a webcam on if I didn't have pants or underwear on are you guys out of your mind?
The risk I told you about the dream that I had that time. That's a reality for me
I had a dream one time for those of you that are new
Where I was sitting here talking and I stood up for a second and I was naked and for a tiny little frame
Like okay, this is weird. This is maybe you click the mature body and sporting
I don't give a shit but like one little frame my like my dick was on camera and
Like a 20-30 minute stop knows I'm talking
but like a tab for like not it was like a little like a tenth of a second frame and
Like I nobody said anything I looked over at the chat and it was like I've realized what had happened
I was like, holy shit. I think like I just my dick was just on camera
I like balls were on camera
But nobody was saying anything and you know for a fact that if that happened in real life
It would be dick dick dick. I could see his dick dick dick, you know, maybe that's what all it would be
So I didn't see that so sitting there going. Holy shit. Did nobody see that?
I like but I have to can't even address it
I have to like delete the vaude
But if I delete the vaude wouldn't that be like kind of suspicious I was like, how did nobody see that?
I was like freaking out about it. I was like fuck man
I think people saw that and then I woke up so I've had that dream before was like, okay ready like I
Stood up first thing. I like stretched my back and we're talking like right
It's like dick right here. I just just right and I was like, holy fuck
I think my camera was small enough where I don't think anybody caught it, right? All right, I'll be right back
I'm gonna pee. I'll see you in a minute. Okay, what's happening? Also, by the way, just to make sure everybody's aware
As of probably next weekend nominations are gonna open up for
The best and worst award show start to get the categories ready. It'll be in the discord
The dollhouse is gonna auto win every category
well
I'm thinking of potentially just graying out the dollhouse
Because we'll end up with the Lord of the Rings the return of the king where it wins every category at the Oscars
That's it. Have it be its own category. Yeah, that makes sense
Ah
So instead we'll only have four streams to choose from what what do you mean four streams?
It should be a moment from that stream. Yeah that I'll get some good categories. They're only four
And
Stop the music. All right, that's very jarring for a lot of you. I apologize. We're coming back
We're going to do how long they're gonna we're gonna click it again because we need to kind of recalibrate here
It is currently there are 40 more minutes remaining
I'll add another I'll add 10 more minutes. So there's 50 is an hour
Let's call it an hour because the BRBs for you to get any more bingos
What's the BRB music from that is from Bloor Dow an incredibly talented individual
He's made all the music pretty much for this channel all the art. Literally the BRB screen
You're looking at right now was made by Bloor Dow. Oh
By the way, let's talk about this for a second. Lord out is currently we talked
Day or so ago Lord. I was making four new BRB screens and they're gonna be seasonal which holy
Champ, right four new BRB screens and I just kind of told him more music. He's gonna make a bunch more tracks
We're gonna get more blood out of music at least probably four or five more
I'm telling you let me be the first to tell you what when when Lord Oh eventually gets hired
We're doing like a fucking it's like a game soundtrack of the year
Like whatever whenever it is because it's gonna happen. Yeah, I just we knew first we knew here first, right?
We knew first it's gonna be so awesome to be like a Bloor Dow hipster when he wins fucking game
Soundtrack of the year in like five years. I liked him. I knew it and I liked his music before you did
I'm excited to see what um, what he makes you're gonna be a gatekeeping. I'm just kidding. I'm not gonna do that
You can't the world is ending in 2022. That's I did why are you saying that? Why you say that?
I mean, he doesn't know you have a setting selected that makes YouTube videos come up much more often
It's part it's part of the site
I wanted to make sure that YouTube videos had an equal chance to show up
It still is like I think like 25% chance though because last time last time we did this
I just was doing the random and it was like 2% chance to get a video
so now what it does is I believe is it picks the video file first and
Then picks a timestamp. That's kind of how I imagined it
So I think it what I think before just picked like a timestamp now it picks a video file then the timestamp
So that that's not rigged. That's exactly how it probably should be. You're gonna stream Elden Ring now fuck that game
All right. Um, let's go. Of course I am I think I can't fucking contain my excitement for that game
All right, let's put the timer back on. Here we go. Let's just remind everybody about the bingo card that currently stands
I don't think it's gonna happen again going over these
No, you need a significant moment for some of these to happen. Who's your favorite Game of Thrones character Varys?
I don't know why I answered that that show is fucking completely who cares about that anymore
Intended like didn't like HBO come out with like the trailer for like new series
They were gonna do and it had like fucking four likes on Twitter. We got like retweeted like eight times
I didn't have something like that. I don't remember stop pretending pretending about my favorite character is do you only know something funny?
Okay, this is a confession
We're gonna do confessional right now the amount of okay the amount of times that I've watched and I don't even know why I still
Do this, but I just do the amount of times that I've watched the Varys. Okay. Hold on
This is spoilers for Game of Thrones
Spoilers for Game of Thrones the the series I'm just gonna tell you. Okay, here we go. Here it comes
You know, if you don't want to hear a spoiler why who cares the show is over
Varys visiting Ned in the dungeon both times
I've probably watched collectively and I'm not kidding. I'm not I'm trying being desperately completely truthful with you
I've watched that scene on YouTube. I'll be four or five hundred times total over the last five plus years
I don't even know why I just get I know every single line by heart. I know the whole thing
I don't even know why I just I like it. I like that scene
I don't know why I swear to God, it's been four or five hundred times. You quoted all the time
I believe I I'm telling you recite it Lord Stark. You must be thirsty
No, I'm not doing this
No, not so much my lord men have been known to die of thirst in these holes hide it push it away
Keep going. I don't think I can well, let me see if I can actually do this. I've seen five hundred
But I'm like on the spot. I'm kind of nervous. I like don't want to do this
And then it goes. Okay men have been noted I thirst in these holes
I'm gonna I'm gonna mix them together
But who cares what madness has led you to tell the Queen the you know, the truth of Joffrey's birth
Madness of mercy. She might cheat save her children
Mercy, I'm done. I'm actually done. I'm not doing this veto veto veto veto veto veto veto veto. I'm vetoing
I'm fucking done. I'm like embarrassed. I'm at this first time
I've ever been embarrassed on stream is that I can't get am I gonna get sued if I dub this if I can see it
I can do it and I'm not kidding. No, no, no, no, I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I don't want to do that
Clear the debt
No, it's not happening. Let's go
Spawn camp
What are you gonna do? You can open up that fucking spawn door, right? That's ours. I'm vetoing another tf2 video
Veto we've seen I'm vetoing tf2. We've seen a lot of it. I'm vetoing veto incoming
I have to I have one more veto after this time has never been the same ever since I got a robo hand built by
Robo and incorporated the grip is just too tight. I keep telling them to loosen it, but they refuse to help me out
I think it's a conspiracy. Do you know robo hand industries are owned by the same company who specialize in PP reconstruction?
Fuck is happening
NKVC thanks for the $1. Here is some free money cuz why not? Thanks man
Mars gaming YouTube again. Thanks for the why am I saying YouTube? It's in YT
Thanks for the $1
Germacraft one word one man. The meme shall not die
Sir feline. Thanks for the $1
Yeah, I'll add it. Okay fine. That was fucking ridiculous
PP reconstruction
Oh, man, there's an opportunity for another 200 community subs. I
Think I think I know what happened tonight
So like the TV bit brought us up to an 11 and then I played this fucking boring game
And it brought us down to like a 4 so I think I think I understand what happened here
We started off at an 11 and we came down to like a three and a half. What like energy wise?
I'm a vamp here the title
Vampire I remember that was that was like a really hyped up game. Wasn't it from what I remember admits it was poor
I'm not I don't I don't think that forget what the story with that was at the opening credits
the huge fight scene happens and
You know Jackie Chan has taken on like 30 people. It's the new Jackie Chan movie credits open bang bang bang bang
Through the guy brings a ladder up
He dies through the ladder hits the guy in the face swings ladder around bang bang bang bang bang four guys around go flying through windows
Explosions everywhere and then the rest of the movie is Jackie Chan at a desk
Writing letters for an hour. That's the rest of the movie. That's what happened today. That's that's what this movie was
That's what happened. Nice elevator pitch for your show or movie
He was writing his Christmas cards for the rest of the movie for three hours. All right, we're looking for well
I'm not looking for this cuz okay naked
Jax it has to be a real Jax moment under these bullshit
The movie was too interesting in the first like 12 minutes and then I was writing Christmas cards for four hours
All right, 20 seconds. Let's go. What the fuck is he saying? Okay, let me translate
Thank you. Mars gaming. The game was exciting for the first 10 minutes and then it was terrible and boring for the next two hours
Lenny face what the fuck that's old. That's very old Lenny face
My god, I'm an idiot. Oh an exit an egg that
I'm gonna use my last video. What you got on me? Not that prick. Oh, ha ha if this ha ha
Oh god, and it's in the title. This is bad. Ouch
I had no idea how this game even worked and I thought it was terrible. I thought this game was awful. I
Didn't even pay attention to any of that. I was too busy laughing at my like stupid jump. Yes, I'll do it. Sure
Yes, screw your family, I just shut this guy up
Oh my god, oh
Oh, oh
Wait, I didn't know you could do that. I didn't know you could do that. Oh, no
Was I not supposed to do that hog face? No that you have to see it on camera. Sorry
Wield right weapon two-handed. Oh, I can use this as a two-hander. Oh great. Yeah, let me use it
Dude dark souls series where you have to unplug your head from the matrix to understand even why people play fighting in a stupid hallway
I can't even swing my sword
Back in like 2012 2013
This was not as popular as everybody it is now back in like 2010 2011
No, don't kill me. This was just like why the fuck do people like this?
I don't even know where's the bonfire. I didn't even get it. Like I was like, why do I die so easily like it?
What's the guy I have to start over again like this?
Stupid when I first played it fuck is going on
I had to pull the cord out of the back of my head and go wait a minute
This is incredible if we're like I gotta I have to play this it took like a year after this video
Not gonna be an idiot. Oh, that's so much more damage. I had the exact same experience. Yeah, I want to know the actual statistic
Of people that played dark souls when it first came out or demon souls
Said I don't I don't get it and then came back two years later and played it again and was like holy shit
It's my favorite game ever made
It's probably a shitload of you
What does that even do? I can't even do it. Look at okay. You can't get me while I'm jumping
I know I want my this is an edited video of dark souls
I'm in the tunnel before the asylum demon and I'm five and a half minutes into an edited video
This is how you just know like what I don't know what the fuck I'm doing
Easier that way that was a double hit you like double cheeseburger hit. Yeah, you do the channel yet
It's just start second German channel stream highlights other videos very frequent upload. This is my goodbye from YouTube video
twitch.tv see
Tuesday Thursday and Friday 7 p.m. Eastern time every single time no exceptions
No, unless I get like sick then I won't stream but Tuesday Thursday and Friday
Twitch.tv slash German 95, but that's all I gotta say. That's it
I hope I could make it clear enough that these things are happening and no direction the channel is taking now and yeah
Go subscribe to German too, and I'll see you guys soon. No
See you later. Have a good rest of your summer. It's not even summer. It's like it's like September 26th
Oh my god. Yeah, the last time I made like a hey, what's up guys video was in
June well like May this is the last video. I did have a good rest of your summer
Is that the last video on the channel? No, I think there's more. There's another one. Okay. Well that was 10 15 seconds
Yeah, well, I got like a bunch of fucking chest and back problems. Hey, hey, hey German from like four years ago
Thanks for the fucking curse. Take it off. Take it off. I know there's a fucking goddamn goblin or like
Genie or something watching this right now, then put that curse on and you're sitting there going like
Yes
Take it off now. Take it off. We're so good. Goblins aren't real
Yes, they are. You best start believing in ghost stories because I'm a guy. I'm a goblin. That's whatever
That's so rude
So rude
I'm just it was a just a joke everybody relax. I'm kidding. Oh my god. I'm kidding
Is Santa real yes, who else puts the presents under my tree? What was you gonna say? It's like my mom and dad
Let's go. I got a ninth. You know, let's just leave it on whatever. What's next overuse Santa joke
It's like getting to be holiday season. They're in style right now. Please don't tell me this is the corridor mission
No, not that one the one after that one because the corridor missions to Earth Defense Force five equipment
Do we eventually get I wonder if I call italics in this room and he's in it
Um, I don't for fence Spencer, I don't know. Yeah, I don't remember them having support
Let's try the bolt gun
Okay, are you hurting me? I am
Edf teaches you pretty early on to go back and farm now that repeated weapons get upgraded
So I guess if you find the same weapon again game was so much fun. That's cool. I
Remember we were gonna play this a shitload better than one and we just never did ever again
Who this this thing is actually really great
It's a great single target. They come up with another one, but it wasn't Edf
It was like Edf Dragon Lance was a good choice. Whoever suggested it. Thanks. I don't know what it wasn't a numbered one
I'm gonna go that far though
What's the new one? It's so easy. If six is coming out
Well, I don't play it
Three new ones. Holy shit. I love these games. It's just shoot shit
Iron rain sucked that that's what I'm thinking of. I'm not seeing very many crates. It was maybe a different studio, right?
It's so slow. These are so heavy
Doing this because if I look tiny
I'm just look if I don't frame myself correctly. I look really small
If I frame myself like this, I'm fucking huge jacked like handsome and shit. You know, I mean
Six would be good. All right
This definitely doesn't feel harder
Crap
This is just playing the game. What happened to you being jacked?
I mean I was in the gym. It only goes into four or five days a week
That's what happened. I stopped doing that. I got it does but I missed realness made it hard to really do stuff like that anymore
Now I just like eat food this thing I'd rather just use the other lighting gun
Wait, why are combat? I missed the 500 sub celebration video
30 more seconds
Alright we go you've got about 30 minutes to fill the rest of those slots. It's so hard to aim
Yeah, you don't see it anywhere to buy. Yeah for some reason thousand people here
We're on the PlayStation store, you have to go look no you have to like look for it was up like purposefully search it. Oh
God in 2018. Yeah, I explained what we're doing again. I think I've done it a few times
Man that was crazy. I can't believe that just happened. I hope it doesn't happen again
Protect me my BS protect me
Weapons they don't even know where they're going
My god, they're awful. They're not even attacking anything just running
You guys suck
This is a classic a classic comedy
This goes out to the broken hearted
We already have singing on there. Don't worry
It's my life and it's now or never
I don't want to live forever
Not bad. I just
He hasn't talked this whole time
I died with god Modan. I have no control over my character
I'm just on fire. How are you on?
What wait, there's a dinosaur
Oh, yes, I got up there I forgot about this. Oh
Man back in the back of the day when I remember stir used to hit me up and say hey
I downloaded too many mods and my computer crashed. Would you like to play GTA? He's like, yeah, sure, of course
All these videos of all the weird mods and all like just the the asset replacements the character replacements
GTA 4 I think is my favorite GTA probably out of all of them
But I can't ever go back and play it ever again. It's it's I can't
I'm just imagining a car flying by and like an elephant in a giraffe falling out with parachutes on and like
500 explosions going on behind me and like I can't die and shit. Like I can't play it anymore
I have over modded to the point where I can't even enjoy it. Same thing with Skyrim
I play a character. I've never played before and like know how to play this fucking game like this character
You got another complaint stream. That's too much pressure. I hated this game, too
I've really hated this and I didn't want to say I hated it because I knew a lot of people liked it and I didn't
want to be like the
contradicting Andy
What and everybody would be like, oh you fucking just suck at it. Like I hated this
Actually, this is great. Can I go back like years later so I can tell you what I was really thinking
I hated this game. Yes, you casual
Bend that guy for life for real like give the gift that guy the first
Real full full band for that I've ever given man that guy fucking fine. I don't ever see that guy again. Damn. I
Hate this game. I really don't just turn the chat off. I don't want to know turn off the chat
Keep it on we were doing 2v2s. We were getting destroyed. No stir was like carrying hard and I was dying and getting mad
I don't do that. I'm kidding. I'm curious. How does it play out?
shield bad
Shield is broken shield guys broken
still
Holy should you hear that exhale? Oh
my god
Is this game still my service? Is this service still library? Is this like get we shopped?
You know what is this thing still live? I'm gonna beat this guy
Fucking brought that guy's health to zero you can cancel out of literally anything with revenge mode
So mid-grab you probably had one hell that that dude
I stabbed him three times with zero health and then he pressed triangle and got all his health back and can kill me round two
What? Yeah, why is that?
Wow, what the fuck is the point of that no explain that to me playing obi soft I want an employee
Hey, would you like an explanation? They added that mechanic into the game to help you win?
against multiple enemies
Karen and yet he was able to build revenge
I
Am kind of a gamer Karen aren't I?
Seriously, I was I was somebody from management to tell me I want a written letter about it. Oh, we just did this
The next room contained an oh, yes under the dear hatchet family crest on the desk were many
Recent veto. No, I'm not wasting my last veto on this. This is I loved this. This was a ton of fun old coins wine
cryptic runes
Decide for the runes, but it's our veto. Are you guys gonna use one here? Just as I picked up that'll leave you with two
The candle lit itself and a funky phantom friar floated into the room
No veto
This guy looks friendly, okay burn his papers enjoy wine and candle light. Are you naked here?
I don't he's snapping fingers the candle in a glass of the house
Extend why this dream was a week ago the ghost what?
Why would I extend this frame? You can just go well, I didn't want to kill him
He just wanted to hang out six days ago. Oops. Well, uh
Sorry, I'm one I couldn't mute
What's the deal? No that you thought half of these monsters
I want a very non hostile walk of the Golden's place
We're staying to watch the stream that just happened you can do a Thanksgiving stream. No music room. I want to go to the music room
You do but your voice sounds different. What happened dude?
We sound completely different you like leave the cellar search the cell. Where's the music room sounds like older from now
Hmm
Dude you sound wicked jaded music room sound jaded whistle sound hummer first floor say second floor second floor
I'm gonna use my last veto you guys won't
The second floor looked dark and uninviting
It's only another 50 seconds. It could room at random find the kitchen waste your veto. No
Good eats the room. I next entered was obviously a library of some running out of time
Well, yeah, you got a great job. We had about 20 minutes. Oh
There is there was a door to my left
See the reason why you should be using your vetoes as a collective chat room if you have you'll have three you still have my right
Looking for bingo here and I'm telling you right now
you're not gonna get it here and you have about 25 minutes, so you need to really kind of get your act together and
Skip some of these streams that are three minutes of just waste time. Let's go right. Let's see. I'm just telling you
I couldn't put my finger on it, but there was something odd about the woman in the kitchen. Here we go
You're hungry
That's why you haven't seen me lately
but I'm coming right back at you with this daisy game play and I've been playing this game for the last three weeks or so and
Something to remember something of note. I've died every single fucking time. I've ever played this game
I don't have any really suits or any sniper rifles or anything like that
But I live on the edge. I live dangerously as you see right here walking on the main road
This is new to me, I don't remember this
Vito
You have to vote for this
Eons of centuries of rust and this was owned by
Alright, alright, it's unanimous
Catherine of England. All right, you get you know, that's not all right. We're going you got it done. I
Am currently on my way. Hey Jeffrey Jeffrey. I need to talk to you. Where are you lad? I'm currently bleeding and
Profusely from the face and I need some bandages. I need some help here. I'm having fun playing
I haven't played in a long time. Is everybody even listening to me?
Hey, hey, look, that's true. Let's work together. Come here buddy. Come here. You didn't get scammed
Well, I'll add three minutes to the timer. You didn't get scammed
I promise you didn't get scammed to the Warcraft 3 custom map thing on battle.net
The only thing you would see was Dota Dota 3.6 Dota 3.06 all-stars Dota Dota Dota Dota Dota
That's when everybody really started to get into it and I was delicious. Face it. I was really bad at it
I tried it a few times
I tried to play for a couple hours on the Dota games and I would just get
Rocked and it kind of turned me off for the rest of my life
I'm not wasting if you know was when I was probably 16 or 17 years old
I'm not wasting a long time ago, but it turned me off from MOBAs
I never really wanted to get started in them again League of Legends, huh? They're all they all kind of were the same
They're all that Warcraft 3 Dota that I was terrible at but now
What? It's you? What are you weirdoing?
Which I wasn't really that excited for I didn't really read up too much about it
I just knew it was a new mobile one more I think a mobile like you're out of vetoes man
I think you got one more on I think a Dota 2 and it just kind of was like I don't want to play all right
All right. All right. All right. Did I know that this game was WASD to move? All right. All right
All right person Jesus Christ. He's my using the default scatter gun the Criticola and the Sandman
This is the first time I've ever equipped the Sandman in a commentary ever and not just a commentary
I haven't put this thing on probably since it came out back in like
2008 or 9 whenever they released this thing. I haven't used it once since then
This is also on CP gravel pit and it's on defense if you couldn't already tell now here
Let me tell you why I'm playing scout scout on gravel pit on defense
He's really really awesome because I don't see in the bottom of the screen. They have to cap
You know veto veto veto good place. I win. This is a good one. Oh fuck. We have to do it again wheel man
He'll die. Don't worry. God damn it. They're like little mice. You're trying to catch a mice with your bare hands
There you go. He's dead
two minutes, oh shit losing down now like I
Can't believe we skipped
Shitty this looks
My streams my god, this is like 2,000 bitrate. It's like 2000 like 15
This is back before like they I could do that raised the cap again left again
Think I'm running fucking circles, you know, I mean this is a rumor and doi doi doi. No, it's not
Rumor has to be somebody driving by it's like perfect dick idiots
The download counts towards the hour. No, it does not
You still don't scream in 10 ADP turn this spaghetti
That's because you need to leave you need a higher bitrate to go higher than 720 if you don't have a higher bitrate
Then it looks like shit, especially if you're at 60 FPS. I don't scream at 30
Go, please
Cops are teleporting by the way wearing the fence. The fence is now part of the car. Nice networks
transcoding Andy Oh
How far away is why can't you raise your bitrate? I see this 1080 and 60. Come on
They probably have a screaming PC. They probably streaming at more than 6,000 do it
6,000 bitrate 1080p 60 FPS
Just it doesn't look good motion game like please get there and do it doesn't look good in motion 12 seconds
You're doing 30 you can do it
You can do it. I have a 30 90. Yeah, I don't want to get in a circle get in the circle
Holy shit, relax. What the fuck was that? My mic peaked
Yeah, I think you guys are in trouble, I don't think you're gonna get another I don't think you're gonna get another 100
You got about 15 minutes at 5 15
You're looking for gambling you're looking for Drew crew you're looking for a wink
Looking for naked you're looking for a room or any room or driving by
You're looking for an extreme Jax moment
And even if you get Jax, you still need to get the naked moment, too
It's a different game
We go to Tokyo chocolate here. Not yet 10 out of 10 game. By the way, I need to go to Kona
It's a grandma game. This is a pretty damn fun. Grandma game. It was I don't care grandma games can be fun
Are you kidding me? Oh, there is gambling in this but you are a grandma fine
But is it right here? It's too early
Yeah, I don't think Lee Wonka
It's a different a different island
Zachariah tangi is a friend of mine and I understand that things are going quite well with you in the shop in Morocco extend
I too am interested in forming a partnership be careful here
If you use your last life here, you have one more my signing over this you wonder if you have two more
Take a hundred and twenty cases of your tart of the moon to Zach. I don't really enjoy
I think the gambling happens one very very much ordering further in this pod
You have two more you can either extend or you can beat a app store
I'm staying here because I'm likes my own game. I don't have anybody else hates it, but he's keeping me in business
It's too late. Yeah, you could veto this in 20 cases. Well, I have to get that ready
It's far too early for gambling. Even if you extend it twice. God damn it. What do I need?
Tart of the moon is so such a pain in the ass. No, no, no, it's yeah
I'm just burning the clock right now against you guys. Okay, I need
125 lemons I hiked the ball and just went down
Lemons, okay. Let's go. We need to hold hold. Oh, it's so late to do a veto now
That would be a waste on the clock pick talk run the clock. I'll take lemons, please
I need a hundred and twenty five of them too late now. Oh, I love how this is just so slow
There's nothing happening. This is perfect for me. Perfect. What I just buy let's get a reminder here
Look like a lemon. No, look at me either. I do that every other stream. I'm surprised even seen it
It looks like a lemon. I just clicked it and said go whatever. It was a part where click master on every stream, too
I got eight hundred sixty thousand dollars. Who cares?
Let me extend at that. I'm making Tart of the moons. All right, I can do better than 21 though
I said not a crunch time. Let's go
Okay, come on. This is gambling. No, it's not
Well, we're gonna go for it cactus. Canyon doesn't like me
This is that oh, it's absolutely not gonna be
Nope, that ain't happening. I think our way back again. Oh, I've seen a lot of vetoes here. Yeah until 515 repeat
Can we do it? Although wait a minute. Hold on and here we go. I'm not gonna pay attention to me
Oh, I'm done. Okay. There's a lot of going on here. This is gonna be tough
By the way, if a veto does come through you get the full hundred eighty seconds again. Just make sure you understand that
Wait
Cactus candy was so good. Get him out of here. This seems pretty unanimous so far
You give me that over. All right, you give me that over and things are gonna change. Oh
Thanks for hanging out run up the stairs on all fours. I can do that. No, I'm not gonna do that
I'm not going to do that slide down the stairs
You want to make like a sled and go down the stairs? What are we looking for? What do we have a chance?
What am I gonna use for sled? You know, I could probably use the like what we use the bed sheet
This is the dumb actually be possible. I might actually be that makes me be easy
No, this is all shit. Okay. Oh, right. I don't know. How long is this? Oh, no, that's his opportunity here
What am I doing? Oh shit, it's an extension. What a weirdo. What are you doing? Oh, no, it's gonna happen, isn't it?
I don't know when it happens though
Fucking shit was in there. There was like a bunch of costumes. Why is this Vaughn so shitty?
Do I know that I'm live why does it look like I don't even know the camera's on did I think I turned the stream off?
I can't even hear it make a dinosaur to clay. Yeah, I know I'm extending
You were so thin and young this is like three years ago guys
I don't know
Okay
Will it happen in the next three minutes? Thank you. I need to put the mic back up to my mouth
What am I doing? So much you aged like milk. Um, excuse me. I don't think so Mike
I've aged like a fucker. I think I've aged like fucking blue cheese, which is moldy and old, but it's fucking delicious
What is this on me? Oh
ghost ectoplasm
Fuck is that?
He slimed me there was like a cobweb that was like a spider web that was fucked up
Anything you didn't hear anything. I actually kind of like this little microphone, right? I like it
I it's fun. There's a spider in here somewhere
Probably I probably ran it over when I was doing the fucking six sled move that you guys just saw
You're drunk is fucking this am I do a ghost hunt stream. Is it where is this where do the magic tricks closets?
Those might do the magic trick where I unplug my router on camera and plug it back in and like it turns the stream off
But it like doesn't write the paint cans that he has in his basement. I just disappear off cringe
You extending again. Oh, this is risky. I can't do a house tour guys. I can't believe that worked
I unplugged the ethernet from my router
And I would plug it back in and sprint out of the fucking room and I would just disappear why was that happening?
This just like scraped my nose all in we're trying to do anything right now
I have been trying to kill time here for like in a fucking hour almost and it's still not working. Look at me
Oh, yeah, it's it's off. Do I like pretend to take my shirt off do this?
Like can you guys hear my stomach you want to see if we could let you want me to do like an endoscopy?
See, let's see if you guys can hear inside my like esophagus. Could you could you hear it? It's loud inside
Hold on. What are you doing?
Screaming
Everybody's waiting for it. I don't know what's gonna happen though. Ears are dead. Really? I turned it down so low too
I'm so sorry blame
This is such a cursed stream. It was gross. It probably was how was my birthday pretty sick
So wait, okay. Hold on a second if you guys are out of extensions, that's it
We're good. You're not gonna see the thing you think you're gonna see. I don't
What are you talking about Lincoln I would say probably
Face probably Jefferson Grover Cleveland. I saw Grover Cleveland. You were fucked up three years ago
I can be a pretty good Lincoln. I think from this angle
Lincoln was I had a full bald head, right?
Lincoln Lincoln had like a ponytail, right? So Lincoln had like a bun ponytail up here
Okay, and he had like these long you get another one here. I get another one like that
If you get another one, I get another one too down here. You really want to make that trade. Do you want to extend?
Put it up. So, um, you got ten minutes
Looks like I can close my eyes and see him
Big eyes up here two big eyes
blue fur the cookie monster his mouth opens like this that he's got the no nose and
That's uh, he's eating cookies eating cookies a lot of are we doing it? Hey, right? Okay
Do you guys want to see it so bad? I don't know if it's gonna happen though. I get another one, too
Among us character on the whiteboard
Except a side profile of red
Is that what you mean?
That's so fucking funny, I'm gonna go just rage eat no, I'm not supposed to be angry about this
Oh, by the way, everybody
I have a lot of work to do you got so much work you've extended but I've got I've
Received into my bank account of veto
Interesting so I could veto this right now. It's there interesting. Well this camera angle cuz I can't even unplug
And tell you you don't need to know when I want to use my video I could use it whenever I want typing into
Google buzz feed quiz and I don't even care what the first one is. That's the one we're gonna do
Okay, take this pizza pizza quiz. Take this pizza quiz. How's my punch the camera?
We'll reveal your mental and actual age pick. Okay. Hold on a minute. Let me get this on screen
We're gonna do a pizza quiz. It would be stupid. Nobody gets anything
I'm gonna hold it because I know everyone's waiting for like the look of me poses and shit that I'm gonna do
But it's I don't think it happens and they already think it already did happen
Yeah, I think you guys I think you guys screwed they're gonna get my age here
They're gonna get my mental age and my physical age. She was laying on the whiteboard
Oh you guys are you guys just blew through two extensions three extensions. It's over and I and you gave me a veto
It happens at 29 minutes. Oh, no
No, I'm the star. It was an opportunity for like a pose. I think this still is an opportunity
We got meat lovers seafood. Who the fuck is ordering seafood on their pizza? Yeah, I agree. That's that's weird
What's on there? I don't like that dinosaur feet on here. No, absolutely not preem. It's a bad take. Whatever
It's fine. Give me a bad take lovers. There's no meat on here meat lovers sucks. It falls apart
It's like be you're eating a lasagna barbecue chicken
Are we kids all right pepperoni that's pretty good, but who the fuck who the fuck was put who put the olives
walks slime rancher
What else should I do here? I could buy another plot. Wait, they're actually my I'm this was peel growth. Let's go
Yeah, this is peak like poses and doy-doy-doys and shit. I might get rid of this
Oh, yeah, I remember I'm soft lock myself in here, right? Okay. So what's over here? Nice. Nice. Nice. Nice. Nice
Why is the camera so bad looks awful in a rooster get a rooster? Well, there's no roosters over here
What plots it's always been this bad what not this bad I built this area myself
I'm just dumping an entire coffee on my ground on my desk and everything. I already did that
It's just this just like makes me feel cool
I still can't believe I actually did that earlier like a couple hours ago. Remember get a rooster
I will that sucks because it's been so clean in here. It really has and now it's gonna be like gross coffee
It's not about coffee spills. I don't know what the vile
Disgusting properties like enzymes and coffee or whatever
But when you spill coffee and it dries it smells like that dirty fucking ass garbage can it's
Disgusting milk. I don't I don't put milk in my coffee, but it still does that it just smells like just like just
decaying dead flesh or something. I'm gonna clean this again when I'm done
You look so young dude. This was this was like
Seven months ago
I just have a shaved face
I have a shaved face and a haircut
It's kind of weird because you guys have a real-time vision of
Decades plus of my life. So there will be a point where I kind of look old, right?
It's but maybe it's starting to happen too. You have a barometer of a decade plus of on-camera shit
You'll be able to know the moment that I turn old
Pushes away slime and you need some space you got fatter
Yeah, I told you I know rooster guys. I meant remind me to get a rooster not spam get a rooster
Will be okay grandpa
Hey look, I'm telling you I'm almost I'm getting closer to 40 if I can keep this up
If I can look
Do
Vito Vito Vito Vito Vito Vito and you Vito's Vito
What's like the first thing you did after you were pregnant?
Vito Vito Vito Vito Vito Vito Vito Vito Vito Vito Vito
I'm out of videos
Get this spy out of here. Ah
No, keep them up. Thank you. Keep them off the cat. What's in there listening to that shit?
But asking what like was I just asking what like your pregnancy cravings were what am I talking about?
What's what am I what is wrong with me what the fuck Jeremy what the fuck are you doing? What's wrong with you?
I can smell ya. I can smell you from a mile away. Oh, yes smells
enough the elevator
That's from home alone. Oh come on. Nobody has any vetoes left. We just yet not the elevator
Oh, you was here last night to wasn't you? What was it? Uh you was here and you
You wish you know everybody that is such a fantastic movie. I remember this happy new year
Keep the change you're filthy animal. That's a spy. Wow. Yeah, like four snipers sitting in the back. I just got clubbed
I'll save my century. Thank you Marcus van machinery. You are
Machinery. Yeah machine. Am I even saying that word right? All right. I'm feeling generous
I didn't know how to pronounce the machinist with Christian Bale. I thought it was called the mechanic. We each get two more vetoes
The mechanist let's go
We each get two more vetoes or extension. Oh my god that guy. He's killed. Let's go. How is that guy still up there?
Yeah, you know where to go the gates closed behind them
Kind of trapped we're supposed to be over. Oh, yeah, we're supposed to be over but I've just I did my ultimate extension
They're coming through the tunnels use one to go back. That's not how this program works
No deal. What do you mean? No deal the devil man is devil man up in that top left. He's being a real prick
Yeah, there's a heavy up there in a medic
This is the bonus round stuff. We're in bonus round territory. Have you said look
Oh
Look at how close you are
You really want to throw the opportunity away
Me you already won once see look at that. Look at that. It's all right there. What's the pyro pyro spy spy spy?
All right, let's go
No deal means the stream turns off have you guys speaking yourself you're doing that. Thank you you guys double enough
Wait a minute
What do I get
So if you get okay, how about this we're gonna remove all here's what we're doing we're gonna remove all
vetoes all extensions
Nobody can do shit. I'm gonna do the randomizer five more times
If it hits I actually want to veto this one. Why is why is the world shaking?
I
Can hear noises that I don't like to hear. I'm not naked. I have I'm just sunburned
What's that? What's this like fairy dust on the ground? Oh, this is roller skates
Sick I got like the roller skates I can compete in like the roller derby. I'm not naked
Alright, no vetoes five. This is good. This included this one four more rolls and that's it
I don't know what it was back in the old YouTube days. I was always red
Was always just sunburned every single video
Scares already up there
If I still had a veto I would get rid of it right now I swear to God it's gone
What is what is that? It's not there anymore. Is this before your nose job?
Body just tensed up. I feel I just lifted 200 pounds of weight
All my reps for like the week. Excuse me. It's like the thing with like the the flaming
Dr. Doom skull was looking at me
Why aren't you buff anymore, I don't know because I'm in my 30s indication of where you're
30s because in this video, I'm like in my mid 20s and I'm fucking jacked and sunburned
I would had so much vitamin D in my body that it was making my skin red
Okay, I'm in my 30s you some land
Any more of this that's not a pog
It's a pog face it's pog. Oh, no, this is getting hard now. Oh, yeah. Yeah
How long has it been I've only been recording for five minutes
Well, doesn't do anything. It's just kind of there for fun. Everyone got a new hat to new sunglasses
New new hat and every oh snooze
Human revolutions news. This is gonna be fucking boring
I can't veto this all these items if you pre-order Deus ex the new Deus ex game or you can find them in drops and they
Are craftable if I laugh at this I will give a hundred subs because I wanted Deus ex anyways
So let's get into this guys here. We're gonna start with the engineer and the new engineer items
Let's start by saying that this is a very very odd mechanic. Take a look at my ammo count down there
It takes 60 ammo to shoot it. You do not have a clip anymore. There's no reloading. There's no
Reload time or anything like that. It's just
60 metal to shoot that gun and it's 35 metal to shoot the new pistol
Very very weird mechanic because
You'll find that you'll have no more metal left to shoot the gun and you're kind of just like oh crap
Now what do I do?
It's gonna take a lot of getting used to but for a combat engineer
This will be a awesome new item
Especially the new shotgun because how many times have you been able to not place a mini century down when you wanted to?
Because you didn't have enough ammo or metal see look at my ammo count
113 96 you shoot you lose but you gain it's weird and then this new item here this new pistol it electrocutes people
It's very very odd
Hopefully we can figure this all out guys in the near future in the next couple weeks
It works on buildings as well. So if you shoot a building, I believe point-blank it gives you let's see here
I think it's I think it's 80 to 85 metal per point-blank shot. So I electrocute this sniper
It's kind of a weird we can't it's it's like a tesla coil kind of and it spreads I didn't want to show myself lose
You electrocute somebody I was getting killed around it will hit I cut single person around there
This also destroys projectiles the new pistol see how I shot that building how I did watch a see
Plus 60 plus 60 if you get close enough to people it's sort of like having infinite ammo and you never have to reload
But the problem here guys is you have to be a good shot if you miss all the time if you're not good with the shotgun
I do not recommend you try and get this item because you will just lose metal over and over again
So I get a little assist with that thing. It's very weird see 60 60 60 80 80
It's very very cool. See look see how this thing is spreading. The electrical charge is spreading around
Maybe it's a new spy check mechanic. Maybe you can check for spies. I'm not sure yet guys
This is the first time I've ever played with it
Just want to make sure I get you guys some cool gameplay with it. You see exactly how the item works
I haven't tried to destroy any projectiles with it yet with the with the pistol because I hadn't I didn't really have a chance to be
Honest so trying to get that to work
I'm assuming that it's sort of like a reflect you just click it just did it did it did it you just click once and
That's it. Let's move on to the spy. This is really really cool. You'll see I think I'm all right
I decloak next to this century over here. It doesn't matter like I'm all right mini century
It can be a big century backstab the engine. Thank God. Okay, please
Thank God
People were saying these clips are so bad
Guys wake up at 5 a.m. Some of you do e3 2019
Well, most do you get up at like 11 10, you know, why some of you especially during the summertime, you know
I've got that got demographics. I actually do page. I know I know
Count Olaf hair. Well, I look so much worse
I look so much better over here. I mean, I'm getting that haircut again
When I was in college, I don't get up till fucking like 6 p.m. So you look dirty
Oh, yeah, we get up at 5 every day. I don't look dirty. Who's older. Sorry the data says otherwise
How do we know how old you are? I just have a beard. I have morning classes. Not right now. I wink here
What are you in that you wouldn't high school or college right now?
You're out or into this you're at school
You got up at like fucking 8 o'clock this afternoon Hugh Hefner
That's how you can tell I fucking stay up really late 8 p.m. Is like in the middle of the afternoon old German that smells better
Mmm, I don't think so. I think we smell about the same. I stayed up all night
I was thinking about doing that because I didn't want to miss this because I really
We got three more
Left arm is creepy. Why cuz I'm wearing a bathrobe
There's no wink I would have been delirious
Lipstick no, it's called that. My lips are always dry. So I have to always put an application on right now
I've a lot of different looks guys, although I haven't worn a suit and probably ten years
Well, you should do that. I've done that before and it's I just okay. Do you remember the first?
15 to 20 minutes of this stream go watch it
Look like you drink blood. Let's go. But do you remember go watch that?
I was sitting here just turning the stream on just barely had woken up and I'm just like I
I was weird. I was a weirdo
In a cap, but there's no reason for me to be here
I'm gonna try and pick off people that come out of the spawn and nobody really comes out
Again no reactions at all zero emotion or I'll give the hundreds of trying to find somebody that I can't shoot that guy
I can't shoot that guy
So I just go over to the right side of the spawn and I end up getting a heavy
He just kind of comes out and he just bang gets him right there. That's gonna be the end of the gameplay guys
Thank you all so much for watching. I really appreciate all the support over
So I'll see you all next time and take care everybody. That was a great gameplay
That one doesn't count. Yeah, actually does not count. Oops
It's not over. No, it's not that doesn't count
Tris to game play commentary and tonight
I don't plan as the demo man with the stuff that's on the screen right now
I believe it's the strange lock and load the charge and torch and the
Islander strange Islander and of course you got a hats and crap the miscellaneous whatever battery canteen
I don't want to give advice. No, it's an advice video not really to do about the game. It's an advice video
What's the advice fortress to specifically how to get better at landing your pipe? Oh, no, no, no anything in this game
No, no, no as travel time. No, no
No, although this will probably help you out with your skits his skit scan
What the hell was I gonna just say with your hit scan as well?
But it's mainly gonna focus on the travel time things like the demo man pipes all the checks moment
And even the syringe gun this could probably help you out with the syringe gun as well
And what it is, it's TR walkway
I didn't know anything about this map for the longest time and just very recent. Wait, we don't have that there was no
Deal it's a map you can play pretty much by yourself deals begins now and shooting bots no laughing
It might seem like the most mundane boring thing in the world
But it actually is pretty addicting and they just keep coming out and you're on the red team
They're on the blue team and it's just they walk in a straight line straight at you and you can kind of make some
Adjustments you can make them do jumps. You can make them move in a different direction and it's pretty fun
You'll find yourself just sitting there for what seems like hours
Shooting at these bots and it's so important that you do this for a while and you practice inside a TR walkway
This is good. Eventually your memory will get down to a point where you know exactly where to put this is not cringe
This is actually good advice. You'll go. Oh, this guy's moving in the direction that I'm used to
I know where I'm supposed to place this because I know exactly how it's going to move
I know how the trajectory is gonna go and it's gonna hit the guy and he's gonna die and I'm gonna get more points
and I'm gonna do better in team fortress 2 and I mentioned why it's so important to be good advice is cringe because
Everybody always says that to get better in the game
You got to play you got to practice to get better
You just play and you get better
But it can be pretty damn hard sometimes because when you get into a server and there's a bunch of people that are way better
Than you you're not gonna get to practice your rocket launcher
Shots because they're gonna just kill you in less than a second. So true. You're gonna start to feel bad
So what did the bots don't attack back is the main thing?
They just move and you can practice and it's a way better
Environment and a way better place to get comfortable with the way that these weapons actually work. That's right
Yeah
You don't have to feel so pressured by going up against these guys that have been playing forever that I know everything about every class
You can take your time with it and just sit sort of in a corner and just get used to the way the
TF2 was out for three weeks after I made that, you know, I come on
The game came out two weeks ago according to this video is one thing but my pipes landed with demo man has gone up
Significantly, we got two more
He said I'm gonna give you mortality and send you back to earth to solve the world's problems
And I said, okay
Send me back Roger that and I arrived in a basket at the Denver School for baby
Ninja frog people and I befriended your frogs and they said thank you and I said except for one frog named
Timmy he used to make I can't veto anymore. He's dead. He's been dead for 70 years. Holy shit
Let me look at my calendar here the fucking these drawings there's German's birth. There's my birthday
Wow, really? It's been like 82 years since I killed Timmy. Hope his parents aren't that mad at me
Whatever. Let's get back into this. So I got a job selling old shoes or
Well, you can put whatever you want here cuz I didn't have a job for the last like probably 40 years
I got a job at the fishing dock. I was the guy that peeled all the fishes scales off
I used to eat them and might be weird to a lot of you guys
But do you think I give a fuck and then came my adult life?
You've never seen you've never seen quite an action-packed adventure like this one
Gather your friends and explore the wonderful land of Azeroth
I actually don't there's context for these videos
I'm about to pause this motherfucker right now and again drop some knowledge on you all okay
2002 listen, all right listen to me out of an airplane there and Insta died on the concrete
Oh, we're gonna pause this we're gonna pause the timer too. It doesn't matter. There's not even as much time left in the video
Okay, so a long time ago. I had this character named grandpa, right grandpa
I made videos for machinima and they did really really well
I made like grandpa as an MLG pro and holy fuck people loved it
I got like two hundred thousand views and remember I was like a
I got that guy was like a thousand two thousand three thousand views a video on my youtube channel
So holy fucking smokes. I just leaned into it
I leaned into it hard and I made like fucking 20 of these so I was holy shit people like this
I'm gonna keep making more of these grandpa videos, so that's why this is here people wanted to know more about them
I don't guys I canonically killed this character twice
Grandpa's dead. He's been kin. He's canonically gone from the universe into heaven and then here's a funny story guys
I was in Moses's science class and guess who sits behind me, but God himself
I walked up to him after class at his locker, and I just simply asked him God
You know could I have like five more years on earth just Peter Griffin had to trade my fucking lunchables for it
But I'm here. I don't even need to do that. Oh, it's super toothless. Joe. Whatever his name is these guys freaked me out
This is scary, this is a long time ago. I've had all the warhammer games for a pretty long time
Super super yeah, you are a fan of super yes, I would highly recommend you get the original dawn of war I
Wasn't a fan of dawn of war 2 this is my old Isaac better than the new Isaac
It was a good game, but I don't think it was nearly as good as dawn of war 1. What is this and?
Grandpa tries
Come on come right here come on you want to talk about leaning into it come on same error and soda and
Holy shit, this is the same era. I wasn't making that up
We need to find that part
Fuck the timer. I'm freezing this
I'm literally gonna find where grandpa plays cuz I want to show you guys what it really means to like grab on to something
And fucking lean into it
In the title it's in the title of the video so that means you know
It's a it's about four to four to ten seconds in the actual video
It's probably less than 20 seconds in the actual video. Where is it?
Where's grandpa you know what we might even do it again good position times
Lean into the sus guy you don't think I've learned my lesson by now. Um I've learned my lesson
And I died whatever you're gonna
Okay, so here we go up. Yeah, I just eat Isaac. What's that just come down?
Down here you gotta play, but his grandpa's gonna play is oh
I want to know if it was requested gosh dart it if it was requested. I come off the hook well
That's um if it was requested. I'm off the hook so now you know what's gonna happen
His grandpa's gonna play as question mark question mark question mark shit
No, Jeremy, no somebody requested gonna go get grandpa grandpa can come in and he'll sit down
He'll talk about how he loves this game not request. We'll see what happens. Oh god damn it. Hey grandpa
Hey, you gotta get down here. You gotta play Binding of Isaac right now
Unsolicited unsolicited theater kid
That just like needs to just perform and he didn't doesn't care binding of Isaac
What's that?
Just just play it just sit down and play
Okay, I sit down ready there we go
Okay. Hello. Let's play the
Binding of Isaac was it did I just eat shit?
What the hell was that nice? I wonder the controls in this game up down left right? Okay, so here we go up down
Left right. Okay. Good. Let's go this way if I interact with myself more like a dozen times, then it's pretty it's I'm not upset about it
Stupid what a dumb game. So you what you just killed spiders and that's it. This is it. This is stupid
Why would you ever play this game? Okay, let's keep going
Where's he go? Oh, he's gonna walk into it and die and there's the title. Oh, that hurts you is the title. Oh
Am I gonna like die let's just go okay, I'm gonna beat this entire game right now, please stop Jeremy
I can't we know we need to stop gonna go down here. We must suffer
Look at you. Look I'm driving like a farm right here a pet spiders. Okay. Hey spiders. So today we're gonna I'm gonna feed you
Some some little bugs and you're gonna eat them again. Are you shoot that?
So how do I do is this like a simulator? How do I get out of here lazy beam?
Holy shit stick keeps going
Okay, so how many lives do I get I'm not gonna do anything I'm not there anymore are they see I'll do it again
Get rid of all the stupid goddamn bugs
Did he die
We're doing it again, we're going to do it again go you get out of my way
Get out of my way. It's actually this one grand puffy that I think that I really like
You play super meat boy, he dies the first level and he throws the controller through the window
Anybody find that one
All right, let's go back to what we were doing. I'm telling you I leaned into it
A lot of you guys can't it stayed on this channel for grandpa
Actually, you know, I can't talk shit about grandpa literally launch pad my entire career online
If it wasn't for grandpa, I don't even think I would have grown at the rate that I did I really don't think so
I went from like
5,000 view youtuber to like getting hundreds of thousands of views on videos because grandpa was in them
It was springboarded my whole career. I can't hate grandpa. I core I can't somebody found it. Okay. Well, we'll watch it in a second
Let's go. We have two more and then that's it. I'm done. Here we go. Turn the timer on we got two more of these
No, don't turn that off you idiot
invasion stuff German versus star and the
Really easy just to turn your brain off and if grandpa shows up, I'm fucking leaving
I'm gonna play Diablo 3 just kind of run around and swirl when people maybe
Maybe I'll play like Hearthstone and be terrible. No, I veto this whole
Delete this stream delete it like what's
German and versus star in versus TF to wait German versus star versus TF to in binding of Isaac
What's that title supposed to mean? I don't have a game to show you look at this old
Like starting soon screen. I can either play Hearthstone and be terrible binding of Isaac or Diablo. Which one?
Those are all awful choices. I would honestly if I'm in the stream. I'm hitting the X
I'm gonna warn you guys watching me play Hearthstone is going to drive a ton of you crazy. I didn't even hear that
I've been gone for at least 30 seconds. Let's do a
I'll come back and see if he's playing Isaac later
I'm gonna do one of those fancy poles that you see from time to time. He couldn't do comedy without grandpa
Grandpa was sort of a an outlet to be a weirdo. He really was changing
I didn't even guys I didn't there was a period from when I first started doing videos
I started out kind of like vulgar like I did like vulgar like swears and stuff and then like six months after I started YouTube
I
Went to no swears
Completely like PG PG 13. I didn't say okay. I didn't say shit
I said like crap and like oh like freaking and stuff. I didn't swear
I used grandpa as a means to just say and do whatever I wanted and we have you have
30 seconds to vote by the way
You have 30 seconds to vote on this ball because it's grandpa is not me
It was a period of like at least a year or two where I didn't swear and then stir made a video of all this
Footage
destroying everything
stir made a video of all of all this footage of like him recording me and like being in like me freaking out and like saying
swears and just kind of
Uncensored and then I couldn't be that guy anymore
you know what I mean when you have me like calling stir like a piece of fucking garbage and I'm like I
fucking want to like
Attack him with like a fucking hammer or whatever like I'm gonna put cigarettes out like you know what I mean
Like you can't be the guy that doesn't swear anymore after that. Well, I could not keep that up after that
It was exposed
Give me a real tree, please. God damn it. Why could you get mad at real trees? What the fuck are these?
How do you get mad at minecraft trees?
How do you keep fucking knife and I'm stabbing a motherfucker in the chest? I swear to God
What the fuck are you talking about? What?
What is he saying?
What?
Shit-faced
Eat my asshole. Seriously my god. I have to feed on this one. How was that an apple?
What's wrong with me why am I so mad
Where's PG Jerma blame stir?
He caught me on camera talking about like cigarettes butts being put on like my dick and shit and I was over I turned into
This guy I would have been like PG Andy. I
Would have my career. I want to know what my career would have looked like after that
Digging straight down. Yeah, that's fine. We'll be fine
I would probably have like a hundred million views on my videos playing fortnight, you know
I would have been like I would just I don't know
What would I have done some armor if I didn't go down that route God road would I've been on he's still here
Stir saved this channel. I
Don't think I would have done that though. Now. Let's go get some let's go get some goddamn armor
What do you say? Well, I don't know
I can't tell you the different like multiverses would I have okay if stir didn't make Jerma is mad one two three and four
I mean how would I have been playing among us and leaned into the sus guy? Jesus? That's something to think about
What is that noise? What the fuck is this noise? Why does it look like ass today? Okay, keep going
It's so blurry and like zoomed in. What do you say gamers? Just wait it just give me a minute
All right, this is the final one. We're ending on this one. This is it. Whatever it is in the description
It's a horror game. Oh my fucking early
It's one of the scariest damn games ever made now
I don't do well with these types of games and as you can see I'm down the first flight of stairs and I already don't
Want to play is that is that I don't do is that kind of easy cheese in there in case something crazy
Yeah, what's that cheese? So let's get started and to try not to psych myself out while I do this
I'm gonna give you the
Backstory of the game so pretty much this game
What's this room? This is my old room. So pretty much from like 12 years ago two days
19-year-old German. No, not that young. He said he did it on coffee breaks and it's a stairways
Somebody's coming behind me right now
Yeah, who cares?
Really all you do. God. God. Damn it. Who fucking makes their bed? Nobody
This is literally acting and I'm faking this whole thing. Aren't I look at me?
Dude, this this this could last like less than three minutes
Like I this could end I might just rage to quit look at how I do look so young though
I was probably 25 maybe 25 26 Jesus damn it
I hate this but you go down a series of stairs
Over and over are you so caked because I was in the gym every day
That's the game and the goal is to see how far you can go down how many stairs you can go down
I'm at floor number six and I'm almost ready to just quit this game
And it looks insane to that. I think I keep on repeating myself probably but that's because I am terrified right now
You look like you sniffed radioactive material
It's called I don't I didn't white balance my cameras and the screen is like green
Extend all right fine
Yeah, which sucks I I it's okay here's thing it's a lot different streaming a horror game
Then recording a video for a horror game because like I don't feel alone when I stream it
But I am alone when I record it
That's the worst part about this stuff is getting just loud horrible. It's a little it's different. It is see it's so much repetition
That it's you just you're doing the same thing over and over again
And you know at some point look like you're wearing eyeshadow
I think I just have that I'm just young something horrible is gonna happen. You just don't know when so I
I'm gonna my if you hit escape you end the game hitting escape ends it
Yeah, I know that everybody the meme was like you have a toilet paper roll and like lotion behind you and like a can easy cheese
I don't know whatever whatever the fuck that is
I don't know if it's in this video or not is that toilet paper back there next to the bed
Floor 20 floor 20 I've lost that accent in the last 10 to 15 years. Holy shit
This is not even that long
Bastard you son of a bitch you have a Vegas accent now. There is no Vegas accent
I don't think I'll be able to I think I'll be able to go past 30. We want 10 more
There's no more timer we're just gonna go timer was fun
It's the first and given a hundred community subs from the bingo no more bingo. We'll just play some we'll do we'll do it
Like five ten more times. Let's kill that timer
The shadows are really starting to mess with you now
Like the shadows are really starting to kick in and really stuff
It just shows you just how much horror games have evolved in the last 10 years
people were freaking out over a
little mask on a staircase in
Outlast 2 you like birthed a demon baby. I can't even look at the screen
I can't I seriously can't look at the screen and my whole body is like hurts right now, but I turn off
What is that? That's a face. Oh my god
Like scary anymore
That's like just a guy all right. What's on the back there? What is that? It's like a fucking orange juice. There's a guy
Orange juice a fucking oh mega Bible. What's this? Oh mega Bible like I don't know what this is
What is this a minute made like a hairspray a huge thing of lotion tissues?
I don't know what this even is I think this is cheese. This is like no what is this like oil for your car
Spray like CBD spray. This is a padlock. This is a fucking padlock
I don't know what that goes to coffee mug
I don't I don't know what all this stuff even is supposed to be I have no idea
There was a shelf here with I don't know what I don't know this aren't like is that a bell pepper?
It's a car guys. I have no idea you just didn't have it together
Hold on. What's it? Do I move to see the other side? Let me see the other side
This is like cigarette juice
Was like dipping and like spitting tobacco into this thing. What is that? There's a dog food on the ground
What was it? Hold on. What is this like rat shit down here?
What is this? What are these pellets? I don't I haven't guys I have absolutely no idea. It's soy sauce. Hold on. Oh
My god, Jeremy. Hold on move move the head. I think that's cologne move. This is a candle
I think this is like Vicks vapor rub. Oh boy
Listen to me. Okay, this is really important. I don't know why this is in the room
I have no idea what it's doing in the room. But listen, this is dog vitamins
This is big a big pump of omega-3 for dogs. I don't know if I was eating this
I don't think I don't think I was eating this but I mean it's possible. I might have been I don't think I was eating that
But like it's it's a huge pump for it's not lotion
It's literally fucking dog vitamins. I don't know why it's so big is exposed
It says it was omega-3 dog pump vitamins
I have no idea what that is and I don't even know what the hat was either. It's like a gas station hat
I don't know what that even is. I can't even make out what the fuck this is on my head. Is this like a
Valphaline, what is this?
Okay, this is like a jiffy lube hat. I don't even know what that is
Hey, we're gonna do another one. Let's just go again. Oh nice dusk. I was there's a Jax moment
We can add it. Why did you have dog? But I don't know
Stuff just kind of accumulates in random places
Yeah, and the tissues and the dog vitamin lotion was in a really weird place
I understand but I'm not it wasn't just sitting there. I oh
My goodness, I don't think I was eating it had to be a reason why it was there right next to the bed though
What is it doing there?
Keep a timer on so you don't stay for too long. I
Can keep an eye on it was lotion. It was not what lotion company?
Do you know that makes a weird?
gigantic like coffee syrup pump like that
That's that big with a long neck. They don't make it like that with the yellow front
No, they don't have like the big long fucking turkey neck
It wasn't lotion was dog vitamins. It was a dog vitamin omega-3 pump
Something else it's kind of funny to note and I will give you a little bit more
Like ammo to fire at me the tissue box was empty
Wow must have been really fucking it must have been really going for it. There's nothing left in there
God I was just me playing dusk. Whatever. I'm good at this game. Oh, this is a classic. I love this one
Has this game seen any updates? I feel like this game is really fun. Where's the other wrestler? Oh, they were invisible
Right. I forgot they're invisible
You can make the characters invisible
Wrestling Empire got an update. Yeah, that game was the funniest thing I've ever seen
All right, let's go again skip
Little set of clips here, especially in this first one
circulation nine people in a row and
Really after playing with this for maybe an hour or two
I think it took me maybe an hour to get this gameplay
So after playing with this for a little while I've come to the realization
What is it I want to do this with the connivorous kunai get a backstab on somebody and just go for the headshots
All right, fuck off. Yes
This guy's shit face. He'll be easy. I
Love it classic. I want to just please have need to make I want more of these I would pay a hundred dollars
Retail for one of these another one. I would pay a thousand dollars. No, that's way too much
I'd pay I'd pay a hundred bucks in one of these
Did he just not even shoot the gun?
Time for diet and your time has come
I knew it was in the book. I knew it was in the fucking book and now I lost and it's over
Yeah, I want to okay, I want to like see some other streamers play these games
You know, I mean quality acting job lady. Which one is it? I like member when we talked about sharing things
Yeah, I would love to see other people play this cartoon bag
I want to watch like streamers play this that's seriously she ran out of there with like a mcduck bag
You're not gonna fool me. What about this guy Vinny played? Oh Vinny is a connoisseur
Shit, it doesn't surprise me. He's 500 fucking IQ brain. That does not surprise me
Thank you shot the ground
Did they shoot the ground this was directly into the dirt?
Why is that guy a quick draw fast McGraw? No, we need to gate. He's no get out. We shut up
No gatekeeping video games
I have no idea what this guy just said
Hold on. Wait, that's one of my favorite lines
So your mama let you come out and play today. Why is that guy a quick draw fast McGraw?
That doesn't make any sense
I have no idea what this guy just said
Target time. Yeah, this could be imagine trying to get the fastest record in the world here
Oh, there's a mattress right
You see that mattress behind her that's like a stunt mattress I
Love it. I'm glad you fell on that stunt mattress inside of a saloon
Are you sure it out of his hand? I forgot about that one. That was a channel meme five six seven years ago for a long time
You can't tell oh, yes, the gun and then shoot
Come on now wasn't that a sub sound for a while that it was wasn't it? Yeah, it was
moving on
Get up and walk around after a 50 plus foot jump right there when he fought me
You're in from behind. They're not even coming out in the right order. This is supposed to be a gauntlet match
They're not even coming out in the right order. It's supposed to be one after the other. What are they doing? What triggered this?
I seriously don't it was such a pain in the ass to edit
Santa Claus has been under that ring for probably like three hours, by the way
Meanwhile grandpa not paying any attention to who's behind him. That's bad boy with a clothesline
He's supposed to be dead bad boy is supposed to be dead right now
But for some reason he just snuck up behind him is even supposed to be in this he's not
Everybody that is supposed to be a combatant in this gauntlet
It's over on the left side this is back when and bad boy is in the ring does yeah
So back the after like 2013
It wasn't just a rumble. It was like oh, I want to do a bunch of matches and have a big storyline and
The thing about the old wrestling like WWE 2k14 2k13
You know the the good ones were before they've ruined everything and the game was a piece of absolute steaming fucking garbage
So before that you could there was like these little like clip mode
Well, you could put wrestlers in and make a little scene and you could create and craft these weird rants
It was it was like the movies
Where it's like here's a scenario
Who do you want to be as it's like two like mannequins are standing in and you can just make up your own little storylines
they were like dozens and dozens of clips and
Then they made it a sports simulation Madden game that we just update the roster and the game breaks half the time
It was so good
It was awesome that half of the clips that you see in these all germa rumble videos
Were sort of string together
In that weird sort of puzzle of putting a little scene together and I would cut it and I would put it into the actual match
See like but they were just wrestling but you are this was
This was not just part of the match like I had to go in and piece this together
It was so much fun to do
And then they got rid of it
The new one coming out I am gonna hold my breath completely
Oh, yeah, that's what I was huge
This is still going on. This is still going on backstage. They're still beating the shit
I
I'm gonna hold my breath on any new wrestling game that comes out cuz I feel like they've lost their way completely across every single
Piece of media from the shit that's on TV from the shit that you play in in your home on your console
They've lost their way 100%
Some of these new organizations are starting to try to be a little bit more fun and interesting
But no, no, it's it's I'm gonna hold my breath you go back to the way that like kind of they used to do
This shit back in like 2013 2012
2014 I know that the company that used to work on these games
Split off right was it a AKI? Whatever was what's the name of the company?
they said we keep making the same fucking game over and over again and
It's youks. Yeah, you okay. I was the other company that worked on it, right? They made like a statement saying hey
We're gonna make our own wrestling game we think because we just keep doing the same shit with these WWE games
I have such high hopes, but I don't want to have like it
I'm holding my breath again that they're gonna bring this kind of crazy shit back and yet THQ everybody gave shit to THQ
But man, wasn't that kind of like a turning point when THQ went away?
I feel like we lost a lot of kind of really wacky creative fun shit that that that studio was doing
The people give a lot of shit to THQ. Ah, the games are fucking terrible. They're like sevens out of ten six out of ten
They're like kind of shitty and dumb. I look back at the catalogue the THQ had it was pretty phenomenal
And I even remember being one of these people that's like, oh THQ when I business whatever who cares
I guess they were they were okay
What if you actually go back to see the influence that they had on the industry and all the stuff that stuff that they were
Making holy fuck they had a lot to do with a why shit was even people were even to have been making fun games in
The first place it was one of the last remaining double-a studios. Yeah, I wish they would make a revival
I wish like somebody would buy them and just let them kind of go again. It was kind of like a weird THQ Nordic is
Making a comeback. Yeah, I hope so. It's the new revival. What are they making? What are they working on?
They're doing time splitters three destroy all humans. Yeah, I hope so because they would just really creative funny things and fun stuff
Look, we've kind of gotten into this mode in video games now where I think a lot of these companies are taking themselves way too seriously
Like everything's being taken way too seriously. It's got to be like this. It has to be like this. It's got to get done
It's got to be like I I kind of miss like when devs kind of just fucked around and made fun shit for because they
Wanted to the indie scene is still doing that right? But it's almost like this just to it's like indie games and just triple-a games
Right. It's like we lost that double-a kind of mentality. Hope it comes back. Anyways, let's press the button again
How can you say the double-a studios don't exist when game Freak still makes Pokemon?
I have it Pokemon is like a mmm a monster property owned by Nintendo
I I mean, I can't speak to oh that was an insult. Oh, okay. That was an insult
That was insulting. I get it. Okay, we're gonna click the button
Here if you think that that's like stupid
That's like a book and one of the most catchiest songs I've ever heard in my life. What is so I'm sorry
What song I need to know
What's the song I don't care enough to tell you that aren't you curious on Super Mario RPG legend of the seven stars Oh
Based of course my kind of music based absolutely 100% based. We have to actually feed the fire
All right open. Okay, the oven needs to reach the optimal temperature
I'm glad we did this again the thermometer on the left side of the oven as time progresses
The oven will slowly run out of fuel make sure to add logs from time to time keep fire
I'll just a Pete the pizza one right get in there to do it again. All right, get it in the green
Yeah, I want enough time to pass where we don't overdo it though a wood-fired pizza. Yeah, that's the best again
You will come with shibby
Yeah, it's kind of rolling through by the way, let me just tell you this right now. I remember this video
Let's go take that last point. I remember this specifically and you know why I remember this specifically because this was like a holy shit
This is a big deal shibby. This is back when I had like 500 subs on YouTube actually 2010 2011
Whatever it was shibby was killing it shibby has like 30,000 subs 50,000 subs and he like reached out
He was like, hey, man, we should do a video sometime
I looked at his channel and I was like like holy shit this guy this guy this is a god
You've got 50 fucking thousand subs on YouTube. Are you kidding me?
Yeah, oh sure. Let's we'll make video should be then went on to work at machinima
And then he started working at other companies and he's like in the industry now
Do you like if I think like talent management shit? I should be should be a good dude
I I've talked to him recently
I was he was always like really supportive of like the channel even when he moved on to kind of do the stuff like in
The industry we would talk we would hang out
Yeah, I've this is that I was like really excited to do this because I was like, holy shit
YouTuber, oh, we just want to sit in the rain all day. Oh
stereotyping a city
Damn, and by the way, I'm nervous in this video. I'm like, holy fuck. I better be funny and good
I have to like be good like I'm gonna be medic and just like heal him
I'm gonna heal the fuck out of him as medic. No one likes me. I'm gonna switch demo. We got three medics right now
It's down. It's down. Oh, maybe if I do good and I'm like I heal him and we like have a good conversation
Look at how much fun he sounds like he's having this is awesome. Yes, he's having fun
75 FOV yikes. That's right. This is 70 FOV default weapon Andy
This is before they did an update with a demo man got new items guys
The demo man didn't have new stuff to play with this is just the game
Not true, I think I don't remember the demo man had a new item stop he's trying to move it up here
If they was it was only like one or two
Have the oh
Probably was only like three items battle. Oh
Teleporter and centuries down. Oh
What's the point of me getting?
D I remember this this game is awful inventory sticky spamming in a pub
That that just scared the shit out of me
Did you left the menu sound scared the fuck out of me? This is look I can't even see what's going on
I look like I feel like I'm shit-faced watching an old CRT TV with one eye open a button a minute
Gliding down
This is the last one whatever it is
We're going out on it play it really at all
But kind of a little bit because we're gonna talk about something today
That I noticed and it's when you notice these things that you start to go
Why the hell am I doing that and it freaks you out because you start thinking about it every time you do it
What I'm talking about what is it weird?
Obsessive compulsive habits that we have when we play video games. Oh, no, it doesn't have to be just team fortress, too
It doesn't have to be just an MMO or an action game. This is across the board. It's just a different quirk
It's just a different compulsive thing gone for anything. Yeah, I know. Ooh
This game was a this is awesome. I loved this game
No, I did it again the rock is back in Ohio I keep doing that I keep telling you exactly where I'm standing
It was just one hit kill only rail gun. It was so much fun me. Okay, good
Give
Bring this back
Bring this game back. Don't you believe it? I've got a hacker on the server
I mean, it's I mean this game was fucking unbelievable. I bring this back
I'm just gonna like focus up here new new twitch meta
You think I think it has an opportunity to be one hit the fucking pole
I hit the pole this really could be one of these kind of new meta twitch metas telling me
All right, hold on to this thought
As in the tournament type shit you do lead tournaments with this would be insane
I work on it my perspective. It looked like I hit you
You could do a kind of like a bunny hop rocket jump
Yeah, you're gonna pull that on me you're gonna pull a me on you you're gonna pull me on you
Gonna hit up Ludwig
Ludwig I've got another harebrained idea for you. It's called rats is to give get 40 people to fucking show up
All right last one whatever it is is it classic we're leaving on this
I know I realize it's Adam Sandler
And you use the site yeah
Nearly there
Now one more
No, this isn't a bad game. This is weird. I was just making a reference to the fact that all the recent Tony Hawk games
I've been fucking awful
What is this?
this game just is a thousand times more difficult than Tony skate 3 I
Didn't play this
Let's go back to the marker. I don't this is this is not even my video. I think this is wrong ramp
I don't I think the the ramp. All right, it's somebody else's stream. I think I don't think I have enough speed here
Let's do a pump. Yeah, this is not even my didn't stream this
This is what okay for all the new viewers this was considered one of the worst streams I've ever done
Okay, I
Spent how long is this two hours and 32 minutes and it's just me being bad and talking about how the game sucks and
Skate 3 is considered one of the greatest skate simulators ever made and I was so salty
The controls sucked and the game was fucking awful and shit
Yeah, this is this is one of the worst streams I've ever done putting myself in a really stupid awkward position
Let's find it only because I wouldn't want demon days to
Let's find it. I'll own it press a press F and then fucking things to do
Even days is a good album. Why can I just never have any responsibilities and just play skate and learn how to play it and do good
He beat me up
Well
Jesus but yeah make that shit when do I am I like misremembering this don't I talk about how I hate this whole thing
And this game is a tutorial
All right, you gotta stop doing that man
Speed here. I don't
What?
All right, last one one more. How do you manual you're a concern with this item? No. Oh
What the fuck who did this channel trailer? I don't want to alarm anybody here, but uh, I'm sorry
I may have taken a shit in your house being one of the top ten players in the world. That's right
This is German grandfather here
Good as me he can't give you the tips
He can't give you the strategies and I can so let me just tell you that I'm the best players in the world
I've not seen this in a long time
Did I really have this in me the whole time and the answer is yes, but should I go back
Mold them together. Oh, no. No. Oh, no Luna's my
This cup is good. Oh fucking god. Oh, no. Oh, I'm trying to get you to some. Oh, no
No, no, no people around here call me. I'm hey you person that just landed on the channel page
What's going on? My name is Jerma nine eight five or you can just call me Jerma
That's what most people around here call me
I'm a gaming channel you probably could guess that by all the different playlists and all the videos below
Which you should check out and you should go watch some of them right now and possibly subscribe that's the whole purpose of this video
I'm trying to get you to subscribe to my channel. So hey subscribe to the channel subscribe you see on this channel
I like to call myself. Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Jerma because
I'm not doing anymore. I'm not gonna do anymore. I'm not
Review content. I don't do any reviews. I didn't do what I've reviewed two games
I have a very professional side where I review content. I review packages
What I don't review packages, so why did you keep it in the video?
You know what I mean? What was the point of having this in the video? I review games
I review packages
Why does it look like somebody farted right in my face?
Like right now like I did like I just farted in his face. I don't want to hear it again this channel
I like to call myself. Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Jerma because I have see on this channel
I like to call myself. Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Jerma because I
Jekyll, Jekyll, Jekyll, Jekyll and Mr. Jerma because I have two different sides. Go Longhorns. I have a very professional side
Where I review content I review packages what I don't review packages. I've review like games
Oh, here's like here's a cup. This cup is good. There's a whole lot of stuff here though. I have my fun
I have my professional side and I mold them together
Into sort of this lunacy that is Jerma985
So hopefully this little trailer will be able to give you an explanation of this channel and hopefully you subscribe as well
So, please subscribe subscribe and subscribe and I'll subscribe you all next time. Oh, no, of course subscribe
Subscribe I can't watch it anymore. It's over. That's it. I'm never fucking making another video ever again for the rest of my entire life
I'm never making another video ever again. Well, why would I this is worse than Manos? No, it's not look
I'm young and I'm excited and full of energy
I'm young and I'm full of excitement and full of energy and I'm ready to go for it as you'll see
For this channel trailers to the kind of things you can expect to see when you land on Jerma985
Welcome to the channel. Let's go. What can you expect? Hey, what is going on everybody? Oh, hey, what is going on everybody?
Hey, what is going on everybody Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary
Meet me at the statue at 12 o'clock. Okay. I don't know what the statue is. I don't play this game
I don't play Call of Duty. I just like would want to think I did you were gonna beg what?
That's incredible or by the way Mario you have to do all the dirty that's I'm getting this trip down memory that's incredible or
Incredible orb was such a fucking awesome, dude
Because he can jump higher than Michael Jordan, I remember he wanted some funny here his listen to this he still streams, too
I gotta fucking like rate him. He's just he's from Sweden. So we just never stream at the same time
So here's thing about incredible orb. There's some tips a little nut tip, but here's some insight for you
Incredible orb is the only person is one of two people that I have met through like YouTube and like content creation
That's ever met my parents nice machinima shirt. Yeah, I literally have nothing but like swell things to say about incredible orb
I just like was just a class act and I'm sure still is take it home. Remember. This is cute
He just ran a bunch of marathons. Yeah
He see he kept doing the healthy shit
I remember us having conversations about all lifting and being healthy and like working out and I turned into like fucking like an
Insect person I turned to like a bug. I turned to like a big fat like beetle person and he's out here running marathons
No, good. That's good
The sway the sway
I put a in my channel trailer for YouTube ten years ago
Strafing that's just strafing case. You didn't know
Well you non gamers they don't know that pressing A and D makes you
Step left and right without needing to move your mouse
That was so important that I make sure everybody knows that I thought I was such a brilliant
Smart motherfucker. I thought I was so goddamn gifted that was in the the four minutes of real estate of
Small amount of real estate that I had to show you to make sure you knew I was a gamer and it worked
I was good
also
Put smite in the channel trailer cuz I thought I was gonna play it every day and it was gonna be my new game
I think this burger boy in this and I think he's Matt. Yeah, he misses the table
Best players in the world and I'll show you right here. Look at this. Get the fuck out of here
Grandpa there is the whole time turn it up turn it up. Yeah burger boys in this video
All right, let's go tell yourself it's possible and you have to act on those possibilities
Okay, so they did on the burger boy there's a video of my channel burger boy in a Twinkie eating contest and
He there was a little
Okay, there's some context so burger boy and exoskeleton bug Millennium boy two different people by the way
they did a Twinkie contest for 15,000 subs on the channel and
Burger boy one is a disgusting video. I don't even know why it's still uploaded
so after the videos over I it's a burger boys the champion and
There's like maybe like four or five Twinkies that are left that he didn't eat and he went to swing his hand down to smash
Them and it's like a hard just like granite countertop. He misses the Twinkies and smash you see smashes his fucking hand
smashes it and like destroys it listen to this that was a hard granite countertop and I think after that he's like
Oh, and the other person's like, I'm sorry. I missed it. I didn't I'm sorry. I missed it. Oh, yeah, I threw a cake in his face
Hi guys
Fucking washer dryer a generous channel there a spoonerism. Holy shit
Wow
So thank you all so much for watching
I really do appreciate it and hopefully you subscribe to this and hopefully you lean into the microphone
Convinced you to do that and you can be part of our little community here the germs
That's not what we call them you idiot. They're the germa mites. Excuse me. So join the germs
I hope to see you all in the comment section and thank you for watching again. So take care everybody the Andes
No, you're not Andes. Oh
That was so much fun
drew crew
All right
I'll see you guys later
That was the trip down memory lane through the ages if you want to play with this
You can it exists right now if you'd like to mess around and just go find a random
Timestamps of random videos is available for anyone to use we have somebody can please link the website everybody
I thank lazy Luke lazy Luke is the one responsible for putting this together
Just like he did last time also did it this time updated it gave a few more control panel things lazy Luke
Obviously knocked it out of the park again
And there it is germa org slash random so you can find some more quality cringe content
We'll do the outro now. I'll hang up another few minutes. Thanks to all the subs. Thanks everybody the next time
I will be live will be that's a good question. I know I think I broke my did I break the oh shit
I broke the credits the website is down well
You can't all go do it at once if everybody goes it does at the same time. Oh, that's why the credits don't work
Because the credits are linked to the same web server. I think oh oops well you guys broke it well shit
Well, thanks for the subs everybody
I'll see you guys probably the middle of the week keep an eye on the sus maybe like midweek Wednesday Thursday
Maybe Alex, and I still do need to play Resident Evil 6 which just gotta figure out when we're gonna do that
We'll see let me get my stuff up here and
Yeah, I've been around for a while. I've been around for a long time
Sometimes I forget just how long it's been when I watch videos of me when I was like 25
It's it's a weird feeling. It's kind of odd
But it's cool. I'm glad it still exists that it's still there hundred subs. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, yeah
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. You're right. I forgot completely we do that right now
Here come 100 community subs for you getting bingo nice job
Excellent work everybody hundred community subs incoming in
very very small amount of time
100 community subs let's go good luck
Good game good game huge subs huge subs from German. I mean holy shit
Bing what do you mean Bing what a great investment right right? Yeah, we'll do it right is it Vinny streaming?
Let's die. Let's go say hi Vinny. Oh, by the way, I need to make it no more raid song bullshit
No, but you that's probably annoying the fuck out of everybody. No more raid song shit, please
No, no more raid song. Stop doing that. I can't every time I raid you guys
Not raid you guys, but every time I raid with you guys
I look over at the chat and I can just I can feel the eyes glaring over from the other streamer
Glaring over at it and being like they're fucking saying raid song and I'm not gonna do it
No more raid song. No more. No more. Oh
You're you're grounded
You're grounded. In fact, you're grounded anyways, cuz I you I know that some of you are gonna do it. You're grounded anyways
You're preemptively grounded
But yeah, please go say hello to Vinny
Really doing through crime, New York
Think we actually saw a clip from this game. All right. I'll see you guys later. Keep an eye on the sus
Thanks for watching. These are always fun to do. I'm sure we'll do it again. Have a great rest of your evening. Goodbye
See you later
Take care of yourselves you raid song. I'll be fucking furious next dream and I'm gonna bring it up. Oh
Shit, it is Thanksgiving this week. Yeah, I alright we're gonna be live after Thanksgiving. What is Thanksgiving 24?
25. All right. So we're all right. Well, I'll be live next on Friday
Yeah, have a good Thanksgiving of you celebrating it everybody. I'll see you guys on Friday this week 26th
I have a fantastic rest of your day much love to you as always get that to 9,000 or I'm gonna cancel the rain
Thanks guys. See you later. Take care of yourselves
Good night
Oh, wow