Some of these characters are so stupid.
I'll definitely be in this guy.
Oh my god, it's Zario.
I wonder why this guy's name is Zario.
Might have something to do with it. He looks like-
He even does a Super Mario jump!
Did you see that shit?
He just did the Super Mario jump!
I'm not sure if you're talking to me or talking to everyone else.
Watch out for the copyright infringed copyright strike.
The evil windmill.
Are you ready?
I'm gonna destroy you.
Is it my turn first? Who goes first? Me?
Uh, we're both here.
Oh, well I'm going.
What?
You didn't make it uphill. Okay, my turn.
You used your turn.
Wait, it says press the en-
Wait, what?
What?
What is the goal of this?
I don't know.
Get hit by the windmill a million times, probably?
Got it.
I can't believe that actually happened.
It's a me, Mario.
It's a me, Zario.
Industrial realism.
Highway.
Study each map for the goal.
Please tell me this car is just coming forward at all times.
Please. Please.
No.
Damn it, why is it called highway then?
Because we have to jump onto this freaking highway.
What?
Yeah, again, you're supposed to eject before you hit it, I guess.
That's what I did.
I didn't.
It's a me!
What do you mean find the goal? We're just ejecting out of the cars.
What is this?
I have no idea.
I'm kind of-
Alright, wait, study the map, study the-
We were supposed to study the map.
I tried to study it.
Study the map and get the most out of your experience.
Well, I'm going to try and make this jump right now.
Alright, me too.
Why does this have a 23 on Medicare?
This is the best game I've ever played.
Hit him high.
I have a fucking headache, dude.
When we were tapping triangle, you know what cartridge tilting is?
Yeah.
That's what was happening.
My character was stretching and it was fucking horrific.
Look at them balls.
Oh man, this is going to be sick.
What do you even do?
Let's just go at the same time.
Speed up.
Don't, don't, don't.
We have to study and survey the area.
No.
Didn't you read?
What happened to all of my momentum?
It just went straight up.
I can't.
Still.
Dude, your car.
You should have seen your car.
You should have seen-
You should have seen what your car did.
Your car.
I'll make sure I get over this one.
This time I'm going to get four million points.
Yeah.
Come at me, bro.
I'm coming at the hill.
Get up there.
Oh, baby.
What?
This will be the last one.
I feel like, I feel like we've gotten the fly out of car thing out of our system.
Sort of.
Yeah.
Okay, four.
Score a thousand points.
One thousand points.
Four.