Just open up the first one instead.
You want to just play the first one?
Let's open up the first one. I like that one.
Relaxing stream.
I got a meeting in like an hour and ten minutes.
I went backwards.
I've depreciated.
Remember this one? Remember this game?
I gotta change the stream title.
So what the fuck are they gonna add in the third game?
Is it gonna come with a cook serve delicious eye patch that you have to wear?
Is the game mirrored? Do I have to like hold a mirror up behind me and play it?
Third game's a food truck.
That's actually pretty cool. Alright, let's go.
I know it. Okay, look at this one.
Day 15.
We're gonna go day 4. Yeah.
Because I'm not ready.
I'm gonna embarrass myself again, I think.
Career menu, let's go.
We got patch notes. Alright, cool.
Start new day.
I need to know if I still have it in me.
Nice.
You nailed it.
You lost 2,000 viewers. No, I didn't.
That would be so...
That would be so sad if I did.
I would be sad.
I'd be like, oh fuck, I couldn't do cook serve delicious and everybody left.
I couldn't play this second game.
Oh, you said no salt, right?
This is fried chicken.
Got it.
This is the kind of rush hour I'm talking about.
Cook serve delicious 2 is this one with mods.
Ah.
This is casual. Yeah, this is relaxing though, isn't it?
That's what I wanted.
I quit the second one because it was too hard for me.
But I am playing this one and I like this one.
You're never gonna make it in the McDonald's industry.
I don't need to.
Make it in my own chicken industry.
Come on.
With salt.
Warm up with the first one then move on to the second one.
No, I can't do it.
You know what's funny?
The second that I realized that I was gonna have to like hold buttons and press all the buttons at the same time.
I was like, well, this is the streams end.
This is over.
I didn't want to say it.
I knew it.
I can't. I knew it.
Shift tab and then hold
left trigger and press like.
Nope. I pressed S.
You played it for less than 10 minutes.
Yeah, and I wanted
just to relax today.
Just chill and draw pictures
of cartoons and stuff.
Play it again sometime. Maybe I'll try it again.
I don't know. I just like.
And I know it's not the game's fault. That's the thing.
It's me. No me.
That was some straight up Neo treatment.
Yeah, but I didn't like.
I can tell you that I didn't like Neo.
Uh oh. Here we go.
Uh oh. I was supposed to hit three. Come on.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Oh, shit. Alright, we're good.
Shit. I missed it.
I missed it twice in a row.
You should play Tapper. Is that the beer game?
I'm ahead on that beer.
Am I losing my mind?
Or is this day going on
an extreme
amount of time? Why is this so long?
Am I missing something here?
Why is this going on for so long?
Is it just a slower game?
Or is this endless mode?
Give a picture. Thumbs up.
Alright, I'm going to switch to day 15 after this
because that's the way we were last time, I think.
I think I just need to warm up.
In fact, yeah. Get me out of here. I quit.
There it is. Select a character.
What? I don't remember any of this.
Welcome to Battle Kitchen?
No. There we go.
Alright. So the last time I played this,
this is where we left off. Burgers are now
available. Menu rot.
I got to take that shit off the menu. Safety inspection.
It's time for your five day safety inspection.
Inspector will come to your restaurant a few times today.
How quickly I do chores.
Alright, that's good to know.
What do I have for foods right now?
Good shit. Here's my menu. There's rot
here. Rotten.
Disgusting. It's fucking rotten.
Let's put the steak.
The trout. Lasagna.
Ooh, this might be bad.
I don't know about that.
I said the word lasagna and everyone's saying disgusting.
I agree. Okay, that's fine.
What do I have for money? No.
Let's go. I'm kidding. Lasagna's
not disgusting. Hello?
What's going on? One.
One. Hey!
Hey! What is going on?
Begin. What happened?
Okay, something's wrong. The game, like, is broken.
Uh, is num
numlock?
Is it recognizing the...
Okay, unplug the controller.
Press alt.
I need to restart the game.
Well, that sucks.
I mean, I'm still relaxed. Everything's fine.
What time is it? I got my meeting.
I've got my meeting in, like, 45 minutes.
An hour. It's an important meeting.
Munkas.
Why are you munkasing that?
Okay, here we go. Day 15.
Career menu.
View your active menu. This is...
That's fine.
Start the new day. There we go.
Game glitched. It's all good.
Don't play a bad game and
do a comb stream for an hour.
This is not a bad game.
Season three times in one juice.
For a second I thought the
kitchen exploded. I don't know why. I just heard the...
Okay, layer ingredients above.
Pasta, sauce, cheese, parmesan.
Oh, right.
And then this is ready?
A medium grape with ice, please.
With ice. A medium. I need a medium grape with ice.
Oh, ah!
Ah!
Where? Did I do it? Okay.
Uh...
I can't watch this stream. It's making me too hungry.
Large.
With no ice. Large cold with no ice. You got it.
Steak. Season once.
Twice juicy.
And a little bit of citrus.
And fillet the fish.
And then season it up. Cook it up.
What do we got? I want a small diet with ice, please.
How do I get ice? Ice. Small diet with ice, please.
Small diet with ice, please.
Four. Parmesan.
Pasta, sauce, meat, cheese, parmesan.
I don't know.
A small tea with ice, please.
Medium diet with ice, please.
Four. We got large cold with ice.
No ice, please.
Okay. Pasta, sauce, meat, cheese.
Pasta, sauce, meat, cheese.
Right?
I don't know. I did it fast.
See? Oh, you idiot.
Nice meat soup.
You have to go faster.
Pasta, sauce, meat, cheese, parmesan.
P. S. M.
P. S. M. S.
I can't.
I can't. I'm not capable.
I'm incapable.
P. S. M. C. P.
I have to look at my fucking hands.
P. S. M. C. R.
You gotta play something relaxing.
I'm good. I'm good. Don't worry.
P. S. What was it?
P. S. M. C. R.
I don't know if that was correct.
That was right.
He's just sitting here sweating in a suit and playing a baby game
while stressing about his important
meeting.
I don't own a three piece suit.
Season one's twice juicy.
P. S. M. C. R.
Large. Oops.
Throw it away. How do I throw it away?
Whatever.
Season three times and one juicy.
P. S. P. S. M.
P. S. I. P. S.
P. S. C. R.
Oh! P. S.
Didn't fuck it up.
Oh. P. C. P. S. C. D. D. D.
Down. It's P. S. C. C. D. D. M. M.
The speed run of this is really fast.
That's actually pretty interesting to look at I think.
Okay. Chores.
The second a chore comes up, do a quick
two three. Why do you flush it
and sanitize the toilet? I don't know.
Why flush the toilet at all? It's a waste of water.
P. S.
Just fill it up for like weeks and then
flush it. That's disgusting.
Flush it once a month.
That's an outhouse.
Almost at two stars.
A new catering job's opened up. You can view the
challenge in the extra events menu. Good luck.
Catering event.
Burger pizza party.
Do I have it? I don't know. I don't have it.
I really do need to get a pizza.
Sixteen hundred.
Fuck. No. I can't. I need to save money.
Back to the menu.
We're getting rot.
Should I do baked potato?
Put the burger back on the menu. It's more money.
I don't want the lasagna. Fuck the lasagna.
Get the steak off there. French fries.
We're a burger and fish restaurant now.
Anything else for the inspection passed?
Today's buzz increased by ten percent.
Let's go.
I'm a weirdo that hates steak.
I don't hate steak. I just don't order it.
Oh my god.
Medium diet. Just throw it away.
How do I toss this? Is there a toss this button?
No salt.
Yeah.
No. I don't order steak. I don't like
steak. Really.
I like shaved steak.
But
it's not appetizing to me at all.
When somebody says
Oh hey man. Do you want a
medium rare steak?
I...no.
Absolutely not.
I'll eat like steak and cheese sub. I'll eat
like flank steak and stuff. I just don't
really like it. I like ketchup
on steak. I do not.
I don't know where you got that info.
What do you want? Meat, lettuce, bacon, cheese,
tomatoes. You want everything.
What do you want? Small water with ice.
With ice? Rats.
Drink small tea with ice.
A beer.
A medium diet with ice.
What do you want? A medium cold with ice.
One patty.
Oh god. One patty.
Meat too. Lettuce,
bacon, cheese, tomato. Get it out of here.
Meat tomato.
Get it out of here. Meat
bacon, double cheese, and
tomato. Get it out of here. You want a triple
cheeseburger? Relax.
Holy shit. I
would not eat that. Triple cheeseburger
is too much. Double is perfect.
I don't know how unpopular or popular
this statement is going to be.
But I find
a hamburger patty that is more than
four ounces to be gross.
It's just me.
I'll take a double. A double cheeseburger
with two four ounce patties.
I think that still works.
I really don't like when people make these
big ass fucking gigantic
eight ounce hamburger
patties. There's a balance
there that is just you don't step over.
Yeah, no, I'll take an eight ounce
of meat as long as it's two four ounce patties.
Oops. Yeah, that's fine.
But when people do double patties in this
six to eight ounce patties, that's just, no.
That's too much. You can't do a double
once it's four ounces. I mean it.
What about
a two ounce patty and a six ounce
patty? That would be weird.
That would be strange.
What about a single six ounce patty?
That's pushing it.
Come on. What about a big
thick steak? No, I don't like steak.
Small cold with no ice.
Large cold with no ice.
Bacon, meat, cheese.
Meat, bacon, cheese. And a tomato.
Oops. Small cold with no ice.
Got it. Bacon, lettuce, tomato.
But you don't want to...
What about the burger I just cooked for you?
Why are you guys ordering BLT
hamburger buns? Hurry up!
No, but
I think, and sometimes we go to a
restaurant that
I don't know, I don't know what it is.
Some restaurants, they pride themselves
on having these giant
ten ounce fucking hamburger patties.
And you know when you can taste?
You can just taste
meat. And it's
gross. It's like just
eating a giant meatball. I don't want to do
that. An eight
ounce fucking, a ten ounce hamburger patty
is a gigantic meatball between
two pieces of bread. No.
I hate it when I can taste my food.
No, it's very specific.
Too much meat flavor.
Am I a vegetarian?
I have a very important question for you. Do
vegetarians eat meat?
No. Right. Okay. So
I just, you've seen me eat a McChicken
on camera.
You're a pretend meat eater?
I do actually like the Beyond Burgers
though. They are really, really fucking good.
I cannot pretend there.
I talked so much shit
about those burgers, it was unbelievable.
I was a certified
shit talker for
Beyond Meat. But
I have had it and it is
pretty good. Pretty good.
E.D. certification is no
purchase. Equipment menu.
What is it? What shit
did I talk?
It was mainly how I didn't think the company
was worth even
close to what the stock price was worth.
Because I saw that. I mean that was big news.
Beyond Meat worth like fucking
five, a hundred billion dollars or something.
With like a three hundred dollar stock
price. And I'm like there's no fucking way. What the hell is that?
That's bullshit.
That's worth more than
like Nvidia. So I talked a bunch of
shit. Off camera though.
Alright, I gotta get them.
One more day and I can do pizza.
Maybe we should do these.
Fisher's gotta come off.
No, I can't do lasagna.
I'm not capable.
How many times have you heard that
in this stream?
I'm not capable.
Small tea with ice.
I've had
lots of fake meats before
and almost all of them
are gross.
You name me any of the most popular brands
of fake meat and I'll tell you that
they are not good. I've had almost all of them.
But the Beyond Burger
was pretty good.
You know the most chicken you eat is actually
soy. I don't buy that.
I really don't.
Yeah, maybe from Subway.
Most chicken that I eat is chicken.
Oh boy, I can take the trash off.
Are you shitting on Subway?
No, I just said...
You know what? I'm just gonna say
what up.
Meat to meat, lettuce, bacon,
cheese, tomato. Get it out.
This one is double meat, lettuce,
bacon, cheese, tomato.
This one is meat, tomato
only. What a weirdo.
That's weird. That is like having a ketchup
steak. Small cola with ice.
I feel attacked.
What are you talking about?
People that say you eat steak and ketchup.
That's alright.
But saying having a hamburger with just a tomato
on it is not...
Sorry, that was like
a zeppelin apparently. Okay, hold on.
No!
No, I like all kinds of foods.
I do not
care what kind of food it is. If I like
the taste good, I'll eat it.
Just buttery, please. What about
human?
No, I'm not gonna eat
fucking human meat.
Medium diet with ice.
How long can I
stay quiet for?
Probably a pretty long time. You wanna test?
If I would get an adult
swim show for eating human meat,
would I do it? No.
No, 100 times.
Meat, lettuce, bacon, cheese to meat.
Stop talking. What about for a billion
dollars?
But I don't know. No, because
who am I eating?
I don't wanna do
that. I don't know who am I eating.
Oops. I've seen Are You
Afraid of the Dark before. I know that this comes with
like a caveat here.
Would you eat human meat
for a billion dollars?
I don't know.
I guess so. But little
do you know. You're eating
your dear great
great grandfather and it's like
no! What is it? Meat only.
Can't wait for the pizza.
I did that very poorly. You would do
that for a hundred bucks.
That's not worth a hundred bucks.
It's not.
It's not worth a hundred
dollars. You think eating...
No. This conversation
is over.
We're not talking about this anymore.
What about that meeting?
Shit! What time is it?
Oh no! I missed
the meeting. I missed it.
There was like seven executives I was meeting to.
And I told them like I'm doing this
big stream. I was kind of
short on cash. I asked
them if they could like pay for all the food and shit before
I got there. And I said there was gonna be like
probably thirty people I was inviting.
Uh oh. It's alright.
New active menu slot. Rain.
What's a good rainy day food?
Ooh. Pizza. Let's get it.
I'm buying a fresh
pizza.
1600. Let's go.
Okay. Put that pizza on there.
Now we're talking.
I gotta get the lasagna back in here as much
as I don't want to do it. I hate the lasagna.
PCMSR.
PCMR.
PCR on NR.
PMCSR. I don't remember.
Medium water.
With no ice. With ice.
Fucking idiot.
Call me an idiot. I am gonna call you an idiot.
You opened up the second game and
couldn't fucking figure it out so you quit it immediately.
Grow up.
Way to be harsh. I'm just telling you
like it is. But I
wanted just to relax. I didn't want to have to fucking
like learn a game and embarrass myself in it.
You can't simply learn
like two or three new commands.
God.
If
Jerma986 thinks he's so great, why doesn't he
just do it?
And then
PSMCR.
I don't know.
Ow. Fuck.
No. What am I pressing?
Okay. Small.
I forget. I don't know. I don't know what to do.
I fucked up. I don't know. I gotta. I need to restart.
Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop.
How do you do it? How do you make a pizza?
Tomato sauce, cheese,
olives and onions.
Where's the fucking olives?
Why are the olives on the, on the, what?
Onions is N
again. Slow down.
Calm down. It's not a big deal. And V
is olives. So I think
yeah, I could put too much meat
on anything really. Pizza included.
People do like meat
lovers pizza. You
take a slice out of the pie
and it just center blocks
down and everything falls off and you can't
eat it. You just get like that weird bread taste
with like sauce all over it. And then there's
pepperoni sausage and hamburger meat all over the fucking
box. Why do people do that?
Stop it. I hate you.
I like meat on pizza. I like hamburger.
I like onion hamburger and onion
sausage and peppers and
but I don't like sausage hamburgers
pepperonis
lamb and
turkey all over it. Like I don't know.
Why? What animal
does an onion come from?
Would I eat crickets?
I mean maybe.
Depends.
No, but I do like meat on pizza. I'm just
just shit posting.
Sorry guys.
PSRPSC
Season 3
form juice. Good.
The steaks we need.
Good. We're good.
Not a bad day.
Come on. Hurry up and cook.
Tomato sauce. Cheese.
I wanted to do C.
Just put everything on it.
Jerma slurp.
How did I do that that easily?
Because I wasn't paying attention.
I did that incredibly fast and incredibly perfectly.
Don't ever make that
an emote. Well I'm not on screen.
How would I do that? Jerma your stream is so
loud in comparison to other stuff on Twitch.
When an ad pops up it blows off
my speakers. Yeah.
I don't know what that is.
But I think it has to do with
how I'm pulled through OBS.
And what's going to happen here
in the next, I don't know, I'm going to get
like a hardware mixer to like
increase it before it goes in.
So that'll happen soon.
You're making an entire lasagna for a
This is Chad
from the meeting. Why are you playing this?
Chad I'm sorry.
I got the day wrong.
I bet you can't get through today without
making a single bad order.
I'm not taking that bet. Okay.
Large crowds.
It's weird because if I look at
OBS right now, if I
according to the meter for
my microphone on OBS,
it says I am
very close right now to peaking
my microphone, like to being in the red.
So it's something how I'm
getting pulled into OBS and OBS is not putting
it out the way that it should be.
What I need is I need like a hardware compressor.
But then, you know, this is why I haven't done it.
Because then when you put like a
compression and like an equalizer on your voice, you end up
with one of these. You guys know exactly
what I'm talking about, where everything is like super
over equalized and you sound like you're coming out
of a radio station. I don't like
how that sounds. We need more equalization.
Some people do it fine.
Most people do it fine. But sometimes
you find the person that has just like, you know, let me turn
that up. So it's just
this incredibly weird over
incredibly smooth sounding
sound and everything that they say is sounding
kind of like this. Well, you know guys, the
thing is, yeah, I think I have to go
pick up that thing on the, yeah,
what do I need, uh, ten of those? I think I need that. Yeah, I do.
Am I shit talking? No, I'm not.
Uh, guys, I'm getting one of these.
You know what I'm gonna do? I'm gonna, okay, the first
day, you're gonna know I have this, because the first
day I have this, I'm gonna, I'm gonna bang
up the equalization as high as I
can go. It's gonna be so
awful. I want every syllable
to have a
compressed sound to it. Every single
syllable is going to sound like this.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
I'm gonna over equalize the fuck out of my
voice now and I'm gonna keep it for like six
months all right let's take, uh,
bake potato instead of steak,
keep pizza on there. Put a hard limiter
and just crank up the gain.
Just butter.
B for butter, Y for butter.
This is Chattington, your boss, you're fired.
No, don't fire me! No, don't
do it! Do you understand?
That's this whole thing is just trying to get fucking fired.
fire bad worker you can't fire me i quit oh hey so by the way coming up on the 21st coming up
on the 21st there's gonna be something really really interesting check it out if you can get
a chance it's gonna be the carnival dream you will be able to control throughout with your
twitch chat interview what do i do pizza tomato sauce cheese and pepperoni
yeah i don't have a problem with equalization i said over equalization dan you made me press
three instead of two you just went on a rant about it yeah that's what we do here we just like rant
child h please i beg you we need a facecam no don't make me go off on a facecam rant
that's what we do here fucking i hit two again shit is there actually a meeting no i don't have
a meeting i have a lot of shit to do that requires talking to people but no there's no like meeting
actually what time is it but how long did i say the stream is gonna be like an hour and 10 minutes
yeah i was like guys this stream today is only gonna be like an hour and 10 minutes
it's three hours and 15 minutes wow i'm fucking way over way more than i said i was gonna do
you're gonna miss the entire meeting just butter butter is why right no but all like i'm just
fucking around all fucking around aside i cannot wait tomorrow's the last stream until the carnival
and i seriously can't wait it's gonna be so much fun i've been talking about this a lot
i know because come on you guys don't understand that it's happen
sour cheese sour cream butter butter cheese medium water with ice 21st that's right
this uh that would be saturday right
peace water
tomorrow we're gonna do the activities it's gonna be another short stream
but it will be four days in a row come on hurry up no salt you got it tomatoes cheese tomato sauce
cheese pepperoni and sausage got it yeah if you can catch it live then i hope to see you there
this better be worth it oh god the pressure
okay i have to answer this because there's a lot of people think that i think i already answered it
once uh no i did not pick the 21st because of earth wind and fire that is my favorite song it
just coincidentally that was when all the companies involved were able to come together the
contracting of the robots and where we can go get them the location with the event and the
production coordinator is it the 21st was just like the best day for all of this stuff
i promise it has nothing to do with earth wind and fire but let's just say it does now
because it's my favorite song are you going oh i did it i did it i got to a new restaurant
are you gonna license out uh the earth no i'm not licensing out earth wind and fire
that's probably more money than the whole entire stream is gonna take to actually produce
to license that song for like a day cool i got a restaurant new prep station oh
they're on stage prep station oh extra customer during the day oh up from the previous floor oh
can be a potential income booster by opening up your pantry new specialty foods i don't i need
more money i bet you know what i mean i can upgrade the drinks i'm doing upgraded drinks
active venue okay let's get the upgraded drinks get the lasagna off i should upgrade the beer too
put steak on there he's upgrading the soda fountain like a noob sour cream chives onions
sour cream chives onions oh finally oh is onion medium wait a minute medium cola with flavor blast
flavor and ice oh that's new flavor blast what's a flavor blast it's like when you have a
doctor pepper and you do the squirt of vanilla or you have a coke and you do a squirt of cherry
in those machines am i still gonna be an internet funny guy in 10 years i don't know what i'm gonna
have for breakfast tomorrow uh i don't know nothing on it you're easy what do you mean
no i just nothing on it small diet with flavor blast flavor blast and ice oh you motherfucker
one season twice juicy somebody in chat asked for this so this is yours large diet with ice
small diet with ice sour cream and onion oh that's the chip one sour cream cheese sour cream
butter chives bacon everything everything everything everything what is it what is it
cut what was that i don't know you know i love that i love that like write down c sanitize just
butter we got it you know how people were asking jerma what would you do if you weren't doing
streaming like this wasn't what you did for your income and this wasn't what you do it every you
know every day every other day whatever every couple days every like twice three times a week
you know like it's you do it three times a week if you you know the answer i probably give you
the real answer here i would work it like a fucking soap like factory what do we do
sour cream bacon onion i would just like work at like a soap place and like or like a hand cream
and like soap place why i don't know i just like i don't know it's it'd be like cool to like squish
stuff sour cream cheese sour cream butter bacon and onion and then what the fuck do you want
that's four it's four oh good jumbo a jumbo jumbo water with ice oh shit uh five four season three
times with a juicy large cola with ice and a flavor blast sour cream and onion that was butter
please get to the meeting now this is more important than the meeting last night he got
to an eight and an eight of what really what about my shareholders okay they were dumb enough
to invest in the first place what's butter what's cream what's cheap we are your shareholders no
you're not yes we are no you're not i would i wouldn't put that responsibility onto you guys
why would i do that weather alert rain coming up i feel like i need more food can i sell an item
can i sell my food items yeah i mean technically yes but i mean like sell them sell the recipe
once you get your dad for his birthday get your dad a like a nice coffee grinder
and a bag of really really nice like coffee beans gift your dad a sub to me i mean that's like the
laugh out loud answer the real answer is get a small coffee grinder and some good beans and
what if you already have a coffee grinder then get him a spongebob tie all right wait wait wait
wait wait 700 bucks how much is it to upgrade the stakes 2 000 bucks i'm thinking of upgrading
the hamburgers next have i ever vaped you mean ever in my entire life or do i currently vape
with like a vape pen um no i've never i've never vaped like i've never vaped tobacco
i've had a like marijuana vape before does that count yeah by the way that was only like one
it was probably once in my whole life quick quick now is this opportunity to bring up the
the stream i was going to do that i've brought up like three times you guys remember that one
every time somebody brings up the word vaping we always talk about it wow i need to pay attention
one season twice juicy one citrus two beers jumbo grape with ice and flavor blast
that's a lot that's too much sugar we already talked about this don't order that
we can die with ice fuck a lasagna four four hurry small tea with ice and flavor
i'm getting that down pretty well why would you put a flavor blast in
fucking water this is gross i think these dishes is there a website that that can determine how
fast you click something like how fast you can click something in like 10 seconds
i want to break the world record real quick before i leave do i think people try to get
my attention with outlandish comments nowadays i mean people just kind of write crazy shit
just to write it so i don't think more than ever jesus jesus what's this one i think this is going
to be a this is going to be a perfect day but no i don't think that well the thing is another
thing to keep in mind is the channel has grown a lot in the last year and a half or so last year
so you know the over under that somebody might just come into the channel and just write pee
pee poo poo and then leave i mean it's it's fairly high so you know that's possible
do i wish that i have grown this much i mean that's kind of a weird question because
i guess the my ultimate goal whenever i do this stuff is i want to
make as many people happy or laugh and be in on the joke as possible right so
i don't think it's oh no i don't want to i don't want to have any viewers there's two people tell
me to go back to play team fortress yeah that happens not that often though but i mean that's
what that's i don't doesn't really bother me because at the end of the day no my perfect score
no what if i just don't serve it all right what's that website click as fast as possible about
something the speed test clicking speed test this is cookie clicker this is a cookie clicker
optimizer website is there another one just play cookie clicker no not reaction time i'm talking
how fast you can press the button as fast as possible okay this one so it clicks in five
so how fast can you click in five seconds all right here we go i just want to see yeah that
there it is i gotta get ready for this though okay let's get that on screen okay why can i not move
this why can i not show this what the fuck is going on here oh there we go okay it's because
it's being blocked by cook serve delicious and i just would have known that if i looked at my
screen so let's see how fast i can do this so the record do you know the world record is 14.1
clicks per second are you ready for me to beat the world record i'm gonna have to lie on the
ground for this though i actually might i'm gonna have to lie down that's first try that's 12.4
clicks per second i can i'm gonna beat the world record what do i what do i need 14.1 whoa that's
gonna be fucking easy oh i'm out of the fucking window shit i gotta i gotta like i gotta like
tape this to the table it's moving around i can i need to like bolt this to the table
i know i need to stand up i need to be in the right right mindset for this hold on it's not ideal
this is not this is not like a guinness world record setup here not even an ideal setup and
i'm gonna fucking beat it the mic out of the way no move out of the way stop you know it's the mouse
pad too mouse is like stay here i need to stand up yeah i got it no no this is the one this is it
here are you ready get the guinness book of world records on the fucking line now to keep coming
out of the box in the guinness book of world records there's no box zooming in
hold on wait wait i'm having a heart attack my forearm is like on fucking fire right now don't
you understand and this is one-handed by the way no no no i'm getting too my arms getting too tired
this is not an ideal scenario i'm lying on the ground i'm lying on the ground i want to hit my
head already done what do you mean already done what are you talking about 14.6 the world
record get out of here with you fucking cheats do you hear how fast this is being clicked do you
hear this no fucking human can do it this fast no human can do this you understand look at listen
to this last try the last try and then i'm fucking done this is the one right here i'm gonna get
fucking at least 14 i don't fucking game sucks not even a game it's fucking easy 14.8 yeah well
why don't you call up mr guinness then all right that's it where am i ah 61 whoa what was that one
13.2 let's go no fuck i almost had it every time at 40 okay last one that's it
what am i doing i'm not too tired i'm too tired i would have had it on like the first
i got like 13.2 my arm is like rock hard right now i'm so tight i'm too tight fucking stop it in the
back button get the fuck out of 60 goddamn six yeah i'm done i'm done i'm done i'm done i'm done
i can't do it i can do 66 can't do it i don't think i can
i could probably do it oh my hallelujah is right there in front of my face oh we're at that point
where the the wrist is so tight i can't do it can i get to 72 i'm stretching i'm just stretching
we might be past the point 68 things the best i got for tonight losing i'm losing time losing
steam i'm losing steam i'm losing steam i can't i would have maybe had it like five to ten minutes
ago steams up all right i've done i can't i can't do it i can't do it not tonight it's not gonna
happen fuck that's it i can't my my bright arm is out i can't do it anymore 68 clicks in five
seconds is all i can do but i do have a strategy for next time i'm gonna pick this fucking record
this journey starts now holy shit i'm fucking exhausted you have to have a mouse webcam i'll
do it with a webcam facing my hand next time i promise all right that's it i gotta get going
i gotta get some shit done couldn't get 69 i know i have to do some stuff the tomorrow stream is
gonna be show i'm so out of breath this is fucking ridiculous i did connect five straight six straight
hours three days in a row and be pulsating my wrist how long was it was it was 20 minutes
damn i think i could do it no all jokes aside i think i actually could do that
if i was completely and totally fed no i haven't eaten anything today that's another part what is
it 70 is it 74 72 i could probably do it don't die no i'm fine well i did eat actually i had
something small i had a yogurt so you know i'm hungry all right i will see you guys tomorrow
for the activity book stream we're just gonna do some of the activities should be fun and then
if you're not making it tomorrow then show up on 21st because that's gonna be quite a stream
thank you for joining me see you tomorrow let's do the bits i'm so fucking drained i'm so drained
right now i did that so many times in a row but we had uh slalom thank you uh slalom for the 10
bucks thousand bits thank you so i'm having a colonoscopy tomorrow wish me luck they're very
easy good luck hopefully you can figure out what's going on if you're doing it for uh irritable bowel
reasons or just trying to get a checkup uh they're pretty easy uh that whole day went very smoothly
for me so take care wish you the best of luck taking care of your health that's a good thing
thank you for the 10 bucks we also had uh i don't even like taco belt but 250 german985 oh you mean
that family guy streamer yeah either one works thank you gnarly for the 250 glad i was lucky
enough to play that scribble game with you in chat it was a lot of fun even though most of my
drawings were shitty and me me i'm excited for the activity book and very excited for the carnival
yeah it was nice it's nice to do stuff like that from time to time there's plenty of great
super peters lots of great family guy references but yeah thank you it was my pleasure thank you
phylactery lich of course 69 subs there was a stream today so phylactery comes in and drops
70 fucking subs almost it's ridiculous it's an insane amount of money holy shit phylactery
lich again thank you so much for this ridiculous amount of money how many from each category am i
going to do from the uh for the activity book stream or the community stream um pretty much
just i'm going to pick out the ones that i'm going to talk to the mods tonight and i'm just
going to pull out the ones that i think are like fun and interesting and i'm not going to do them
until the stream but maybe five to ten of each category maybe 10 15 we'll see hey cream corn
thanks the 250 had a lot of fun both watching and playing scribble tonight perhaps you could
do it again sometime but with more words no it was a lot of fun that was fun just to kind of
chill and see what people were going to draw more of a low key stream and i know i did say this is
a low key short stream and then it turned into an intense battle against a world record sometimes
it happens though but thanks for the 250 cream corn thank you low key chad chunks thanks for
the thousand bits ten dollars they say mcchicken time it might be a mcchicken time we'll see
you can buy like seven of them six of them with that ten bucks thank you thanks a lot chad let's
get the subs on the screen toss them up here they should be rolling up here there they are
all of you thank you so much for your subs the time is it right now it is eight o'clock pacific
right now but thank you all of you every single one of you subs that subs to this fucking channel
to watch your guys spam click and window for 30 minutes dot dot dot dot dot dot dot and almost
beat the world record for clicks gotta add that part on the end no thanks a lot all of you means
a lot every single fucking sub every single dollar every cent every viewer you're all fucking
wonderful thank you you made 999 million clicks that's not even real though it's a lie thank you
i don't even like taco bell for the 250 germa doesn't eat lamb pizza every day
is he poor i don't like lamb either here's some dunkin donuts because you're epic this is just
all right i'm gonna give i'm gonna give you a reference here this is what is in front of
the drive-through for every single dunkin donuts the only difference is replace me
why can i not save this there we go all right so this is outside of every single dunkin donuts
drive-through just all you have to do is replace this image is me pointing with rob gronkowski
now this can be altered instead of the finger pointing there is a sandwich in his hand like
a bacon egg and cheese bagel and he's been instead of pointing he's pushing it towards the camera
hey thank you mostly lost for the 250 what is this i think i just ran over something what did
i run over with my chair oh no that's not good i just ran over my headphones because i like those
line on the fucking ground i think these are actually fucked up it's all right all right what
is this is this is you got audio of me saying something fucked up fuck no where's my audio
oh shit fuck no what am i pressing
right i forgot about that okay thanks for the 250 mostly lost and that cool clip
hey abomination zero thanks with ten dollars you're doing a great job a great job thank you
that's what it sounds like when you that's what it sounds like you're in a black hole
but thank you abomination zero for the ten bucks thousand bits and finally thank you to bait uh
bait naily for the 250 and he says general rackleff is the first beer general you're the one
who gets things done around here you have so many friends everybody's counting on you everybody
looks up to you that is the best single piece of media i think that's ever released i will
see you guys tomorrow activity stuff dot to dots where's waldo's maybe some jokes
gonna chill again see you tomorrow goodbye good night have a great day great evening