Hey what's up everybody? I told you I'd be back and here I am. I gotta say I feel like a new man
after the last show. I feel reinvigorated. I feel HD. I feel like German. So I want to give a huge
shout out to all the actors that made it to the competition. Unfortunately none of them won.
I am still here. I still reign supreme. I want to give a huge shout out to Ludwig. Always good to
see him. It was a crazy show. What can I say? But I'm glad I'm still here and I'm glad I'm
still with all of you. That number 13 guy though, I don't know what he was thinking. He thought he
could take my spot. Instead he kind of showed up just looking like a poor man's Andrew Garfield and
good riddance. I don't know too. Like some of his stuff. The Nunchucks? Really? This day and age?
And how old was that guy? He looked 25 going on 50. It's like I'm glad you could do a cartwheel
but don't break a hip old man you know. So speaking of which, I am a new man. I'm here to do something
that I said that I would never do and that's to play Destiny 2. I know I said I'd never do it
but here we are and I want to give a big thanks to Ster and Doctor. I want to give a big thanks
to the Doctor for showing up. You guys are the best and you help make the magic happen.
So let's do it without further ado. Okay we've got here. Looks good. Let me hit launch. Nice.
So I hate being forced to do this. This game is just insane but it's big. Sooner or later I guess
it had to happen but I gotta tell you I'm not happy about it. Pretty much every fiber of my being is
just ugh right now. But gotta make you guys happy so let's go. I mean honestly I'm only doing this
because I feel fresh. I mean granted my back hurts after all that breakdancing
but I mean I keep telling myself I'm not gonna break dance anymore but you know when you wear
a leprechaun pimp outfit that shines like that how can you not bust a move seriously. Here we go.
Warp speed. This game takes forever to load. Piece of shit.
Control. Dominus cryo. The zones are yours if you fight for them guardian.
Okay here we go. What level are these people? That guy's level 459? Enemy claimed zone C. Yeah this is much better with the controller.
What's that? Auto isn't here. I'm still on location. You captured zone C. You have zone
advantage. Enemy claimed zone B. Enemy claimed zone B.
Get some. Yeah baby. Oh platinum trickery. I feel like I kind of look like the moon knight.
Zone C lost. Enemy has zone advantage. Bench. Oh I drew a stun. So now I gotta kill that motherfucker
twice. Slide attack. I don't even know how to do that.
Yes. Race. One for one. Payback to me. Son of a bitch. Aaron! Aaron! What? What was that?
Some kind of crystal shield? This game is crazy. Blood.
I'm going to kill you if it's the last thing I do with platinum trickery.
I wish they would just stay still for a little bit. You know considering how high level some of
these people are, I'm not doing as bad as I thought I would. Yes blood for blood. Love to see that.
Why do these things have to be so violent?
So yeah it was especially great to see the doctor. I haven't seen him in almost three years now.
He's been three years? That's crazy. Time just flies by. Time flies by and then someone named
Huckababy Brian shoots you in the face. That's life kiddos. He's dying. Turn it into ice cube.
Yeah get some. Get some.
Get happy. I don't even know what the plot is. It looks like we're just here to turn each other
into ice cube. Shoot each other with some kind of bdsm techno knife.
What? Just a little bit quicker on the draw. Can anyone hear me? Can anyone hear me? Where am I?
It's so cold in here. Hello? Is that the game? Did you guys hear that? I don't know what's talking in this game.
Take this without a fight. All right I guess they do talk. All right. You know I think I've died
enough. I think I'm gonna relax on the bed. Zone C captured. You have zone advantage.
We have zone advantage. Zone C lost. Enemy has advantage. Your enemy has defeated you. What?
This is when you have advantage to defeat within four seconds.
What is that? You eat monsters for breakfast. You can win a battle for territory. Again.
We lost! How much do we lose by? Yeah look at look at that. Combat efficiency.
Let's not look at that score again. All right well I think I'm done dying for a little bit.
I gotta go use the restroom. I know where I am. I know where I am. I am in the hotel room.
I know. No it doesn't happen. No. I don't know how to do anything else.
Where am I? I don't even know where I am. I'm in some type of in-between area. I'm gonna haunt
these motherfuckers for the rest of their lives. I promise I'll haunt them forever.
Feels like I just got done pissing a sailboat. I don't know what's wrong with me.
All right let's try this again. This game has some weird audio. All right settings.
We're ranked seven out of. All right. Dr. Chunk invited us to the clan. That's that must mean
something good. We're not completely awful. All right well I'm gonna do something a little wild.
I'm gonna play backwards. Yeah this is how it's done. I can do this with one hand behind my back.
One hand behind my back. That's the ship. We're taking the ship to war. Hey thank you so much
for the subs guys. Keep them coming. Let's take the ship. Keep them rolling. So we're guardians?
What are we guarding? I'm talking to you. Whoa okay that. I'm talking to you right now.
What? Did you guys hear that on the chat? It's not the game. Number 13. Number 13's not here.
No beginners here. Yes front desk please. Your team is relying on you. Hi um I've been hearing
some strange noises in my room. No I didn't. Is there something wrong with the piping or?
It sounded like a voice. I know it sounds crazy. All right weird question. Has anyone died in here
recently? I'm sorry guys. I'm hearing a voice that's not in the game. It doesn't sound like that.
The enemy is ahead but you can change that.
Okay. He'll never do this boss like he just did. Is there like a ghost in this game or something?
Chat is there is there a ghost in this game? There's a ghost in your room number 13.
I'm not number 13. I'm Jerma. I'm just trying to play this game.
We killed you 13. We killed you.
Because sometimes you have to grow as a person. You can't always do the same thing.
Okay guys I'm really getting creeped out right now. He sounds just like me.
On the plus side at least we won.
I have this image on the screen. It's a big red pulsating mass. You should probably look at it.
A pulsating mass? What is that voice? It's getting cold in here.
People are the horror. It's like someone turned the temperature down in here.
They don't care they're not freezing. They're just gonna shoot me anyway.
You've seen their strategy in action. Time to counter.
I think it's gone now. Guys this is the scariest room I've ever done.
It doesn't help because I haven't played this game before. I don't think I'll be playing it again.
I'll tell you that. All right well weird stuff happens. Anyway let's talk about the show huh?
That was one of the craziest rooms we've ever done. It was a lot of fun. Some of the actors
phenomenal talents. You've seen those impressions. Time to counter. Some of the musicians
they needed a little help. Some of it was excellent. Really amazing. Meeting Connor was fun.
Meeting Connor was an honor. That rhymes. I'm a poet I didn't know it.
All right. These guys jump. Every time I start to hit somebody they jump.
That's all right. Stand up and fight again. Combat efficiency zero. Zero. That's one less than one.
No heavy ammo. Why does ammo have to be heavy? Best serve cold.
They don't stand a chance.
I'm not going to show my feet. I'm not going to show my feet. Trust me you don't want to see it.
Match point. Time to wipe the smugness from your opponent's face. I've got hobbit feet.
Gangly toenails. Yeah let's try going to a different one. Yeah sneak up on them. It's
like an office building in the future that's just been torn apart by a warfare. Stop jumping.
Ah come on. What is this? I'm like glowing.
I'm not a ghost. This is freaky. I can't wait to get out of this hotel. I don't even know.
Honestly though I'm lasting longer than I thought I would. That's what she said.
Triumph completed. Learn from this moment. Learn from this moment. This game sucks.
Graphics are nice but I want to get killed in three seconds flat like this. Well when I went
on and on and said I would never play this game now I know why. I'm always right. Even when I'm
wrong I'm right. Just like the talent show. You could say I was wrong. I didn't let anyone win.
But you know what? I'm right. Might makes right. Winner winner chicken dinner and who's sitting
here. Yeah I think we're going to ban that guy that suggested it for an hour. Banned. Ban him.
So this is the spaceship that just keeps taking me to my doom. Floating there like a high tech one.
Number 15. I finally was able to have enough energy to go through the first door and
10 locked doors. Where I can find the key. There's a whole game I'm playing for number 13.
I'm playing an escape room in purgatory and you better believe I get out of the second door.
I'll have enough power to do all kinds of other things. I would suggest number 13
that you leave that. Leave this place and never return. But before you go to number 13.
If you could possibly look under the bed and see if there's a number because I'm missing the middle
number in this locked second door and it might be under that. If I do will you leave me alone?
Oh I will leave you alone. Okay. Is there a number under that good? Number 13. Go chat.
I feel the chat. They say. Okay. They say. It's one of those shitty hotel room beds. There is no
number. There's it's just a block under here. There's nothing under here. What? I swear I try.
There's nothing under here. Dude there has to be a number. I'll look again. There's not a number
under there. What check? Check the ceiling. Is there any four or five? Just look at the corner
and the ceiling. These games are so easy. Is there a number in the ceiling? Oh my god. What does it
say? Yeah. What does it say? I can't believe this. Yeah there was a number.
7.3? 7.3? What does that mean? 7.3. Okay. All right. Thank you. No I actually really appreciate it.
Thank you. That that helps you somehow? Yeah. Thank you so much. Just you go back to whatever
you're doing. You can play that stupid ass game. I am about to solve also say I'm gonna get you
second at work. Oh thank you so much. Seriously thank you. Glad I could help. But still like
fuck you and like yeah I'm gonna haunt you for the rest of your life and all you grandkids.
My grandkids too? Oh my grandkids. I thought I thought if I helped you you wouldn't haunt me.
You're always going back on your word.
Is that scary? Yeah. I don't know what I'm gonna do about this. It's actually just kind of fun.
I think I'm gonna stay like this. Stay in. You know they show up like every week ever maybe.
Wow. So it's it's fun being a ghost? It's actually pretty cool. You can get you can see any movie ever
made in the video game you've made. It's actually really awesome. I'll bet ghost is popular.
And you can keep this shit. This this real world shit it's it's no good.
No it's fun. You're you're in a lot of trouble. If it's fun to haunt too. It's funny I can chase
people like the people I can like hide in a chaining and be like Santa Claus and stuff.
It's really relatable. That does sound fun. Do you like watch people make out and stuff?
No. I don't know why that's the first thing I thought of it. No. What? Yeah no I'm like that.
I guess I was like if I was a ghost it might be one of the first things I do.
Well I'm losing power. I'm losing power. I wish you luck but it sounds like you don't. No no no.
Thanks for the number dude but there are a lot of children when I get
when I get more power you're you're lost. You took everything from me even though it's really
actually not that bad. And I'm gonna haunt you for the rest of your life. You better run
and you better never you better never look back. Okay uh so no no no yeah I'm out I'm out this has
been too weird guys. Sorry. Fucked up game. Fucked up ghosts. I'm out of here.