I can't wait for sports Johnson and the football Barion's Christmas special.
You're telling me that that little kid has that like
47 year old man voice. I don't buy that at all. All right, let's go. We're gonna score a goal, right?
Score a goal. You got it. Do I gotta kick? Do I gotta use my feet?
Or can I use my hand? Because I know in soccer or football, I know it's supposed to be say, I know I'm American
I'm sorry. In football, you have to use your feet. So maybe I have to use my feet
Kick it. Don't think this is working very well. Okay, that was horrible. Don't even tell me okay
I was gonna say if I had to go like retrieve that I would have been so pissed about this
Kick it. Hold on. I think I figured it out. I think I figured it out
I gotta go way back cuz my stretchy ass legs. All right, fuck it. We're gonna use our hands
We're gonna play like hockey with my tentacles. Oh, this is way easier now. Okay, you little shit daddy's home
Yeah score a goal
Yeah, whatever whatever you say Shaggy from the Scooby-Doo crew
Zoinks dad
Knock down the tower of blocks simple. That was so easy
Couldn't have made it any easier
Stop. Oh Jesus. Where am I going? Don't just wait. I did it. What did come on activate? Oh my god
Oh, I gotta go behind. I should have done this before I broke all the stupid Jenga blocks quit getting your crotch stuck
That was so stupid I was standing at like a Buddha statue, did you see that I win your little games are over you little bastard
I currently have a table attached to me. Do you want a table too?
Cuz I brought it for you son. I love you
Where is it? Where's the suit? What the hell on you? Oh the clock it's in the clock
Well, why where's her why what's her suit doing in the clock? What kind of fucked-up family is this?
Okay, I'm sorry about this but this I have to do this. Hello my baby. Hello my honey. Hello my ragtime girl
Send me a kiss my wall, baby
My heart's on fire and if you abuse me then you'll lose me and I'll be left alone and tell me about oh and that's right
That's broken
Monsters, honey. There's no such thing as monsters
Sure, I'll check under the bed for you. What's that? Is that a little locked above the doll?
We got some new objectives
We've got to check the closet for monsters in my daughter's room. Stop the spiders bring Stacy
Well, there's a lot of stuff to do. All right, check the closet for monsters. Okay, sounds good. This is the closet, right?
There's a gut. There's a good what is in here. It's like that weird sushi chef
How did you get in my house, how did this guy get in the house?
What a psycho what a psycho?
You want a unicorn, honey, did I ever tell you the story of when I became a man
Yeah, this is great. This is great. I'm glad I know that my house is
Infested with bugs that that's great to know and they're all they're coming out of the vents you spiders
I'm just holy shit. There's a million of them. Oh my god
Oh my god, I don't know what to do. There's too many. They're gonna like eat my daughter. I
I
We're going in all right, where is it get down and dirty here get that block out
Get this whatever you don't need these. I'll buy you more. I'm a rich person. I'm a rich like octo dad. There it is
the beautiful dolphin
Yes, I know you're so pretty
Dolphin, let's go this way. Tada
Yeah, drop that this is a creepy-ass doll. Why would you be sleeping with this? Look at how mean this faces?
Yeah, you better off with a little dolphin the octopus. What's going on? What the hell is going on? What happened?
What what a game over? What did I do? I don't do shit. All right
I gotta be careful because the last time I did this she like I turned into sushi
Drop that on the ground get real close, but get really quiet
Don't want her to wake up. Thank you. Apparently that means you were a success and there is your dolly
Thanks for my dolly