And I came up with a much better title in my tweet. Oh well, this was a much better one.
It's okay. It's too early. I'm right on time. 3 59. I just rang your doorbell.
You looked at your watch. Holy shit. I'm not going to step into your house until exactly four o'clock.
And hello. How are you? Hey, you ordered me. German on eight five. Hey, come on. If I come in for it,
I got to get in there exactly this time. Everyone riot. What are you doing? Don't wait. Don't be
them. Hey, no, not right off the bat. You're an escort. Okay, I got to relax. Hey, what's going on
with me? Did you order me? German on eight five. Oh my God. No, it's it's me coming to your birthday.
Fuck, I can't today. They were in play no more heroes to when I've been putting off for a long
time. When did I play no more heroes? One. What do you know? I said I was going to play this
probably 200 or 300 times. Since about three months ago. Yeah. This has been the game I said
was going to happen next week for three months. So I'm playing it. Here we are. That's based.
Vito this shit. No, if I was going to veto it, I would have vetoed. No, you can't. Not everything
in this stream is a veto. You guys get one make the streamer angry enough to turn his stream off
once every six months. That's not happening today. Beautiful Joe. I got beautiful Joe too back here.
What am I going to do with it? I'm going to have to display it on the shelf. But yeah, let's let's
get started. This is no more heroes to welcome to a new week. We had a good weekend. We should be
live here. Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday. All right. For a second, I saw I thought I saw
Kim's name go by doing German walk German walk and something about the Drew crew. I was like,
I don't even know. I don't think she even knows what that is. I was going to say what the hell
how that quickly like why is Kim doing the German walk? Anyways, let's get started. This is no more
heroes to welcome. We're going to play. I love this game. I don't actually remember this game
as much as I remember the first one. I very vividly remember though almost the whole first
game. Not this one. Let's see. Give it a look. The music is good. Yes. Oh, I know.
We watched the opening cutscene. Should I just skip it? Don't ever skip. Once a god-forsaken city
where the bodies of angels littered the streets. Much has changed in Santa Destroy. Giant
corporations. Rampant city development. The assassin's underworld has become a commodity.
A chance for profit and entertainment for the masses. Colonel. But shadows from the wilder
days still linger. Or grandpa. A man who slashed his wing to the top then walked away has become
an urban legend many even doubt was real. Here, the strong devour the weak. The weak kneel before
the strong. And those who wield true power watch and count their gold. When's the third game come
up? And in this mass-produced savagery, one truth is constant. It's here, right? With each shattered
life, the same vow as others. I will have revenge. Tomorrow? And no assassin can ever walk away from
that. He must draw his beam and stand against the madness. This is Travis Touchdown's desperate
struggle. Hold it, you violence-loving bastard. Before you start your desperate struggling,
you should drop a nice save. Travis, I already did. What I did before the stream turned on.
Oh, I saved my game at the beginning of the stream. What happens? Well, do I have to start
back at the beginning again? Holy shit, saving in real life would suck. Why? Yes, it would.
Because then you would just second guess literally everything you've ever done.
You would have so many save files in your brain back to when you were fucking 14. Should I pick
the french fries? Or should I pick the casserole? Um, let me save it here first. And half these
people wouldn't delete their saves. You would accidentally load a save in your 40s. That was
from you when you were 17. And you'd just fucking wake up in like your 17, 18-year-old, 16-year-old,
whatever body, just like, duh, what happened? But no, but you wouldn't even remember anything.
Right, because that's how a save would work, right? You wouldn't remember the forward. You would just
be screaming, knowing you were going back. You'd hit the button and go back to like 14 to be like,
teenage me. I can't pick. I'm not going to sweep. I'll never forget. Quick load accidentally. Yeah.
Night for the first time in 120 years, snow fell on center destroy. It was a sign. Nice fetish.
Another change, both beautiful and deadly. Making a shitload of save files in your head is
what? Yeah, you guys would not want that. You would retake your driver's test a thousand times
to make sure you got an S rating on it. You don't think of everything you've ever done and how many
times you've gone back to save points to fix even, even like the smallest thing. I didn't do that
good enough. I'm going to restart that. I could get like 10 more EXPs. It's called fashionably late
fuckface Travis touchdown. This place bring back any memories. It's only where my last killing spree
started. All those screwed up with that one. Now, why would I remember that? It'll be your blood this
time when I avenge my brother draw. That's cool. And who don't you remember the man you fought here?
Um, no, can't say I do. Guess he didn't make an impression. It must have been crazy weak.
You insensitive prick. You killed him and you don't even remember. You know how humiliating that is.
Sorry, I don't have a death diary. And in case you're wondering, I'm even stronger now. You will
lose. You've got no chance of winning this.
You're something else. I haven't been. It's been too long Travis.
When you see your bro in hell, tell him he's still a douche.
There we go. High strike, low strike. I like the scenery of be as high strike attack,
up or down.
Z is lock on, right?
Uh, beam katana recharge to shake, shake, shake, shake, shake.
I don't think I need it right now. Okay, emergency. Yeah, there's a dodge.
Why is he not doing it?
Oh, yes. I remember how much fun it was.
Swing the remote while running is a running slash. Yeah.
This guy sucks. Reset the camera.
Oh, the batteries on the other side. Right. Right. Right. Right.
Button mashing recover from take down. All right. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Take so much longer in this one. What? Oh my God. It takes forever.
I don't remember it taking that long. What the fuck?
Press B when you're down enemy. Yeah.
Just reload your save side. You know, many times I would restart streams.
I was like, think about how many times you've taken a Photoshop of my face.
I've taken a screenshot of my face. I would have just, I would just have like every five minutes,
a quick save. It would take me like six hours to stream three hours.
Then you'd be kind of boring though. Wouldn't add, wouldn't I? If I went back and corrected
every dumb thing I've ever said on every stream, I would just kind of just,
your experience would just kind of be like this. There's a door. Number 13. Excellent choice.
But there's a guy over here on the right. Stream scumming. Oh God.
Where did that cigarette? By the way, what's with the filter on that cigarette? It's half the
cigarette. So what should I tell you this time? Extra filter. It means it's less bad for you.
At some points, everyone's getting ripped off paying for filters.
This is me on the phone. Nice porn game. It's a dumb cut scene.
Oh, king of space. Oh, we're still going.
Oh, you got a gun. He has a gun.
Oh, that sounds like a stream scum. That did kind of sound like a stream scum.
I already did it. You guys don't know. What you guys don't know is I've lost this fight
35 times in a row, but you'll never know because I've just been stream scumming.
Remember that time that I beat all those Dark Souls bosses on the first try?
No, those were 200 and 300 attempts. But I have to make it believable. So I have to like lose
a bunch on some of them and then stream scum half of them. So then you think I'm like, okay.
There goes his head. That was Jevil. It landed right then. Gelter Helter.
Yeah, dead. Somebody gave a hundred bucks at the beginning of this. Like to address it.
Right after this cut scene. Oh, it's this lady again.
Does that quick a turn around on everything that's happened since the last game?
We're not going to be satisfied until you do, right? Oh, give me a break.
We're going to get a recap from the sequel who don't care about continuity. You know,
besides it would take forever if I recap every detail of your fall from greatness.
Players would skip it. It's so boring. Well, I guess you got a point there.
Yeah. Yeah. That's what I do.
What is a scam in the last game?
from rank 51 this time, more competition. The last game success made assassination
trendy. Yeah. But I already fought my way to number one before.
Shouldn't I get a special fast track to the title fight? No, but you will get a special prize.
Shut up. You can't bribe me this time. I've already trusted those goods,
but just a test. This time you'll get the five course meal.
Five course. Wait, I don't get what that means. Did you know I am a yoga? You don't say.
Are you familiar with any yoga positions? Like a down downward dog. The dog can do all sorts of
things. So Kenzie Cobra, the rabbit, Cobra, rabbit, rabbit. Hold on. Oh yeah. I'm in it to win baby.
Number one. Here I come. Hey, but he's still alive. I got a message for you. Oh my, he's still alive.
Pain in my ass. Why aren't you dead yet? Such blind arrogance like the naked emperor.
It was in connect.
I'd love for there to be another camera shot of the cameraman down here
during this just spinning around in circles with a fucking camera.
Now it's your turn to be burdened with another's death. It has destroyed me
and it will destroy you too. This is the ultimate vengeance.
That ruins the illusion. Yeah, it's supposed to. Porn and gore. Yeah, they like stab each other and
cut each other's faces. There's going to be some blood. There's no porn here though. That part
you're wrong. Help you find something. Yeah. We're the fucking super Mario cart. You never have
fucking copies of this shit. We're just here to collect Travis. Got like 20 Madden's, but only
four. You guys can do better than that. Madden Madden 96. What the fuck just happened? That was
always such a pain in the ass though. You'd go to a place like Blockbuster and they have the same
game that nobody wants. Taken up two full shelves and they're all in there. There's not one that's
taken. Not one's been rented out. And you're just like, well, come on, you can't, there's gotta be,
you can't give me more of these that are being actually rented. This is Scott Pilgrim game.
All right. Are you saying that because there's retro video game beep sounds. Hey, you can tell
when this is going out of style. Like right now, when you start seeing this shit in car commercials
and insurance commercials, how many times have you heard the like regular Nintendo sound?
That's how you can tell it. Oh, we, oh, we got it. This is going out of style.
Turbo tax. You guys, you never heard that before? You haven't seen that in,
I've, I've seen it. I haven't seen a commercial in years.
He gets a notification on his phone from Amazon. Your package has been delivered.
There's a photo to prove it. It's just your shattered fucking window.
I can't even pay attention to the story.
Swords ultraviolence to purge their souls of the hatred that blighted them.
A lot of cigarettes put out over there. See, she's got to smoke way more because the filters are too
big. I have set up the next, are you get his, just give me someone to fight. You sound passionate.
What's gotten into you subtitles on someone kill Bishop. I understand. I will, if I, you know,
you have a girlfriend, why are you playing this? Wait, you mean like, why, why am I streaming when
I have a girlfriend? What are you talking about? Do I have any shirts? I do. Okay. Let's get some
good clothes. I can't see it because of the jacket. I don't know what that, I was about to,
I don't know what that is. I want a different jacket and I have to buy it. This is the only
pants. Yep. Is the only everything. The volume up. Okay. There you go. You should be able to hear
sound. Perfect. That's way too loud. That was a, yeah. I put it back down where it was. Sorry,
one guy. Okay. Hold on. This is important. At a Reddit shelf over there. Or does that not count?
It doesn't count. This is a Reddit shelf. So what's the difference? This is what you would
consider. No, it's not. How am I saying no? It's the shelf. Jean's getting way too fat. Try to get
her to lose some weight. Making Jean go on a diet will put her in a foul mood. Dieting in a bad mood
will lower the effectiveness of the diet. Give her a snack from time to time. Jean doesn't like
doing the same things over and over. So once a menu has been selected, it won't be available for a
while. Okay. 24 pounds. All right. Let's do some jumps. Come on. 62 centimeters.
121 centimeters. Let's try again. 180. 240. One more. Yes. 300.
Jean. Yeah. That's got to do it. All right. Good. Now we give a treat. Stretch. All right.
Oh, no, no, no. Holy shit. This guy has a fucking walrus. Stop. You're killing it.
Those are just sound effects.
Okay. Now we need to feed. Here. Only the only premium food for my,
for my little darling. I don't have any money. Oh shit. I can't feed my cat.
Stop. Okay. Am I petting the cat or is the cat a bear against the tree with a really itchy
back? Much better mood. I feel like that you get fucking scratched. What is this?
What is this link? Oh my God. How did you get that? How did you do that?
How did you get it that quickly? Get it. Get it. Get it. Get it. I'll show it in a second. Hold on.
Oh, nice. This isn't even from this stream. Oh, it's just the thing. Get it.
Yeah. Lost 0.3 pounds mood. It's all right. I don't, I can't. Okay. Let's get,
I need to get money for food. All right. First and foremost, we had 10,000 bits come in from
gimme $20. 100 bucks from gimme 20. Thanks for the 10,000 bits gimme $20. They say I rewatched
you through the ages stream and it still cracks me up. Please do another one soon. Watching you
cringe at your old content was hilarious. Also, the original Night of the Living Dead is public
domain. You need something for the next movie night. Yes, we will be watching that one.
Um, no, that was a ton of fun. Trust me when I say that this stuff like that pops up all the time.
And I just kind of have to jump on him if I want to do my right. I okay. That's not good.
God damn it. Viscera fucking cleanup detail. I just had a flashback. Uh, okay.
I just, I saw everybody saying spill joke, spill joke, spill joke, spill joke.
Just like there it is. It's right there. Okay. Let's see.
Spill joke. So funny. Spill joke. Let's do our first assignment on the subtitles.
Let's actually. Yeah. Subtitles on minimap on. Don't invert the camera.
Okay. More bits. Holy shit. More bits did come in. $50 from phylactery lich. Thanks for the 5,000
bits. What just happened to my game? Oh, okay. Okay. I was just, what the fuck is going on?
What just happened? Wait, why did this happen? Oh, cause the TV. Oh, okay. We're gonna start
bizarre Jerry and Joe. What is this? Like a, this is like the generic brand of medicine for Jojo's
bizarre adventure. It's our Jerry. Uh, uh, phylactery gave 5,000 bits. Remember the whole
point of this game is that Travis is a loser. Don't try and relate to him. It's embarrassing.
Nice porn game. Wait, what is, what the hell is, what am I playing? Wait, this is, I played this.
This is the other one. There it is. I don't have to play that. I don't have to do it anymore.
Everybody, the one person that's been begging me to play to Joe Joe. Now I don't ever have to do it
ever again. Yeah. Here it is. Right. He's lazy. Sure. Of course. Don't wait. Don't you let that
long to figure out that I need to do minimal effort for maximum gain. It's not even true.
Oh, maximum game. This one's locked. I'm not even looking.
Don't you have like bombs in these games? What's the button that I pressed that the screen fills
with a red circle and kills everything that hits the circle? Where's that button? It's in all of
these. Dude, you're losing viewers. Oh, fuck. What do I do? Fuck. Is this, I want to find a boss.
No, I'm alive. Holy shit. It's Miku. Who's Miku? Boss time. Let's go. Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I know what that is. I know what that is. I'm all right. It's a fucking game. It's a fucking
pretend game. Why do I care that much? All right. Just beat Toho on screen. Wait, what? I did AA.
Bizarre Jerry. That was fun. I'll probably never open that again.
Wait, got pure white love of Bizarre Jerry 5 video. What was that? Don't watch it. Don't wait. Why?
Are you serious? Are you serious? Should I turn it off? I don't know what this is. What do you mean?
I got one guide. It's not TOS. It's not TOS. People were saying TOS, dude. I'm like, what do
you want to do? Go. Oh, let's just watch it. Yo, TOS, dude. I want an apology every 20 minutes.
Oh, all right. I'll watch it later. Side job. It's horror time. Oh, God is now available.
Oh, I thought that was the side job. I was like, wow, that's okay. Lay the pipe is now available.
Oh, that's right. They got rid of the driving because everybody hated it so much in the first
game. Wow. I forgot you're going to go to burger soup. Am I strong enough to do this?
Now it has to get minus a letter grade. No, that's true. You're right. Is a shopkeeper Sylvia.
I want to make a deal. I'll conquer the rankings, fight whoever it takes. And in return,
you assholes who kill calm down. You shouldn't make this personal. It is the quickest way to
lose a battle. This isn't a battle anymore. It's a motherfucking war. Fine. It makes no difference.
The mastermind behind Bishop's death is the owner of pizza bed, this building,
most of the city. He is the head of the corporation that runs it all.
Listen, you see the whole jumping around from building to building. And as fate would have it,
he is also the number one assassin. You better not be lying.
It is a fact. The object of your game cube rendered wonderfully convenient. Don't you think?
Sure is. There's a new hotel on the beach. The 50th ranked assassin is waiting for you there.
By the way, that junior owns that hotel too. He really is everywhere, huh?
No, there are 50 other fighters trying to kill him. You have no time to waste.
Oh, we're definitely not going to have to fight 50 boss fights.
And what's the hell I'm going to raise. I kind of miss the guitar.
Taking advantage of people's sorrows. He used his music to lure followers.
He spoke of a grand faith, but his words were hollow. It was all to satisfy his own goal.
He'd only found success because of strong financial support from the new mafia
who used his pulpit to gain support for their own agenda.
Someone is a hundred times hornier than the last one. Jesus Christ.
But the real goal that drove him? That's a secret.
Camera's free. Get out of portrait mode, please.
Okay. This is ranking. Let's go to the side job one. There's nothing wrong with no more
heroes being horny. All right. Bug time. So pizza bats offering you the job of a lifetime
hardcore exterminator. Chicks love bug killers even more than doctors and pro athletes.
It's a little known fact. Terminate all the bugs in the stage within the time limit.
You can suck in blocks if you power up enough.
Giant enemy scorpions cannot be sucked unless you are at full power.
Oh, they did. They changed this too, right? Now I remember all the mini games are not actually.
Uh huh. Right. Okay. Here we go. So V is insecticide, A is suck in.
Let's go. Yeah. They made them all like regular Nintendo games.
It's more fun this way. I don't let you say that. And then I just got killed.
No more coconuts. Music's really, really good. This is really good. Can you suck up a mouse?
Oh, shit. Those are bugs. Those are mice. Come here. 800, 400, $4,800.
Mm hmm. You can't kill scorpions. Can I suck up these? You guys, you guys seen these devices
that'll like this? Where it's a little vacuum cleaner that you press onto the wall and suck
the bug up. It's like a tiny little sucker for spiders on your wall. Oh, wait, hold on.
That's insecticide. I don't need it yet. Oh, wait. No, you're talking about up here.
This is, this is papaya's theme. This is, this is bone works. What's this? It's the exact same song.
Holy shit. I wanted to hear it again. I mean, it was different. $11,300.
What? Oh man. What's this one too? This is another one.
What is it? I've heard this. Get them all quick. 21. Every single song is from Undertale.
Yeah, all music is Undertale. All games with soundtracks are Undertale.
E in that piss bucket up there. What are these tools? Is this extra money? I'm,
ooh. Whoa. Oh, these dolls are lobsters. I can't. What did I just do? That's a grenade.
Okay. Kill. Tuck it up. Tuck it up. Tuck it up. Oh, all right. Do it again. No,
shit. I didn't mean to do that. All right. This is, wait, this is a super grenade right here.
Wait, I can suck this up. Oh, you idiot. Get it? Okay. Now I need, uh, can I pick up another one?
It's more fun than the actual game. What does this battery do?
Oh, do I have full power? Does it matter anymore? Can I suck up scorpions? Oh yeah. That's right.
It's full power. Can I get him? He's huge. I can't get him. Just grenade him. What am I doing?
What am I doing? Why couldn't I get him? Grenade. Let's go. Okay. 1920. All right. Let's kill this
guy. Don't be mean. He's trying his best. I wasn't not even close. I mean, no, not even close. Dude,
am I making just a bunch of money? This is cool. Am I just making a ton of money? Why is it not
stopping me? Oh, can't suck those up. You made three dollars. Oh, come on. I tried to,
he just turned in a weird way. I died to a grasshopper. LOL. LOL. LOL. Thank you.
It's too many. Oh, fuck. Can I get him? What just happened? Am I poisoned? Why do I need the
antidote? What just killed me? Let's go. Oh, I lost. Okay. And how much money did I make?
How much money did I make? What do you mean zero? How do you make zero? What? Wait, because I,
you lost it all. Oh, so you have to retire before it's like, um, who wants to be a millionaire?
I get it. Okay. I do some plumbing. We'll pay you handsomely. Connect the exit to the entrance
using pipes within the time limit. Blue pipes can be moved, but not green pipes.
More pipes you connect, the more money you get. Here we go. Play the pipe. Lift, turn, move.
Easy. Let's go. Oh, nevermind. I don't, I hate these. Oh, I hate these. Where's it going?
Oh shit. It's go, I gotta get into the green pipe. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. No. How am I
supposed to get this one? No, you go like this. How the fuck do I get out? Shit. No, get out of the
way. I need one of the, I need this. I need, get over here. Wait, wait, wait. No, it said, oh no,
listen. Listen, it said to connect the green ones and then it go up. I'm going to get more points,
guys. Everyone's like, holy shit, his brain. Oh, his brain is, oh no. I think something
wrong with his brain. No, his brain is fine. He's doing what he's supposed to be doing.
Oh my God. Oh my God. His brain. Guys, something wrong with his brain. Check this shit out. Oh,
yeah. Look at this shit. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Wait, what if I do something crazy?
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Out of my way. Out of my fucking way. Get out of my way. I gotta
move this. I need that piece down there. Wait, get, get out of my fucking way, please.
Oh no, his brain. What's wrong with his mind? Check this shit out. Look at how many of these I'm
going to hit. And please fill it up. I hit so many greens. Everyone thought I was crazy.
And it's $700. Why is it taking taxes out? I went over on the left. Wait a minute. Yeah.
Yeah. This is fun. Yeah. Look at this cool, fun thing. Let's do, I need, I need clear time.
Is he having fun? Yeah, I'm having a ton of fun. Look at how fun this is. Okay. I'm just going to,
should I finish it or should I go for the, go for gold here? Okay. What if I do this? Should I just,
I go down and then around? Okay. I'm going to go like this. Okay. Right. That's what I'm going to do.
All right. I got it. Hold on. Move this. I got, God damn it. Hold on. He's got a Reddit brain.
I don't give a shit. I'm just having fun. All right. I got to move this stuff out of the way.
Cause I won't be able to get back over here. It's not blocking me in. I need these puzzles.
This is why you get this done first. All right. I need one of these. I'm going to go. God damn it.
I have to fuck. I need to get over here. Okay. Something was going on with his brain.
Uh, dude, check his brain. This is check his brain. I have enough. I have too many of these
straight ones. Fuck. Okay. Hold on. I can fix this, right? I can fix it. I can fix it. I can fix it.
I can fix it. I can fix it. I can fix it. I can fix it. Yeah. All right. Now go.
I got it. I got it. I got it. I fixed it. I got it. No, this is good. Hurry up. Oh, fuck. I have to,
I'm stuck in here. How do I do this? I need another set of hands. I need somebody else's hands.
Okay. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I forgot. I can just take the wall down. Okay. Well, good,
good, good, good, good. Hey, look at that. I did it. I used every single piece. Fucking brain.
What about his brain? Is he okay? Let's get those tactics out. Here we go. Fast.
Put all the pieces in the right. And I'm doing peace management right now.
Oh, it's already here. It's already here. It's already there. It's already there. It's already
there. It's already there. And then, and then we got to go, uh, this, like this. Shit. Yes.
And like this way and then that way. And then check this out. Other way. It's too fucking late
now. It's too late. This is what I'm working with. And then we go like this. I, I, what are you
talking about? I fucked it. What are you talking about? How is it fucked? What are you talking
about? How? How is this fucked? How is this fucked up? It's fine. And this goes up all the
way through here. Yeah. How is this fucked up? Is this correct? I did it right. Oh,
oh, look at all these naysayers. Everybody said I blew it. That's actually the dumb one.
Okay. I think I call it here, right? That's $25,000. I'm done. If I lose, I lose it all.
Let's go to the gym. Oh yeah. I got to get the cat food and let's do our first training.
I haven't even played one mission yet and I'm just, it's just fun. Hey there, Mr. I can tell
it's your first time. Don't worry. We'll have fun breaking in. Just tell me what you want to focus
on. Uh, stamina. How much money do I have? 71, stamina. Yes. I'm ready. Stay in shape by using
the treadmill. Press the C and B button alternatively. Ready, set, go. Oh, this is cool.
What happened? I run off the treadmill. Turn it on, man. You don't say three, two, one, go. And
then tell me you're going to turn it on and just don't. I was of the opinion that I had to outrun
the treadmill thing because of how fast it was going to be going at cartoon speeds.
Can I just lose $2,000? I ran the wrong way. Wait, why am I facing this way? What are you talking
about? Oh, I didn't think you could change a treadmill's direction. I thought those things
in the bottom were just LEDs. Make it look cool, but faster. No, why? What? Somebody said what?
Where? Where brain stamina increased? Okay. What's that one?
Muscle. How fast can I tap the button? Up with the control stick. Let's do it.
Is there a jump? I would, I didn't look. How am I not ducking?
Wait, what? I didn't want to catch his kisses. Catching with my brain.
I got hit by a dumbbell. I thought I had to duck. Hey, near shoe, thanks for the $5,000.
Yeah, use your forehead to block the weights. Is this happy Gilmore? I get it now.
Party time. Oh, this dude has no fucking rhythm. Have you said, dude, you see this guy play
catapult? He's fucking socks at everything. It's gonna be real fun when I play the actual video.
Whoa. Attack power increased. Whatever that word is. All right, dude, hurry up and kill someone.
Not all about violence. God, some of you guys only care about the violence.
All right, we've done everything. Let's go back to the motel because I'm going to feed the cat.
Otherwise, this whole chat is going to revolt against me and I won't, I will not be able to
stream ever again because I didn't feed the cat. I feed premium quality cat food. Only the best.
She's happy. That's why the cat is fat, but we can maintain. We can maintain. All right, here we go.
Wait, there's so much to do right at the very beginning. Watch the fucking video. I will. I've
got to play the first mission of the game. It's been an hour. Travis effing touchdown. I've
been seeing you since my last door was closed. Take your time. All right, I want a new jacket.
I don't want to be default Travis touchdown. This is a different style. I don't want this one.
New old school. What about any different pants? I don't like these. What? Never mind.
Did you guys check on your desk? Well, I think it's stuck. Oh, hit the top of your city player.
Okay. That's just like, it was this one time when I was in college where there was somebody
in the dormitories, right? Everyone. We all shared space, right? It was,
it was a line of doors and we lived with somebody. Maybe you had a roommate, maybe you didn't. Maybe
you had a solo room, whatever. Um, but on my, on my area where I lived on campus,
one time this dude had it just, he left his room. He always listened to music very loudly
and he left his room one day and the door obviously locking his door and left his music on
like blaring really fucking loud. But the problem was the CD or something got stuck
so it was just going over and over for like fucking 30 straight minutes until like the building
manager had to come and like, and, and fucking open his door because he was gone for like four
hours at that point. And it was, everyone was just like, this is driving us fucking crazy.
Like the campus, like police had to like get involved. It was fucking insane. Where's the
video of that? I don't have a recording of this, but I just kept laughing my ass off.
Cause it, I mean, it was really fucking annoying, but at the same time, it's just, it was so funny
because it's like, what do you do? It's like a locked door. What the fuck are you doing, man?
Ooh, new music. Now I can't stop thinking about it. I can't stop thinking about me sitting there
and how funny I thought this was. C or two switch target. It's kind of hard to do that.
You fucking asshole. I missed it. Tiger on the bottom right of the screen is the ecstasy gauge.
The gauge will increase each time you attack an enemy. The gauge will decrease each time you get
hit. When your gauge goes up and the tiger turns red and connect your slash combos longer
and activate the high speed slash attack mode by pressing the minus. Okay.
Here's the boys looking for blood. You still here? You get what you're looking for? His
head exploded. He fucking exploded. Yeah, I know. It's pog, huh? Am I just holding the button wrong?
Oh, you're right. You can turn into the tiger. Holy shit. I forgot about this. Kill everyone.
Oh, letter grade. This is not a car. It's basically a car. Well, I mean, it kind of
is the gauge increased. Money. I like this song too. All right, let's go.
It's the title theme. All right. I have a superpower.
Oh, it's you. Okay. Back it up. Back it up. Back it up. Stop. I'm blocking the stuff looking.
They even say that in this game. They have to, right? There's no way they don't. Got a guitar?
Okay. Yes. His voice is so good. He has a fantastic screaming voice. This is so much behind him.
I carved that fucking guy up. Battery. Wait. Oh, come on. Really?
Okay. I don't think they're here right now. Of course they are. They're always here.
Oh, too bad they didn't do it three times. Oh, yes. I love it when you hit more than two or three.
Get him. Yeah, it's the medic. It is the medic's voice actor. Robin Atkin Downs.
The name of the actor. Very talented. Very, very, very good at what they do.
Why are we here? Come on. I need three in a row. I'm not satisfied without three.
Nice.
It really is too bad. There's no more. Are you prepared?
Battery card. You're a pain.
You're all very on the shortcake. Here comes another one. You? You're still alive?
There's more than one enemy type in this one. Yeah, there is. All right. Anything else?
It's over here. No. I thought I just missed something. Okay. Let's go.
Am I going to scream Minecraft today? You know, I was thinking about it. I came to the determination
that I don't think so. No. I was thinking about it, though. A few hours ago, I was like, yeah,
that's probably... No. I was like, Travis Touchdown. I won't let him lie to you. I won't let him lie to
you. This must be karma. Travis Touchdown. Spare me the mystic crap. I came here to fight.
What the fuck? Oh my God. I see the rumors were true. I don't know who's talking about me,
but that nickname's all right. Listen to me, your highness. These rankings mean nothing to me.
Neither does my sect or the mom. My only true calling was to clash swords with you.
That's why I joined this contest. I was starving for a worthy fool. Then you're in luck,
because I'm as worthy as it gets, and I've got a shit ton of anger to work out.
That's what I like to hear. This is it. This is what I've been praying for. I'm weary of this
guilty world. Oh, glitter. No soul. Save me from sorrow, crownless king. Thy sword and thy wrath
will deliver me. You should go easy on that crazy punch. How about I just cut you a new one?
We'll both do as divinity commands. Here we go. First boss. Hallelujah. Here we go.
Oh, I have no more battery. Battery. What are you doing? What the hell was that? Battery.
It takes so much longer in this one.
Good. It's two. Oh, fuck. All right, hold on. Back up. Shit's out of battery already again.
Run. The world is being destroyed. It don't matter. Oh, it's dead again. I'm trying to.
What the hell are you doing?
Get it. Get the fuck in there. Oh, shit.
Like this rock is with an air blast.
Damn it. Okay. All right, here we go. Let's go. Let's go. Chandelier. Chandelier's down.
All right, don't get hit. H3.
Oh, no, no.
Break it. I can't break these fucking huge. Battery.
Extra crank. Shit's dead. To keep blessing himself. I can't.
Okay, I'm ready. I'm ready. I'm ready. I'm ready. Let's go.
Oh, don't do that. Watch out for the laser. Don't get hit by a laser. Oh, dear. He's got more shit.
Shit. He's camping. Oh, you dick. What the fuck? He just hit manned me. He just did a hit man trap.
How did I fall for that? Don't block it. Nobody ever uses the chandelier move and hit man because
it's so obvious. I'm the one that fell for it. This battery sucks. Damn it. I'm gonna die.
Yeah, I agree. Oh, my God. I can't even move. Dude. Shit. Done. Fuck. Oh, no. He's got a plant.
I don't want to do this. I don't want to have an explode on me. This is fucking horrible.
Oh, come on. Come on. Come on. Get him and grab him. Grab him. Why did I fucking grab him? No. No.
Die. Just die. I win. That was all over the place. Oh, my God. He beat the first boss.
Do you want a cookie? How many scums was that? You'll never know. Captain Nemo,
thanks for the 5,000 bits. $50. I just got a big ass unemployment check. So I figured
I'd stimulate the economy. Go get yourself some McChickens. It's a lot of money.
When are you gonna do Rat Movie 3? I don't know. Tomorrow? Never? Somewhere between there.
I can't fucking wait. The job's in the... Rat Movie 3 date confirmed. You heard it here first,
guys. Spread the news. Yeah, it'll be somewhere between tomorrow and the day that I die.
Hopefully somewhere in the low hundreds. I'm really shooting for 110 to 120. You're not
gonna make it to 80, man. Who am I killing? I afforded the directions to your map. I'm busy,
so hurry up. Gotcha. Okay. It happened again. Spill joke. What's on the shelf?
Another $50 just came in. Watch the anime. I got a backlog of animes to watch. I'll watch it
eventually. A one true roadie thanks to the $50. I haven't been able to catch many streams lately
due to landing my dream job. I'm a full-time mechanic. That's fucking awesome. Thanks to the
near decade of laughs and many more to come. If you ever play Monster Hunter World with the
Iceborn expansion, that's something I'd love to see. I probably won't. I haven't played any Iceborn.
I haven't played any Monster Hunter World for at least seven or eight months. It's a great game.
I beat it. I completed it. I went through the next couple little small things after the final
and that's not all right. That's what the cat was seeing when it was being shook back and forth.
No, thanks for the huge money. Just lots of back-to-back-to-back money right now.
I spoiled a bucket. I'm just sorting algorithm awful sound effects.
Oh, no. Coconut grabber. Oh, wait. Pizza. Wait. Oh, pizza. Wait. Hold on. I got to feed the cat.
Okay. How many? I got ones in chat. If you prefer a plain cheese pizza. Okay. Let's play.
At least pepperoni. Yep. Yep. Come here. Okay. How many of you guys
um enjoy like for instance like a margarita pizza?
It's the only difference. A margarita pizza really is just like a cheese pizza
with a little bit of basil on it. Come here. I like it. I think it's good.
That's tomato. Yeah, so does every pizza has tomato. This is not squished up.
All right. Let's do some scratches.
What a lobster pizza.
Not all pizza has tomato sauce as a base. Yeah, but if you order a hundred pizzas,
90 of them are going to have red tomato sauce on it. Sometimes, you know, you get a white pizza
or pesto sauce or most people put pizza sauce on their pizza. Is this something we actually
have to argue that a majority of pizzas sold on earth have tomato sauce on them? You guys
realize that like most people like order pizza from Domino's more than and I'm on a rant. This
is no, there's no rant. It's not like a 30% of people put tomato sauce on their pizza. It's like
close to a hundred. Okay. Get it. Yeah. Guys, don't talk about pizza. That means he ends the stream.
Oh shit. You're right. Stop doing that. Yeah.
That's got to do it. 21 pounds. All right. Bad mood though. A good massage. And this is all
20. I got a 20, 21. All right. Now we're going to feed you the most high quality food.
Premium. Only premium for my cat. She's not breathing anymore. Stop stacking them. Why are
you stacking four or five of them? What the fuck are you doing? Anime. Watch the anime. No, Netflix
has ruined me. I'm not waiting a week for an episode ever again for any TV show that's ever
been released from here going out. I can't, I'm not doing that anymore. The whole thing's just there.
I want to be able to watch an entire series run in three days. I'm not watching one episode
and then waiting like three hours. Oh, we have to go here. This is where the sword upgrades are.
Yo, Joe is on Netflix. Yo, I don't want to, I don't want to watch that right now. Oh, it's you.
I'm not finished with that new toy you asked for, but 50,000 for Amelia and a three. Let's go much
cuter when you have money. Wait, press two during battle, switch to a different weapon.
All right. Let's see if I can level up. I got new side jobs too.
Now let's go to the gym. What about desert pizzas? Um, that's a pie. All right. Stamina again.
Desert feeds. Yeah. I said that weird dessert. I did say that kind of weird
desert.
Well, it's changing on me. He's changing on me real quick. This makes me really,
really excited for the third game. I hope it's just as weird and interesting.
Let's pull things to do. It's the funniest movie of the year. Same. What do you mean same?
Okay. Muscle 4,000. Same. Why I guess it's same. Same. Same. Oh my God. True.
All right. Yeah, I guess you're right. Yeah, I guess so.
Oh, those are hard. Ah, did I pass? I didn't pass. I hate that. I hate those. It's hard to
damn it. Damn it. You excited for the next game? Oh, hell yeah. I wonder just how
not good, in quotes, the one that came out on PC was.
Wasn't the thing with the one on PC was it was not that great. It was still okay.
I fucking blew it again. I can take one hit, right? It's good. There we go. Yeah, you can hit once.
Okay, but it's not the same. TSA is more about the lore. TSA was a vent post by Suda.
Wait, what do you mean? A vent post? It actually was. All right, new side job. Coconut grabber.
It was a shit post. In the city have forgotten our rich heritage. They're not collecting coconuts.
It's a disaster. Tradition says you're not a real man until you've grabbed your first big fuzzy
coconut. You got to be a role model for these kids. They'll do it, right? Kick the coconut
trees to make the coconuts fall. Gather as many coconuts as you can. Carry them to the goal
within the time limit. Okay. Coconut grabber. Kick. Move. Dash. Kick. My head. How do I pick
them up? Oh, I get it. What the fuck? It was in there. How did you do that to yourself?
Fuck. Oh, it's bad. Oh, I got them both. Oh, it's the song. That's gone. I did it.
It's the Mario stuff. Of course it's fucking... I'm just a scarecrow. Can you kick them?
Oh my god. I didn't get one. Shit. You can't kick the scorpion. Hey, watch it. Fuck. I'm not very
good at this one. I have to go like this. Oh, all right. Fast, fast, fast, fast, fast, fast, fast.
Oh, bounce. On the bounce. On the bounce. Fuck. It didn't go in. Oh. Okay. I'm good. This is fun.
Come on. Shit. Shit. Okay. I'm done. This one's fun. One more.
Mario. What the hell would I do that for? This reminds me of Super Frog. I was going to say
Super Mario. You know what's a bad thing when I hear the word super and I want to say Mario?
I don't think of Mario. I think of Super Frog. Come on. Get it. Why?
Oh, oh, oh, oh. No.
Hey, hey. I could have just fucking got it. Wait, wait, wait. Nice. We need a Super Frog emote.
There already is one. The BT Better Twitch TV. Cool. Nice work. Oh, Super Frog. Thank you,
Super Bruce for the 530 subs. Super Frog. Is this a cooking one?
That's another fun one to do. Break. Change gear. Steer. Break. Change gear.
I can do nitro. What do you do? Is this pizzas? All right. High gear. I don't know why I thought
there was a hamburger on the road. Did I pick up? I thought that was a hamburger on the road. It
was very small. That's not food or anything. That's a rock, right? Okay. See? I told you.
There's stuff on the road. They look friendly and just get real close. God damn it. That's not a
car, right? Those are cars. What the fuck? What is this? The Nintendo. Duh. Oh, letter grade.
Yeah, of course. They don't give you very much leeway there. I can do better than that.
Dude, what was that game? I want to play that game. That Super Nintendo game with,
it's like when Montana Max is a Tiny Toons game. We have to spam A and cut down trees and it's
like the Olympics. Did I play that on stream? I haven't played that on stream, have I? Oh,
this is one of my favorite games. That's my favorite game ever. It's the Tiny Toons Olympic
Games game. The Tiny Toons and the games. Somebody will know what I'm talking about.
These oil slicks. Oh, hands on the wheel. Hands on the wheel. Too fast. Too fast. Too fast.
50. Thanks Chunky Baloney for the $50. High gear. I'm pretty sure that was me who left the music on,
but I was pissed at one of our suitemates, so I did it on purpose. However, I didn't know the CD
would skip. It was just supposed to be for like 30 minutes, not four hours. Hey, my bad.
That's so funny. Oh, it's CD guy. That's so fucking funny. The stage just got bigger,
but thanks for the $50, dude. You don't have to do that. You guys pay me huge fucking money.
You want me to get run over by cars? Go, go, go, go, go. How the fuck did I miss that?
Dude, this stage is going to spin horizontal. It's going to be stage five of Teenage Mutant
Ninja Turtles, Turtles in Time. What comes first? Fucking Mack truck. It's hard to determine when
the toads evolve into cars in front of screens. Ah, too fast. Why are they all going the same
direction? I don't know, but I can't wait to spam. I'm playing that like very soon.
Tiny Toons. Outdoor games. That game was hard as shit. It was insanely difficult.
Yeah, wacky sports challenge. You got it. That's the one. Cancel the green screen for Tiny Toons.
What do you think I am? The car is going the wrong way.
I just got hit twice. Am I the one going the wrong way? No, I'm not. There's a middle divider.
You're the yellow line. They are going the wrong way. What? That was actually shocking to me.
Shocking. I'm trying to rip the fucking wheel, man. I got 30 seconds to get the hell out of here.
All right. No more bullshit. Go. No more horse shit. There was no control. I had no control.
I'm not going to do it. Wait, is it straight away? Hit it. Get it, please.
No, don't reply. I wanted to get out. I didn't want to reach. It's high.
You have enough driver's license? Yes, I do. All right. Motel. Save game.
Then play Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles 2003. No, I don't like the cartoon games.
No, I don't like when the game is based on the cartoon. I like for the game to be just the game.
Sorry. Tiny toots. No, what I'm saying is the TMNT game, the new ones are tie-ins with Nickelodeon.
It's not like, oh, Konami just made a Ninja Turtles game. How is that wrong? Is that wrong?
Are you dumb? No, because that's based on the cartoon. What do you mean so?
Okay, I'll give you a hand here. Hulk Ultimate Destruction versus Hulk the Video Game for Wii.
Somebody just made a Hulk game because they wanted to. They didn't base it on a cartoon character.
They didn't base it on a currently running cartoon TV show.
Groupies? What's that supposed to mean? Thanks. If I told you now, I'd ruin the surprise.
Go see for yourself. Fine. Whoever they are, I'll make sure they get a nice close-up of my bean katana.
All you feel is ecstasy when you kill. New clothes after this. It's like you're getting off.
Seriously, you need help. Everybody deals with grief differently, right?
Some people fuck at funerals. I cut off heads.
Do what you must, Travis. What the hell?
Who does that? All right. So, who do I have? Let's go get some new clothes.
You do, psycho screamer. Do you mind something yet? I hope so.
Oh, I don't like this. This is the only one that's different, though.
It's $30,000 or whatever. Don't need this. No, I don't like this one.
It feels like I'm too fat for this jacket. It feels like the zipper won't go up anymore.
Blue shirt? Can I just take the jacket off and be in a graphic tee? Ice cream. Yeah, I want the ice
cream. I'll take it. At least give me new pants. All right. At least there. All right. The screaming
in the background is kind of getting to me here. This is Haunted House CD track 12. Rio-Bate?
15 community subs. Thank you, Rio-Bate. Appreciate it. That's 15 subs. Just dropped right fucking
like. I don't even like this belt. Why did I just get it? I'll take it. I just spent all my money
on stuff that I don't even want. Sing along? Sure. Oh, the Simpsons are riot. Simpsons are riot.
Simpsons. Where's the next Simpsons game? Time for a ranking battle. That's it. The Simpsons game
sucks. What are you, a dick? I got a new weapon. Oh, hold on. We've got a link. Oh, no, no, no.
Super frog. We got, this guy plays Tiny Toons Adventures. All right. Why do they even need to
click on this? I kind of want that shirt now. I kind of want this. All right. I got a new weapon,
right? There it is. Let's see it. Oh, it's like from the last game.
Who the fuck is this guy? Wait, this is just like a worker. Who was that? Wait, it's like a
Reborn. Yeah, that guy was making a delivery.
That was like a, it was like a pizza delivery. I mean, why would you get out of the car?
This looks like a place where I could, here, I'd want to be right now.
Out of limo? I don't know. See, special delivery. Anything else? Could be a secret.
All right. I can do the super slash in a second here. I haven't done enough.
I've been PVPing for fucking decades, kid. Hey, you and your buddy. What, you just new installs?
This guy's still talking.
Oh, he got me. Jesus. What the fuck? I agree.
All right. Take his ass. It doesn't do any damage. Secret.
Oh, not again. You want to roll? Where's the music? Where is the music?
It does feel weird without the, yeah, this is weird. Oh, I'm done. I'll see you tomorrow.
Hey, came killer collection number 52 and some money. You're the music.
He just smashed his head. This guy can't even do anything.
I queued it up. I was going back and forth about to do it.
Another thing I've done like a thousand times. An anonymous gifter has gifted 10
immunity subs. Thanks for the 10 subs, anonymous, whoever you are. Thank you.
I really appreciate it. Shitload of subs.
It's the 10 fucking subs. Cool.
Can't resist.
Oh, sorry. Cool. Chris. Better do it right. Battery juice. Cold cheese. That's fine.
It'll heat up on the burger. He's a celebrity of sorts. Even I caught myself checking him out.
Just looking into his eyes. Just fold the piece of cheese up once or twice. Put it in your mouth.
Close your mouth. Your body temperature. Your mouth is like a hundred degrees. Heat it up in
there for like 30 seconds at a hundred degrees Fahrenheit in your mouth oven.
And then just like, just lay it on the fucking patty. What the fuck? What?
Oh, my God.
Is that weird? Does that make me weird? You guys think I'm weird? No, I'm not. I am. Yeah,
I'm kind of a weird guy. Yeah. You guys think that? Yeah, I guess so. No, he said normie.
No, no, no. Don't let him have that. He said normie.
Okay. What am I? Am I a reverse Superman? Because is my Clark Kent me pretending to be
normal in front of my parents? You guys get to see Superman? Okay, mother, it's time for me to go.
I have some work to do. Oh, work. Yup, that's me. Oh, my little boy's working. Yeah, I gotta go to
work. Oh, can't wait. What do you do for work, honey? Yeah, I'm an accountant. And then skip to
me and put it on my fucking twitch shirt. The phone booth or something. I get out and I'm like,
look at me. Something like farting and screaming sounds. I can put like, putting cheese in my mouth
and heating it up with my oven in my mouth. I wouldn't tell that to my mother. She'd be like,
what's happening to you? Able to make himself sound like a fucking psycho in a single moment.
It's able to complete John's hope in three settings on stream. It's a chair. It's a statue.
No, it's a live streamer. There's another chest in there. McDonald's. Oh, my God. Wait,
you're the streamer? Yup, that's me. I'm talking about my secret identity, which is just me with
glasses on. Apparently people are this dumb. Well, they are. Cool, crisp, LT. X cameras.
We just got to see it. You saw it happen. That's why I don't like fixed cameras
in Resident Evil video games. Play ads now. That's not what you've been listening to for the last
two or three straight minutes. The last like 10 minutes has been an ad for McDonald's. What
are you talking about? Oh, don't start fucking counting. The mature filter on. Yeah, just keep
it on with the helmet on. Mr. Touchdown. It's an honor to face you. Man, I love your name.
You got to fight me with all your hoes. That's my game. But we need a better arena. Don't you
think? Huh? Let's go, ladies. Santa. God. Ha ha ha dot dot dot. Oh, God.
Time to bust out the toy Naomi made. Rocket ship. His long awaited debut.
Glass and Barry. Let's pop. I don't remember this at all.
Gotcha Force 2. Yeah, we get to play Gotcha Force. What? A is slash. B is jump. Z is guard.
Press A or B while jumping to jump attack. I see when the X is full and he's just special move.
All right. All right. All right. You can jump over it. No, jump. See, I saw the background.
I thought I had to do a pipe for him again. No, jump over it. No. Why wouldn't you fight
everybody in this suit? That's a good question. Close, right? Wait, he said it twice. You hear
that? Oh, fuck. Jump. He's so slow. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. He's dead. He's slow to move.
Look at the shrug. Just told his hard enough. He squishes ahead. Explode.
A, B, C, Z. I'll hit them all at the same time. That was just like the skip thing. Fucked it all.
That was like when in the middle of an insanely important part of the story, the thing on the
bottom right pops up and it's like Peter Griffin and Lois. It's like Family Guy. I'm PM on TBS.
I don't fucking ever want to see that again. I should make some of those.
Dirties my style. Just have them pop up randomly. Just made up shows and shit that I do.
Yeah, I'm going to do it. We'll get some made from the green screen incoming.
I'll do some like point of the camera. Walk into frame. Look around. Look at the bottom.
Point at the title of the fucking game or something. And like, yeah, look at that. Thumbs up.
Then like walk back off.
Charlie McDonald? Travis Touchdown. How do you pick your nose with gloves on?
That's kind of disgusting. Well, you take your glove off, you pick your nose,
and then you put your glove back on. Fingerless gloves. Skippable optional boss coming. Do it.
Okay. Ice Queen? What's with the harsh treatment?
Anime time. We will. I like her better when she's horny.
ES2 feet. You guys are fucking crazy. Hands and feet in all old games were just like Lego blocks.
That's all they were. Like all feet in all games before like, like 2007.
It was all like dinosaur feet. And then like mittens for hands. No, I want new. I want to
jacket. Watch the anime. I'm not watching anime. No, no, no. This thing would be fun to have in
your bedroom. Just get up in the morning and fucking roundhouse kick this thing as hard as
you can. And then that's how you start your day. I would start every day like that.
I would get up in the morning and like kind of get in the shower, comb my hair, and then just
do the hardest spinning roundhouse kick I could and fucking destroy this thing. And then I'm ready
for the day. Let's go. Jump. You can do it. You can do it. You can pull your hernia every morning.
I already have a hernia, man. I'm fucking falling apart. All right, let go. Let go.
Lost 0.3 pounds. Okay. Time for some stretches. Stop punching the cat. I'm not punching.
That's how hard I'm pressing A. Which way? 19. Oh, 0.6 pounds.
Lost a full pound. All right, play. That was close. What the fuck is this? This is No More
Heroes 2. No More Heroes 3 is releasing in 2020. We're all really excited about it.
One more. One more. Yeah. When will we get No More Streamer? I don't know.
I feel like I'm gonna break my nunchuck if I keep doing this.
Go, go, go, go, go. That was pretty good. Lined up like that. Beat my record. 23. Oh, God. Okay.
Speed. One of the finest fucking quality food. 18.4 pounds. That's good.
Oh, she's 25 when I started. All right. Take a quick dump. Save more. Watch the anime. Watch
the secret anime. All right. Where's the secret boss? Is the secret boss somewhere here?
Do it. What do you mean do it? Do I have to wait out? It's in the lore. What? I have to watch
the anime. The anime is the secret boss. Get this.
Is this a TV? Is this a show? Why is it like a TV? Like, what is this? Where's the secret boss?
Okay, I was watching that. That's too fucking bad. You missed the boss. You're lying to me. There's
no boss at the end of a tape. There is. Hold on. There is? Unironically not lying?
What do you mean? It's at the end of a tape? Yup. What do you mean yup? Go back to the motel.
We're telling the truth. You're being manipulated. Put up another video over the cringe.
Okay. Hang tight for a sec. Sit right here for a minute. I'm going to turn it on in just a moment.
Hey. I didn't want you to see it yet. What is this? Travis, there's a new challenger coming after
you. Stop. Stop. There's a new challenger coming after your ranking. Her name is Kimi Hoel.
Is this the secret boss? I mean, do you guys really give a shit if it's stretched?
I don't. Okay. She's an all-American beam katana champion. Head over to the university
again to see for yourself. I've got some other info for you too. The guys who killed your friend
Bishop. I've dredged up some details on them. This one's on the house. Looks like they were
henchmen from the pizza bat group. That means they are hiding somewhere in town. The rest is up to
you. Okay, let's put it on. Is there actually a boss fight here? Where's the boss? There's nothing
here. You were wrong. Thanks for the lie, liars. Where the hell is it? Being lied to. There's no
secret boss. It's a lie. It's a lie. Revenge mission now available. It's death time. Okay,
so ranking challenge or revenge mission one. Is this what you were talking about?
I want to do these other things. There's so much stuff to do. Kimi is the secret boss. Do it now.
No, no, no, no, no, no. Do I have to do this revenge mission right now? What are you guys talking
about? Is it time sensitive? I don't believe a single word you're saying. You can do it later.
Yeah, there's a time sensitive. Get out of here. Santa destroys being monopolized. Everywhere you
look it's pizza bat, pizza bat, pizza bat. Soon there'll be nowhere to get a juicy t-bone.
And my lead cook got mad cow disease and butchered my entire kitchen staff. Can you help me?
Uh, wow. Continue holding the button to cook the steak. Cook the steaks the way the customers
want them. And the meat. Ah, this is gonna be awesome. Rare, medium, well done.
Oops, that was right out of the back. Rare. There we go.
That's too done. Perfect. This is making me hungry.
All right. Help me out here. When you go to a restaurant
and this steak on the menu, is it rude to order a steak well done at a restaurant? Are you saying
that, Hey, I always thought that was like, Oh, the chef's an asshole or something, right? Like,
Hey, I'm ordering a steak well done at your restaurant. I think you're an asshole, right?
That's kind of how it's seen. If I'm, that's the etiquette. That's a fuck you.
They hate it. Why do I always have this image of some chef, some waiter coming over the ticket
being like, Hey, the guy at table seven wants a well done steak, steak well done. And they just
start crashing the place. Fucking steak well done. Pots all over the place. Is that like what
happened? Do I watch too much fucking cooking American TV where everything is a constant
problem in the kitchen? See as somebody that watches American TV based on cooking shows,
it's fucking mayhem back there every second of every hour. Is that true?
It's just constant conflict. What was wrong with that?
Like is there always, is this just drama? Like do the chefs all hate each other?
That guy wanted medium? What? It's the quick little seer. Disgusting. Absolutely revolting,
if I'm honest with you. Taking out of the package, putting it on one side for five seconds on the
other side for five seconds. No, that's not for me. Blue. Oh, it's cooking faster.
What do you mean tastes like shit? That was well done. What was wrong with that?
That's fucking well done. It's green mate. I cooked it till it was green. That's well done.
Well done. Perfect. Why does everybody want well done steak here?
There we go. An actual human medium. Give it to me raw. Whoa. Give it to me burnt. What the fuck?
We're all insulting you. Well done. I don't even fucking like steak. Steak sucks. Like I don't
even eat it. Why am I pretending like I'm some kind of, you know, did you say you got an order
from a chef? Does the chef like you? I don't know. What the fuck? What do I care? I don't even like
steak. I like some steak. Some of it. I mean, I like steak and cheese subs, but that's just like
a carved up fucking hamburger. Steakums. Yeah. And I would like someone to come to tell me the
problem with it with a steak. I'd love to know what it is. Take a look at the back of the box
on a steak. Oh, steak comes on the free. Look at the back of that box. You want to know what's in
it. You want to know what's in steak? 100% just beef. There's nothing else in it. There's literally
nothing else in it. It's just meat is no fucking like fillers and emulsifiers and oils. No, it's
frozen meat. That's all it is. This is not a joke. This is me telling you real life.
This is not a comedy routine. This is me telling you, look at the back of the box. Next time you
go to the grocery store and you get steak, it's just 100% beef. It just is. I don't know. But
does that mean it's like eyeballs? I don't know. I have no idea, but it's real. There's nothing
else in it. Look it up. Look this up. What is really in steak? New lawsuit reveals the world's
grossest meat products, probably Steak'ems. We thought pink slime was bad. Turns out the stuff
hails in comparison to Steak'ems, which the name alone should tell you is bad news.
But the uninitiated Steak'ems are not dog food, but are instead kind of like frozen DIY Philly
cheesesteak. But in a trademark infringement suit this week that pitted Steak'ems owners
against the self-philly cheesesteak and pizza shop named Steak'em Up, the ugly truth of the
mass-produced sandwich steak was revealed and the details are pretty bleak. This is 2012, by the way.
Okay. In courtroom proceedings, the composition of the meat came to light. The Daily News reports
that it's chopped, formed, and emulsified meat product that is comprised of beef trimmings
left over after an animal is slaughtered and all the primary cuts, such as tenderloin, fillet,
and ribeye are removed. The emulsified meat is pressed into a loaf and sliced and frozen.
Okay. Steak'ems are not ribeye steak. Who cares? Yeah. Fine. Not emulsified.
Did I say that? Well, no. What did I say? I said there were no emulsifiers in it.
I said no emulsifiers. That doesn't mean it was not emulsified previously,
but not in the package. There's no emulsifiers. There are no, like for instance, there's no like
egg yolk or there's no like oil. Could they have crushed it up and emulsified it in a big machine?
Yeah. But not here. Not when it's in the package. Why am I defending it? I don't know. I like them.
Is something wrong with me liking steak'ems? Yeah. It's like fucking, it's like trimmings.
Guess what's in a McDonald's hamburger? Not filet mignon. You know what's in a Wendy's hamburger?
Yeah. All pure like filet mignon meat. I got some money for that though. What am I talking about?
You eat McDonald's and you eat Wendy's and you're telling me that I'm crazy for eating steak'ems?
It's the same shit. Just one's different. One's like shaved and put in a different box. My best
tile layer actually fell. You're eating dog food. Please. Shaved. They make the patties thicker and
they send the fucking rest of McDonald's or wherever they go. Oh, this is just Tetris.
Okay. Rotate. Oh boy. Wait. Wait, what do I have to fill this whole thing in?
Oh, this ain't, this is never going to happen.
They can get it all up. All right. I got worked up because people were fucking flaming steak'ems.
That sounds pretty good actually. Oh man. Just pick it all up. Look at this again. Okay. Now. Dog food
brain. No, I'm not another dog food brain. This dude sucks. Well, whatever. I don't have trouble
with this shit. I'm not allowed to have a little bit of trouble with some shit.
Of course I can. I can have trouble with whatever I want. I don't know, just a square? You have to
be perfect. I know. And I don't know. I have no, I don't know. I'll get it eventually when I get,
I'm not doing level three. I can't do it. I can't do it. I can't even pay attention to this right
now. It's like too much for me right now. Maybe like this. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Got it. I don't know. I don't know. It's got to be like
here. I mean that where else he's got worms in his brain.
Steak'ems brain. No, we're not going to slander any companies. No, no, no company slandering.
Okay. I can't do it. I can't. This is not right. This is wrong.
This is wrong. It's wrong. No, no. I'm going to run out of time. No, don't I level one? I can't.
You can't do this to me. No, you can't do this to me. Wait and then I got it.
Oh, I don't. Fuck. Oh, fuck you. God damn it. Did it? No, it what? Oh, I didn't.
I hate this piece. I can't. It's a stupid Z. Z's fucking me up bad. Wait, hold on. You piece of
shit. You piece of shit. No.
Fuck.
A termite could do this. No, you don't understand. You don't understand. No, you don't understand.
Which one is it? It's so close. I had it. Oh, don't have it. What do you mean? Yellow, yellow,
yellow. What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? Yellow? What do I put yellow over here?
Done. What? What are you talking about? How do you mean done? I had it. What are you talking about?
What are you saying? I'm second guessing. Second guessing me. What? Oh my God. What? Turn off the
console. No. It's too big. Keep the yellow there. What am I supposed to do with this guy?
Put the red in the bottom left. What? Move the yellow.
I physically cannot do these puzzles. I can't do them. I can't do them. I can't even see them
right. You fucked it up twice. Wait, I got it. Just do this. Where is it? Over here? I have it.
It's done, but it's not done. I can't do it. I can't do it. No. You don't understand. I can't
do it. Did you see that? Where did it go? Why? What happened? I can't flip it. I don't know.
How do I get it to be over there? I picked a great day to start doing CBD oil, by the way.
What a great day to start it during this.
Okay. I need to focus on this. This is important. This is very important.
I was like, there's no way a noble hero is going to have anything that could fuck me up right now.
No way. I was wrong. All right. I'm looking at a fucking guide. I don't even care.
Just give me the thing. Okay. Good. Yeah. For those of you that don't know,
I have bone problems. One of those bone problems, trying it out. I just started it,
actually literally yesterday. I'm trying to see if CBD helps with the pain.
We're testing it out. Welcome to the test. Okay. Let's finish this.
Works pretty good for pain. Not so good on trying to understand where pieces of a thing go on screen.
Wait. This is not even accurate. You gave me the wrong... This is wrong. This shit's wrong, man.
Shit's wrong. You got it wrong. You got it wrong. It don't even fit there. Look at the guide.
I can't flip it. There is no flipping. I can't flip the piece. It only does this or this.
You gave me the wrong guide, and I'm the dumb one. What are you going to say about that?
This is the same thing I had last time. Fuck. Somebody give me a different guide. I can't. It
won't fit. Right in the bottom left. Well, give me a different guide. What are you guys... You guys
were spamming me with the incorrect guide. You gave me the wrong guide. Somebody was just fucking
with me. This is completely different than that one. This is 1000% different. This is not even
remotely similar to the guide that you were linking. We have the last of 30 straight hours.
Okay. This piece don't even fit here, man. This doesn't fit here. This is wrong too.
What are you doing to me? Yellow in the bottom right, and then this shit don't even fit.
What the fuck? No. You can't. Swap the red and the purple. Why do you give me these?
God, this is fucking ridiculous. What do you mean swap the red and the purple? That doesn't do
anything. You guys gave me two wrong things. Use this guy. Swap green and blue. I gotta do it again.
This is fucking hilarious. Holy shit. Do I have it? Wait. Wait a minute. Wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait. Is that right? Perfect. Perfect. No, you linked me this before and it's wrong.
It's not even accurate. Just play the meat game. No, I have to beat this.
That image is wrong. One, two, three, four, five. One, two, three, four, five. It's not even right.
So what was wrong with this one? Somebody gave me a fake one. You guys are giving me fake ones.
This dude is so disappointed in you. He's too high. No, I'm not. I'm not. I'm taking a small dose
to see how it works for pain relief and it actually works pretty very, very good so far.
I'm gonna give it a week. Yeah. No, no, no, no, no. Wait. Hey, look at me. That was, I can't
fucking believe it took that long. All right. I just had to prove that I wasn't like the dumbest
person you've ever watched on live stream. I just needed to make sure I wanted, let's do the
hamburger one. You still are. Ban that person. How dare you say that to me? Idiot, idiot, idiot,
idiot, idiot, idiot, idiot. There you go. There's your, this is your brain on drugs. No,
I'm on a very small dose. Okay. I'm on like three grams of CBD. Okay. It's like,
it's not even like a quarter of a regular one. That's a shit load. What?
No, three milligrams. No, not three. I just rammed with that. CBD doesn't make you high. There's THC
in this thing that I have. It's 3.3 milligrams of THC, which is not a whole lot, but I don't want a
whole lot. I just want to just try to do a little trial for pain relief. Yeah. The goal is for me
to not to get, I'm not trying to get fucked up. Who really wants us to believe him? Share your weed
brownie recipe. I don't have one. Jeremy, you're doing fine. Hey, thanks. I can't play Jump King
ever again. I deleted my, I'm not starting at zero. Heard nothing but good things about
CBD and inflammation. Yes. Especially the idea is if I have neuralgia, if I have nerve pain,
just nerve damage somehow, and there's only a few things I can really do to try to counteract it.
So there, it's, you know, it's out there that for potentially nerve pain,
THC and CBD can maybe help. So I'm trying. I wasn't going to talk about it, but why would I care to
even bring it up if I'm doing like a small dose of CBD and THC? Like, well, I don't care. But like,
if you can't do a children's puzzle in like 30 minutes, then like it's, I probably should,
I should probably tell you. Started a week ago. Yeah. I'm going to give it like two weeks.
Just doing like a very small dose. And I don't know. I'm not going to tell you that it's,
I don't want a placebo effect to happen here, but we'll see in a week. How do I feel? I feel
pretty good. I feel good. And I guess thankfully that was, whoa, that was fine. The really good
part is it's medium. That's, that's a medium steak. It's legal in Las Vegas, though.
How is that not well done? You want it more than that? Like that? You don't want to eat that,
right? That's why he moved there. It was becoming legal in Massachusetts too,
before I left. So that's not why that was well done. He just couldn't wait. I feel like I'm
playing somebody's a monster hunter. I feel like I'm playing monster hunter. Play the actual game.
Yeah, I will eventually click link now, click link now, click link. Stakeham emerges as unlikely
coronavirus and misinformation watchdog. What? Wait, during a crisis, people turned to many
different places for advice, wisdom, and comfort during the global coronavirus pandemic. Many
are tapping an unlikely source, a processed meat brand. Stakehams, the decades-old maker of thin
sliced frozen beef used in cheese steak sandwiches, has garnered considerable attention on social
media during the coronavirus crisis with a Twitter thread warning people to question their news
sources amid a torrent of misinformation about the virus. Did I just eat the onion? Is this real?
This is real, right? Okay, no, it's real. Oh, Stakehams. Yeah, Stakehams. All right, now
let's do the actual mission. People who uses a craft Facebook, who uses like Stakehams Facebook
as their news source. That is a little, that's a little odd. Go to the university. I'm gonna,
I need to save the game. Secret boss, you can miss it. Go to the university. I'm going.
Oh, Stakehams. Oh, whatever. All right, university. To the university. Is this the university?
Where's the university? At the university? Wait, that's the university. It's right here.
Wait, what are you talking about? It's just the next mission. How is this a secret?
I had to unlock. Are you prepared? Oh, you found the hidden boss? You fucking kidding me?
You think I should try to swear less? Like really? Would I be active about it? Should I just think
about, you know, what am I saying here? Should I, should I stop swearing? Place words. Should I
start saying like fuck? Should I say like look out or shit? Shit's fine. My mother told me she
wants me to stop saying the F word. Gotcha. By the way, big fan. Look at you. Gotcha. Swearing is for
CBD users. What was that? Oh, it must have been the secret boss. What the fuck?
What the fuck!
Sorry mom we both did it.
Damn.
All right, get him.
Punch, punch kick, kick, kick, kick, kick, kick. Punch, punch, punch, punch, punch, punch, kick kick kick.
Come on punch punch punch kick kick kick kick kick kick
Why am I laughing at that that's I shouldn't be laughing at this
God was a pain in the ass
Oh
Yeah, if you read this you're stoned
Extra cranked when they're a movie with Jason Statham where if he's if his blood pressure dropped
Was heart rate dropped by certain percent by a certain amount. He was his heart exploded that movie must have been crazy
I wish it was public domain. I would love to watch it
Can I can I do that on Amazon the Amazon twitch watch party thing?
Could we watch crank?
terms of service
It was a secret boss boys
Frank was made public domain by Donald Trump
understand executive order
The movie crank hi put to the Library of Congress. Can I call you Travis the great?
Travis ravenous cool hand teasy-greasy
What a fan of me
Yes, I watched your fight with Charlie too. Oh, you were hard core
so cool
No, I am cool
Yeah, but you hate girls who puke never really thought about it
Don't stare at me you're staring at me if you get me preggers promise you won't ditch me, okay
Anyway, I wrote down all my feelings in the letter here. Take it
Your feelings so this is a love letter
Take it take it or I'll totally die
Okay, thanks. I could use a dose of innocence that last fight got a little sick even for me
But you don't read it huh read it read it in front of you now here
Yes, you have to read it out loud
No, I wasn't even gonna open it and I was gonna shred it to Travis the great. So you read and I'll play it on my flu
Okay
You're you're joking right read this here
Here we go. Get into it to my dearest Travis the great. Hi there, Travis the great
I am the girl who loves you the most in the entire world
The hell is going on that I'm your number one fan
I need some kind of evidence because no matter how much I insist that I'm your number one
Any other chick or bitch can approach you and say the exact same thing
That is why I've decided that I should become strong by doing so I knew that someday I'd be able to get closer to you
Putting my title as Travis the great's number one fan on the line
I embarked on this path and ended up winning the national student assassin championship
I really did my best, but you know in hindsight, it was a cinch
I guess I'm just blessed. I can master in one day techniques that would take others years to do
Pretty awesome, right and then I got greedy a new urge a vision that just maybe I could win a fight against Travis the great
Now my goal is to be had Travis the great therefore surpassing my hero
Oops, and I actually write that it's kind of embarrassing, you know. Well, anyways, I've made up my mind
I made an oath. I won't be killed by anyone
I shall defeat Travis the great in battle only then will Travis the great become mine and mine only
Travis the great's number one fan Kimmy Howell
Okay, so much for the dose of innocence, but you've got the bloodlust I'm sure about that the flute
Yeah, blue weapon and way tougher than I look so
Don't hold back. Okay, because one mistake
I'm all real
If you're trying to give me a headache it's working she was nothing in her mouth
Imagine hitting the wrong button. It's just dead
That's a really bad. Oopsie. If you have potato chip
I
Walk that shit
Look it
Duplex duplex duplex duplex
Sorry looks like you're not
Nice back
And there's Cheshire trusts over there there are there are two Cheshire trusts
This is a real fight with real consequences, sweetheart
Leaking screw this I can't kill a co-ed come see me after you graduate and I'll school you again
Steakums brain don't make a lot of steak of brain
I didn't even say that. It's just another thing
There's another spammable saying I missed those Cheshire trust. Oh
You're right
Not a hundred percent for me. I'm gonna pee. Yeah, let's take a pee break. We're back. See you guys in just a moment
PRP, you know, I'm gonna work. I'm a stream thing crash. Hey, hey
This thing's broken. That's not supposed to click it manually. What's going on with this thing? Why is this thing busted?
All right, I'll be right back. I can't even mute
Okay, I'm back
Yeah, I don't want my little stream deck here is messed up
Shouldn't be doing that but it is
Please don't get mad at me, but I think your streams are great
How would that make me angry?
Okay next coming up is
We gotta go shopping yes jumping jumping I'm not gonna why I'm not gonna play jump
Yo, just stop it just quit it
Cut it out. Cut it out. Hey quit it. Hey quit it. Oh, yeah
Got a match it has to match it has to match it has to match. Oh, it's gonna match. No
No, no, no, no
Yes, no
Maybe
I'll take it
All right
All right, the belts gotta go this is horrible better
Hey shoes, yep the whole outfit
But these gloves got to go too. They're terrible. Yep
And then sunglasses, oh, hey, uh, yep
Change the t-shirt, please god. What that's all right. This looks good. This one. I'll take you
Xbox man
Yeah, it is
2012 minecraft skin they get a new job true true omega low. I didn't play that much minecraft
I can't omega low with you
I wish I could
All right more stamina
Dude this makes me want to just open up punch out for nintendo and beat the whole game without getting getting touched once
No, doesn't that make you want to do that?
And every point of damage I take a community sub gets paid for i'm just i'm just nobody
I will never take a single hit in that game
I streamed it. I streamed the new one for the week. I didn't stream the old one with the regular nintendo
What oh I don't have any money
I gotta go do a job
Dreamer just shut up. Shut up. Just shut up put up my money go
All right, which job do I want? Which one which one I want?
the pizza one
now
Coconut grabber. What is this one?
Oh, that was cool. But
I'll do bug out again bug out was fun. You wasted everything on your premium minecraft skin
Look out. Hey go
Do you guys think I could do wario like could I be the official nintendo wario?
Here we go
No good get over here i'm trying to get you man. Oh, he's going super fast. That was a really bad joke. Whatever
That's fine
That's a lot of money
Let's go. It's a hard minus two
Okay. Well now I know i'm looking at you
I took unnecessary damage
Not fine, it's fine, it's gonna be fine
It's gonna be fine. It's gonna be fine. Just a little a little bit of paint and a little bit of buffing out
It'll look it's fine. It's barely a scratch
of all
Backed into my garbage can it's fine
It's a little bit paint
grandpa
That can is government property
Government property watch out for the
Cup that can
Get over here. Oh
Whoa
Tuck him up. Did this ever change or is it the same thing every time?
It's just about the speed. I come up
Uh, and there's the third battery
Let's go
Go faster than this trying and I just suck them up. Is it gonna work?
This is going very slowly, but I think it might work
My full battery
It works 27 000 though next stage. Here we go
Oh, there is more. That's right. There is more. I got my ass clips here
But I cried here, holy shit, I cried here didn't even touch me it did I didn't even touch me
It didn't even touch it. It didn't even touch me
Let's go, I'm gonna three two one blow. Oh shit. That's a lot of people
Come on, get the scorpions at least
Get the scorpion. All right. I'm good. Give me that battery
No, whoa
Ah, this is most
Get out of here most
Get them both 19 more bugs get them. I can't pick at that guy, but I can smash him in the head with this
Oh, there's a lot of those now
No, I don't no, I don't no, I don't no, I don't I can't I need three batteries
It's time get the hell out of the way. All right. Now I got three i'm ready
Get them both
Come on
Two eventually. Oh i'm gonna make a lot of money on this one
How many more are there?
10 more
Tell the story about the oysters
Okay. Um, once I had my eight oysters and I they didn't sit with me and I shit my pants
Um, what happened there? This is gonna be good ready?
Let's get them all right down this alleyway
Oh, don't go up there. I thought I could like go up and look and grab. Um, don't lose
Oh man, that's so
Sad that I did that
I was trying to skip it because I wanted to go down look up and grab because I was just trying to save time because I was
Yeah, I just
Tell all the stories
Oh, okay
One time I had a peanut butter and jelly sandwich that didn't agree with me and I shit my pants three hours later
One time I had a sleeve of oreos and I threw up my mother's bed afterwards because I wasn't feeling well
One time I ate a steak that I may have been uh, too undercooked me and I shit my pants and threw up my mother's bedroom
Uh one time I ate an oyster and then I ate captain crunch after that and I shit in my mother's bed and then puked
In the toilet and puked in my mother's bedroom
Is that satisfying them all?
Yeah, do how many more do you want how many more times do I have to tell these
What about the shit stain story? That's not even real
Somebody just said that one time in chat like three months ago and you all are just jumping on top of it
Let's move some tiles
It's only 10 000 for one of these that's not very much I can get 20 000 eating bugs
All right revenge mission the audio get lower. Oh, it's because I actually lowered it there it is
No
Revenge mission star kill all enemies within the time limit
i'll try
Perfect sword, too
For the humidifier story, oh one time I I thought that I could put essential oils in the humidifier
And overnight it got like really really really heavy in the roof
And I woke up and I was like, holy shit. This is so
It smells like a eucalyptus tree in here
Oh, so I then I got on an airplane and I flew all the way back to boston
Had back to my parents and threw up in my mother's bed
I can hear you. It's okay. Oh turn it down streamer too loud
I'm like close
There we go. Yes
That's exactly what had to happen. I would not have been able to do it. It would have been bad
Play three more
Let's eat a pizza
Bring it on
Stars of stars apartments jungles good. We've already told that you already know what that means
It's like heat wasn't working or something. No, it was like the middle of summer and he didn't have like ac
This house was like 90 degrees
There's something wrong with this heater it was either his heater
Wouldn't stop pissing out heat no matter what
Or the heater was broken and it was in the middle of like july something like that
It was one of those scenarios where you do like the air in the room is going into your mouth
That's how you can tell when it's a little too hot and humid somewhere
Get your kill on how much should I get for that?
Decent amount
Okay, let's go ranking battle
No, no, no, I gotta do the gym
Know the toilet gaming story. Why do you guys just want to hear things? I've already told you
Tell us again. Tell us again grandpa. Tell us the one tell us the one about the boy in the train
Oh, yes, of course the boy little boy in the train sit down. Here it comes. You know the whole thing
But you just like to hear me say it
Yes
Oh, I blew it already
He's so comfy
These are getting fucking hard deal with the cat
Fine
Am I nervous for tomorrow the fuck happens tomorrow? He doesn't know he monkey ass. He doesn't know
It's it's taco tuesday tomorrow what don't tell him he's forgot what's supposed to happen tomorrow
He doesn't remember. No, I don't what does it happen tomorrow?
Hey the fourth no, that's now
That's sick. So tomorrow's thinking tomorrow
What about it promised something I promised something
What did I promise?
A game
I didn't I say I was gonna play this until I beat it
I'm not gonna play the jedi star wars game. I'm i'm doing it now
Is present evil four how many fucking times did he do it?
Holy fuck there's a guy coming with a chainsaw behind him
I missed that grab how?
I don't think I did
Out of the tunnel get out of the fucking tunnel
I like the guy over here
tamed doorway
Jesus this fucking guy with the chainsaw
Oh, I got him
It wasn't the drew. I never said I was gonna play the nancy drew. What are you talking about?
Basically, what are you getting this info bad info?
I can't read don't read
It doesn't want you to read read what?
I promised I would play tamed fortress
How I know that's incorrect because no I did not why would I ever say that when did I say that?
I was drunk when I said it
No
I said I will play the first game that people write and somebody wrote jump king and then a thousand people wrote tf2
And they thought they were first, but they weren't
And I think I remember that
You said cinco de mayo tf2. No, I did not
No find a clip
I'll be waiting
I gotta get a good swing here
Somebody get the clip. All right. He's roaring. Is he roaring? Here we go
Jesus I deleted the clip
Jump he farted ha ha ha damn it. We're going to get that clip of where he farted
That was easy
How can one chat be so wrong?
I don't know
Tell me you're in it
Play tf2 play tf2 play tf2 play tf2
Let's see the validity of this
Fortress
Uh, that's you just that way you clipped that from 35 seconds ago
Not a really good
Face you're making here
please
Mega low right there. What do you mean? It's right there and yeah on my steam account. I'm not gonna fool
No, i'm not doing that
It's right there
It's close, but it doesn't matter how close it is. I'm not doing it
Promise nobody can come up with a clip of me saying this weird
Usually you guys are really really quick about this
Not today apparently music trouble in your virtual world
Activate it
Oh, yeah tf2 tf2 tf2 tf2 tf2 tf2 tf2 tf2 tf2 tf2 tf2
T
f
Oh here it comes
Let's hear it. What is it? Say it. I said it's tf2
What is it?
Um, but I i'm hold on
I didn't say I was gonna play this
on tuesday
I drunkenly said say any game and then people wrote tf2 and I said no
So what are you talking about? That was like a week ago
Oh shit, i'm gonna die
Get up
Gonna knock me back to normal
No
You said do you play any game?
I said, yeah that night and then I said I don't want to play tf2 and I was like
And jump king was the one I played and I deleted my save file
I'm not playing tf2
That it was because of the download time
Yeah, it is
big
Big excuse
Get them all
Yes, it's a bad excuse
Oh here here. I've got a i've got a really good excuse for you
I don't want to play it
Okay, that's good. All right. I'm
We've got it. All right
But is this like a fucking homework assignment that I didn't turn in
It takes one hour and 30 minutes to download no, I can probably get it in like no, all right
Silence silence
Silence
I don't want to play fucking tf2. I have no
Bone in my whole body right now wants to download and install and play tf2
I don't have a bone in my body right now. That's like that's do that. No, that's not gonna happen
I have to be honest and real with you
No, and no amount of dot dot dot dot. Maybe he'll turn his face game on and poop on us
So whatever we're gonna we want him to do
Maybe we'll turn he'll turn face game on if we go dot dot dot
Nope, that's not gonna happen
Oh, you said silence it well, yes stay that way
I don't want to hear it. I don't want to hear it. I don't want to hear it. No, I like talk to me
Okay, you shouldn't be doing thc
That's a that's a dose. It's a fucking like quarter dose. I did like six hours ago
It was an excuse as to why I couldn't do a four-year-old's puzzle quarter ounce if it wasn't a quarter
Us
All right, all right no more no more I demand silence again
Who's this boss? That's a really good image there. It's just what it looks like through his glasses take them off, dude
He looks so stupid
My it really is a minecraft skin
Either that or a powerade bottle
Blame thrower
Psychotic fucker time for a little pro bono ghost busting. All right
All right, what do you do who you moved
Let's see. You got a oh boy an overhead slash
Oh another overhead slash can't dodge it
Oh nice overhead slash
Oh magnetic
All right, don't be cocky here
I'm your later sounds
Trick to you. It's egypt
Oh fuck i'm gonna die
Get out of the way, man
Run, okay. I felt like I had a lot of health for a second there and now I don't have any
What happened?
He's got killed by a pyro
I got full. Um, okay
wall
F'ing stupid
All right, this is f'ing stupid
Dogs underneath it
Yes, I can
I can't tell if that's hurting me or not
All right, get out get out get out fire I think yeah, all right in
Fire, you know
Oh, I caught it
Hey, I was spinning my hand around
Dude, I was spinning around like crazy
Yeah, well i'm dead I go no you gotta spin you gotta spin it i'm just gonna just run around in a circle
Yeah, that's not hitting me
How do I get away from that one though
What if it's
There's so many stupid fucking boxes everywhere here they just block you fast let's destroy them all
Like just cut the whole fucking place down before you fight clear the wii area didn't you learn anything
I'm doing it
I can't block it
It's like when you move the camera moves with you. So it's like just kind of all over the place
If you want to dodge to the left it actually ends up making you dodge like in a weird place and you don't want to go
I'm gonna swing once and then run backwards. Let's do this. You have to get perfect dodges
So, okay is a perfect dodge actually hitting the dodge button or is it just side step
side step
Kind of hard to even tell if i'm dodging
Side slash is the one that's not dodging
Walk it right
Dodge at the right time, which would be
Through dark step is way harder in this game back in the action
Yeah, because isn't it like they raise their hand up and you run around i've done it once or twice already
Do I even have the give you have to lock it or something or no?
Area sucks such ass this area sucks such ass a lot of s's in that one
Say 10 times in a row
Serious sucks ass
Maybe it's that one. I have to dodge your own just dark step. I'm trying
It's just you just hit left right like there's no like the person plotting with it or just hit left
I'm just gonna close
I just did the exact same thing. I did last time I did it and it didn't do it
Oh
Can you center bar see you naked? I don't know. All right, here we go get the fuck out of the way
Oh this place sucks
Fucking objects everywhere you just bump into
No, and i'm trying to dodge the other way and you can't you can't do that
because your body
I'm trying to dodge left. Why is it going backwards?
This is a mess
Dark stuff don't work. I okay i'm trying what the fuck
Forget the dodge just
That's what i'm talking about back in the action with the health chest
No, that wasn't a good run
Okay, i'm just gonna cheese the fuck out of this boss because I hate this boss. I don't like it
I don't like this area. I don't like this boss
Stupid it's fucking stupid. This boss is fucking stupid. The game's fucking stupid. Really mothers are stupid
Do another fucking move. What the hell?
what
Fire my god, this the fucking lock-on is just so stupid here
It's such a dumb fucking area where it's just
Actually mad. Yeah
It's fucking stupid
What?
Get up burn the gotcha force disc
How how do you actually avoid getting hit by that?
You actually burning. Oh my fucking god just run around the circle. I think I don't know. Is it working?
damn it
Get in the oh my god to give no, no, no, no, I want the health
Fucking boxes out of my way
Oh, he's starting to actually get mad he's done to actually get mad
Get the fuck out of
Use the other sword
I'd love to see what video game i'm playing right now anybody have any fucking idea what game is going on on the screen?
Can we get out of this fucking room?
Why are you in here?
No, i'm trying to dodge backwards. What the fuck?
Why is it making me dodge towards or i'm trying to go i'm hitting down on the fucking d-pad man
Damn it. Did that hit me through the fucking wall?
Get away
Already spraying fire. When did you start doing this?
Okay, stand up where the fuck am I just die god damn it
Die
Fuck did you get that fire?
FATIONA
All right, let's see that image fuck off
And
What's a kid doing here what's that whoa that was a kid
This is the problem with fighting the supernatural you cannot kill someone who's already dead
Okay, are you on the pipe
It's absolutely perfect left to die in this house as the story goes he made a pact with the devil with his final breath
Revive through the dark arts the child murdered his parents and now rules this forest a felenting regs
Thanks for the five community subs
Assassins have fucked up somehow or we wouldn't be in this profession
Nothing surprises me anymore
Now you are ranked 24th still a ways to go until the top you are not getting tired
Huh? I haven't even broken a sweat. Why don't you bring me a real challenge?
24 omega low
Boss was dumb. I will not let anybody sit here and tell me that that boss wasn't dumb
Very dumb
Oh
If the people left when you did that they'll be back when I get it last boss and beat it in three swings
Check out some math and go when you please. Oh, and by the way, I thought that was her face for a second
I just thought that was like her head and neck
The Association can't pay for everyone. I was looking over at you guys. I was like, whoa, that's her head
Cool did I get any new TV shows?
It's the same one
We've already seen that one at yeah, I'll get that I'll get the cat I'll get the cat stupid stupid stupid
You mean all right jump?
I missed it. Go back. You're fine. Yeah a little higher
That's a bugleberry noise Oh because I was going
Oh
Reto man
Thanks for the hundred bucks Reto man
And they say
That's a huge amount of money. Mr. Frito. We are all a part of a single consciousness
Split into micro realities to experience a single reality in an infinite number of times and ways in the infinite flow of reality
All of us have converged in this single point in a repeating time
But to watch German get mad at this game instead of playing pat upon to shake in my head to be honest, man
Won't be go. I'm it's a fun game. I gotta break my record
26 she's lost almost a full pound. All right, let's play
Thank you Frito man for the we're living in a weird simulated world
Thanks for the 10,000 bits. Thanks for the hundred bucks
Just gave it me and I'm gonna use it on gotcha force figurines. Oh
What's the cat supposed to weigh in the cat what 12 15 12 pounds
And to 14 10 pounds. Yeah, I said like 12
Let's go just more mini games the funnest part of this whole entire franchise
They have these in the PC one getting trashed is now available
Okay getting trashed. We cleaned our streets by rocketing all of our garbage into space
It worked like a charm, but now the trash could fall back to earth and kill us
We don't really didn't really think that through. Will you go into space and collect the floating junk?
How about all the debris floating in space and store it in your space shuttle?
They'll dump it in the ocean or something later use your air jet boosters to control your position to take some skill
You get too close to Earth's atmosphere. You'd be pulled in by the gravity. Be careful
I'll be careful getting trashed turn on air boosters release
control boost direction
How do you how do you grab stuff? Oh
This one's kind of fun
All right, i'll play this but I won't play super frog this is a mini game inside of another game
Get in there quick gravity suck. I'll try for the meatball. I see him
boost
Oh, I got a meat boost. Yeah, that was pretty good
10,000 you guys ever wish that isaac newton didn't invent gravity
What he's patented it? That's already had a patent on gravity
Well, this sucks
Come on up up up up up up up up up up up up
Worked out. Oh
Oh, come on what?
Did I have a photo of the running back of your credit card?
Hold on a minute. Let me go get it
Quick. Okay, good those wacky digits here
One more I only gotta get one more. I got almost two minutes to get it
Done. How's the booger wall story?
No, no, it's another stage
Oh this one's gonna be fucking hard
Hey, tell us that stirr's apartment is a jungle story
Grandpa really does tell the same five stories
The kids all the kids at first just want to know when he threw up in his mom's bed that time
Tell us the super frog story, please a lot of games
That said there was almost a million games in it
And it wasn't correct it only had like a hundred
One of those games was a game called super frog and I thought it was really cool
Best game on the disk
It was very generous rounding
700 000 to 1 million
Yeah, but it's still yeah, uh, yeah
I'm gonna make a ton of money
No problem
Shit no
All right, slow slow go go up up up up up up up up up up up up
Up get in. Yes
55 000 dollars. I got a lot of money now
I do visit revenge mission two. No go to the gym
Got cash
Hey, it's kyle from mrs hunts class. They said we could hang out in your class today
Okay
Get the upgrade. Yeah, I will
What about naomi? I don't know what that hold on
You gotta get
jacked
We can hang out in your class today
Do you get wait? Oh, are you talking about like online classes like online zoom classes?
No online spin class
Online pottery classes with
Oh this one's
Just kill me just kill me just kill me. I gotta redo it. This one's tough. Just kill me
8 000 to fuck this up. All right
Okay, we'll try again
I'll get it this time. Oh my god. Damn it. Is it over? Did I do it? Yay?
Thank god
That's not even the hardest one
All right, let's get the beam katana upgrade
It definitely is one right that has to be naomi naomi name. Well, yeah
No toy i'm not even close to done go earn some money
What do you mean that new toy you got what had 300?
How much is this?
uh
That's 300 000 dollars
I can get I can make that I'll just make hamburgers for a while
Uh lay the pipe
coconut grabber
Pizza with a vengeance dude revenge me. Yeah, i'll do the other one after this
Okay
Okay wrong
Okay, okay so uh down
No, no, no maybe hold on
Okay
No, no, no, okay
Fuck
Okay
Shit shit it's close
Fuck
Get rid of this
Okay
Fuck
Oh shit wrong
Purple dick shut up. Shut up. Why?
Got it
I'll make it a little you're a luck. Sure
Coconut game
Remember, I want to see your face. I don't want you to see my face. I don't want you to see my face. So no
Let me try to get this clean
Now that I understand how this works
Really? I got it
Here comes drop there flip
Good go
Yeah, i'll get a minute. Is that worth not bad?
5600 dollars
Ooh around the rim. Oh bounce in there. Aye
All right one last one
Get away from me. Get out of here. You fucker. How does it not go in? Neither of them went in. Uh
What?
Get the fuck in there
I got it 22. Is germa always this mauled?
Yeah
I got it fine with the bounce
Right in the fucking skull. Oh, come on
Why do you have to do this to me
Finally, we got more community subs fermenting dregs. Thanks. No, the five subs 18 000. That's good
We also had 50 from yes is online
Thanks for the 5000 bits. They say any streamer born after 1985 can't do puzzles
All they know is funny voices reddit karma complaining about game mechanics gambling addictions and lying
Um, all right, be terrible
See fucking eyeballs
the eyeballs
That was perfectly placed to hit me in the head twice
Thanks for the huge amount of money
All right
Wait, ah
I gotta wait
Hit him. Wait hit him. No
No
26 000 dollars
Hey produces a son. Thanks for the five communities ups produces son produces a son
Now let's go to revenge mission number two coconut basket torture kill the target within the time limit
I got five minutes to do this
Kill him, I don't who cares about the other guys
In the corner
Round stab him. That's it. This just doesn't help at all. Are you gonna beat this game in one stream? Absolutely not
New revenge mission is waiting get your kill off
Back alley. All right, how much money do I have to do one other side job?
I like this one. It's fun
300k
Oh, I should have it pretty close after this
Where we're gonna go first I want to go up and then I'm gonna go down
Oh, there's nothing there. Is he mad? Why is he not talking? Is he mad?
No, I just was focusing a little too much apparently focusing a little too hard
Okay down
And then this way I gotta get one of these in there put it down. What the hell are you doing?
No, I can't get out of here
Okay, then we're gonna go down spin it just go up up again we're gonna go this way and then
Yes
Get this fucking thing out of my face
Okay completed this might have been editing any flash game
Had to use all of them
All right. This one's not time for money
It's not efficient at all. This is not efficient. This is very inefficient actually
Get this all out of here straight down through there another straight piece
Down here another straight piece
And another straight piece and then we go this way straight piece
straight piece all the way
Here I gotta move this shit because this is stuck over here now
I'll never be able to get these again if I don't get them now
That was a hesitant pug
What's a hesitant pug?
Wait, no, we only work in pog absolutes here. What are you talking about? Okay. Now we go
this
Oh
It's a tyrant. No, it's yeah, it's a sith
Dermis sith
What the fuck did you not know?
Thought it was pretty clear
I gotta get this finished. Shit. I need a straight one
Um, wait, where the fuck is this going? It's gonna go like this
and then like
this
Straight and then oh
Okay, we gotta I need that piece over here. Okay. Now I can actually build this fucking thing
I'm getting trapped
I need this law. I need this
I need this piece
up here
And then the rest of these guys, how do I get this over there?
Oh god
Put it in the end. I can't
Okay, good
Wait, what?
Oh what happened? Oh
That's all right
Okay. Now I need to get this piece over here
Done connected. Thank you. You're too relaxed
Why is it a bad thing?
3000 minus 2000
Speed run time. Um
Should I
Just go
I'm trying to go times two speed. I'm trying. Okay, and then we go
Uh this way. No. Yeah, I need some straight pieces
Connect that straight over there this one goes up. Oh wait. Yeah
Okay, that's fine
Is that fine?
That's fine, right? I think
We'll find out and then we turn up this way and then we go
Oh, we missed one
I missed one
Oh well
That doesn't have to be perfect. You just have to get do it
Wait, I got i'm fine. I'm fine. I'm fine. I'm fine. I'm fine. I'm fine. Everything's gonna be fine. Everything's fine
I just have to
Go like this
Oh shit, it's not fine
Has to curve into here
What the whether you're not pieces
Take the middle part that you're not using
middle part
Where we mean?
aim over
I need to undo the curve
The green piece in the middle
I can't wait
Okay, but I still know I still can't do it
There always has to be one over here. I screwed it up
It's an unused curve
Where?
Yeah up there
Yep, I had to go through that
Can't move the guys. You can't move green pieces
I can't pick up the green pieces
Stop prolonging it. Fine. I'll just let the water hit me in the face
Come on. I can do it
Come on
So don't retry don't don't do those sounds anymore though. I like doing those sounds i'm gonna keep doing them
I'm gonna keep doing those sounds. I like those sounds i'm gonna do them
All right, how about pizza with avengers do five minutes of cat puking sounds? That's probably I don't think people would want that
Okay
Let me try to do this. Well, let's do that when chat starts misbehaving
Let's make this clean
I'm not gonna go over anything stupid and drive the car
Stay in the middle. Watch out cares about the nitrous. So I almost got it. Sorry
This should be clean money. I want to play the montana max again
That game is so much fun
very much funny
Everyone doesn't even know what counter steering is
Um
Uh, what do you mean? I guess I don't
Big turn i'm coming up
I stayed with it pretty good
Oh, I feel like i'm riding on a giant dragon's back and it's trying to get me off
Watch cars
Go watch cars, man
Careful. Oh
That's too bad
jeez
Stay right in the middle. Come on. Hurry up. It's right there
Get it. There's no way I could have got it. There was a car in every lane
My god
Okay, good
Give me that money
Man, no more heroes two sucks
Why?
It's a hundred thousand dollars pretty much to do this. I didn't complete this one last time. I'm gonna I have to go for completion
I'm gonna try my hardest
Jesus
It's no joke
Too many too many fucking cars
Oh just complete it. It's just like the rosie on the other side of the fucking road
It's like almost like don't even pick up the nitrous it just it's it's hard
Even when he's torn I like i'm not gonna fucking make it am I
Too slow
No, it's too fast
You have to pull as hard as you can to the other side
But if you're not in the right spot when road just rips in a direction, you're gonna get fucking crushed
All right, let's get this new thing
It's only two hundred fifty thousand. Fuck
Out the door. All right, how do I make fifty thousand dollars fast?
burger buy bitcoin
No, I didn't say how do I lose fifty dollars really fast? I said, how do I gain fifty dollars really fast?
You must have misheard me
Well done here you go that took a long time perfect
This is a minigame collection you could say that is yeah kind of
Can you match this pitch probably not i'm not even gonna attempt here you go
When is a well-done steak ever been delicious well
Never six thousand. All right, do it again
Need some more
I need some more money
Get them nice get the perfect
Bears are easy just put it on for three seconds. I better be right
How is the type of steak that you eat raw
uh
What's guys what's the appeal somebody tell me
What is the appeal of?
Actual no, i'm not talking about medium rare. I'm talking about
raw
Rare
What's the appeal?
Is there an appeal there?
Like what is it about it? Would you get blue? Would you guys eat a purple steak?
If the top and bottom was seared and inside was purple, would you eat it? Oh, yes, it'll melt in your mouth
I don't think I don't feel like it would
Is it grape flavored, I don't know why would it be grape flavored steak
And well done
It's a purple steak
Yeah
Steaks aren't purple on the inside ever
They could be like blue meat are you eating
Fucking world of warcraft, dear
No mess ups no screw ups all perfect look at that
Holy shit, that's that's forty six thousand dollars. The freshest steaks are green
um
In who's bill?
Is that enough money?
It's not enough money
I need to go
Suck up like a few bugs. Let me try a dodo steak. No, what the fuck that is
Does this motherfucker eat brown steaks?
I don't know why that's making me laugh so much but it is
Because
Brown
Does this motherfucker eat brown steaks and then um, what do they mean by that?
oh you mean like
Like dog like poo or something, right? Is that what you're saying?
Uh-huh. They mean well done
What? Is that what they meant?
Let's go
This reminds me of the uh ghostbusters game. Holy shit. That was horrible. That hurt me looking at that
Change the subject. What do you mean?
I have enough money, but I just want to keep going
Sending chat into the shadow realm
Watch it. Oh not again
gaming on toilet stream petition
You know how uncomfortable that would be
It's been almost five and a half hours. You want me to sit on the toilet for five and a half hours?
Look at that. I need that battery. Why are you guys such weirdos? Why do you want me to do that?
Answer me
Okay, I mean the super juice
He's gonna he's baiting me to go turn me turn off the stream turn off the console right now
All these streams would be improved if you were just sitting on the toilet one day
That was funny to have a face cam just turn on and i'm doing it. I i'm it's gonna happen
Have like a toilet flush
10 times
Because you wouldn't even have to get up to go to the bathroom. You could just piss right into the bowl
I wouldn't have to get up. I would just just mute my microphone and make sure that the camera's on
The camera
the peony
Buy it
All right
Let's go do
Has it really been five and a half hours? Damn. I'm just kind of
screamed by
Holy shit
Why is me having fun?
At oh, all right get new clothes
Hectonics
I don't want new clothes though. I like the clothes I have now
Because I just spend all my money
These threads suck. I don't have enough money for this
I'll take it
That's all I can afford
Can I get purple pants?
All right, that looks fun
He's the joker now
I'm sure there's been a version that looks just like this
All right ahead of you
All right ranking battle. Let's do this
Try our new weapon
And then after this i'm going to call the stream and i'll see you tomorrow do it again
Infiltrate the prison island slip past the tight security if you're seeing you're dead
Wait, do I am I accidentally doing this? I thought I said I was dead
Am I dead?
Don't think so
Yeah, i'm fine
Never been better
Uh, this is not the right
Please move the camera, please move the camera
Please
Who's aren't
This thing is slow
This is a heavy two-hander
Damn they don't let you hit people one time
One hit and they're dead
Wow, this thing's insane
Oh, yes time for a tiger
We kill everyone I think that's it. Oh no
Come here
Yeah
All right out of tiger mode
Okay, no more tiger mode. I need help. That's important
Why is it so hard for me to do that?
Yeah, full health good. Yes. Okay easy
Prison, okay
Come here i'm not a first time
It's so slow, but it's so good run. It's so much fun just to slash people this thing
Ooh, yes
A lot of health kill kill
Holy shit, I don't even know what's happening, but it seems to be working
shoot
Drop the floor I popped out of something
This thing is so crazy more what's happening now, holy shit
Did I win
You know needs a lot of fun. It really is
This thing's great. Wait
Take it out the crickets think so
But what about winrar president pain I gotta look at these cards
Winrar pain blastin berry
Whoa, yeah, I can do a charge shot of this too, right? Let's see what it looks like
It's pretty insane
It's got such a stupid range
Stupid drain
Nice
The else I cleaned the whole thing up
That's swinging wildly
in every direction
best item
You're a pain. What a joke
You're a pain
I'm gonna hit you with a nut. I'm gonna hit you with a nut. I forgot about that line. Yeah, that's not in here
Okay, it's time to save
Fight time
Big cheese pizza
No, save the game, please
Well, that's a bunch of gross noises. I didn't want to hear this game time 5 33
My streams in life are 5 35. Wow
I'm gonna sneeze like this is what I can do about it
I think I got it. This is what I can do about it. I don't
So the damsels in here, uh, I already don't like this chicks put out for their rescuers, right?
Right
You know, you're lucky I don't have a bondage kick
Acid spit
Damn what was I thinking? She's definitely not abroad. I'd want to hook up with don't say that handsome
Actually, you're just my type. What are you doing in there?
But no, thanks
You'd be even more dashing if you were riding and adding come closer to me
No, no, no, don't let it touch you. Don't let it touch you
Yeah, that's right a peony
Poison
What how do I get poison off?
Oh, no, okay. Uh, is there a run I could do?
Get away
This is just me what I look like when I play vr
Where's the antidote? All right
Stay away from the gas see enough
Don't touch the gas
Now that I get the peony this game just got way easier
What are you gonna do? I spent three hundred thousand dollars on this
I did mini games for like two hours
Look at the fruits of my labor
It's just bosses don't mean shit
All right, just go
She's dead did I really just kick the shit out of this lady with the peony?
All right. I'm gonna do a sloppy hit to win
Oh, sorry
Oh, did I bump you what are you doing? Don't come in the room to knock on the door before you come in the room
What the fuck you all right?
That's not good, I didn't even know their name chloe walsh that weapon is unbelievable
Gotcha i'm there
Nice
Dodge duck what the hell that was bullshit
Okay, now I got the best weapon in the game. I spent the money. I did I did the work and I spent the money
the new mini games
Um, I love these games so much fun. Here comes a scorpion mini game. Is that real? I'll take care of the cat
Don't worry. Don't build things up. Just tell me already
Gotcha don't listen to me bought this sword with his inheritance
How's it getting a 300 000 inheritance?
buy
a beam katana replica
Watch the anime we already did
All right cat
16.3 pounds
Let's go
Yeah, get it
That was huge
Got more, uh leap 0.3 pounds. Okay, do some stretching
And breaking the spine i'm not breaking anybody's spine real life
14 can I look at them? Okay
All right now it's time for a massage
I don't think i'm gonna break any records, but i'll do okay. Yes. This is my speaking voice now
Cat is paralyzed with fear
close
Rigor mortis is setting in
Stop come here
One more come here
Get it. Yeah
All right 13.9 pounds
I eat the highest quality food
Here we go. Look at how fat you were when we first started
All right, do we get any new mini games? That's all I need to I I just only care about that right now
Yes
Stings so good is now available
I just want to see and then we'll come back tomorrow. This is the absolute worst one was the worst one
It's the worst in the first game too. Hey
Wait a minute
three two one
What
What is this bullshit? It's it's if not a mini game. It's a
This sucks. This is intentional. That was a blue scorpion. Is that worth more?
We're the scorpions
Okay, i'm fine couldn't you sprint pick pick it up
Oh my god kick him up
Uh-oh
I can't use more than once
But we saw this one. Um, I will never be playing. I won't be playing this one ever again
Cool. All right one more out of the gym. See you tomorrow. I hate you with all of my hatred
Let's see tomorrow
the worst game
Oh
I don't have any but we'll have to pick this up tomorrow
All right
I'll see you guys tomorrow for more no more heroes 2
And keep playing it. I think it's a lot of fun
It's very quality
This puts us right exactly at about the five to six hour mark, which is exactly what I thought was going to happen
And that's good
I'm ready better play more. We'll play tomorrow
Thanks for joining me. Hope you had fun. I did
We'll see you tomorrow
Those of you sticking around will the bits hang out to the subs?
Uh, i'm gonna keep this song on why not
Uh lm man, thanks for the 250
If you're not gonna play sam and mac season three, can you at least play strong bad's cool game for attractive people?
For the wallace and grommet grand adventures. They both made by telltale
No, i'm not really into the
home star runner thing
And I don't it just doesn't do it for me
um
But wallace and grommet though
Got me interested
You do have me interested in wallace and grommet, of course
Probably very easy
designed for children
So maybe i'll try it
Hey gnarly, thanks for the 250
Speaking of games you haven't played yet that you intend to
You're still gonna stream chrono trigger
Yes
Just not immediately
Not right now
There are a couple of sequels that we have to get through there are a couple games that I really need to beat and be
Done with this is one of them
I've been putting this one off for months
I'm happy to play it
One game at a time and then resident evil 3 is after this
So i've got a i've got quite a backlog
Let's see. What was the thing? Oh tiny and tiny toad adventures. Uh, my summer sports
Another one that has to happen immediately
Yeah, hey smelly boy. Thanks for the 250. What do you think is the worst chat? We hate this game
What is what do you think is the worst chat? We hate this game saying veto or next
Also, please bring back next
Uh, it would depth next is way worse because I created that that's my own fault
Veto is just hey, i'm gonna veto this. Oh, you're gonna veto that next was like a joke
that
I created that monster with the fucking ipad string
That's where it came from so I would say next that emote existed for less than 30 days
And I was no no
A whimsical moose. Thanks for the 250. I have been waiting for this for three months
I'm really excited for three
And i'm 99 sure that travis will be in smash. I believe that as well
I think travis will be one of the dlc characters
I'm pretty sure that'll happen
Followed by the three stooges as one character
What if they did the three stooges?
And it was the first three characters
It was moe curly then larry for one two and three in the fighter's pass. Can you refund the fighter's pass?
Fighter four is hey yoda 985. Thanks for the 250 donate today. I would not thank you
May the fourth be with you padawan elbertson ps
Your star wars pajamas
Be wearing you must
Thank you
Thank you freak out for the five dollars. Don't forget about the secret boss germa. I got the secret boss
There's a detailed description of where to get that boss
And then they list a bunch of songs
Okay, thanks for the five dollars
Switch to the normal music why is this you freaking out?
Back to our star wars, this is not not good. You don't like it. What's wrong with it?
Okay
Better better more normal more relaxing
Freaking the fuck out
But thanks for the five bucks
Hey christmas 95. Thanks for the ten dollars thousand bits his brain
No his heart with a big heart
I'm just like they're replaced
I'm just like my brain is down here in the middle of the chest and my heart is up in the brain
And then it's way bigger up there
And then the brain is tiny. It's like the size of the heart
They flipped they're in the wrong places
No, and actually I don't mean that as my heart is so big it like replaces my brain
I i'm so
I'm I love everything and I want to make sure everyone I no no no i'm not talking about that
I'm just talking about think like just physically speaking. It's way larger
To my brain is
He's hippie germa
Dude my heart is so much bigger than my brain
God, it gets me in trouble sometimes
I care too much about stuff that would explain the tetris part
Hey, swiggity-swanky. Thanks for 250 nice. Happy penis meter for your weapon
Noodle is bad at gaming. Thanks for a thousand bits
Since we're quarantined. I haven't actually been buying anything. I have more money to dump on my favorite streamers
And on another note, this is giving me flashbacks to laughing my ass off in the bath
Hearing you read my sex dream message out loud on the new year's eve
No more heroes stream
Yeah
Yep. Thank you. Noodle is bad at gaming for the thousand bits ten dollars
Sticks renegade. Thanks for 250 best pizza is cheese and the toppings are pepperoni and cheddar cheese. Try it
Domino's eight dollar large pizza carryout seriously though eight dollar large is a steal
Especially since little caesar's is five to six dollars and it didn't even fresh
Well, what do you want me to tell you you want me to say i'm gonna you want to rebuttal that
I can't
I can't it's eight dollars for a large pizza. That's
What do you want me to say? Oh, that's not worth it. It probably is. Yeah, what am I gonna say? No
In some places it's like 16 17 bucks for a large. It's like 15 plus dollars for a large in a lot of places
Do I like domino's? No
Do I think domino's is gross?
Yeah, maybe kind of if I was presented with domino's and we said hey, I got domino's
I'd I'd be like, okay, this is fine. Now i'll lead it. What do I love? No, I don't love it
I don't hate it
I think it's good. Thanks for the thanks for the uh, thanks for the 250
It's fine. Yeah
Hey alum. Thanks for the five dollars. No message is five dollars
Leon x thanks for five dollars psycho streamer cooks his food using his own body heat in his mouth
No, I just I was in a thought project
Just a thought project man. I lost the
There it is
Uh pepper the doctor. Thanks for 10 bucks. I cannot stop watching this. What a legend you do realize this, right?
Thanks for all the entertainment. We really do appreciate it boss. Uh, it's it's this
It's me falling down in the chair. We saw this day of the day. It's me falling down in the chair
That was about to be that rap that's the part they're talking about
I don't remember doing any of these things. I remember that
How many times have I fallen out a window?
Is that pretty normal occurrence?
Thanks for the 10 bucks and then pepper the doctor again three more dollars
I almost forgot people at work are singing the wear rat song
I asked them how they knew the song apparently it's becoming a popular tiktok meme song. Like I said, it's fucking legendary
Yeah, I the rats are their own thing now
They've flown away. They've flown off
Some people know that it exists and they don't even know that
I exist which is fine. I'm that's fine with me. It's it's taken on it's its own thing now. It's
It's become its own
Little fun thing that people think is fun and cool and I like that that's i'm happy about that
So people show me hey, what do you think about this? This person put the rats here
This person said this about the rats this person did a rat song. It's like that's fucking cool
I'm happy that it's people using it and playing with and having fun with it. That makes me happy
Kim wants mcdonald's
Um, I don't I don't think we can do that
It's food
We have food in the fridge
All right, you guys realize something
If kim and I were up to our own vices
We would eat mcdonald's three times a week
I would eat mcdonald's two or three times a week
If it was like
I mean, I guess I could couldn't I I could
Do americans really?
Yeah, we love it. We love it
Kim and I get so excited going to mcdonald's you guys um, everyone. Oh, wow. I wonder what like expensive tastes the streamer has
Put I bet you he eats lobsters and getting and crab dips
No, no, we get excited
In the drive-thru to mcdonald's
That's what excites us. We don't wonder that well now you now you do
Nobody wonders that yes, they do somebody somebody does
I'm sure one of you did
One of you beamed that into my head
Expensive taste says the guy that loves steak. Um, so we didn't think this
Oh, yeah, all the evidence has kind of just been there, huh?
Whatever who cares it's I love mcdonald's
I love that place
Back when I was a kid like the play place you could play there. There was like all kinds of toys
You go in the ball pit and stuff and then the hamburgers were awesome and the chicken nuggets
But I don't do this anymore. I advise everybody call me a child. I don't go to the ball pit anymore
Oh god, i'm about to get fucking i'm about to get roasted right now
Bingo sunshine
Thanks for the 250 blaming cbd for making you misinterpret the position of the light blue block in the second image
It's like when teens give someone a joint
With just plain grass in it so that they'll pretend they're getting high, of course
As I was writing this you clarified that there is actually thc in the oil you're using so i'm the clown
I was certain that there wasn't going to be any mind using things today
Donald is beta fast food. That's unbelievable. Oh, come on. The big back is the best thing ever. Um
Now if you weren't here
I have been
uh
small dosing
Cbd with thc in it or to try to
Shut my nerve pain up
Osteochondritis is incredibly annoying
Seeing if it works seeing if it calms it down a little bit
He's baby dosing yeah, no, I don't want to i'm not looking to
I'm not gonna get messed up weed laughing my ass off. I guess he's micro dosing weed
Yeah, i'm just losing up a pain relief
I'm testing it to see if it helps her with pain relief
What's wrong with that?
Is it working? I can't tell you that it is or isn't because i've only
It's only been something i've been doing for a couple of days
so
I'm gonna see what small doses of this does every once in a while
See if it helps
We'll see
Smoke weed instead. I don't want that much
Ehc
I don't want that much
because what i'm doing right now is
Only a couple of milligrams
So I don't really want
You guys thought I had a problem with the children's puzzle today
I don't think I would be capable of live streaming. I mean like oh, yeah when gerber has a few drinks
Oh, yeah, he's drunk and he said he only he's look. Oh, look what he did. He look what he's saying
You know, look at the stream. It's fun
If I were to be like a higher so I don't want to do that. That would be fun. I
I'm, not sure that would work
I would forget I was streaming and sit here and just kind of I don't I wouldn't even talk to you guys
I'm, not sure I want to do that. Of course. He's a lightweight. He's five two
I don't want to take in a bunch of thc
Well, I don't want to be completely like screwed up
I'm doing it for a therapeutic measure not to
Talk about how big the solar system is
Although what we did that today we talked about aliens, right? What do we we did? What did we talk about today something weird?
We did that today. We did something weird today. What did I do?
Long story short, we'll see how it goes in a week
Find out a flat mc tragic. Thanks for the five dollars germa enter the sun
Sundaverse the pseudiverse
Enter the pseudiverse
You could replace half of the characters that suda comes up with with germa rumble characters
It's kind of his germa rumble
Uh, what do I want to make? Uh, a mutant man
There's a guy. There's a mutant
He's got horns coming out of his ass
All right. Perfect. Can you guys can we make that feel like that's kind of what he does
Yeah, hey robo fussing. Thanks for the 250 you changed after that week long cbd binge, bro
We never hang out anymore. You only come around asking for bits and now I find out that you spent five figures on some carnival
some help man
Bementing dregs. Thanks for 20 dollars 2 000 bits. I tried playing tf2 just had a curiosity recently
after a long absence
I had at least a thousand hours in the game prior and one guy was like
Have you played before?
When our team lost so basically the community is what I remember if you rejoin it
It will be like the chat dude. Have you played before?
No, that you said always say no
Don't get don't get defensive to that say no. This is my first time
because then that person
from then on out will
You've had that you're at the bottom there anything you do after that would be like, oh this guy's a fucking fast learner. Holy shit
He top frags. This is like a second game. Whoa, I respect this guy
And then 10 years later when they're the best man at your wedding you can tell them this story man
We were almost enemies. Thanks for the 20 bucks though. Hey ruined bloodline. Thanks for the five dollars germa
Please say something funny. I lost almost all my money investing in germa stocks and I need to make that money back
Please I beg you trading germa
germa comedy currency
Because I am not a comedy advisor. I am not somebody to tell you when you should and should
Should and should not laugh at a joke
I can't tell you those things you have to be in control of that and you are it's not nothing to do with me
all I can say is
Nothing, that's I've said what I needed to say. Thanks for the five dollars
Prating just be careful. There. It's a wild world out there
A soup gg. Thanks for the 250 germa. I enjoyed your diablo 2 playthrough
But I think it had the worst joke of the decade
And no one's brought it up yet. It made me physically cringe when I heard it. What are you talking about?
What is what's doing? What's so bad about this?
Turn around what are you getting to the person behind you spaghetti turn around mr. Spaghetti
This is the worst joke of the decade
What are you getting to the person behind you spaghetti turn around mr. Spaghetti?
Um, I don't know how new you are to the channel, but you're gonna have an issue every single day
What you have just linked me I believe happens 30 to 40 times
An hour on this stream. I don't know. I'm not sure you're gonna be
I'm not sure you're gonna want to
uh
How dare you?
Those are the only jokes he made that's not even true
I make equal parts
Say a name and a noise
Versus like let me tell you this
I'll give me some credit here. I deserve it. I deserve this credit
50 of the jokes are a name and a place a noun and a verb noun and a verb
Mr. Noun and a verb mr. Verb and a noun. Yeah, okay. Yeah, but the other half
Are carefully crafted scenarios and crafted comedy. Don't forget being bad at the game and ranting like an idiot
No ranting like a philosopher being bad at the game is not on purpose
Is it making me realize the germ is always high?
I
Know i'm not
All right, let's do the credits
Oh, that's right streamlabs was was done. I tried to uh do this before is streamlabs still dead
Dude streamlabs is still dead
I can't yeah, it's dead
I cannot roll the credits
Come on. Why can't I get on here? Wait, hold on. Is it working?
German gnome
Yeah, enough of you was saying it. Let's see it
Name the gnome that's not funny. Okay
You laughed at it left that a friendship over you laughed at friendship over
Done done
No more friend. That's it. I've had it up
No more
no
Show the clip. No you show the clip turn around. What are you getting? See the person behind you?
Spaghetti
What's what's wrong with that? I don't see a problem with this
Yeah, you can tell joel that the life-size
the life-size
Cardboard cutout that I have that I painted of him sculpture of him out of clay
That I just finished painting and it just came out of the it just I just baked it
I was gonna send it to him not anymore. So i'm gonna melt it down and turn it into a bunch of pencils
You can tell them go ahead y'all go ahead you can tell them i'm gonna say spaghetti sell to us instead
Why am I?
Okay
No, I saw I saw the clip. It was a funny clip
uh
Joel
I'll see you in Morrowind multiplayer
one-on-one pvp
Long swords only can you even do this? I turned the music off accidentally
long swords only
We'll find out
How much of a gnome I am?
We'll see
This dude can handle a long sword pretty well
Can you we'll find out on the stream that will never happen?
That means Joel and I have to
Do it and we'll see if that happens
Hey c4g, thanks for the 250. I miss animal crossing. Can you bring her back, please? I miss her so much
I miss animal crossing. Thank you, sir
Uh, no
Remember that if we're gonna do the bitch and i'm gonna fucking do play animal crossing that ended
Uh during the move when it's the only thing me and kim had to do
And then now it's done
played it twice
On stream. I played it twice
Off stream. I played it probably a couple dozen times
Hey control x thanks for the 420. Thanks for the stream
jerry
uh being a
Hema fencer who can't sword fight due to corona. It's refreshing to see some epic lightsaber on
action
Ernie, yeah, i'm excited for the 420 easy bake mouth oven micro dose lsd stream which is tomorrow
Cinco de mayo 2020 anyway spam this heart to make germa fart
420 easy bake mouth oven micro dose lsd stream
I feel like I want to have that
I want that to be the title of the stream
Will I get into trouble if I have that be the title?
I feel like somebody would be not happy about that
420 easy baked mouth oven micro dose lsd stream
I wonder i'm gonna run that by twitch to see if I could fucking have that
Probably not
Thanks for the uh four dollars and 20 cents. Thanks for like the best title of that stream
Oh, by the way, you'll be guys will be pleased to know
all the packets
I have
Probably 20 packets of different foods and items. None of them are expired
They're all good to go. They don't expire till 2021
Well, I can eat them
Can't wait. All right. Can I get this to work? Let's see. Will it work?
Do that credits. Oh
I was waiting
that's um
Doesn't seem correct
That's did one person sub
What is this?
Did anybody sub?
What are we what are we looking at here?
I'd sub
Well, I can read them
Thank you guys
What's going on with this thing tom along one
Metal something thanks for the subs
I can get them all
yordle tickle roll
Lars blood axe knight arthos tom along and metal something. Thanks for the subs
Five
I told you stream labs is fucked up. Hey, even if it was five
Still five people that decided to give me five dollars today
Or we'll pay five dollars
All right
Even if it was five
That's still a lot of people
We have few more bits to do
I don't know why that happened but stream labs is kind of messed up tonight for some reason
Uh nearshut thanks with a thousand bits. When is the resident evil four stream?
Roughly praise the mighty jera
uh
Um, let's see no more heroes two tomorrow if I don't finish no more heroes two tomorrow
And finish no more heroes two on wednesday
And then potentially after completing no more heroes two tiny tunes adventures
summer
Vacation and that stream and then thursday resident evil three
or if I
beat
The game tomorrow no more heroes two resident evil three on wednesday and then thursday is tiny tune adventures. Here we go
then monday
Uh, I want community community content. I on me the probably the middle of the week on from the 11th to the 13th somewhere like that
then
No community content. It's gonna be thursday, right? I remember this
um
So the 11 12, uh, let's let's say july 30th
I think there's enough time for me to read that. Oh, okay market
Yeah, that makes sense. Hey, yes xd. Thanks for the five dollars germ
I just want to say that there's nothing wrong with not wanting to play tf2
You've made content before for years
I totally understand if you feel like you've had enough of the game don't let chat get to you
I'm sure they're all just joking good work
No, I just don't I
I just I don't it's not like i'll never play the game for the rest of my life
I don't know. I typically would if they come up with something if there's a new update or if they said
New one or something else to talk about or do or then I would probably try it
Or just please say slash s
But I have don't don't have any intention to play it
I spent
A decade playing that game and it was it was the best game i've probably ever played
But you know, I don't it's just not something I really want to do
I don't know. You gotta pretty missed a frog coin. Nice
Hey bingo sunshine. Thanks for the 250. What are you fiddling with in the background? We can hear it
uh batteries
It's batteries. I always have batteries here for some reason
Uh mu means mu. Thanks for three dollars cardboard cutout made of clay. This streamer is really suited on a micro dose
This is like this is like seven hours ago now guys
You're referencing that you're referencing something that happened like potentially almost a whole day ago like eight hours ago
nearly a year ago
And finally, I will see you guys tomorrow
for more normal heroes, too
The blast is always
C4g. Thanks for the 250. I miss
animalated crossing, please
Let me get an island tour, sir. Let me see the animals one more time
I miss the funny cow and phoebe and the other one the monkey that one
They'll they visit your game, too
Mu means mu. Thanks for three dollars. I found you mentioning the tf2 sync of the mile stream
I was only able to rip the audio. Unfortunately, okay
Hey guys
It's me derma 95
I'm gonna play tf2 on sync of the mile
coffee to your chicken
damn, well when you
When you show that to me, that's
I guess I did say those are all things that I would have said
eating
Incredibly close to the microphone, too
I must have had a setting wrong. It got my webcam mic
I guess i'll have to fucking just lie and not do it
Hey king of acorns. Thanks for five dollars derma
I was the one guy who recommended you build the gamer birdhouse and still can't believe you actually did it laughing my fucking ass off
Does that thing get any use or did it get thrown away? I'm so curious. No, that's gone
That's gone. Nobody wanted that fucking thing
That was hideous
I hit it with a hammer fucking recycled it
Whatever whatever happened to it
It was sentimental value there
Remember you should build a sand castle on stream
That sounds like a really fun idea
uh
I live in las vegas
There's no such thing
as a beach here
so
There's plenty of sand
But not enough sand to make a sand castle because it's not the right kind of wet sand
How would I would I build a sand castle in with sand but i'd have to wet the sand and have to I would have to drench
Five acres with water
bring water
Use water dumbass just use water bring a water truck rent a water truck
Buy beach sand online use a garden hose
He's landlocked omega low
Yes, so it was like fucking it's 70 percent of every country on earth
What do you mean? Oh, he's landlocked omega lull
Why is that so funny? Oh my god. All right gooberry juice. Thanks for three dollars
Hey bad advice giver nine eight five
I got an update for you on my whole bird problem
And well, uh, my sprinklers broke and wouldn't turn off
They were on for like 20 minutes and by the time I found out my entire yard was ruined
Oh, my scarecrow was out there too. He's fucking dead
More updates coming soon
What the hell are you doing back here
What what why are you like the jokey infomercial person that has everything horrible happen to them in black and white when they're trying to
Put a bird house up or put or make soil in their yard
It's dead
Oh, no
No
It can't be
Holy shit. He's dead
I don't even want to look at that anymore. That's
Dude's dead
Thanks for the three dollars. Uh, wish you luck
Hey johnny nice mountain. Thanks for the three dollars, uh, legosi documentary coming out soon. Maybe check it out
He recently passed away. So they shot the film in honor of his memory
I don't even know if that's fake or not
All right. I'll see you tomorrow
Get some sleep back before no more heroes 2 tomorrow
See you soon. Take care
And there's a reddit link here. What's this reddit link?
City is an empty glass words to I don't know what that is
All right. Good night guys. Goodbye