Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with a Battlefield 3 gameplay commentary, and this is going to be a live gameplay commentary.
Just wanted to give you guys an introduction, because it's been quite a long time since my last Battlefield 3 video.
Playing with BooMan61, who you'll be able to tell his voice the second he chimes in here in the live comp.
But I think he was flying the jet around, so he was having a grand old time.
I think we're playing on Firestorm, and the game mode is Rush, which I've become very, very accustomed to.
I love Rush. I love Conquest too, but they're both very, very good in their different ways.
But this brings me to the next thing I want to talk about. I want to try getting back into Battlefield.
Now, I don't know how much I'm going to upload it, I'm not sure what I'm going to do for videos, but maybe one or two a month I want to try and get into that kind of a flow where you get some content every month.
But I've got to get better at this game, and I've got guys like Boo, Shibby, I've played with Pwn before, as my mentors.
So I've learned a little bit, and I think I'm getting a little better.
But we shall see where I go from there, so definitely let me know, whether it's from a rating or from a comment.
Let me know what you want to see, if you like this, if you want to see more Battlefield.
I would love to know, because I love hearing from you guys.
So yeah, hopefully you enjoy the live commentary. It's going to kick in right now, and I'll see you guys all next time.
So take care, everybody.
I'm making a run for it. Oh my God, maybe not. Come on, somebody show up.
Where are all these dudes? Oh, I see a guy right there. I wonder if I can hit this guy from this far away. Hit him. I didn't kill him.
All kinds of crazy scaffolding on Firestone, first base. That's what I mean, this first base gets a little tedious if they don't attack you very well.
I'm jabbing that tank. Oh, he smoked it. Shit. They planted. Where are they? Where are they at?
Yes, it's right underneath you. That guy dead? Yeah, I killed a couple of them. Nice, nice.
Stay alive, stay alive. Oh, disarm it. We've got to get it. I got it. Hell yeah.
Straight ahead. Tank, take that tank boy out. I got faith in you. You've done some damage. Was it you?
No, I didn't shoot one thing. There's a guy coming from the right. Yeah, there's a guy coming from the left side of the truck.
Unless he died? Yeah, he's died. Got straight away right here, straight to the right. Boink. I just boinked him.
Boink. That was the worst boink ever. Is there something going on over there? I probably shouldn't be standing up here.
I'm assuming this is not the best idea, but I'm going to do it anyways. I'm going to balance beam right now. I'm in the Olympics.
Should I spawn on you? I'm pushing pretty far forward. That's risky. I'll take that as an absolutely.
Okay then. I got us guys all. Yeah, I see the guy right around this corner. Two of them.
Got him. There's guys in the pipes running along. Guy down right there. Tank. Tank is dead and guy in the pipe is dead.
Nice, nice, nice, nice. I love this semi for you. Oh, beautiful. To the left. Lot of dudes. I'm turning. I'm running this way.
Holy shit, I just took a sniper shot. Can you throw some health though? Yeah. Oh, no man. I got it right here.
Thanks. Are they all coming from over here? Yeah. I see this one guy straight ahead. Oh my god. Oh my god. There's like an army coming right now.
This is why you'd like to have a sniper rifle. And there's a helicopter or something coming out of the way.
Oh yeah. If I had a sniper rifle right here. See right now this guy probably has one. Yeah, that guy probably has one.
Question is, did we make the wraparound? Can we do it, you think? Oh, what was that? That was my javelin. Probably a bit of overkill.
I just used it to kill this tiny little robot thing that takes three bullets to die, but it's so pesky to hit. Oh my. Wow.
I just got like. Oh, it was the tank. It was the tank, I see. Tank, be honest. I don't even know where he is. Get out of my face.
I just held out. That guy just saved my life. Run, run, run, run, run. I need help.
Alright, I'm going to plant right here for a second or two. Looking for some. Is he on the. Where is that guy? Is he up here? What the hell? Where is this guy?
He must be right here. Is he up top? I am so confused. Yeah, he's right here. What's that? That's F. F is knife.
I'm just sitting. What the hell? Okay, I killed him with a knife, but it was like face stabbing somebody like the spy.
Like just like I'm the chaos stabbing someone. Yeah, they're the funniest ones. You just like put your hand on their chest.
I didn't even do the animation. I was just like one, two, three. Oh, right. You just like slashed him? Oh, God.
I just slashed that guy to death. Oh dear. Oh God, they planted both the charges. Holy shit.
Yeah, there's a tank. I'm dead for sure. For sure. There's a tank right here. Oh my God. Maybe he won't see us.
Well, maybe. Whatever. Did they plant it, you said? Yeah, we defused. Got my first ever magnum.