Oh, I see you. There you are. I see you next to the, you near the helicopter.
No. Oh, I see Lee. Okay. Okay. Well,
you didn't expect somebody to break through the fucking glass, did you?
I did. I saw you. Oh, where's the checkpoint? Checkpoint. I don't know.
This is confusing. Are we going to do a one V one now? Yeah. Checkpoint.
I've won. I'm in the lead. That's not what happened. No, no. What,
what did happen? Oh, there is another person here. Well, whatever. Wait, wait,
wait, wait. Don't shoot me. Don't shoot me. That's you.
I'm going to jump in that window.
I almost got it. Oh no. Oh no. I'm okay. Just go. Just go.
Just go. Just jump. Just go. Just jump. Just go. Hi.
You're missing me. You cannot hit me with those punches.
I got you.
It's like falling. That was so stupid.
I am at the helicopter right now. Hey, here I come.
Double action slide. How do I get out of here? Oh, are you stuck in there forever?
Here. Just watch, watch, watch a master. Do it. Watch a master.
What did you, what happened to you? Come to me. Come to me. Come to me.
Please come to me. All right.
So you're going to break through this glass and we're going to start the fight.
Okay. Okay. I'm just going to come down on you.
He's going to break through the glass.
Are you ready? Right through the glass. Do it. Right through the glass.
Why didn't you break through the glass? You messed up the stunt action movie.
All right. So, so get in there. I can get in there. Can you,
I don't know if you really can. You've like, okay, you didn't get in.
You didn't make it in, but, uh, I'll take it.
So now I'm going to break through. So I'm going to go like this. All right.
Action movie. You know, why did you not do the action movie?
I didn't want to get blown up. You threw a grenade in. Oh, hi.
All right. I want to get the action movie clip. Okay. Oh, he's getting away.
He's out of his mind. He's getting away. Action.
Okay. I want to get the action movie clip now.
Fuck off. It's a brawler.
It's rocking. I want to get the action movie clip. Get in there. Okay.
What is the action? What are we trying? I'm doing the action movie.
This is my movie. I'm the director. I'm the producer. Okay.
No, you can make it. It's supposed to be part of the movie.
Honey, I've got your favorite breakfast material here.
It's pop tarts. Oh, pop tarts.
I want them too. Ooh, that was stylish. I got, Oh, what's this?
Slow motion. I better hide from you.
He's coming after you. He's really is. Why did he spawn right here?
Cause this is where.
No, these corners right here is like the majority of the spawns.
We're just all spawning on top of each other.
You think you're going to be able to mess with the walker?
You're not a walker. You have to be certified to be a walker.
You can fuck with the walker. Dead. Where are you hiding?
It's not hiding. I'm running around doing the checkpoints.
That's not very stylish of you to do. Oh, good grenade. Good night woman.
That wasn't even close to that. I seriously was not even close to that.
No, when you see that, you're going to see that. You're going to be like,
wow, I can't believe that actually. Oh, wow. That's interesting.
Yeah. Go fuck yourself.
I can only imagine that I must've looked like a rocket.
You really were like jet propelled in my face.
Uh, the noise you made too.
Is this thing reloaded?
How could I not have hit you by now?
Did I get you in the head? Probably.
Where is this guy? He's up there. No, that's you again.
I'm not going to mess around this time. Who's slow mode?
Him. He came in behind us. Can I slow mo his slow mo?
You can slow mo his slow mo if you slow mo. We're stuck in slow mo.
Shit. Just come meet me at the secret hole.
I'm coming to meet you at the secret hole.
I'm down near the secret hole in the secret,
in the secrets of the lost temple of doom. Hey, what's up? That wasn't even you.
That wasn't even you. And I, I, I'm,
I waited for him to do that. Are you serious? Yeah.
I just watched him coming down the hallway.
I probably scared the shit out of that guy though.
Cause I think he knows we are both secret hole and cause he kind of saw me go
down there. Does he know about the secret hole?
Well, he doesn't know about the fact that I'm behind. Oh,
he jumped at the same exact time. He still doesn't know I'm behind him.
He doesn't know anything about the secret hole. Come look for me.
Come look for me in the secret hole.
Oh, he came and looked for me and it was perfect cause he has slow motion.
Grenade. You're just throwing grenades down the hole. Yeah.
You are a fucking dick. Secret hole.
Meet me maybe in the secret hole and you have to come down.
You have to come down the actual secret hole.
You can't like do like the sneaky secret hole part seriously.
Why would I think you were going to do anything else?
Why would I ever think you were going to do anything else?