Like, seriously. My guy right now looks like a rubber mask. He looks like he's wearing a Halloween mask.
Who's that guy? It's a big fat guy.
What? I d- I d-
Well, no, no, no, I just- I dropped in the water. You're telling me that, like, I- what am I, made out of cinder blocks?
And I just sank to the bottom of the ocean?
That wasn't that far of a jump.
I feel like I've jumped in water way higher than that, and it was totally fine.
Are you- are you shitting me right now?
No, no, no, you just sank to the bottom. Your character weighs 15,000 pounds.
What the fuck is wrong with me?
Alright, now I- now I'm like a shredder.
I just turned into a shredder from Ninja Turtles.
This is the awesome best game I've ever made.
Praise the sun, by the way. Are you ready?
Apparently- I guess something's happening up here.
Bright spot ahead. Look out. Be wary of gorgeous view.
Okay, alright.
Light ahead.
Hurrah for gorgeous view, but be wary of hope.
Are these fortune cookies?
I'm gonna keep doing what I'm doing, and I'm gonna get the kill.
Okay, one of your cronies is behind me now.
This is not good.
Now I got two of you assholes to deal with.
You're gonna fuck this up for me.
Holy hell.
This is taking- it's taking so long.
Welcome to Dark Souls 2.
The hardest game ever.
Bang. See you later.
See you later. Where's my money?
Where's my cash?
Night sword. I got a night sword.
I did it.
I completed it. I killed the boss.
And here's the boss song.
No, no, don't die. I can't die here.
I seriously cannot die here.
How do I climb down?
I was singing the fucking boss song.
Don't freak out. Don't freak out.
Don't freak out.
Okay. Chill.
Chill.
My brain.
This is my shield?
This is the shield I just put on?
This isn't gonna block a sword?
This is not gonna block a sword.
Are you fucking serious?
It's just a little baby shield.
Screw you.
My baby shield is better than your giant sword.
Walk onto him, you dingus.
Yeah.
You don't get a baby shield protecting your ass.
Baby shield.
What an unbelievable item.
Seriously.
You think you could fuck with the baby shield?
You know, I could make the joke right now.
I really could do it.
And I think I'm going to.
I've been saying I look like the shredder this whole time.
Well, this is legit a fat ninja turtle.
We're about to see the epic showdown
between huge fat Michelangelo
who really let himself go eating too many pizzas with pepperoni.
And, holy god,
he almost just insta-killed me.
Hopefully he doesn't do that.
Well, this is an interesting fight.
Kind of like who falls off first.
Can I push him off?
Are you seriously kidding me right now?
Let's see how you died.
That's a pretty big sword.
Of course he did.
Of course that's how he died.
I feel for these people.
What was that guy doing though?
What was that guy...
Is this seriously how like all people die in this game?
I mean, I've done it a bunch of times too.
I've done it a bunch of times too.
Like, this is how everybody dies.
Monsters don't kill you in Dark Souls.
You just walk off cliffs.
Got the fire arrows.
His like butthole face cannot scare me.
You think you're going to scare me with your butthole face?
Oh, geez.
What is he doing?
I didn't get hit.
How did I not get hit? What a miracle.
Watch out. Don't let him stop on you.
Good. We're in good shape.
Through the legs.
You goddamn giant.
Not that bad. Not that bad.
We're okay. We're okay.
Of course when he does like the stupid super jump backwards
that's not okay.
Fuck me.
Drink the goddamn apple juice.
Drink the apple juice.
Don't let him do it again.
Yeah.
One more hit. One more hit.
I am
the Dark Souls 2
master.
The last giant and the soldier key.
You can thank this grandma
faced fuck for saving the day.
Alright, this is going to say
uh, up?
Up?
My message to the world at this
boss is up?
He's like yeah, yeah, let's go. Come on, man.
This guy's name is like a swear
I think. Alright, well whatever.
Let's go. Enter the mist.
Alright, let's go.
He's coming for me. He's coming for me. He's doing his
thing. He missed.
What the hell? You throwing like spears
at him? This guy like killed him instantly.
Dude, this guy
he shot me
with those. He probably
thinks I'm such an idiot.
He
just like unloaded on
me.