Oh, hey, how are you? How's it going? How have you been? It's been a little while since we've
last seen each other's faces. I'm here. Good. Well, relatively good. Relatively good. Did I,
did I just send a tweet and like reply to somebody? I hope not. Did I in my speed reply to somebody's,
like on my timeline to say that I was streaming? That'd be so fucked up. Ah, we're good.
Yes. Hello. You haven't seen me in over a week. There's a few reasons for that.
One, if you didn't catch the streamer awards, I was there. It was a really good time. I got to meet
and network Andy with a bunch of people. Some people that I have already met and already knew,
but some people I'd never met before and that was the first time I've ever really
said hello. It was a very, very good time. This is the guy that won two awards. Yeah, I, I get,
hey, you know what? I guess so. I guess that, I guess I am, I am that person, aren't I?
It's time to flex a little, okay? 2022, no more like humble. No, I'm, I'm putting on a fucking
muscle shirt and I'm flexing now. See what I'm talking about? I'm not, I'm not ready. I'm not
ready yet. Hold on. No, in all seriousness, I, there's a really, really tough category in both
categories. I, it was a really great time. It was really fun to be there. Anybody could have won
those two categories. Seriously. And they're all cool people. I've met pretty much all of them
besides the ones that weren't there. You need to explain Peppa Pig. They handed out coloring books
so I started coloring. I didn't bring a Peppa Pig coloring book to the streamer awards. They
handed them out. Why am I good at public speaking? I don't, I don't know. Okay. You want to know how
to actually public speak. You just have to pretend that everybody in the audience is your friend
and they're all there to let, you're just hanging out with your friends. That's one of the best ways
to do it. You just literally pretend that everybody in the audience is like, oh yeah, I'm talking to
like, I'm talking to Burger Boy. Yeah, he's just, it's all Burger Boys. It's just, it's just a
audience full of Burger Boy, which I would definitely not recommend. I would definitely,
I would probably not attend that event. I would, I would hope that event would be like streamed so
I could watch from a distance. I would not want to go to that event. But no, honest to God, I don't
know. I don't think I'm really that good at public speaking. Just have something that you think you
really want to say and just say it and be, and confidently say the things that you want to say,
I guess. I was kind of nervous. It was, it's kind of nerve wracking, you know, going up there and
it's just a sea of people that you know are, these people are, there's a lot of people in
this audience right now and a lot of them are like big streamers and people from the press.
It's like, I don't want to like, I don't want to have like a booger come out of my nose and go into
my mouth in the middle of that like speech because then that's it. The second that astray booger goes
out into mouth and I go, it's like, okay, I gotta, it's time to quit. So like every time before you,
before public speaking is, I mean, maybe I'm a weirdo. Like I always like make sure there's
nothing in my nose. I always make sure my teeth, my like teeth are okay. There's no like, there's
no like boogers in my nose because I don't know, it's possible. Even if it's a 0.01% chance,
that will be your legacy. Eating a booger accidentally on camera during a speech.
You're taking notes. What? No, I'm just fucking kidding. I'm like, God, relax. Thick nose,
Andy. I do that before coming on here too. You guys don't think that I make sure that I look
clean? Anyways, I've been so, so ready to play Elden Ring. You have no idea. I'm gonna tell you
just how accurate that statement is. Um, so I've been, last week I've had digestive problems.
Those of you that don't know, I got diagnosed with like colitis and then proctitis and they thought
it was Crohn's originally, right? Like I've, I've had IBD bullshit for the last like 15, 20 years
almost. Uh, I, I got a flare up. I don't know why. Sometimes every, maybe once every like,
maybe once twice a year it ends up happening. Stomach. Well, it's not really stomach. I don't
want to pretend like it's a stomach thing. Uh, I have problems with my digestive track. So, um,
how long are we going tonight? As long as I can without needing to run away. Uh, I think I should
be good. If I need to take a break somewhere in a few hours, uh, see I'll do what kind of like we
did last time, which is actually a pretty good idea. Uh, but I have also in the meantime,
because if you see where we are right now, I have not moved on this character.
I've probably played through Limgrave like eight times because I just want to play so bad. I've
seen, I have seen every last detail of Limgrave. Everyone. I could tell you if you open a book,
have you opened up just a naked map of Limgrave? Nothing there. I could tell you where every
grace is. I could tell you where every dungeon is. I could tell you where every, wherever every NPC
is. I just want to play so bad. So I was like, I don't want to see too much though, but uh,
I guess I'll make a new character and go through Limgrave again. And it's like, Jesus, man,
I'm just glad to see something that's not like the tree sentinel. You know what I mean? You need
to prove it. I don't have to prove anything. No, cause then like I'll miss something and people
will be mad. All right. Anyways, here's what we're doing. You remember this guy, baby rattle?
It's, it's the, it's, you need to play with me strong. I'm not going to play with me strong.
No, no audio. Fuck. There you go. How come the characters are furry? The characters.
No, it's a stick of furry statue mask. Fine. I'll give you that.
You promised me strong. I did not promise anything.
We laughed about a scenario where, because me strong is supposed to be just a naked guy with
a club. And I want to try to just put every single point in strength and get the huge club
and just be a caveman running around. And everyone was like, oh, that's really funny. And it's like,
well, what if you were inebriated? I guess that makes it funnier that I'm just this guy with no
health and like 80 strength and try to kill the bosses in like four hits and die. Like a fucking
caveman just running around. That's like the thing that people need to be concerned about.
Oh, tarnished. It's just a naked guy with a club. All right. Hit the thing. Me mad. Yeah.
All right. So I have to remember kind of what, what I did last. And what I remember is I remember
I was in a, I was, I was, I was in a state of a little bit of delirious.
I remember you guys were like, it was like hour number 12 or something. And I was exhausted. And
I couldn't, I couldn't even like read and you guys are like, oh, keep going, keep going. And I was
like, all right, fine. I'll keep going. And I killed a boss. And then I, it was like, no,
keep running up the tree. And I like ran up the tree and I killed another boss. Well, I didn't.
The mimic tier did. Then they nerfed it. So that's not happening anymore. Ludwig wants to play
Fortnite with you. We're doing a thing in a week or so. Hey, you want, you want to see my games
that I might be picking for this little event? I wonder what I might be. I'm wait, is Ludwig picking
Fortnite? That's not one of the games Ludwig is doing, right? It's not Fortnite. Oh God. Okay.
Well, I got, I got a few picks myself. Okay. So I, that'll be interesting though. All right. I need
to figure out it's, it's been a while. Okay. So my entire experience so far, the last like nine days
has been this area and maybe like a little bit of here, but I, I kind of like have a ton of time
that I like, my hard drive got overwritten because I just, all I know is Limgrave.
Everything else got deleted. So I believe the last thing that I did, I killed Morgoth and then I like
turned the stream off. So let's just, let me just, let me just go here, right? Yeah. I couldn't get
into the urn tree. And then that lady sat down and she was like, Oh, we can get in there eventually.
I guess if you go here, right? Oh, wait, no, no, no. It was marked. Okay. So this is where I need to
go, but is that where I'm going to go? This is a Limgrave expert. I would say so, but this is where
I have to go. But is that where necessarily I'm going? What is this? The rolled route. I'm going
to be very honest. There was a bunch of shit in this Capitol that I did not see and I really want
to see it. I'm level 98. Oh, I'm almost, do I have any crunchies? Oh shit. I have this. Oh, wait,
I did just like fucking turn the stream off. Didn't I? I did. I didn't even go back to the,
to the round table. Okay. Go explore the Capitol. Yeah, I was going to go do that first.
This is also going to be a long one. And I'll tell you why, because I'm not sure if I'm going
to be able to scream tomorrow. The idea was to stream tomorrow, do like more Elden Ring,
because I'm an Elden Ring streamer. It's the only thing I play. So, you know, you go to the
volcano. Okay. So I might, we might do a super stream today, at least like eight to 10 hours.
I want to play Elden Ring. You know what I mean? Like I don't, I am, my body is going to have to
backseat here. I want to play Elden Ring and I want to play it on stream. So if I have to diarrhea,
PMI. How did I just say that? It's been like nine days since I've streamed. I forgot. Like,
I can't say everything on stream. I forgot. Like sometimes I forget that like there's a camera on
me and there's like a bunch of people here. But you know what I mean? Like if I have to go and
get like a drink, if I have to like go like take a quick PRB, then I, then maybe I will, whatever.
Who cares? I'm going to be fine. What did he just say? It's you. Pay me any mind. It's not him.
Just lay out your arms. Oh shit. Oh, we got something to talk about here. They buffed the
fuck out of Sorcery. Sorcery got a massive buff. Almost every spell. So if you don't know,
Patch 1.03 came out. They nerfed a few things. By the way, this, this is not one of the things
that they nerfed. I saw a lot of people that were very upset about this. Where is it? Where is it?
Come on. I know everyone's going to revile back when they see it on screen. They didn't nerf the
Moonveil. The Moonveil is still great, isn't it? They did nerf the Mimic tier and a few other things,
right? A few other like combos, spell combos or whatever. But Sorcery got a big buff. Almost
every spell got its mana reduced and some of its damage increased. So maybe we have to lean into
Sorcery. They nerfed, wait, the Moonveil got a stealth nerf. Really? Really? What is it? What's
the stealth nerf? All right, let's, let's get into this. I don't want to overwhelm myself with a
bunch of like bullshit. Like I just, I'm using the baby rattle. I, I, I'm almost a plus 10 baby
rattle, which is max. I'm here for, whoa, that was a weird. All right. I'm definitely, we're
going to have to get the boys up because I definitely utilize them a little more.
Okay. Because if the Mimic tier is not going to be a thing anymore, if this got nerfed,
which I put all of my shit into, and it's not that good anymore, then we're going to have,
we got a pivot here. We're going to have to get the boys up. The Mimic tier is still good.
Well, it's a different currency, so it's fine. All right. So what's new? Oh yeah. This guy over
here. Oh yeah. That guy died. Sombra Miner's Bell Bearing. When did I get this? Oh, I can buy
somber smithing stones up to four. That's a big deal. And I can buy this, uh, gloveboard as well.
Very cool. All right. Let's, let's just go. Let's just go. Let's go. Mimic's still good.
Pleased to know that Radan was nerfed. What did they do to Radan? Oh, talk to the finger reader.
Yeah. Why did he look like he had his head hanging out of a car window in the wind? I don't know, dude.
Okay.
The urge tree has spurned you.
They went into standby mode?
No matter for me, but you. How will you ever manage to wait?
You know what I never understand about these grand overarching video games and stuff? It's always
the most powerful deities, the most powerful beings, the most intelligent
god sage-like beings apparently don't fucking know that there's a door in front of the urge tree.
How can you fuck that? How do you fuck that up so badly? This all-knowing entity that
converses with the greater will doesn't know that there, there is a thing in front of the urge tree.
You think that you would have known that already like 10,000 years ago.
Oh, what a turn of events. I can't believe you can't get through the front door.
Let me spend 10,000 years up here trying to figure out how to get you in the front door.
I want to burn the, oh, that's right. This didn't, she sat down, right? And she's like,
oh, I want to burn the tree or something. It's been a while. That's his magical sword.
Regal Omen Barn. That's it. Int and Faith. I... Int and Faith. B for both?
This sword is arcane and dex. I can't use it. I need an int. It's a CSGO knife. Yeah,
this is a usable item, but is it, how is it any good? I'm not getting the good scaling,
right? Because I don't have any faith. CSGO knife. I don't know. I don't think all the usable items
that are, I feel like they have some utility, but it's more of a look at this cool, okay.
This is the kind of item that you do PVP with and you just use it to be different. And people go,
whoa, wow, you're using, that's a cool thing to use. I mean, I'm going to R1 you four times
and you're dead, but that was cool what you did there. That was a nice, I know, but I haven't
seen anybody use that yet. So I, I'm just going to get the runes. This is really cool though.
This makes me want to make a like dex arcane character. I do that. Stop shitting on me.
I do it too. I'm just saying that we know what we're doing. I want to burn the impenetrable
thorn. Burn the tree. That's so fucking weird.
Would be unthinkable. This thing's just like stuck in standby mode. So why didn't you guys
figure this out before I got here? I've been walking around the whole world and not trying
to help you. I don't know who's good and who's evil in these games. Wait, we're talking,
of course, this would be a toilet flush like in the background and then the fingers start moving.
I'm back from my 10,000 years of conversion with the greater will.
Okay. How do I burn it? You're a dog barking in the background, like a zoom call.
Okay. What am I? Like there are like 30 endings in this game. Okay. I couldn't get in the front
door. Fingers are pissed about it and I'm going to burn the tree down. I guess. So we're going to
crush that thing. Interesting though. Okay. How many souls am I going to get for this? 100,000.
30. That guy was not very strong apparently. All right. Well, how's my character look?
Maybe more into mind endurance. I got 50 intelligence, 25 decks, 40 vigor.
I don't know. Endurance maybe. Maybe some more mana. I have 15 endurance omega low. Yeah. Yeah.
I mean, yeah, that's pretty bad. That's like really bad. Yeah. I mean, that's like really bad.
Okay. I am ready to move. I'm in a position where I think I'm good. I'm ready to move. All right.
That took a little longer, but I needed to kind of figure out what the hell was going on and where
I was. And when, I mean, the last time I played it was like 10 days ago, unless you're talking
about limb grave. All right. I remember here, here, there was a place to go down and there
was a big dragon hand. And I remember saying to you guys, I want to do that when I come back.
Here we are. All right. Let me head down here. I think this is where I need to be. No. Where is it?
I got to get this stuff burnt back into memory of like where I am. Is it not this one? Oh,
this is right. Is it right? I thought it was. Oh my God. I thought that was a fucking enemy.
I was like, why does I have to fight that thing? Uh, I think I'm gonna go down and see.
It's really hard to navigate the Capitol. Um, I thought I kind of knew what I was doing,
but it's just been a while. I'll check down here. Oh shit. Wait. Okay. Hold on. I see an item over
there. Okay. I got, I got wicked bad glare on my screen right now. It's fucking me up.
These guys suck. This is the best item. Everyone that we were talking a lot of shit about the
baby rattle, but it's very good. Are the awards on the shelf? They are not. I actually,
actually forgot them, but it's okay. You know, the Jake is on the case. I'm going to get them.
I know I, they, I had them and had them and then two or three cocktails later. I didn't.
Oh, that's right. I climbed up this shit. All right. Easy, easy, easy. So if I go,
can I go down from here? And is this the right way? I don't think so. What about the other side?
Is this where I wanted to go? This is, it has to be right. I think that's where I needed to go.
Yeah. Cause there was a big arm on the ground and it was like cool looking. Okay. Let's go.
I got this fucking glare on the screen. Is he supposed to be hiding? What the fuck? Should I
go down here? All right. I'm going down here. We're fighting this thing. I got this,
I got this glare that I got to take care of. Give me one second. It's a, it's a goal. This
room is glaring. I think that's, that's better. Yeah. Uh, there we go. Address losing the awards.
I didn't lose them. They just were put in a box and then I left the box and I forgot to take
the box. So we're good. We're good. Community Jake is on the case and he has confirmed that
I got him. We're good. We're good. We're fine. All right. Um, let's go. I fuck it. I'm going down.
Wait, you don't come down. Oh, that's not what I would. That's not what I anticipated.
We're fine. Fine. You do melt them down. I wouldn't want to melt them down. They're
not made out of a material that would be safe to do that. I feel like I wouldn't want to breathe
the air in the room that I did that in. All right. Where's he at? Can he fire up here?
He can fire up here. All right. Whatever. Stop. Oh, they made comet better. I don't know why it
sounded like that. It sounded like a weird like talk show host, like a radio host. Why am I doing
it like this by the way? Just go down there and fucking attack him. Go. I don't even man up.
All right. That was so simple. I don't know why I made that way too complicated.
All right. So there's nothing down here. Maybe that block. He's blocking the path.
I don't know. Intriguing. Are you going to use the guide for the remaining quests?
No, I don't think so. Look, this game, this game is so unbelievably ridiculous that playing through
the game again, look, I have like four characters that are ready to get out of limb grip. Um, so
playing the game another two or three times and experiencing more stuff, I kind of want to leave
it. I kind of want to leave it. I'd like to experience more stuff with other characters.
Okay. So that's, I can't go there, but let's try over here. So people that are saying, oh dude,
you're going to go back and do like every single secret boss and secret thing and you're going to
go clear out. Probably not. No, I don't think so. I think that's fun to be able to experience it.
Um, again, with another character and just do different stuff that I didn't do.
That's good. He hates Elden ring. I can go up here. I, there are noises coming from over here.
I get to, wait, was I was already down here, wasn't I? Wasn't I already down here? There's
like a, one of those killers, the Omen killer people were here. Are you going to do a retch
playthrough? Uh, I don't know. Retch playthroughs are awesome, but you end up like hating the game
in the first hour or two. And every time I've ever tried to do retch or whatever they call it
in the other games, I go, oh, this is awesome. And I get started base level 10 with everything.
That's perfect. And then I get, I start playing the game and I get killed in like two hits by
something or I can't hurt something. And I go, this is stupid. Why did I ever do this? Like,
what a dumb thing to do. Just pick one of the normal characters and I like flip out.
I didn't go down here. Isn't me strong a retch? Yeah, but that was only because I had to do me
strong as a retch because they start with the club. That's a different scenario. All right,
let's go this way. Retch is enjoyable in this game. Is it? I don't think so. Fuck you.
Poison bone dot. How come you don't know how to put a suit on? I know how to put. All right. First
of all, I, okay. I know how to put it. I don't know. I know how to put a suit on. I just don't
wear them that often and hate these enemies. I have not had a reason to put a suit on in a long
time. Don't you understand? What? Why did that happen? No, no. Oh my God. I fucking,
I actually hate this enemy. I'm out of fucking juice. Riding the guys in this hallway is so bad,
by the way. You can't go anywhere. And I need my lantern or like starlight or something. I can't,
I can't see anything. Yeah. I don't know. You, you hold on. Skin's coming out of my mouth.
I still haven't done anything with those either. No. Okay. Did I get the lantern? I feel like I
didn't buy it. And every time I don't buy it, you guys remind me to buy it. And I go,
nah, it's all right, dude. I got fucking starlight and, and then I don't put it on.
And I'm just walking around in darkness. What's your favorite lunchable? The original,
I believe was ham, cheese and crackers. That's it. None of this. I don't, there's all this new
bullshit. Oh, like pizza in like a fucking tube or whatever the hell it is. No, excuse me. Ham,
cheese or turkey and cheese. The little circles, nothing else. Please don't give me any of that.
Oh, like tacos. What the fuck are you talking about? That's zoomer food. I mean, it's food
for kids. I don't know if it's necessarily zoomer food. Zoomer food. I mean, I ate that when I was
young and I'm not a zoomer. All right. I gotta get back there. What the fuck? Oh, I am so strong.
Although I'm probably going to, that confidence is probably going to disappear very soon.
Oh, this is where he was. All right. So what, is there anything else down here?
What else is down here? You're outleveled for this area. Yeah. But I did a lot of
exploring early in the game. That's fine though. I don't care. Level 98, 99. All right. How do I
get that? How do I get that item? Oh shit. Okay. So I don't think I can do anything else down here.
I'm just going to go up unless, did I build this? Yeah, I did. No, I didn't. Okay.
My thoughts on the game so far? It's, I, I don't need, I don't really don't even know what to say
anymore. It's not like nothing compares. Have you guys found it like funny? Okay. You know,
isn't there like still like 400 plus thousand concurrent players playing this game right now?
I think like everybody's just been sort of waiting for a game like this for like a fucking decade.
Even Dark Souls three, right? Was like good. It was cool. That was fucking fun, but
Sekiro was good. It was fun. It was challenging. It was hard. I mean, I, I don't know. I feel like
I haven't played a game like this in a decade. Guilty hood? First hood to cloak of olive brown.
It doesn't really do anything. What does it look like? That's cool. I mean, I need, I want the,
what's the intelligence, right? Uh, I mean, the, the issue I think is that so many people have
been waiting for, I think what a lot of people can say, let me, let me say, I think, let me say,
I think like 10 times more times in a row. So open world games have become sort of a form you,
form your Lamatic thing, right? I think this made the open world concept a lot cooler because
it's sort of, it's not the way that normal open world games play. You kind of just have to go
explore. You have to go figure it out on your own. And something about that is, is so overwhelming,
but so welcoming at the same time, because nobody is telling me where I have to go. And it's like
terrifying because you'll accidentally walk into some places you might not, maybe it shouldn't be.
And it's this horrifying, but equally like interesting experience where you kind of did
that to yourself. Even if you, it's not that different. Sorry. Sorry. I thought you, I thought
you, I thought that we were on Reddit. I thought you replied to me on Reddit. I'm all right. I'm
okay. I did this. I remember this Reddit brain, but it, it, okay. It's not that different,
but everything feels like it's in its place. Okay. Everything feels like it was hand placed,
like everything does from the starter area to the later areas, to walking around, everything feels
hand placed, handmade, like this was crafted in a fucking clay and everyone's saying breath of the
wild. I haven't played breath of the wild yet. So let me experience that and I'll give you my,
no, because then people are going to be pissed. All right. That was not, did I fucking miss
anything down here? I think I cleared it. Play it, play it, play it. But what if I play breath of
the wild and I stream it and I'm sitting there as Mr. Streamer mode, trying to desperately say,
fuck, I don't like this. And then I'm going to have to be like, it's okay. It's pretty good.
I like it. And then they're going to go, he's lying. He hates it. And then I'm going to like,
stop playing it in two days and I'm going to lose 50,000 fucking do it. That's what I'm scared of.
Um, I probably would actually really like it. What's this? Do I have this? Oh shit. Is this
down or up? Do I have this? Oh fuck. It's just literally this. It's just, I could have climbed
up there with my fingernails. Why do you think you'll hate it so much? I know I don't think,
I really don't think I will. I think I would probably love it a lot. All right. Um, I need
to get to that area with the arm. I gotta go. It's been so, it's been too long. I gotta,
I don't remember. I gotta go like that. Where's the dragon? Dragon has like an arm on the ground,
but it has to be this way. It has to be up in that area over there by the boss, right? This
dragon has an arm that's on the ground. I don't know where it is. Let me go over here. Let me go
backwards from here. It's just like, I can't remember. Where are you trying to go? I'm trying,
there was a place like kind of down the bottom where the dra- like a big long dragon arm is on
the ground. And I remember looking down there and thinking it was important. I feel like it's out
here. Like this way, maybe? What'd you find? Top, top, top, what? Okay. I remember running,
yep. I ran by this. Go down the well. There's a site of grace near the main road. You need to
go down the well. Okay. Hold on. Let me, let me go backwards from here. Cause I, you know,
the reason why I didn't put this into memory at all is because I actually just sprinted
through this whole area to fight the two bosses. I like deliriously tired. So I think I just need
to go backwards and just play from here. There's a well under the dragon. Oh shit. All right.
How'd I get that? Sons out, guns out. That's right. Okay. I fought Godfrey in this room.
I remember that. And this went around here. Let me go down this way. Cause all these dead
um, finger ladies, don't listen to them about the well they're trolling you. I mean, I, I, I,
I'll find it. Holy grease. Okay. Times six. Jesus. Okay. Now from here, how do I go down from here?
This is smoke. Grace in here. What's out here? Ah, this is where the roots go. And this is how
I went up the first time. Yeah. Okay. I remember this. That led all the way up there. So let me
rock down here. Did I play the demon souls remake? No. Cause getting a PlayStation five
is impossible. So no, I, I unfortunately have not played it. I have, I have absolutely no idea how
good it is. I'd love to maybe experience it one day. All right. I think I'm close. I just don't
want to miss anything. Super important, right? I get up there. Oh my God. What have I done?
What happened? What? They, who killed him? Oh, this move is so good. This move is so good.
This baby rattle is fucking unbelievable. It really is. I got the damage on it, the scaling.
Oh, I, oh, wait, have I been here? Didn't I, did I kill that? I didn't. All right. So this is new.
This is new. This is new info. All right. I got new info. I haven't been here yet.
Let me fight this. Please show. No. Oh, the seeds over there. All right. Nice. This is why I didn't
want to just run. I didn't want to just disappear from here. Is it aggro everybody? I had to get
rid of these guys quick. Get out of here. Jump your fucking party horns up. Jesus Christ. Stupid
idiot. Is he healing? Why do I feel like he's healing? I hit him with a 1500. Gargoyles halberd,
C and E scaling. Oh, bronze halberd wielded by valiant gargoyle. Just like the wielder,
the missing parts have been mended with the corp, with corpse wax, a patchwork of champions.
Spin. Is that that? I don't think that's, is that unique? I don't think that's a unique move.
This is the guy that growled at Chad and turned purple. Yes, it is. I fucking can't believe that's
got to be one of the, I don't even know what to say about that. All right. I definitely have not
been here, so we're just going to keep going whatever way we're going here. There it is. There
it is right there, right? Is that what I was looking for? That's definitely, yep, that's
definitely what I was looking for. I don't even know what category you put that in, but that was
the worst of something. That was the worst something. I don't know why, but it was bad.
It was very bad. Do you ever need another move? I don't think so. This, this thing almost got
voted off the island too. Yep. This is absolutely where I want to be. This is exactly what I was
looking for. Does that need to go down there? There's the hand. All right. Yeah. I didn't go
over there though. That was survivor reference. Where'd he go? Nine golden rune. Pretty sick.
So do we, do we celebrate getting to level 100? Cause that's going to happen in probably like
10 to 20 minutes. I kicked that guy's ass by the way. Like that, I fired, I kicked that, that
garbill's ass. Can we be, you see like those perfect dodges? Let me jump over his sword and
shit. I don't, I don't, I don't think I saw an appraise for that one. I looked over and I
saw like a couple of pogs, but like I didn't see like a wave of them. I thought that was quite
impressive. All right. Yeah. I remember, no, I sprinted through here too. It's such a fucking
blur. This is the round table hold, right? And I sprinted through here and I was like, wow,
what is this? This is a round table. And you guys are like, go to bed, go to bed. And I was like,
no, I don't need to go to bed. I'm just going to keep running. I, I, yeah, this is round table
hold. This is the round table hold. So let me explore this a little bit more than just
running through it and picking up random items by my sword. Are we like all dead or something?
Cause this is where the lady sits. Are we dead? Like, and this is, we've been dead in the real
world or something. Cause this is the round table hold and there's a bunch of dead people here.
Nobody's alive in here. Yeah. Fucking what the heck we're going to find our body.
Aren't we? Our body is going to be lying on the fucking ground and the music is going to
kick up. The violin is going to kick in hard and it's going to be a fucking item on me.
It's going to be a single rune fragment. So what the hell, what's okay. So what is actually
going on here? Why this has got like kind of Hunter's dream vibes to it. Is that the guy?
It's a different area. But yeah, but how we're going to find that guy and he's going to be like,
charnished seems you found the truth. See seed bed curse. I need one more of those.
First grown on a body defiled by the dung eater, tenderpox afflicted with omen horns.
The dung eater cultivates the seed bed curse on corpses. By doing so, he prevents dead souls
returning to the herd tree, leaving them forever cursed. One of the most loathsome things found in
all of the lands between. I know, I know where that is. Oh no, damn it. Come on.
All right. So I've, I'm very curious about something, but I don't want to teleport yet,
but I, let me just look through this fully completely. Yeah. Where's the, uh, where's
the Smith usually anything else here? No, not in here. Okay. He's so high. I'm not, I'm fine.
Wait, I don't want to miss anything. I know I'm walking around and sit. Okay. This is where the
Smith usually is. Hmm. This is not usually open. Okay. All right. All right. Outside. What about
the finger lady room? Yeah. I don't want to, you know, there's no, there's no rushing through Elden
ring. This is like the best game to come out in the last 60 fucking years. Okay. You understand
how sad you're going to be if you rush through this and then like 20 years from now, you're
going to be like, God, I wish I, I wish I'd slowed down. I wish I had slowed down and, you know,
enjoyed life more and paid more attention to the Southern side of Limgrave. I feel like I
didn't explore it completely. Chat was really odd. My case about hurrying through the game.
Oh, grandpa, it's okay. No, it's not. This is closed. It's not what's in here. All right. That's
what, all right. That's where the, that's where the fingers are. Let me guess. Coded sword. What is
that? And how badly do I want to look at it? Hey, fuck. Okay. What? Oh my God. This is cool.
It only, it starts at B faith scaling, by the way, nothing else in sword. Once granted to the
tarnished of the round table by the two fingers, a formless cipher comprises its blade, which does
holy damage. No shield can repel. Champions would gather at the round table hold and days long past
when the two fingers were masters of operation, their flesh yet full of vigor. And it has the
unblockable blade spell. Holy shit. Thanks for the bug wing from software. Why is a faith gets all
the faith gets all the cool shit. Okay. Like really? That's so fucking awesome. Bro. It literally
gets everything in this game. Not the cool stuff. It gets everything except the cool things.
Look at how cool that is. That's cooler than the bug wing. I know what that's like such like a straw
man, right? Like, oh yeah. Like we get the bug wing. It's like, you also get the baby rattle.
I guarantee you there's people that have like 50 points in faith that saw this item and they went
fucking God damn it. Faith sucks. You mean to tell me I could have a solar system flail
that does a crazy magic damage and these end fucking pieces of shit get the best stuff in
the game. All right. So I think I got everything. That's cool. That's an amazing item. I want to,
I don't want to go that way because I'm scared to go that way. I want to go out where the
arm was. What is the scale with this scales with int at decks and at strength, but not really.
All right, let's go. That was cool. This is cool. All right. Now that I spent the first
hour walking around in a circle and just talking, uh, if we can actually do some progress here,
which I count that fucking gargoyle. This progress. All right, let me get out of here.
Zero on fire here somewhere. I feel like they probably is. I have to go back and I want to
talk to that guy down the hall. I always, I always get like stuck in the round table hold already.
All right. You know, I'm just jumping over the balcony. I came in here. I remember this,
but did I explore in here? I don't think so. Not fully up yawning. There is. All right. Thank
goodness. What? I didn't, I already had it. Think not. I shall see to that. I ask of you
is to make the journey to the snowy mountain tops of the giants far above the clouds.
So you can burn the urge for you to commit a cardinal sin, but it must be done to reach the
path. Do I have to do that though? Is the path I wish to travel. Well, uh, you, you wish to travel
that way, but what if I wish to travel a different way? I think we might be at ends here because like,
Oh, this is what I want. This is what I, what about, and what about what I want? How about this?
All right. I'll burn the Erd tree, but I want you to give me 50 faith right now, right now.
Give it to me. We both get what we want. Maidenless. I'm not maidenless. Look. Okay.
So now I know where I need to go. So let's do this. This is, what's this bonfire called?
The round table hold two or something, fortified manner, first floor. Okay. Let's go see what's
going on here because I have a feeling he's by the usk people, which is okay. This is where that was.
So let's see what he has to say.
All your flesh trapped in the sewer jail below the Capitol and kill you
and defile your corpse. Then the pox will truly be your own. What is the key?
What if he, what if he kills me? I have to be careful because what if he kills me? Do I,
do I like, does it fuck a bunch of stuff up? Unlock sewer jail door said to lie beneath
Lindell, the Royal Capitol. So that's down in the sewer. Okay. Oh, okay. This guy's at.
There's a well under the dragon's wing.
I'm going to kick his ass.
Yeah, we'll see. Oh, you talk a lot of shit from behind that fucking computer screen. Don't you?
Mm hmm. Sure. Oh, you talk a lot of shit. I'm about to see you in fucking real life.
This guy's a literal shit eater. Oh, this is the, uh, desperate Roger.
Yeah. He's a, he's a very close friend.
He's a very close friend.
This is like one of my best friends.
I went to his wedding. I was in his wedding. So, hey, okay. Fuck. You got anything else to say?
No, I was in the wedding party. I look blown out right now. I think the light's too bright.
What the fuck is going on with this guy? Is this two people? That's his right arm
and his left arm is there. That's another person's arm. Oh, wait, it's, wait, is this one of those
costumes that you can get at the party store where it's like, oh, look, I'm riding on a dinosaur.
And it's like, my legs are the, are the dinosaur's legs. And like, I'm, I'm like inflatable legs are
riding the horse or whatever. Are you sure? This looks like it's two people. Wait, why,
why is it going like this? If this was just armor, why, why are you going like this? Why are you
covering the face of the armor? That's his right arm is holding that. That's somebody else going
like this. No, you guys got it all wrong. This is two people. This is actually two people.
Does he have four arms? That's arm one. His, that shoulder is arm. Oh, wait, is that shoulder fake?
Is the armor like posed like this? So then why is he holding underneath? No, you guys got,
this is two people. I can't, I can't wait till this guy stands up and like, in like another 12 hours
and he has like four fucking blades, like general grievous style. And the other, the other head
starts talking. Thank you. All right. So let me, I guess go to the sewer. That's interesting. Let's
do that right now. So underneath the sewer and he's in a cell. Apparently this is under the dragon's
wing. I'm not done exploring yet. Hold on. See exactly. This is why you can't just, this is,
I'm telling you, this is once in a generation. Am I going to get to walk up those stairs
and get that item for the first time? Those NPCs are friendly and you triple jump. You cannot,
you can double jump on the horse. I don't know how to get it. Oh, what is it? It's just, it's
all right. It's, it's not purple or legendary. Those guys had dialogue. We didn't hear it.
All right. I'm going to say the area that I wanted to go was this way, right? That way. Yes.
Progress. It's fucking cool, man. There it is. There it is. There it is. There it is. Finally.
I found it. I found it. It's pretty fucking cool. I have to do better than that. Lightning is like
one. You don't do it when he puts it up. It's a second after it's like, boom, dodge, boom, dodge.
I have, that was 50,000 souls. I don't want to lose those. And let's also be able to be a magician
here. It's the guy that beat dark souls three on stream. I actually replaced that with secure
because less people did that, right? We have to like move it up. So less people beat the last
boss in secure. Oh, then beat the last boss in dark souls three. We're going to use that from now
on. You know what? Yep. First, that's going to take a lot longer. You don't come over here.
Oh, that hurts a lot. Please don't kill me. Please don't kill me. Don't do lightning. Don't
do that. Don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't. Damn it. Stop fucking shooting me with a bow and
arrow for a second. These guys don't get any hit recovery Diablo two reference, but you know what
I mean? They're like, what was that? Okay. Jeez. Ooh, that was so loud. And I'm so glad that my
eye have a noise gate because holy shit. All right, dude, you know what? I've got, I've got
some items. This is ridiculous. Okay. I need to craft some items. I'm going to make some of these,
I think. All right. Some of these scale anything scale with intelligence doesn't look like it
arcane. All right. I'm just going to make, I can make 11 of these. I'm just going to make
11 fire things. Um, I don't, I guess I'm going to make, um, some of these sure. I'm going to make
this impede healing actually kind of cool. That's kind of cool. I think for invasions,
I heard it. I didn't hear anything. Fire bombs alleviates blood loss. Okay. I'm going to make
some of these alleviates frost. Look, just make shit. What's the point of keeping it forever?
Just make stuff. It's the first time I've been this long in the crafting menu and almost a
hundred hours in the game. Okay. All right. I think I've made some stuff. Okay. So now let's
over here. Now the items here. So creepy. This is it right here. Yep. It's going to be right here.
How would you build that? All right. What's going on? Apples stone.
This is not it. Oh, wait. It's not it, man. It's not it. Fam. I feel like I can get up there,
but wait, I make that good. Very good. So this is not it. Is this not as under? So it's under the
other wing. I did want to come check this out though. Anything else I can do? I could go up
there next game. No, I'm an Elden ring streamer. I've solidified my place as Elden ring content
creator. Yeah. I'm not a smite streamer anymore. I'm an Elden ring streamer. All right. Well,
this is not it, but I kind of feel like I can get up here. Maybe. What about over here? No,
it doesn't look like it. All right. Well, I'll go the other way. What about Mario golf? Yeah,
I did play Mario golf for about two or three hours. It was fine. It was fine. It was fine.
Okay. Those of you that want to get like a big hot take from Mr. German to tell us about how much he
gave Mario golf for seven. It was fine. It was fun. It was interesting. The game was fun.
I haven't watched you in 10 years. Who is the TF2 content? Um, there's 10 years worth of it
on video on demand right now. Did you guys understand that like you have the amount of
content for every season of Seinfeld and every season of friends and every season of game of
Thrones as team fortress to video content. Just go, go to the, go to the, my Netflix fucking page,
whatever. Go to my YouTube page. It's like, there's like, there's like 700 days of TF2 videos.
Probably way less than that, but you, you, you understand. Okay. So let me go over this way now.
Not net. No, I'm not, uh, don't get me in trouble. I just said like, it was like a Netflix esque
platform of YouTube content, video on demand. All right. I'm going that way.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. I'm going this way. This is new. Oh, fuck. Oh, yeah. Oh shit. That's two.
Fuck your timings. Fucking what? Where can you even fall there? That's, I don't even understand
where you fall there. Oh, God damn it. Am I seriously here? Whatever. Well, you just, yeah,
I don't get it. I need to look at that. Is the baseball stream definitely happening in March?
No, the baseball stream I can tell you right now is 100% confirmed to be the next stream that is
like an event stream, which I mean, I really wanted it to be in March, but it's a lot of moving parts
and trying to get all those moving parts to work. It's a lot of people to have to get together,
but I will stop at nothing. That's for him to happen over the next few months.
Okay, let's get this guy. So when did I fall down? I didn't even know this. Okay. I like knew this.
I thought there was a railing. Where did I even fall? I thought, okay, that was weird. I thought
this was like a railing. I almost did it again. Oh, dude. Fucking dungeon down here. Oh, yeah,
this is fucking dungeon down here. Am I, is this safe? Oh, yeah, absolutely. Absolutely. This is
definitely something down here. Wish I could get on the horse. I saw an item and I freaked out and
I was like, I need to go get it. All right. So where does this go? Nice. I actually really need
these. Oh shit. What's over there? I need to, I want to just keep that marked because this like
somebody lying down over there is an invisible bridge. If this is a lie, I'm turning my stream
off. Do I? Infirm it. Otherwise it's going off. All right. Well, I can't go that way. That was
cool. I just like this. All right, let's go back up. I want to go into this Coliseum. There are no
invisible bridges. From Software did it once and everybody thought it was the worst thing they've
ever made. So they were like, we should probably not do that again. Actually, no, this is the
right way. I remember playing that area in Dark Souls 3. It was in Dark Souls 2. I remember. It's
like the weird crystal area. And I did say out loud, this is the worst thing that they've ever
made. Didn't I? I say that all the time though. Does that not hold any more weight at all? Because
I keep saying that it just holds no weight. This is the worst thing I think that they've made.
All right. Well, you've said that like 15 times. Do you even like this game? Do you even like these
fucking games? This is probably the worst fucking area they've ever made. This is the worst boss.
I think they've ever made. Jeremy, there are only two other areas that are in the game.
Yeah, whatever. Talking in third person. He's a fucking ego weirdo. All right, pay attention.
Eat shit. So good when you get it. That was a little cocky allegory. Oh, what do you got?
Duelist helm. A duelist helm. What is that? Bronze helm decorated with innumerable snakes
worn by gladiators who were driven from the Coliseum. The wearer becomes a slightly easier
target for foes. What? You have a bigger hitbox with this on? The snake is viewed as a traitor
to the urn tree. And the audience delighted in seeing these bronze effigies beaten and battered.
Snake, tree. Is there an apple in this game? There are apples? Put it on. I mean, I look like
a weirdo. I don't have to have a bigger hitbox for his mind. Ooh, what am I wearing right now?
Okay, it's too intellect. Do I give a shit about intellect still? Because I have so much of it. I
have like 60 something. Does armor even do anything in the game? Um, you know, it's funny. I've played
every single From Software game essentially since like 2010 or whatever. I still don't know what
armor does. I just know it has blue numbers and red numbers and the blue number is better, I guess.
I still don't even know what it does. It's just one number is 12 and the other number is like
8. So I guess that's, it reduces it by 8%. Is that 5.8% physical damage negation?
No. So you understand how I don't get it then. Like a 5.8. Those numbers on the right are even
more confusing. Anyways, let's go. Nobody else is here, right? It's just this guy. All right,
let's go. Ready? Oh, that day definitely made that better. Without a doubt. Oh, fuck you got me.
Shit. Watch out. Watch out. Watch out. Watch out. Watch out. Watch out. Watch out. I got this in the
bag. Just fucking don't do an idiot move. Choke slam off the top rope. Battle hammer. All right,
cool. That's, I know. Do I even need to look at it? Because I'm not going to use it.
Ladditorial combat used by duelists who were exiled from the Colosseum. Why are they all
getting kicked out of the Colosseum? These guys have all been booted from the Colosseum. What,
what'd you do? Why? They drank, they chugged mid duel. Ritual shield talisman. They got kicked
out of like the PvP. Raises defense when HP is at maximum. Okay. I feel like that's kind of hard to
do though in this game. Being at 100% HP, especially in a boss fight or in mid fight, is really hard
to be there. Maximum, right? Like see, you're always kind of hanging out around here. That
helps reduce a one-shot kill. Yeah, but you have to be at full max health. All right, cool. So I'm
imagining there's something scary in there. Is there a bonfire I can get over something?
There's gotta be like a bonfire right here, right? Go in there. Seems wild. Dude, can I? No,
I definitely could. I thought I could make that jump. No, you cannot. Wild. That's crazy. Nuts.
That's reminds me of like when a game company puts like a YouTuber or like a streamer's quote
on their like Steam store page or something. German985 says, wild. Oh, craziest game. I think
okay. Dude, that was intense. That doesn't mean they didn't say the game was good.
Oh, German985 says, oh, that encounter was intense. He later went on to give the game a three out of
ten. They don't say that part. Ooh, what's going on here? This is free fucking free soul, baby.
I'm so sad. I took his shoes. That's like so fucked up. That's so fucked up. Look at the gear
I have right now. Okay, my outfit is probably worth like 50 to 60 thousand dollars and like
I'm going to take this guy's shoes is like just regular like Skechers or something. What? Like,
do I need this? I have like 150 thousand dollars worth of stuff on me right now.
Why would I need to take that guy's just sneakers? Why would I need to take his
like little loafers? That's so that's so awful. Yeah, I might need these later.
There's tons of items up here. Star fist. Oh, I got one of these too. Is this what I got?
Oh, it's a faith thing. Okay, that's bloodlust. Yeah, it's a it's spiked hands. I gotta see these.
Oh, I got under a sea creature. That's cool. All right, those are actually really cool.
Strength. Really? I would think would be um, well, I guess it makes sense.
So many fucking items. Okay, that's cool. You can be Meta Knight. You can become Knuckles.
All right, it's time to fight whatever's in here because there's absolutely somebody in here.
There's no way you have a huge Coliseum and but there's no bonfire which I'm concerned about.
And then we're going to the dragon. We're going to the sewer. No bonfire. Is there a statue at
least? I don't think so. Maybe there's a statue. I guess I could come down from there, right?
Wait, hold that thought. Can I go up there? Lindell is so I am just so overwhelmed. Like I
keep seeing other I keep getting halfway to my destination and stopping going the other way.
This is okay. This is okay. That's the sanctuary so I can come out there and go this way. All right.
Let's open this door. ADHD. That but I mean, to be honest, this is like one of the most
so many ways to go you could just walk in a direction and then there's like five ways to go.
And you might go one direction and then give up halfway through because you see something more
interesting that's a mile behind you and then you don't ever get anything done. It's remarkable
that I've gotten here so far because I just I'll always go halfway and then something else gets my
attention and I just go the other way. Here we go. Really? Where were we going? We're going
underneath the wing right of the dragon. Okay, let's go. I want to go over there. Shit. I want
to go over this so bad. All right, we're going to the wing. Let me check and see if there's anything
else I didn't get here. So that I should probably just go like this, right? Because if I need to go
to the wing and it's under here, the wing would be out this way, right? Do you see the wall? You
have to hit like 35 times. Yeah, I heard about it. I think that's a bug. I don't think that's
actually supposed to be in the video game. All right. That's where I need to go, right? I'm
really far away from this fucking thing. That's a bug. So I'm way too far away. I need to go
like over here. Yeah, I'll go closer. I think I have to go under the wing and then I need to go
way further in here. All right, here we go. I gotta go there. Under which wing? Under the big wing
there? Like over there? Under here? All right, let's go. Wasn't I already over here? I was already
over here. Is it right here? Oh, it's right here. All right. Okay, let's do it. I found it. Oh,
fuck. I don't open this. This is the- I gotta use the key here. Is there something to- I- but what
if I get killed? What if he kills me? He said he was gonna- he said he was gonna like do weird- he
was gonna do something horrible to me. There's definitely a bonfire down here. Hopefully that's
not- I fucking need starlight or just buy the lantern. It's like a hundred runes.
Oh my god, I need it. I didn't- I never bought the lantern. I didn't buy the binoculars either.
Okay, I gotta come back. Gotta buy a fucking lantern. Do I have a torch?
How do I not even have the torch? How do I not have any of these items?
There'll be a bonfire down here, right? And I can just put on starlight. Oh, fuck. I don't
open that. Get the lantern. Okay. But there might be a bonfire down here. I can just put
starlight on and it's easy. I'm gonna terrify- it's so dark down here. Okay, that's not the cell.
All right. Subterranean shunning grounds? What? Oh lord. Is there a bonfire down here? That has to
be. All right, I gotta be careful. I'm gonna be a total dickhead here. Dude. Boy. Nice damage. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm not looking to- I'm looking to win. All right. One, two, three. Oh my god, there's so
many. It's just a regular enemy. I'm so fucked. I hear- I hear, uh, sprinkles. All right, let's go.
One at a time, I should be all right. Don't go this way! No backstab! Oh! What the fuck? Jesus,
these guys are fucking crazy. There's only one more. I just gotta kill one more.
Minus two joke? What? What'd I do? What'd I say? I didn't even say anything. I didn't do anything.
Oh, I've never been so relieved. Okay, I can level up. Do I get endurance to 20? Is it level 100?
You had dead air? I am dodging for my life here, okay? I'm sorry that I'm not, like,
iframe, iframe, iframe, dodge, attack, dodge. Sorry, I went to Dunkin' Donuts today. No,
I'm fucking concentrating. I can't just, like, tell you about the Dunkin' Donuts drive-through
story. Not when I'm doing that. All right, I need- okay, so let me tell you. I was on an airplane
recently. I would get hit every- I would- I can't speak when I play these games. I'm doing endurance.
I feel like it's gonna really bite me in the ass if I don't. Now, let's take one second. Okay,
this is- thank god. Underground roadside. This- this motherfucker has the lantern in the first
10 minutes of the game, right? No, just buy the binoculars, too. Who cares? I don't have any of
this stuff. Who has it? It's in Lunera, okay. All right, talk to that guy. All right, wait, where is
it? I'm so glad they put the NPCs on the map. You don't have him on your map. You know what?
Fucking don't care. All right, I'm- whatever, I don't care. I don't care. Here's what we're gonna
do. I'm gonna use my spells because I'm a fucking wizard, okay? I haven't used- okay, I treat spells
in this game the same way that I treat apps on my iPad. If I haven't opened them in over two weeks,
I delete them. It doesn't matter what was on them. So, I have not used eternal darkness in
two in-game days. Two in-game weeks. It's getting deleted. I'm obviously not going to use it ever
again. So, where's starlight? Buy a torch, you one percenter. What do you mean? Why are you saying
that? Why are you saying that? One- why are you calling me a one percenter? Do you mean like I
have a lot of runes? What do you mean? It's not- okay, let's go. I- so much shit that I don't even
have explored. This game is fucking crazy. I can't believe this game is real. It's like so much.
Buy a torch? I have starlight. Starlight's better than a torch. It fills the whole room. It's better
than the torch. I mean, I do get like kind of pool eyes, like chlorine eyes, but whatever.
Is there anything else in this room? All right, get him. Wait. Okay, let's go. He didn't like that.
Oh, you are not even mad for me. Oh my god. Oh, I am unstoppable. Could be the best weapon art in
the game. I never would have thought it was moon build. Nope. And everyone- oh wow. So, I watched
blood-soaked mask. Jesus. I watched this guy trip on 9.85 and he- the bastard stars turned out to be
like one of the better items, especially in BPP. You know, I didn't think that they were going to
be that good. Turns out that's a lot of runes. What an ego. There's a lot of those guys. There's
like two in that room. All right, so I can go down, but let me see. There's another room I can go in,
right? I'm not quite ready to go down. Maybe I am. I'll go this way. Uh, I'm gonna go this way.
Why not? Remind me that that exists up there, because I'll forget. The boys on, uh, on call?
Yeah, there. I did just upgrade them. Freezing grease. God fucking damn it. Thankfully, it's not
far. I did not think it went down that far. That goes down an eternity. I thought it was maybe a-
maybe 50 feet, maybe tops. Okay, so I thought it was- yeah, whatever. So I- I hear the sprinkles!
I hear sprinkles and I- I want it! Oh, hi there. Blankum. Hey, buffed comet. Comet is so much
better. Comet is a million times better. I would say a hundred million. Before, it was- you can
only cast it like once or twice. You can cast it like four times now. Yeah, maybe I need more mine,
but you know. Where is the sprinkles? I hear it. Probably below me. Fuck out of here.
Right. Right! This baby rattle does not seem safe for children. It's because it's an adult baby
rattle. It's an adult rattle. Why do I have such low mana? Uh, because I didn't put many points into
mind. This casting was not supposed to be number one for me. I don't know, a lot of people have
been very upset with me because I haven't been using my spells that frequently. And let me tell
you. First of all, fuck up. Second of all, uh, C1. And number three, I wanted to make a character
that scaled on intelligence with weapons. Sorry. Oh, that was based. Because I want a two-handed
intelligence weapon. I wanted a two-handed intelligence weapon. Fucked up. All right,
pay attention because I just like forgot where I was. Wait. Oh, this- this is like- this is what
I'm talking about. I can go like three different directions. I don't know which one- I don't know
which one to do. There's so many places to go. I feel like I'm in like the McDonald's play place.
It's just like a- do I go down the slide? Do I go in the ball pit? Do I go and climb through the
tunnels up there? There's too many choices. The McDonald's play pit is the Dark Souls, uh,
of like kids entertainment, by the way. Some of the- there's shortcuts? Don't you guys want to see,
uh, don't you guys want to see Miyazaki make a fucking McDonald's play place?
God, that would be so cool. Can you imagine how crazy that would be?
I'm telling you, there's a cross promotion there somewhere. I think that it's-
it could be huge. I couldn't get out of this area without a guide. Wait, you physically didn't know
how to leave? Like you- can you not teleport out? Oh. Oh, I thought you meant like you physically
couldn't physically leave. Like you didn't know where to go and you didn't- you couldn't teleport.
That's funny. If that- if that actually happens. All right, pay attention. Um, I came from this way.
Did I? All of a sudden you're gonna hear like- you're gonna hear-
fucking kids are just going through these tubes. You're just gonna hear like,
ow! Stop! Do you hear like a slide down here? All right, stop getting overwhelmed and stop
being weird. Let's go. I'm gonna go this way. I've chosen to go this way.
This is the entrance. Turn around and go the other way. There we go. This is the way. I'm
gonna go this way. I'm gonna go over here and I'm gonna head this way and I'm gonna jump down
onto this pipe. That is what I've decided. That's what I've chosen. And lobsters down here.
Oh, that hurt. Did I do that wrong? Oh, sick! You see? He would be unnatural at making a play place.
Or a dog park. Oh, shit. That's bad.
What are you doing? Run. Run. My eye- my eyeball is itching. He's like stuck in his ass.
What the fuck? Did he just spit at me? What the hell? What was that? What? What? Oh my god.
I can't even fucking react to it. It's gonna kill me. Stop being so confident. But this is
how this has to work. Oh my god. Just fuck you. Your friend over there needs to-
The thing's just a spinning stump. Don't! Oh, I'm dead. All right, I got the spinning stump.
These guys have a ton of health. He died to lobsters omega low. Dead. Just don't do any damage,
actually. I got a plus nine bastard stars, man. And I got like 57 intelligence. I'm doing
damage. This is just- these guys are hard. This is a hard area. This is an area that is very,
very tricky. It's very- it's a late game. A moment to late game, you know? Later game.
I'm not fighting. These guys are just gonna fall off and die. See who cares. Oh, that's bad.
Is there- okay, right there. Let's see. That's a quick way to do it.
Don't miss. All right, I'm good. He'll die if he lands here. All right, we're good. So, where are
my souls? It wasn't really that many, but you know. All right, I'm just gonna get items and run.
Really? You're gonna- that was bullshit. You waited till I- Why are lobsters the hardest enemy in the
game? That's a lot. I gotta get all these things. This is- this is smithing- smithing stone seven.
No way I don't get all these. Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay. Over here. I think it's on seven.
Holy shit. This is the place to go to get these. I couldn't do anything. I couldn't- I couldn't
move. I didn't have- I couldn't move. What the fuck? I want that. Whatever it is. I actually
couldn't move. No roll? No, it was- I was- the animation wasn't done. Okay, well, I don't need-
I don't have to climb down that. Just fall. All right. So, whatever it is, get it, and then I gotta
figure out where I am. Okay, there's one more. Get the fuck away from me! It's right behind me.
Mog's Shackle? Oh, I can go that way. Mog's Shackle. Ooh, whoa. You can't get in here,
right? Oh shit, bonfire. Nice. Hell yeah. Okay, so what did I- he's got something.
Mog's Shackle. It's a key. Was it a key? It wasn't a key? Was it a talisman? It wasn't a weapon,
was it? Where is it? Am I just stupid? Did I just pass over it? There it is. Mog briefly binds Mog
once imprisoned to Earth. Pettish bathes in golden magic. Shackles were used to bind the accursed
people called the Omen, and these ones were made to keep a particular Omen under strictest confinement.
Though faint, the shackles still retained vestiges of power, enough to trap the once-bound
Mog on Earth, if only for a short time. Binds Mog. Wait, if I just use this, what happens?
Do I, like, converse with Mog? If I- can I- do I- do I spawn Mog right here? If I use it right here?
All right, I gotta go up this way. You use it when you fight Mog. Who the fuck is Mog?
Am I supposed to know who that is? Wait! I'll get it. Wait! I'll get it. Jesus, this- look at how
confused- this- I don't even know- there's so many ways. Is there too many ways to go?
This was up. This is up. I can- I can go down still from that bonfire. I gotta remember that.
What? Where did you come from? I think these guys just spawned. You've killed Mog twice. What are
you talking about? Who did I- I didn't kill anybody. Who's Mog? I have not killed Mog?
Who the fuck is Mog? Mo- wait, wait, wait, wait, wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute, wait
a minute. Mo- I thought Margit and Mor- Mor- aren't they the same person? They're the- they're the
same person. What do you mean I've killed Mog? I've killed, like, three versions of the other guy.
I have no idea. You haven't killed Mog. Oh, Mog, Mog, Mog, Moggy. How many- whoa! Shut up.
You fucking idiot. You should have drank way before. I try- I try to dodge. I didn't do it.
I'm gonna die. Relax. I'm fine. I'm fine. Shut up. Shit. Did I have souls somewhere buried here?
What happened to them? What did you do with them? Oh shit, this is- okay. This is the
bad first area, right? Yes. Yes. Is it- bonfire is over there. Yes. Yes. Let's keep going. I, my lord.
Wait, I've already- I've already been here. Haven't I been over here? I already did this.
Uh, yeah, I did this already. This just goes back up. So then I have to go from here instead of going
this way. I go- yeah, because that's where the elevator is, so I can keep going down.
Okay. Didn't I pull the lever? Walk by- I pulled the lever, didn't I? I thought I pulled it. No?
What the fuck did I pull then? Wrong lever. What? You guys have a fucking million health.
Ugh. That was a backstab and you all know it. Don't get poisoned. All right. There was another
contraption to pull? I know you- I knew you were right there. Thought I was going over there,
didn't you? Shit, I'm dead. I feel like I need to- under the flask thing. You know what I mean?
Under the sacred tier. I feel like I'm not healing as much as I should be.
Well, a hundred damage. Ghost glove ward. Nice. Very nice. Always check the ceilings. You want
a tip for FromSoftware games? Every time you go in a corridor, just go like this.
How do you not kill the other guy? I didn't even get fucking hit. Not going- let me go over here
first. He's still in the toilet. It'd be weird if I was, wouldn't it? Okay. I know I can do this,
right? Yeah. Bring me up. Bring me up. I want to go up here. Bring me up. All right. I think it's
just a- it's just one of these things. Oh shit. It's Mog. That was really dumb. Fuck you. Let me
get it off. Get out of here. Fucking Mog down. Mog down. That guy's kind of crazy. That's Mog
down. Incrucible scale talisman. Holy shit. What is this? Raises damage taken from critical hits.
What? A talisman fashioned from a scale that embodies the aspects of various creatures.
Said to have grown on the human body long ago. It's a heart. Reduces damage taken from critical
hits. I mean, that's kind of cool. Good for PvP. Yeah. What level are you? I'm level 100. Exactly.
You guys talked all this shit about Mog. That was not even a problem.
That's kind of cool. It's bad in PvP as well. All right. So now we're going to keep heading this way.
That was pretty fucking cool, dude. All right. Up here. That guy was harder than-
well, actually that's not true considering I just beat him with the first try.
That was a really interesting move set. What do you got?
Didn't think I was in reach. Holy shit, man. God. Oh my goodness. I got too cocky fighting fucking
Mag. You're on the fucking stairs, bullshit. I got plenty of mana. Fucking cast it.
Oh shit. Why didn't I cast it the first time? How come I didn't cast it the first time? I had
mana. Oh, now I'm all the way over. Whatever. I don't have to go fight that other guy. I got
dog shit. That was what we like to call in the industry. Dog shit. Just got Mogged.
No, what happened was that guy, I had an intense battle with his brother or his other teammate.
He was way stronger than him in every way. And then he got the last hit on me because we
happened to have to fight again. Like this guy did not beat me. Let's be really honest.
That's like if I sit there and try to open the jar that's really tight over and over again,
I'm using all my strength. Then you open it and look and see how strong you are. No, I did that.
You just came in and kill stole my fucking jar. That's what happened. Why can I not fucking fight
this guy? I've fought like 10 of them so far. How do you stay and not get staggered by that?
Fuck you. Why am I so tilted fighting this guy? I've killed 10 of your fucking siblings by now.
With no problem at all. These guys fucking drive me crazy. I've killed like 10 of this person's
siblings without an issue. And I'm just getting hit by every fucking one of his goddamn moves.
What? Oh shit, I had the physics thing on. Dude, I beat Magic Mog first try and get hit twice.
Regular ass Mog comes at me and fucking kills me over and over and over again.
I'm too confident fighting regular Mog. I got too much confidence because Magic Mog was
fucking decimated and it was very tough. Jesus Christ. Come on, man. Here we go.
Why is it not staggering? It staggers everybody else. My God, you regular ass Mog. I swear to God
if you kill me again. Don't fucking die to regular ass Mog. Okay, we're good. Oh, Omen cleaver.
It's just strength, like a quality weapon. Heavy bladed curved sword of colossal size
awarded to Omen as a tool of war. This weapon is made to take advantage of brute strength.
It's de-scaling with strength and it requires 19 to put it on. That's not brute strength to me.
Kind of cool, I guess. It's cool. Oh, that swinging pattern is actually really good.
I don't really like those though. I don't like the slam. It's too close.
That R1 is really good though. Curved greatswords are POG. They seem like it.
Okay, well, let's keep going. Brave Glovewart 9. That's probably almost the max, right?
Is Glovewart 10 the max? Just checking. I know. Wait a minute. I haven't been down here.
It looks like I was down there. Wasn't I down here? Was I not down here? Okay, what's over here?
What's over here? Wait, why is this open? Wait, what? What? When did I open that? Oh, shit.
That's, um, the first one that I pulled? Oh, fuck. It's a MOG. It's MOG. It's a regular MOG.
Yeah? Oh, is that what you're gonna try to do? Fucking MOG Jr.? Dude, fight this guy back here.
Fight this guy back here. Okay, we just have to fight one more regular ass MOG and that's it.
And then I can keep progressing. It's just one MOG and he's got the sword. It's the one that I
don't like to fight. Thank God. Golden Rune 11. All right, the MOG room has been defeated.
Why does it look like I can go back here? That looks like I can go back there, right?
Kind of weird. Yeah, man, you beat MOG. Yeah, I know. So that was the first one that I pulled
because I pulled a lever already. So there's another one. Okay, so I need to pull the second
lever, which I guess I'm gonna go over here. Oh, I went down there already. Is there a place I
didn't go? Uh, this way. Uh, wait. I was already here. I think I left. Um, didn't I- I don't know
what kind of fucking MOG trickery this is, but I didn't- okay, I didn't go this way. Wait. Wait,
what? Why is he back? I'm not fighting him. This is weird. What's going on? Where's the- he revived.
Holy shit, he kicked over my fucking head. Stun him! All right. All right, there's two MOGs
dead here. Am I gonna come back and there's gonna be a third one? What's up there? I did this, but
is it- is this different now? This brings me back up to that room with this guy in it, and then-
wait, this is different. Dude, weren't- weren't we doing something? You know what I mean? Like,
we- we were doing something. I'm in this dungeon now. What happened? How did I even get here?
I actually don't even know how I got here. I was like looking for the dung guy, and then all of
a sudden I'm in one of these dungeons? I don't know how this happened. Okay, so this is- I go down this
ladder? Where does this go? Oh shit, there it is. But don't get killed. Wait, somebody's gonna jump
me here. Somebody's gonna push me off the edge. Okay, so that's to the- now I can go back to the
entrance, right? That should be the- the- that should be it. There's a bonfire right there.
Help is right. Now if I go this way it should be right here, right? Dude, how do I get out of here?
This is all so new. You weren't here before, were you? How do I get the fuck out of here?
You're going the wrong way? Uh, so back this way and then through the other door? There's no way out.
Sorry, you were actually- you were going the right way, was I? As long as I considered a bonfire and
then it's- it's the door right next to here. Okay, this is it right here. And there's the bonfire.
All right, nice. That was kind of weird. I have to pee real bad. So we're gonna walk in here,
probably die, and then I'm gonna go pee. Five golden seeds, really? And then two spine. I- I
kind of- I might- I'm gonna lose all these runes probably, but I want to see what it is. Let's find
out. See if I can do it first try. Both headphones going in. Let's see if I can get it. If this is
three mobs, I'm gonna be very mad. Ezgar, Priest of Blood. Come right up on me, huh?
Can do that. Yo! What are these fucking bugs? Get out of here.
Did I die? Oh, he did. Okay, let's go. Lord of Blood's ex- exultation. That was kind of scary.
Blood loss in vicinity increases attack power. Where's the attack power when blood loss occurs in-
okay, I don't understand this. What does this mean? When blood loss occurs, does that- okay,
I don't understand this. Does that mean if I get blood loss, my attack power goes up?
Or does that mean if somebody has attack power, blood power, then it goes up if I'm in the area?
I have to be bled for- like, I have to be bled. When blood loss occurs in the vicinity,
any- any enemy or you. Oh, okay, that's cool. This is really good. That was kind of a cool dungeon.
I- I guess we did it. It's either you or the enemy. Okay, cool. So, I don't even- we were-
yeah, we were like all the way back here. All right, I gotta remember- I gotta pee.
Let's pee. I'll be right back. Give me like, I don't know, two minutes? Three minutes?
Kirby, you know something? For the first time in a long time, my room is not like 80 degrees.
It's actually kind of nice in here. I wonder what happened. Have you played Cuphead? I-
I streamed Cuphead and I beat the game. That's uh, available to watch as a video on demand.
I did- I did play it. I'm gonna play the DLC when it comes out.
Real fans. You beat Cuphead? Yeah, I'm looking forward to the DLC. Turn the audio back up. All
right, I really needed to pee apparently. That was kind of ridiculous. Am I too blown out? Maybe.
All right, so I need to figure out how much is- I can definitely do it. Did I tell you
I want to do a run where I don't break any of these for the entire playthrough until like the
last third of the game? So just save up like 200 of these and then get like a million souls in
one minute and then level up like 30 times. I feel like that'd be like kind of fun. All right,
I need a lot more than that. You'll only level up twice. Not with this many. There are a lot of
these in the game. There are a ton. How's my camera moving? How's the mouse moving my camera?
I need 60 something thousand. Maybe one of these will do it. Okay, I'm still gonna go with endurance.
I feel like that's important. Get it to 20. Once endurance is 20, then and only then will I start
putting points into mind and that's pretty much where I'm gonna end. I'll probably end up doing
that till the end. Maybe a little bit more in intelligence. Okay, so where the hell was I going?
It was this little cave here and then there's an elevator that went back up. So I want to stay down
here, right? Why? Is it where the lobsters are? Is there another way to go from the lobsters?
What are the roadside graces? I'm already underground. I think it is back up. This
doesn't count as an underground map, does it? Interesting. Okay, there's a hole in the floor
near the grace. Well, let me just go up. Okay. Yeah, so then this takes me back out of here,
which leads out to where all those imps were, right? Okay. Fuck you. What? Where am I?
Oh, right, right, right. Okay, okay, okay. Now I can go up. Do I want to go up? Do I want to climb
this? Fuck you, Mog3. As soon as he moves. Oh, I made it. What are you gonna do? You can't climb
this. Good. All right. Interesting. Very interesting. Is the rest of the grace nearby?
Is that the hole you were talking about? No, they can climb. This guy is not climbing this
ladder. I am assuring you of this. There's not a chance in hell. This is where I came from. Oh,
fuck. You're right. Okay, well, let's go. Let me go rest of the bonfire and get my bearings here.
Okay, so that door is locked. Was there another way I could go from here? We go down there again.
We like the imps were. I don't think there's anything else over there.
I feel like this probably somewhere. Okay, so I got to get up there. How do I get up there?
They went all the way down. All right, so from here,
can't really really get out of here. All right, I can go that way.
Get the fuck out of here. There's too many of you. We're going to go this way. Oh my god. No,
we're not. There's 200 of you. Where are they coming from? Why is there like a Minecraft
monster spawner right here? Oh, fall. Go back up hole in floor. Go back, go back, go back,
go back to grace. Go back, go back. What? What? What? Go back, go back, go back, go back,
go back, go back, go back, go back, go back, go back, go back, go back, go back. Go back,
go back, go back. What? Go back. All right, I'm going back. Relax. This is not even the right one.
He fell for it. That was too many people saying go back. There's a hole in the floor.
I don't see a hole in the floor right here. Is this a hole in the floor?
Hole in the floor? Hey dude, yo, there's a hole in the floor. What? What? There's a hole in the
floor? You need to go north. Is there a hole over here? Oh, a hole in the floor. I found a hole in
the floor. Oh shit. Hole in the floor. Thank you. We did it. You guys did do it. Thank you.
I would have just completely glossed over this. Were you in one of the boxes?
If a rat kills me. If a rat kills me, seriously, like I have to eat a ghost pepper.
Like, honest to god. What happened to the Paper Mario stream? Uh, yeah, I kind of just like didn't
do it. I just like didn't really feel like it. It's so funny because, yeah guys, I'm not going
to be streaming that often anymore. Games that are games that are more than like 30 to 40 hours,
I'm definitely not going to be able to do them. I'm not going to really get into them.
And now I've streamed like a hundred fucking hours of Dark of Elden Ring. So yeah, I've,
yeah, I get it. But I'm not as passionate about Paper Mario than I am as Elden Ring. Okay.
I don't have the real passion for Paper Mario. I think it's cool. I think it looks fun.
Cool. It looks fun. Did it make this better? Not really. Takes way too much mana.
Just one comet. Yeah. Why would you ever use that? I guess maybe the...
Why is it so dark in here? I got starlight. What do I keep getting points? Oh fuck.
Fuck you. Get that shit away. The stone sword key. Ooh. Any more of these I can open?
I don't believe so. Damn, this guy's good. Oh fuck. I don't know. I can't cast this. I don't
have enough mana. Wait. Yeah, I do. I can eat one of these. Use to gradually recover FP. Use.
We're good. Oh my god. Oh. Guys, I had one hit. I'm not going to use mana.
I can't even reach this one. There's so many here. They're not that dangerous, but I mean,
what if I need to run down here? Someone's going to chase me down this fucking tunnel.
Ugh. What the fuck? Not an illusion? Okay. I'm like unclogging the drain.
I'm going to come out and there's going to be running water in the capital.
They're going to be all clapping for me. Okay. I could go the other way too.
What was that? Hole right there. I don't want to fall through that shit. Rainbow arrow? Wait. Dude,
this is so... Where am I? I'm just going... I'm not even going to attack these things anymore.
What's the point? Fuck. I need to clean up the sewers. I hope there's a on fire or something
down here. That cast speed on that is so good now. God. Oh god. I don't like this. I don't like this
at all. I actually don't like this at all. I got to keep starlight on call here because
something's going to come out here. Oh no, no, no, no. Not one of these guys. Not one of these guys.
Not one of these things. What do I do? What do I do? What do I do? Just kill it.
Fuck you, man. I don't know how to fight you without a horse.
Dude, why the fuck are you supposed to fight this guy?
Shit. Oh my god. That guy's so horrible. It was like, I do even have the same... There aren't
even enough frames to attack him before he attacks you again. I can't even call the boys.
I can't call them. They're not available. I'm like, I don't know how to get down there again.
It's gonna be a nightmare. Okay, so wait. There's like two ways to go. Fuck that way. That guy's
almost impossible on foot. All right, there's two ways I could go. We're going this way.
Remember, I baked cookies. Oh, that sounds awesome. It actually sounds incredible.
What kind of cookies? And by the way, soft or chewy cookies. Very important.
They just put every awful enemy in the game down here. Like, these guys are fucking worse, too.
There goes 23 cows... cows and roos. What the fuck? I hate the hands. That was a big hand,
too. That was just a huge hand. Do I have to kill that thing?
Chat. Chat. Tell... Hey, chat. Tell me now. Do I have to kill that thing? Chat. Tell me now.
I'm going that way. That guy with the crown, that goes...
...and dashes around and teleports and does like 12 frames of attack animation when you have two
frames that you can move. I don't want to fight that guy. I want to go down there later and kill
him. Okay. Fucking starlight. Stay on. What? Why did he not... That's so confusing to me.
Who's screaming? Somebody's yelling. What was that? Who's making that noise?
I don't know. I feel like someone was just mocking me. Oh, fucking thing. Fucking
starlight kid. Okay. So, I'm just going to go buy a lantern because I fucking don't want to keep
casting this stupid fucking move. I mean, is it brighter? And by the way, this hand is dying now.
I hate these enemies. It's the worst enemy in the whole game. It is the worst enemy in the game.
I hate them. I think it's awful. I don't like the design choices around them. I think they're too
big. I think they have too wide of an arc. Their damage hitbox is like a 250 degrees in front of
them. They're too fast. They have way too much stamina. They're too... You know what? I don't
just... I go to the whole fucking room. I don't even care. It's not going to happen again, is it?
It is. Get up! Oh my god, dude. All right. All right. Is it going to kill me?
Then, you know, if I can... Yeah, you know. What's that? I'm going to be alive. It's fine.
Wait until I'm down to the flowers. They're blocking the fucking ladder now.
You can't get out of the fucking way. He's got like a million health. Oh my... Why is he here?
Stagger. I can't even hit it. I'm facing the wrong way. I knew he was going to do it.
All right. I'm poisoned, but it's okay. I'm just going to chill for a second.
This guy's almost dead. Like actually pretty much dead. I need to do one more cast on him.
Worst enemy in the game, by the way. Without a question in my mind. Hey, hey! He's supposed to be
dead. No, don't cast starlight. Get out of here. Jesus, kill it. Dude, these enemies are the hardest
enemy for me in the game. Oh, okay. These are... Whatever. I don't care. This enemy is the bane of
my entire existence. Use fire? I have magical spells. I don't have fire spells. I guess I could
throw a canister at him. Okay, we're good. Jesus. Look, somebody was screaming back here. Oh,
that's him. Throw some shit at him. Kill him. Do not kill. Don't kill him. Do not kill. Kill him.
I am killing this motherfucker. This guy told me he was going to kill me, eat me, defile my corpse.
This guy's dead. Don't. I'm going in there and I'm just going to fuck this. I just are wanting as
hard as I can. Oh, I don't know what to do. I don't know what to do. I don't know what to do.
This guy's fucking weird. I don't like this guy. Leave your jail? I don't know. Should I let this
guy out? This guy's a psycho. No, we're being bad. This is evil. I'm about to start R1ing.
I'm about to start R1ing right now. This guy's a fucking evil maniac.
Don't kill. Kill him. I don't want to live to live. He's going to kill somebody
and it's going to be somebody I like. I don't like this guy. Okay. I don't like this guy,
but I feel like it's an interesting thing that can happen. I don't know.
I'm very curious what happens if you let this guy live. I have no idea,
but it's terrifying. I'm having such a conflict right now, but I want to see the interesting
thing play out or do I want to save potentially the lives of the people at the round table hold
because he's probably going to go there and he's going to kill like three people.
All right. I'm sticking with, we're going with pure evil route.
Pure evil. Let's go. I did it. Pure evil route. I'm very curious what happens.
Are you good?
I've decided to leave the round table. I'm off in search of a noble scholar known as the gold mask
evil to beg his instruction. We need again for some time. If there's any incantation,
it's a work of heresy. It's incantations. There are no lineage from the tree.
Can you stick around and help me kill this guy that's about to like rampage us here?
Like we need to, we need to do this stick together because I let a guy out of,
I let this guy out of prison and he's, he's going to come and kill us all. So like we,
we should all work together. So what can I do? What were those incantations? Flame for increases
fire damage park flame from this is, this is so old. Oh no. I'll defile you next. Come to the
outer moat. I'm getting challenged. I'm getting challenged. Meet him out at the outer moat.
Here's the moat outer wall, outer wall, capital. I mean, hit the moats right here. I'm going to
assume it's this one here. I'm kind of terrified. He's not coming to get me Lake below the tree on
the map. All right. I'm actually terrified right now below. Yep. You should really explore the top
lift area. This is consequences. I'm actually scared. I don't know what's going to happen here.
I thought that was him for a second. I was like, why is it coming out of the ground?
I don't want him to kill me. No, I'm not. I'm, I'm going to try as hard as I can to not die.
He said he was going to like defile. He's going to curse me and shit. I got to kill this guy
first try. Is he actually going to fight me or is that bullshit? Oh no. I thought that was him for
a second at him. Oh fuck. Oh my God. I'm off the horse. Oh my God. Get away from me. Bugs. I don't
want to deal with a fucking bug right now. Did you say bless you? That's not fair. Wait, what?
Why does he get a friend? Can he kill him too? Please attack him. Bless you. Oh my God. He could
kill him. Come on. Crap friend. Kill him. Oh shit. Don't kill me. No, I can't get defiled. Oh fuck.
Please get over here and help me. I got him. Oh, he's not dead. He's fucking dead. He's dead.
Did I beat him? Did I get him? He was fucking easy. Sword of Milos. What happened? Don't defile me.
Is he going to defile me? That doesn't count, right? That doesn't count. Like if I died in the
fight, he's dead, right? I'm not going to get like a bad ending. He said if he killed me,
that he was going to defile me and like give me a curse. I don't think that happened though,
right? No, I'm good. All right, so I got Sword of Milos. What was that? I think it's crazy looking.
There it is. Sword of Milos. D and D. Strength and dex. The great sword. Wow. From a giant's
backbone. Milos was undersized for a giant and was viewed as sullied and terribly grotesque.
The scream. Oh, that's what he was doing. I think it's cool. It's cool. This is cool.
Wow. This is a three hit combo or R2. That's actually really good.
Fuck over here. All right, well that was cool. So now I'm going to go.
Can I go back to the sewer? Because that was an invader. That wasn't even him. Back to the
round table. That sword's really cool though. All right, so what happens now? Is there something
there? He didn't do the shrimp guy quest. I didn't. He's back. So what's the problem? What
the fuck? I kicked the shit out of you. What?
Wait, we're like friends now?
Jeremy Elbertson. The dung guzzle.
So. Yeah.
Where is it? I have it. I own it. Where is it? First grown on a body defiled by the dung eater.
This is one out of 99. Okay. Oh, it was nice to meet you. What is this gigantic patch on my chest?
I haven't even looked. This is like a paper. This is like a cardboard shield that you would
give to like a 10 year old to go dress up as a knight for Halloween. What is that? All right.
Well anyways, that was kind of cool. There's like a bunch in the game that you've totally
permanently missed by now. Oh, oh well. I did get some more stones. I wonder if I got enough to do
the staff. That was cool. That was really nerve-racking. I have to go back to the sewer
though. Or should I hold off on that and go actual game progress now? Talk to the spirit girl.
Please take care.
Learning.
That's you.
I can understand that you said it himself, actually, that I'm no mere apprentice any longer.
Once again, I'm pleased to make your acquaintance, Moderica, the certified spirit tuner.
Great. You did it. Nice job. Heresy. Oh, that's cool.
All right. I can do, um, I need a somber ancient dragon smithing stone,
but I can get this up, which is what I want to do. My, this is, it goes to s scaling with int.
There we go. Now I'm in business. This thing is now the real deal.
We'll talk to via via the ugly lady. Oh, I see you've had presence of the two fingers.
Oh, yes. Seems you've talked to the two fingers. Where should I go? That's progress.
If you would say no heat, no sin, unlocated demigods.
There are four more demigods.
Four?
The undefeated swordswoman, Princess Rani, brought her to renown.
Wait.
Three. Because I did her quest.
You already did Rani's quest. Yep.
Okay.
Hello, final boss of the game. It's you.
I'm going to do all this work. I'm going to get all the great ruins and he's going to be like,
oh, tarnished. Excellent work. He's going to like do like the villain walk on clap.
And he's going to stand in front of the fucking Elden tree thing.
And he's going to, he's the final boss. It's going to be this guy.
Like he's going to steal my thunder because it was going to be me.
And turns out, turns out you don't want to fucking be the Elden Lord because it's,
it's horrible, right? And he's going to be like, what's, what's happening to me?
And it's going to be like this horrible, horrible thing. And it's going to be like,
I'm glad it didn't happen to me. That's what I, that's what I think is going to happen.
That's my way this is going for me. That's a Disney ending.
Okay. Let me talk to the, uh, hug lady and then I'm going to go that way. I'm going to go,
I could, I could go this way or I could go over here or I didn't explore that much over here
either. So many places to fucking go. I haven't seen any, look at this road. This goes this way.
So that's interesting. Then is this way. Close the guide, please do top left. I mean, top left
to me, this is like the end of the game, right? Oh, go, go, go to the grand lift of rolled and
go, I set the tree a flame, right? That's end game stuff. I imagine. So in the meantime,
let me just see what else is over here and let me talk to the hug lady. This guy's pretty good.
Where's the hug lady? Please, would you like me to? No. Good day to you. Okay. Do I have any death
root? This guy. Did you need something? Idiot. Why? What? Let her hug you. No, I'll get to talk to
her. I don't want it. I don't want to hug her so I can get the fucking Baldi's basic blessing,
whatever it is. I don't, whatever. I don't know. I don't want it. You had a lantern.
May I ask a favor?
Weather dagger. What was her name?
It's a very precious thing. It must have a special place in the owner's heart.
Thanks. So I would like for the original owner to have it back if you wouldn't mind.
I'd like you to find the owner of the dagger. Very precious. Thanks for telling me anything.
You know, the most annoying part about this is instead of her just telling me what the person's
name is, she engraved it on the weapon and like, I have to read it. This belonged to Godric,
Godric the Brave. Okay. Yeah. And he resides in Castle Fortnite. Like you, she just can't tell
me that. Like just tell, why do I have to read the engraving? To a certain someone.
He wishes for it to return to his rightful owner. It was once a special weapon of gold and silver
intertwined but is now worn down and marred. Okay, it doesn't say it on it. I don't know
who this belongs to. I thought it said Fortnite grave. Oh, I have this poison, right? Small flask
from syllabus containing a cloudy tonic. It's going to, it's poison. Find Nepheli and ensure
that she, no, you have, didn't we come across this person? I feel like I know who that person is,
but I don't know where they are now. The person's dead. Wait, they are? Wait, it's this person's
dagger? Why can't you just walk in the other room? Why not just, okay, it's like somebody's car keys.
I found a pair of car keys. Does this belong to anybody? Oh shit, yeah, yeah, that's mine. Is
that for Subaru? Like how come I have to do this? Okay, now what? Rest. This motherfucker's gone.
It's gone. Okay, so did you see where he went?
I'm missing some context. What happened? You all right? Why are you telling me this?
It's on Mount Gilmere off the old leads west from the town of windmills.
That is the contact. They killed his friend. Just you wait. Oh, okay. So where's, um,
where's this, where's this guy? All right, um, eat this blessing. I don't want it on me anymore.
So now it's time. I have the options now. He's still here. Is it? Oh, you would use
he was talking a lot of shit about you. Oh, no, I like this guy. This guy gave me my first weapon.
Remember he gave me the plus eight rip here. I like this guy. That's sad. He's like one of
my favorite NPCs. He helped us so early. Remember how excited I was to get that weapon?
Where? Okay, so you say he's still here down here. Maybe it's all the same. He's saying he's still
here. Blind one prayer assassin's prayer book got faith faith faith faith faith.
You know what I mean? So where is he? He said, I can't see the blind blind blind.
What the fuck happened? What happened? Why is he dead? What? Finally, it is returned to its
rightful place of the exalted noble. I must bid you goodbye as well. Though I ask you deliver
this message to the round table hold. I am via deathbed. We really fucked up here.
crowned table disturb not the death of godwin the exalted he who humbly live in death live
in waiting to one day welcome our what right does anyone have to object our lord will rise
the lord of the many and the me sorry bro oh man oh we get to fucking we get this we get this we
get to take that drip how good is that armor where is it oh my god it's good it's weird though
i don't like it ill medium load right i'm depicting entwined twins of gold and silver excuse me the
two known as d are inseparable twins they are of two bodies and two minds but one single soul
not once do they stand together and not one word do they speak to one another perhaps this armor
excuse me everybody said i was wrong everybody said that that was wrong that that wasn't two
people it isn't two people it is see how it looks still medium and it's not too weird i don't like
it i don't like it i don't think so i don't think so wait a little bit it's a little cooler now
i'm all right with this that's weird so now that lady's gone interesting i don't know why he died
i don't know what killed him you see what happened over there
voices of the tormented spirits are silent again but it isn't my last time most certain
the spirits have escaped their confinement did you have anything to do with it i wonder
did i do something i didn't do anything and by the way if anybody asks me and d shop at the
same store so if anybody asks so i just want to let you know oh and by the way he said he's
taking a really long vacation all right let's go i want to go here and i want to go here let's go
i'm ready this is where we're going this is what we're doing and i will not hear a single complaint
about it i probably need to go on this one right fill the dragon will you finish this no we are
very focused on going this way right now we're very focused in fact we're incredibly focused
on going here first and here and then we're gonna round it out here but we're gonna start here just
i want to we're gonna be we're gonna do a little bit of exploration you fucking dung eater you
didn't finish this sewer it's fine i'll be fine i'll go back later what is this i gotta go back
the spell that you will get does 21 000 damage okay herma only reads every other
herma only reads every other sentence in the item descriptions i also take every other step up a
staircase as well so i mean i i kind of do that i do every other step i go two steps at a time
all right who's this all right too we gotta go around i gotta get up here and this is a better
what about downstairs oh i mean you can't really do downstairs you'll you'll trip and hurt yourself
and what a what a stupid thing to say i don't need any of this shit okay we're going to two
no we're not because i'm on a cliff what how do i get up there i want to go look at this stuff i
need to get up here around here all right i no longer give a shit about uh about one because
that's gonna be like a memory stone i don't care right that's gonna be like a turtle puzzle
with a memory stone in it i don't want that i don't care about that we can go ahead and take
that off the list it was four i don't care yeah i'm not even using all the memory stone slots
in the first place all right now that's somewhere that i want to go we're going there first
this looks like a church probably sacred tier probably please don't die definitely nice sacred
tier yeah that's exactly what i wanted i really needed it mog related enemy monk s
haha mog related the extended mog family what's going on down there uh i do i do want to go here
basically any blood enemy is mog like i guess so what's that what's going on what was that do
you see that it was weird what was that weird like sprinklies what's going on here what was
it you see you saw that i don't know what was that for it was like a tube of uh of sparklies
what's up what's up what's up what's going on here okay what is going on right now
uh okay i think i just did something yeah i got him i got him i don't know what that was for
necessarily but it's it's okay it's you have to break the three seals and then the memory it's
gonna oh i might as well just do it right it's gonna be three seals get out of the tree that's
gonna instantly kill me if i'm not careful wig all right so where's the other this is there's two
more seals probably right around here somewhere that is a bonfire over here oh shit give me that
get out get out get out get up cool all right we're good sit down sit down like it goes straight
that way or where was that it was that horse jump thing i think i want to do that that was over here
somewhere right this puzzle is really bad i mean there's another one here yeah this is two out of
three touch three fan okay this is mirage riddle touch three phantom but this is two there's a
third one okay thanks you're here so there's one more but me strong will take care of that one
oh well all right wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait there's another one should i go
up again jesus okay um where am i ah all right hold on there's like a thing over here ruins or
something right here you got a map you dumbass i know i know i just wanted to go to the other thing
you got a map you dumbass i know i have a map for it i know me strong is gonna need some quests
to do okay me strong is not gonna get very many quests so we're gonna give him some of these
things that he would be interested in doing now there's one right in front of the tower
it's one right here right in front of it no right here i already got the tower one i did
so there's one by the bridge okay so that's the one by the crumbling bridge okay okay it's over
here it's like right here somewhere all right you got that one you already got that one so
it's not going away don't worry let's do this this thing hostile i guess probably there's probably
a dungeon here that's pretty cool all right looking for a dungeon i'm not gonna kill all
these things what about this way that was the horror actually kind of looked like it yeah
all right there's that but hold on let me see if there's anything around the corner
i'm a big fan of the dungeons i love them okay all right uh i don't see anything else the blood
dogs oh okay we're just going for this we're just we're just going for it all right let's
go for it we're going for it whatever's in here let's do it sanguine noble oh wow you're gonna die
very quickly that was not a mog type enemy bloody helus there's some really cool weapons in this
area arcane and dex and it's a thrusting sword oh that's what he was using designed to bore into
flesh causing severe blood loss at the wound the extracted blood trickles gracefully down the length
of the blade nimbly avoid an attack securing some distance from foes follow up with a strong attack
before we start to lunge and press strong attack again do it again this thing's really cool all
right this is the only uh rip here that i would actually use in the game this is actually really
cool does that have eye frames damn that's really cool all right so that's arcane and dex which
i mean still got baby rattle but you know it's good to say to see the other stuff that's cool
that's fun that weapon is being used for speed running you know after i finish this game i
definitely want to check out the speed runs because i'm really curious how you do it because you can
go pretty much anywhere you want in the open world right you just get on the horses go but do they
just ride to the final boss somehow there's a lot of warp skips 28 minutes currently they use
warps and then just run to the final boss i wonder that's i'm so curious eventually
okay that was cool i can go this way there's an all remembrance run that's probably cool too all
right so here we go we're on the road here that's nothing nothing in here really all right so there
was somebody here right there's a a remembrance soul or something right isn't that guy talking
about it wow you got a funny story let me tell you something i don't not right now mount gelmere
very cool one of these what do i add plus um plus eight i'm imagining this probably plus 10
plus 15 all right let's take it in let's see what we got man this is a whole nother area this is
an entire another zone isn't it what the fuck have you ever attempted a soul level one run no
oh i don't have the skill to be able to do that one of those what's it fighting
get advantage point hi these guys kind of suck but i will help you fight it
yo 777 all right that's dead okay what's been your favorite boss so far you know weirdly enough i
complained about him a lot but it's probably gaudric you see he had the most personality i
think he the best music and the best personality so far all right is that why do you have the dunce
cap on because it gives me extra intelligence and it doesn't make me look like a weirdo like
the other one does progress i don't i don't have to kill these guys or anything but worth at least
looking around anything else on the edges check always check the edges it might be a dungeon
awesome radan lore is pretty cool so you guys saying they patched him what happened
oh go go go go go go go go oh my god oh i'm in trouble holy shit why is it five people here
three of them so what do they do it does way less damage now okay i wonder how much less is way less
what was that ladder over here oh my soul's on the ground so i can't use that as a marker
it's like right here right hurry up allegedly 40 less range on his swings holy shit
that's actually a huge deal that's a big deal you beat him before the patch you get bragging rights
i mean i'll be honest i i kind of don't care about the bragging rights i fucking hated that fight
like i almost wish i didn't fight it until post patch so i didn't like lose two years off of my
life he's a cool fight he is a cool fight but fuck that fight just wait i yeah i know there's like
another fight later or soon that's like good luck but i think i'm gonna go i'm gonna go i'm
at level 100 right that's a pretty good place to be but most of the um somewhere around like 120 to
130 140 is like kind of the end of the video game in quotes something like that right 150
wait till 150 150 120 what's going on are you hostile what are you doing stop don't do that
okay i'm sorry it was like lying with your friend i felt bad for that i beat it around 135 135
i think most people are in like the 110 to 140 range from what i've
heard i don't want to go too too far over level though right that's why i mean i there's tons of
stuff i could probably do and explore but i i'm kind of afraid of just leveling up a ton 140 to
150 is average for late game okay so i'm not i'm not concerned about it then there's a whole
other way to go down there those birds are gonna come down aren't they yeah they are yes they are
that's it i don't know what they do they're like starting a fire but some guy just rides
it in a horseback and kills everybody in one swing all right a couple of smithing stones
they're eating each other oh what the he's eating he was eating they were eating each other
that's terrifying oh they are you guys they're eating each other did i really just say hey guys
look they're eating each other guys they're eating each other you can't see i i guess i need to
describe that to you for some reason i don't know i don't know why oh my god where did you come from
these guys don't climb right i don't think so i really no they don't you climb how come you
swinging around a cat toy no yeah sorry not gonna happen you know get on here so i can punch you
like in the back i'm gonna put you in the spine as hard as i can come on get down here i'm not
gonna let you fuck this up for me get down all right just kick him in the fucking head
fucking god you little i'm bouncing off the fucking wall what the fuck how are you still alive
oh my god dude this is the sloppiest fucking thing how sloppy is this
okay why can't he not hurt him oh my fucking god just run
all right they all came down wait get out of here come on push him push him push him push him off
dude why can i not he's dead this is the stupidest thing i've ever done
so i'm telling you i'm serious let's just go ahead and take care of this now
i didn't even want to i'm just trying to rush so okay i'm fucking actually getting
you know what just eat shit dude seriously i got his head okay pumpkin head very cool
you can fuck your you can yeah you can you can go fuck yourself yeah see you later
i'm not putting that up elden ring is easy slide down the ladder what if there's any more clowns
up here i could hear those mouth noises all right so what was even up here a bow hey bow and arrow
oh hooray nice hey a bow made out of string and like fucking like hamburger meat what was that
this thing is made out of this is a toy holy bow police in springs that's kind of cool though
there's a summoning sign right there that's the best bow is it actually the best bow in the game
i can make this jump right yeah i mean of course i can i fell off it like fucking 10 times all right
let's let's go that nerd tree or that used to be an urtree or something right look at that
that shit's burnt that's an urtree that shit's all burnt look look why are these here
how come these stones are here when he's putting stones down what do we have here what do we have
here what is will you leave me the fuck alone item he's gonna fall the whole way i guarantee it
he's gonna sit here oh damn it i thought it was gonna be like
elmer hero's grave the beast eye quivers does it odd watchers skip what is this heart place is
ass no no no not this place you're saying this place is ass find out good luck with this i think
i'm good to go i'm i'm pretty leveled i'm in a good spot i've got a lot of health
whatever it's gonna throw my way is this is really spooky
minecraft yeah i see it how far does it go oh what it goes that far okay i hate this stupid
shit i fucking hate these things you're gonna need more macha for this one i hate these it's just the
perfect timing i gotta hide in there or can i just get to let me just get into this little
little nook over here we're and it didn't hit either one of them thank you where's the archer
who's got the bow oh shit they dead you need to spend these souls now because you ain't getting
them back all the way up oh get out of the way you fucking tarnished okay here we go
it stops here and then keeps going oh he went in the flame okay he's fine it goes all the way down
stops okay should i go i go when it goes up here see one three four five enough we go now go back
go back i hesitated a second go back going for right there what do you idiots have to be in
every single one of these all right then we're going i'm gonna jump to that oh this is probably
an instant kill if you're going to lava i okay follow it down maybe let's see four five six
seven yeah it's enough time we go oh here we are all right but wait is there any more
there is oh fuck oh fuck oh fuck oh fuck ah you go so slow um what it's gonna keep going
where is it does it come back i don't know does it come down here i don't actually don't know if
it comes down here or not oh my god it does no it doesn't okay go oh my god you fucking
assholes that's safe actually how the fuck am i gonna do this the door but isn't that a door
that needs isn't that that door doesn't open is it locked by a contraption right like all the other
doors in every dungeon what what are you talking about there's no lever for this fight oh shit oh
shit there's a statue right here oh boy oh boy say goodbye to these souls they're gone use a dagger
with quickstep that's actually a pretty good idea all right what is it i wonder if um if i'm
leveled enough to kill this pretty easily that's my note okay red what it's one of these wolves i
can handle it oh oh this game's fucking easy bloodhound knight flow that was a lot of souls
for that actually was it that it's a legendary summon death root oh okay so whoa all right
you skipped half the dungeon you skipped the you need to stop making wolf noises you took a secret
route i didn't even know about this dungeon was much longer you missed half the dungeon
now do the dungeon now keep exploring but i don't fuck this place i've never seen somebody run
past this entire dungeon before really i just wanted to get over get it over with as fast as
possible i hate those things fuck the rest of the whole dungeon none of it actually helps you build
it all i'll give it a glance i'll give it a glance that was cool though i'm doing such an
ungodly amount of damage there's no armor in here just skip it place sucks and whatever fuck it
me strong will come clean that place up that was cool though oh there we are that's what i want
right there number four no everyone thought i was gonna do it i'm really curious about this like
burnt erd tree i'm gonna go check that out right now there's a legendary hilarious weapon down there
all right these are here for what why are these here all these little stones what do they do why
they're here it's a summoning thing well read message hold on wait i have to deal with some
asshole for a second bro you got 800 damage on all the stones what does the message say
rainbow stones lead the way to riches it's gonna be patches
mm-hmm mm-hmm oh my god i'm slipping off i don't see any more i don't get it
why is he such a dick then stay away from the volcano manna what's his problem i don't get it
what what is passion why is patches such a piece of shit like he's not even chaotic evil okay he's
not even chaotic neutral he's just like i don't even know how what you even describe him it's
just annoying you know what i mean like oh where are you on on the on that like chart
uh just annoying sometimes he's friends sometimes he's foe but he's not even like he just i guess
he just does whatever he wants whenever he feels like it i'm chaotic good yeah so everybody says
nobody wants to be like a lawful good right because that's not cool no i'm chaotic neutral
i do whatever i want i do what i want and sometimes i'm good sometimes i'm fucking
instantly dying with 50 000 i don't even know where i am no i'm good chaotic good is like i'm
good but keep an eye on me they're gone forever you literally can't get back down there why not
i'll just man i'll just kick him he can just kick me off again he'll just boot me off again
i can't believe you fell for it twice chaotic good is the second most cringe alignment that
lawful good is the first why do you say that is why is it because like lawful good is like i'm such
a good i'm a good person and i follow all the rules and i'm a i'm a good boy and i oh chaotic
evil no i'm good and i play by all the rules boy scout andy well then what's not cringe
okay which one of them isn't cringe neutral cringe pick a side loser okay neutral good you
don't do enough um okay what else is there true neutral neutral evil that you do bad shit but
you're not in the you're not in the bad boys club no you're not you're not like bad enough to be on
the villain team you're just like they they like hear about you sometimes cringe chaotic evil oh
yeah you're crazy cringe like they're what which one which one of do i get to be
chaotic cringe can i actually not get back down there i don't see the stones anymore
cringe good cringe evil you know i i feel like i've seen like tiktoks of what i would describe
as like cringe good and like cringe evil you know what i mean cringe neutral chaotic cringe
oh shit oh my god you're gonna kill me and i'm gonna have to run all the way back here
your body is so weird i don't even know what when you're swinging and when you're not swinging
no fuck you swing what in a swing i just jumped my god chaotic neutral evil yeah chaotic neutral
but then in parentheses evil scavengers curve sword yeah i talked about yeah ball of yarn chef
where's flaming hot cheetos on that list right they need to see like the joker with like a like
fucking flaming hot cheeto fingers like doing that like big smile and he's like holding the
bag up that's that's super chaotic evil how have they not done like a tie-in with the joker like
a flaming hot cheetos they're crazy like me right how come they why have they not done that that
feels like they would do that yeah make them green make them a green flaming hot cheetos
and it's like oh yeah this is like it's like the joker he's like crazy and like spicy and my mouth
like hurts and everything it's crazy that's the all the joker version it's green don't tell me
i'm wrong because like that i please as they're already do blue talkies okay they are one step
away oh excuse me is that somebody you didn't think you'd be dealing with somebody that was
level 100 sorry not happening today green talkies only available at walmart
eat like the joker that wasn't that was a leprechaun i have to hide whenever i do something stupid
oh saint patrick's day yeah it wouldn't it would be just like it would be uh whatever oh
that was that actually like irish it wasn't right no that was the joker i'm trying to
listen to the joker talk and a leprechaun talk and they're the same voice in my head
what do you mean oh yeah batman it seems that i you have been caught into my trap
i can't um they talk the same no not mark hamill's joker they talk the same
are you doing charlie day and charlie dave would probably be kind of would probably be
a pretty good joker all right he could be watch out by the way talkies are fucking disgusting
but let me tell you something i have a confession to make i have been eating off-brand talkies
and i think they're incredible i think talkies are dog shit but the off-brand talkies that are not
talkies are amazing to me trader joe's makes an unbelievable talkies rip off and they're way better
honestly i like the doritos ones the doritos ones that just a straight up copy of talkies
i think are better but i'm serious like the trader joe's ones are the way that they should be
that's usually true yeah i'm saying i'm telling you if you like love talkies
first of all cringe i'm about to falling r1 this guy i'm just kidding
confessor this is what the confessor oh your inventory you're kind of bad man
i only got one stone sword smithing stone key come on i'll buy this i guess i don't know what
that does volcano pot and roped volcano pot cool this area is really cool actually i really wish
i could see anything is that i like the scale very very cool going up i'm just looking at the view
this game comes out like i once a decade a game comes out like this i'm gonna take a second and
take the binoculars i'm not gonna look at the view oh you know what i wanted to kind of do
okay if i set up a poll and everybody picked what they thought they were for like the chaotic good
neutral good neutral evil right i'm very curious what the makeup of this audience is aren't you
i'm very curious this keeps going should do it um maybe i'll do it in a minute oh i hate these
guys the lightning wow i didn't think you were fucking with over leveled andy
stop saying andy i you did this to me you guys ruined it you ruined me you ruined me i never
said this shit ever this was never a phrase that exited my mouth until like 2019 2020 you guys were
saying it all the time so i was like oh that's kind of fun yeah something andy that's funny i
get it's cool that you guys said it so much that i yeah i got into it whoa sick the assault on
volcano manor swallowed the sick the blasphemous a wretched unending war with no glory oh there's
one of those i'm gonna go get it yes i am i think one of these bridges is gonna something crazy
gonna happen it's gonna fall oh it's like a there's a tortoise spurs the hare scenario
or i could just skip the ladder but i feel like this is a tortoise in the hare scenario
i'm not gonna do it what happened to all your ruins uh patches kicked me off the cliff and
everybody laughed and i like i like threatened to turn my scream off a few times uh because it
was like almost 100 000 souls i lost and i i calmed down though all right so yeah this is
tortoise first there that's like oh let me go up really fast but if you go up too fast maybe
somebody shoots you out of the earth an arrow there's no way they would put these right next
to each other without it being like uh i'm lazy and i'm gonna skip content this is gonna be the
correct path old groan i didn't get to read his name why would you put a ladder there
it's the same thing so wait a minute is from software anticipating that you don't have the
horse like what the fuck all right i'm staying i'm getting off the horse he goes click click
click with him click click click is this an on-horse fight or off-horse fight i wonder
oh all right you guys are away from it oh shit still hit me oh this is bad this is not that bad
ah shit he turns around i thought he was gonna go forward all right oh that's bad i'm dead oh
fuck i'm alive that hurts him a lot but it takes way too long how many fucking times are you gonna
do that move that has he takes damage from that a lot wow that's way better than actually
attacking this guy oh hey oh boy oh shit too cocky oh i'm fucking dead here my god it's
fucking boobs that's disgusting amount of damage i think this is an on-horse fight i really do let's
see if i can do it i thought i had like the uh poison things that i could eat that's all right
i'm gonna stay on the horse yeah there's no reason to get off the horse you know that you can dodge
when on the horse i'm gonna turn purple in just a few fucking minutes okay out of here yeah you
should stay on the horse it really is this is a non-issue on the horse oh please oh oh oh what i
thought he was done with his move don't do it don't do it don't do it don't do it this fucking
menu i swear to god ah fucking mario 64 had it but not the move i wanted to do but it's all right
he's dead he's dead he's dead oh my god don't be a cocky little shit i swear to god
this is not a problem i'm fine all right that was not bad that wasn't bad hey that was a cool fight
i got him oh two i got two smithing stones and then falling star beast jaw
colossal weapon strength int and dex art and shining black fashion into a weapon with its
sharp point it's called this colossal weapon can skewer foes wow 20k but 60k gone yeah
can i do the move this thing is wild looking all right very cool well maybe a strength and
int build or kind of all over the place yeah strengthen it um that's cool that matches
your stupid hat yeah but i can't use it all right so anything else here that i
anything else that was pretty fun there's i would consider that to be a manner and i would consider
that to be volcano fluid in the manner so i'm imagining that's where i need to go
let's just jump from here no way so i need to go that way we're gonna go down and then around
okay don't go right ahead don't don't i'm not gonna i'm not gonna do it wait maybe i will
oh wow yeah i am gonna do that this is here for a reason look look at that perfect very cool very
cool this is a cool game all right so let's turn the corner here oh give me that please i don't
want to do anything else until i get this oh there's an invisible cookie box right here
don't be an idiot uh there's another little urd tree seed there's a pouch menu yeah i used it i
used it for the i'm using it for the boys all right where is this thing excuse me frame rate
what's going on here oh fucking fine i'll wait for him he circles right here he circles the rock
fucking elmer fud rip i gotta pee again hurry up ruin through ash of war
oh now this volcano mana all right there's a scary guy up front where is fucking map fragment
down there i'm getting the map fragment first we're not going in the front door without it
but i died why does this particular area run like such ass no i don't want to fight these
is this a hand zone this is the hand is this a this is a hand zone
i don't want to be can i skip this do i have to be here okay i have to be
i'm just i don't want to piss so much i'll be right back
so
okay i am not kidding that was insane i've never had that experience before in my entire life
in my entire life i went to go pee i did a full 30 to 40 second full piss i was done that's it
okay grab a water come back come back over here i got the urge to go again i peed a second full
time like a full 10 to 20 seconds again and then it happened i went to go sit in here and it was
like i have to go pee again what happened that was three full pisses i am not fucking making this
up you have a uti i don't know i don't think so there was just a lot of volume like a ton of
volume cranberry juice i love i drink cranberry juice not that cocktail bullshit i drink cranberry
juice real i don't have a uti stop i don't have a uti oh alignment pole cool this all right so
let's see we've got uh i'm very curious neutral good chaotic neutral chaotic good i'm gonna okay
yeah bullshit i knew that chaotic good was gonna be up here hi what is okay honestly what is neutral
evil even supposed to mean right i don't like what what is neutral evil supposed to be god damn
it i just like broke my goddamn game please don't tell me please please please please please please
please just you're just an asshole but you're not evil yeah like you're just like a kind of a dick
you're an asshole but you don't know you're an asshole okay interestingly enough chaotic good
is up there right yeah that's what i would assume all right so i got this map now which is this is
crazy that there's even another area too all right look at all this shit to do look at all this look
at all this stuff you can't know what you can't even do in one lifetime that's where i died this
is where i am now all right so look this is like shit over here to explore ruins and all right
horse in pouch bro huh i'm actually kind of surprised that it took me this long to do that
i think that's all i need look at all these ruins too i'm not crushing any of them all right
oh finally it only took 80 in-game hours now let's start the process i went this way i want to go
there's like a probably a side door let's do side entrance we're gonna do side entrance
probably side entrance i don't even need to fight these guys fuck them oh yikes
no side entrance what's down here this guy is huge oh man he's like a giant one of these things
oh don't you know what we're gonna go ahead and do this oh that was weird he just went so fast
all right that was pretty fun a larval tier oh oh this is the burnt urn tree this is really
interesting i wonder why this is like this what the heck i'm getting immersed one of these guys is
down here oh fuck you oh what don't get cocky you idiot
fuck you i hit him what is going on what did he just do why did he do that oh shit in my fucking
pants fine i'm fine i'm fine i got plenty of health get out of here i have enough experience
fighting those guys that's like the fourth one i thought oh leaden and what do those do
eliminates all fp consumption what i drink that and just spam spells um i kind of feel like i need
that it seems unbelievably that that seems like game breaking how good that is that's god tier
you can summon any spirit for free jesus okay that's cool anything behind the urn tree
oh that was pretty cool though i will say i the i fought that worm spirit ulcerated free sap
thing like five times though i have lots of experience and where are we going i'm heading
this way now i don't know what this is what happened here is that the manner i think i would
say this is the volcano manner i'm gonna yeah i want to do the manner you saw the front door
yeah yeah okay so i'll go back up i want to put that on too the manners right here
yeah getting lost is the best part of the game yeah i know absolutely it is oh this is wrong
but whatever i want to put that flask on okay the the you don't take damage for one hit is huge
so i feel like this is going to be insane very interested it only lasts for 10 seconds so
you drink it and just spam a move just spam spam spam spam spam spam spam spam and then be done
with it lord ryckhard this putrid field of death is what your blasphemy would bring
then i can no longer abide no one can what happened this way where's bugleberry these things
i'm just going to the front door i actually despise that enemy uh where is the wait where's the front
door am i going the wrong way up and around right yeah there's a big guy standing in front of the
front door i don't remember where that was we don't wait is it right there i can't make that jump
though can i yeah i remember turning the corner there we go there it is all right volcano volcano
manner time let's go so what's with all this shit why they why is everybody hung upside down um
oh it's just it's a giant okay i was like what is that that's fucking ridiculous wow okay what
is happening right now get out of the fire all right all right can you make my bit rate of my
stream go any lower please stop these guys are so much easier with magic i can imagine
being a strict melee character here uh it's probably hell and potentially like five to
ten levels ago right yes five to ten what is the all right what would you guys say the like the
sole level of this area is 90 85 90 a little higher maybe 80 80 to 90 okay so i mean i'm not
i'm a little over leveled for this area but not like egregiously more around 90
i thought this is a mountain of fire but i hardly feel a thing i'll then what you're fine pretty
much level wise yeah it feels that way oh lots of buds okay that's interesting all right let's
head in the manor oh oh this place is cool looks like resident evil oh good thing i got starlight
don't miss the secret wall um well how are you supposed to miss how you supposed to not miss
a secret wall if it's a secret wall and you don't know where it is i'm probably gonna miss it
volcano manor i like this place a lot this place is so this place is cool it's kind of like a
creepy vampire version of the round table hold those npcs this is the place with the
wall you have to hit 50 times are you precocious we rarely receive visitors to the volcano manor
without invitation fascinating and not unlike another guest we had long ago so tarnished
have you ever harbored doubts about the burden of grace and the dogmatic ramblings of the fingers
i mean recently yeah not doing the volcano manor us rise with us against the urd tree okay but um
okay burn urd tree or don't burn the urd tree it doesn't really fuck anything up
okay your decision is most welcome now you belong to the volcano manor the drawing room
lies down make yourself comfortable i am tannis the proprietress of this house
i don't like the way he's looking at me an honor to have you drawing room key i don't like the way
he's looking at me by the way as a new member intimidating very intimidating i don't like the
he's very intimidating presence the drawing room is through the hall use the key i handed you
the drawing use the key all right that way or we can go up let me go up first are they am i
gonna get attacked here or we on the same team oops hey get out of here dog get out of here
there's a dog up here wait what invaded you're not even level 100 geese's wheel there's so much
wacky shit in this part of the game where is that d blood build up 70 70 this is probably the best
blood item in the game then spinning wheel strike the wheel against the ground instead of
spinning at top speed all right that's pretty cool that's the funniest weapon in the game
those don't break nice smithing strong very cool well that person i got i destroyed them baby
rattled second best weapon in the game anything else that i didn't do all right down the hall
wait i can level up i think i can 62 56 guys tried two weapons and he thinks it's the best
weapon in the game it's up there let's say my eyes are the worst i don't want to use the big one
it's like 10 000 that should do it 102 all right let's go drawing room key i don't want to go in
there yet that's shut okay i gotta go one room at a time this is just wacky rooms probably right
let's go one room at a time it's gonna be wacky rooms nothing in here there's nothing in this one
check the walls in these rooms i can't swing hey i'm new here i'll be back doom bottle all right
hi guys pleasure to meet you brave tarnished scout very pleased to welcome you to the volcano
manor staff school lady tannis guidance may you tread the path of valor brave tarnished under
lady tannis the path of valor letter from volcano manner and a recusant finger attempts invasion of
other players world oh this is where you get is this permanent and then where's the other thing
that i just got where is it letter from volcano manner a written request from volcano manner is
disclosing the name of a tarnish to be hunted old knight istvan he can be found in limb grave
find the red mark on your map for the exact location why is it giving me like hitman assassin
missions that's funny you what in heaven's name are you doing is a pit of recusants who spit at
grace and hunt our own what are you doing here the weight of my words i understand you understand
what you're saying i thought you were tarnished bred by virtue perhaps playing that part led you
to your doubts i wonder is blasphemy and leads only to a miserable death before you consider
hunting any of your own kind think on that this blasphemous path leads only to a pitiful death
before you consider hunting any of your own kind think on all right well i i know you
it's you is it what's happening nice to see you again so you've been invited as well i see yeah
then we're comrades in arms henceforth you watch my back and i'll watch yours yes i um i can tell
you're wondering about lania well you see i after much internal debate i've come to realize
revenge is not the answer according to lady tannith i've got the stuff of champions oh and
champions ironic as it is are oft forced to walk okay let me tell you man it hit me like a bolt
from the blue we should just bolt my former thoughts were simple naivety of course my heart
weeps for lania we should get out of here incident was a cruel twist of fate indeed
you're starting to believe your own bullshit here cause won't make me a champion will it
lania knows this i'm certain fate has laid hard roads for us both you're starting to believe
your own bullshit and that's not good trod by champions all right man i always resented these
hands their pale complexion a far cry from any warriors the shame of house hoslow but that won't
be the case for long they'll be darkened by grit once i've set out on the path of champions
the tale of house hoslow is told in blood after all i feel like i'm on vacation here and this is
like a really expensive kind of larp session with actors and shit and they have to pretend that i'm
honorable warrior and stuff like i don't i definitely don't look like well i
look a little bizarre these are all paid actors and i'm here and it's the larp session
warping on vacation yeah i mean there's like isn't uh isn't like disney doing this like larp
vacation thing eventually right where you like check into the hotel it's like freeze rebel scum
come with us right isn't it they're doing this they're doing a full-on make-believe larp session
where you check into the hotel and like the people behind the counter are like quick come this way and
you do like a whole routine where you have to give you like a laser cannon or something i swear to
god i think that's happening it's six thousand dollars for like three days it's already open
it's two thousand dollars a night do you get a lightsaber how do they do that though like if you
were gonna okay you can't like nobody can like touch you right in a lot of these things so if
you were gonna like fight count dooku how do how do you do that with like a larp with an actor
they have to be like rebel scum it's time for you to die hit me it's your turn it's your turn to
swing the foam sword at my leg oh you got me oh and then go how how they can't how are you gonna
do this well like here we are i've got my blaster cannon there's the rebel right there and there he
is he's there's the rebel their two sons their daughter and they're in mickey mouse t-shirts
there they are all right captain we have to wait for the two-year-old to come up and hit us with a
fucking stick oh he got us dip i don't know how this plays out it's that's gonna be so weird
the honorable thing is to fall over while laughing yeah okay this is like a 2.0 version
of when like a three-year-old has a stick that they say is a magical wand and they go like this
and you go oh oh you got me oh and they do this two to three hundred times it never stops
ever like you will be in the middle of eating dinner you'll be eating food you have a fork in
your hand and you have like eating pasta and they'll be like it's like oh yeah oh and they've
run away laughing as you have to keep that up otherwise it's not a magical stick is it it's
not a magical stick is it if you don't keep it up so if they do that one time and you don't commit to
it then it's like what everything's a lie i thought this is a magical stick so that's gonna be like
the 3.0 version of that there's gonna be some some stormtrooper's gonna be on his lunch break
with a fucking sandwich in his hand sitting outside with the helmet off and he's gonna be
like he's gonna look over he's gonna see like the kid in the fucking like hans solo t-shirt
is gonna come up and do that and he's gonna have to be like oh oh nice job son oh hold on let me
get the helmet back on destroying property and laughing in the this place you think i give a shit
i'm the strongest person in this room okay you know why because i paid two thousand dollars a
night to be here so they have to deal with all of my bullshit i kind of want to like do it though
right and get really fucking into it i want to like have them like we're like in a blaster battle
and like go like like like like that got me and go down be like and roll over like lie on my back
and just like lie there would somebody come over and be like oh here's here's like the
medicine that we can give like to rebels that i how what would even happen you like dodge roles
and stuff i would be so fucking annoying all the actors would be like get this fucking clown out
of here like seriously this is shit like fucking children when are you gonna do it you should
stream it i don't think i would be allowed to stream that are you kidding me 2k a night that's
fucking crazy can you imagine if it was like they really went crazy with it and you're in bed
in your like hotel room and they it was like at like two o'clock in the morning was like
we have an invasion from here they come here come here come the here come the the last order
whatever they are and like it's like oh shit you gotta get up and like put your clothes on
get like your like blasters that are on the wall and like oh my god can we take a shower
hold on like somebody turns the water on like well let me take a shower first and like they
kind of have to like wait outside like they hear the water running it's like fuck they're taking
a shit they did somebody in the shower we can't like we have to wait it's so fucking i i just
don't know how it works i'm very curious how that plays out don't forget the secret wall all right
all right all right they stand there all night because that's what it is right it's like a
you are on board an enemy vessel or something from what i've heard it's going to be something
like that there's secret walls here i'm looking for them right now people said dodge dodge dodge
i'm looking for the secret walls right now there are youtube videos of the hotel already
i don't want to see them all right i don't care about the secret walls what am i supposed to do
here i don't get it what what do i do i have to do though go do the quest you got just go to the
quest you missed the only wall that you didn't do that too which one are you referring to you need
this first room dumbass don't i i'm trying to find it dude this is the i feel like you guys are
lying to me this is bait this is horseshit it's just impossible it's impossible it's not it doesn't
it does not exist it actually doesn't fucking exist you're lying to me i got it no i didn't i
didn't hear anything oh let's see the kid it's got i don't have starlight on why are they like
slugs in the wall
this is kind of cool this is ridiculous but i never would have found this if you guys didn't
scream at me there's more down here great uh oh no these guys are way way i'm able to kill
these guys without profit now bloodhound claws that sounds pretty cool blood loss strength and
dex oh all right there's a way i could go back there don't let me forget this is the door um
all right oh shit okay whoa go back go back go back go back go back rip rip content rip content
go back all right all right you literally just told us to have you not forget that i know i'm
just fucking kidding i'm just messing around oh do i even i don't need to fight these invisible
wall whatever the fuck it is oh that's bad brave perfumer car man do the assassination before you
do that boss i can't open this this is not openable through the wall what wall the wall 50 times
which one is it i don't care do i really you think i'm really gonna sit here and care about
that i'm not doing the 50 hit the wall no i don't care all right so that was that that was pretty
cool i am going to um i want a bonfire here i feel like this i'm far away the wall challenge
i'm not doing it you can riot all you want it's not happening i'm not gonna go hit the wall 50
times we've all seen the gif it's very funny it's very interesting it's it's it's a bug
and bugs are weird and it's crazy and it's a little kooky i know but i'm not gonna do it
all right this bonfire right there so let me go kill this guy where is he keep going that way
so let me go do this why not this is kind of interesting i need to go here wait this is an
npc is it i'm about to kill an npc where is he oh it's his body's a wolf oh shit he was
fucking so crazy invade old knight ist van's world what he's playing in his own game so i'm
an invader you got hit he died just double i tapped him he got tapped he got tapped
you're an evil you're evil old knight ist van defeated is just teaching me how to invade
people imagine getting killed by the sus guy whoa all that am corroded metal is reinforced with
rock hard scales making it highly effective against non-physical attacks this thing's really
unbelievable actually am all right what else did he have this is good but it's i'll be heavy
that's pretty good all right cool now i'm gonna go back there i just keep turning these questions
you got a five o'clock shadow that's more than that i haven't shaved in like a week
that is the van guy sucks i'm gonna go watch another streamer you killed him in your playthrough
too in fact you stood on top of a ledge and threw rocks at him but you're calling me out so who do
i turn this into so you blooded your sword in the hunt then i shall introduce myself
all right now recusant just like you recusants have particular battle arts styled to our methods
of slaughter why not add some to your repertoire oh very interesting sassin's gambit grants grants
near invisibility and silent footsteps eruption storm blade this is no skill very cool you've
come to understand now to take power and make it his own the recusant must hunt his own kind
to raise the flag of revolt against this sanctified pillaging we recusants must become the most
wretched of predators all you can do is laugh all right so you sell those what about you have you
killed anybody i always resented these had a pale complexion but that won't be there'll be darker
any more notes any more letters i can pick up what about you strange sounds here at the manor
yeah there's snakes in the walls like breathing slithering scales oh it just is impossible
okay so yeah that's how you find out like breathing all right that sounds cool what
about the uh talk to the yeah the lady over here did you read the letter left for you that is the
task the volcano manor desires you and i did it you will be compensated once the deed is done
amy if you are loathed to hunt your own kin so be it but you must leave this house at once
this is a war against the earth tree we have no place for the meek nor the luxury of keeping
clean ham amy i did it you've completed your tire am pleased now you are a recusant true
and a full-fledged member of the volcano manor this is your reward as promised
you got faith bullshit never forget that the recusant fights to tread the path of the champion
the way is tainted but for this very reason it is the true path to valor give me more faith
cool faith stuff rounded in my face yeah it is faith it's any 10 faith why is a lump of magma
sorceries i need to put a guys i have to put four points in faith that's not happening
or that's gonna cost like 400 000 souls you put a talisman on to do it yeah but i don't want to do
that i'll test it out maybe okay so now all right so you're gonna give me another task when i
reload the area looking forward to fighting that guy because you know i am please kill him
that horrendous serpent greater ryker you're tarnished here to put the demigods to the sword
why is he like this then please just spoiled it is it
the tarnished brandish the spear and run him through the great serpent all right so where is it
in the lord's chamber
have you killed someone i haven't heard an enemy in probably 30 minutes
that's that one guy once he gave himself to the serpent whatever that thing is it is no longer
praetor right someone must kill him to spare him okay so the big snake ate this guy and he
is now like in the lord's chamber is a spear where's the lord's chamber
how do i get in it the lord's chamber it is the all right where's the lord's chamber
is it this door over here okay well i'm going to imagine and imagine here that
i'm going to imagine that that's something that i get after doing all the assassin requests
it's a guess but i don't know we're just gonna go that way and i'm gonna walk on the rooftops
it was a letter i'll go i'll do it later i want to i want to i want to walk around
i'm very i want to explore this don't even think about poisoning me
okay you can't you can't do the boss before the assassinations that's what i figured but
you know i'm sure there's gonna be bonfires all over the place and i can teleport to other bonfires
and finish up i just this area is so cool i want to see it i was way too late on that
shit these guys don't even do it again and you almost just got grabbed again no such a
fighting this guy up on this ledge sucks because like i don't want to fall off the edge
oh i thought he was gonna get back pain in the ass very cool i could go around the rooftops
and you know what that's exactly what i'm gonna do good fuck i'm overwhelmed um that way that way
that way that way that way okay there's like four ways to go let's just go i'm gonna just
walk around the perimeter i think he loves this game i do it's just it's so good but it's
no i want that i don't care i'm going down now who the fuck are you it looks like we're going
down great omen killer cleaver so many weapons how do you even pick one to play with you know
what i mean how are you supposed to pick one of these oh there it is blood loss strengthen decks
hideous horns cause blood loss adding vibrant colors to the ongoing mayhem all right well
it looks like we're gonna do ground level first you have 58 int why don't you have any good
sorcery uh because this character is kind of a little bit of sorcery a little bit sprinkled in
it's mostly int weapon scaling damage i wanted i wanted to swing an int weapon
grocery spine i use it sometimes i have a lot of cool spells free uh pre-pump or pre-patch
i didn't really want to use it too often like a lot of the spells i was finding were uh was it was
that were dog shit um there's like three moves that i actually like to use uh so i'm sure there's
others build is fine yeah i mean i i wanted okay here's the thing when i first played uh from
software games for the most part my first playthrough is fucking my god i'm gonna fucking shit my pants
these dogs seriously um what was i saying i okay i usually like to do a melee build
at least like a not 80 to 90 percent melee um i feel like it's helps me learn the game a little
better oh make no mistake about it i will absolutely this is cool though i will absolutely make
characters that are just 100 faith or 100 sorcery and just don't even fucking swing a weapon okay
what about up here because i don't fucking use those i am bird tree seal what is that by the way
i don't know why every time i talk about this move i do like the boston guy i don't i'm i'm
not understanding why that's happening but i'm just it's it is for some reason where is it what i
just got bird tree seal still this mob thing where is it damn man i i feel like i have like a
fucking like purse full of shit i don't even know where anything is what was it it's a faith weapon
but sometimes i seriously feel like i'm looking at like a tf2 backpack why do i have four of these
i need to like consolidate some of this shit i do i really need like six of the same weapon
like honest to god like do i need these all right you said it's a faith weapon
oh so this is like a uh faith cast thingy c scaling to start where did the other one start c
grow up always look don't bother looking for it we the chat chat don't like it
chat you guys are calling yourself chat chat i actually kind of like that uh all right let's
go through here i'm a man there's the rooftops up there too let me see if there's anything over
you can go this way
chit chat with the chat chat nice super mario 64 level name
um i'm definitely going to use this gravity i'm dead all right i made a dumb joke for no reason
and now i'm far away like a fucking idiot well i can i can i can i can um go on the rooftops
all of you i thought you were dead dude wicked chaotic cringe vibes all right right there uh but
hold on just a moment i'm not ready to throw in the towel here i want to see what's up here
oh monka s not really that great um don't die there's a bunch of souls over there
i mean but here i'll be fair though that move that's that's that's a sorcery move
that's a sorcery move that actually scales off of intelligence so like i'm i am casting a spell
don't please seriously i'm but can you slow down
bud stop doing the same move over and over again without me getting a turn
oh i thought i was gonna be safe opening the door oh fuck is that a person i'm fine i'm fine i'm
fine i'm fine i'm fine i'm fine we're good mom said it's my turn to attack yeah i mean that's
how it works you go and then i go and then you go
see this guy gets it go play final fantasy kid i mean actually uh what i've heard is a phenomenal
fucking game so your insult didn't work kid come on kid i know i'm gonna get my souls but
there's a thing to do over here and i know i don't have any mana potions or potions but
i'm still going in we hey something about you know fucking some fucking style i can
what's wrong with these guys i thought that was an invader what are these what contraption of these
guys in god terrifying wait i this is i don't know progress i think let me go back how are you a
wizard and you have less mana than my strength and faith build because you're way over leveled
you're like your level your soul level is like 150 you're over level i'm not 176 actually all
right who cares but where's my souls they're right here i'm just gonna run in here because
these guys are a huge pain in the ass is that cope yeah yeah or i know that guy could be so level
like 50 and really good at the game don't get caught up in this all right what was in here
this is a stone sword key all right plus one greatly increases maximum stamina i mean health
wow that's actually a lot i'll take the stamina one off i'll drink you're gonna kill me my q
all right where did i want to go i'm just running by this after this you guys are horrible
hell didn't ring hell didn't ring i bought this game and i'm starting to regret it let me help you
here um you should you got okay these guys here you got these summoning spirits use them all the
time whenever you can don't stop saying refund the game come on uh you got summoning to help
don't feel like okay let's say you're let's say you're reliably getting a boss down to like
30 health after using all your flasks so you okay let's say you have like four or five six
glass right you drink drink you're trying so hard after like 20 30 attempts you're getting
the boss down to like 30 i mean like so he has 70 help remaining what i would advise you to do
is don't worry about the boss forget about the boss turn around and go here don't go i mean i'm
assuming maybe you're here maybe you're like doing this shit here maybe you're fighting market or
something right turn around and like go over here and go fight this stuff go over here explore
fort hey west check out the urn trees go level up five to ten times and then you'll come back here
and after like you know sometimes it takes like three or four plus five plus hours right
i wouldn't i wouldn't say grind i don't think grind is the right word i think the right word is
go play the game and if you're getting stuck on something there's no reason to continue to suffer
go play go find a go find a dungeon and just go clear it they're much easier than the actual
all right so for instance like murk water cave is 100 times easier than fighting market 100 times
easier another thing i'll give you for a tip because i mean i'm an elden ring streamer right
i mean i'm an elden ring streamer this is this is what i i'm going to give you advice
another thing you should take into consideration is you need to start to understand never mind what
am i going to say you need to understand iframes so what that means is i feel like i'm making the
spy fucking like ambassador video again and like years later people were like wow dude this is like
dogshit advice i hope nobody listened to you and i'm like okay that's right you need to learn iframes
what that means is you are completely invincible your character cannot get hurt
even a centimeter of your health right now now now some people have these swings where you you're
you're trying to get hit when you're invincible don't think about getting away i gotta get away
from this guy no you want to get near that guy you want to when he's swinging you want to get hit
by the sword when you are invincible get it it's not about getting away it's about getting hit
when you are invincible and now watch me not do that over and over again but it's this theory
there's a lot of hairs okay i know that like oh man we're all like man we're all from software
buds we're all from software fucking chums we i got like 6 000 hours there's a lot of people
that they literally just got this game for the first time and they have never played a from
software game ever you know we how about the new players we okay don't you guys understand
that the more people care about this stuff the more like money that comes in the more that from
software gets to keep making cool stuff like this think about it right more more companies will make
games like this it won't just be 5 000 markers on a fucking goddamn open world minimap that is just
go touch this thing in the world and that's literally it if we get more shit like this the
more people care about it there's still 500 000 people still playing this except these new players
they're they'll they let them and it's gonna be hard and the game sucks you're gonna be pissed but
you'll get it you'll get it eventually you will and you'll feel happy about it where am i okay i
got it so now let me go in here kind of it kind of changes the design though since they can't afford
to take as many risks um i i don't know i mean that's what people have been saying i remember
when dark souls 3 came out and everybody was like oh fuck here we go uh here come the normies
they're gonna start playing it because it's like a popular thing now and that game kicked my fucking
ass that was one of the hardest games ever played and then they made sekiro and the same thing oh
god i saw the trailer here come the normies now it's gonna be ruined sekiro is gonna be fucking
easy it's gonna be the simplest game ever activision's publishing it it's gonna be
you're gonna have like you're gonna have like 10 extra lives
securito was one of the hardest things i've ever done my whole life that was actually the hardest
game i've ever played it was un-fucking- believably difficult it was unbearable unbearable at times
and then this came out and now let me before i say anything do i think that this game is harder
than sekiro no i don't i think this game is as hard as you want it to be because of the open
world nature of it because you are allowed to go wherever you want sekiro will go down for me as
probably this i'm talking sekiro will go down that's probably the hardest thing i've ever done
truly um but this game is i would say you can say it's accessible right but it's only as hard as
it's only as easy as you're going to make it you can there's no like easy mode right just
you don't start the game and go oh yeah i'm gonna play on a normal casual experience where you know
you have a good time and uh the story plays out and no you have to learn how to make the game
easier the game's not gonna tell you how to make it easier but you can um and if you need to level
up a few more times and whatever who cares that's not a big deal if you get enjoyment out of you
know coming here at soul level like 60 or 70 damn that's gonna be fucking hard why are you still
talking you're stun locked i've been just rambling but what i'm a streamer well i'm literally live
streaming right now you what i'm not supposed to talk you are i'm literally live streaming right
fucking style i'd get um but do i think this game could be the hardest one it could be i think the
bosses though so far have been some of the hardest when you fight them at the you know current like
on a level that you're supposed to be in quotes but i think this is this is probably the most
enjoyable of the from software games i truly believe that if you want to play a game that's
going to literally beat the ever-living fucking shit out of you without any remorse and it's it's
secure um this game can be that but it doesn't have to be and i know that there's bosses coming
up here in the next like six to ten hours in the game that people have said oh my god i wanted to
fucking uninstall the game right we'll see dark souls 2 is the most enjoyable but you get to decide
that depending on how you play these games secure is still more than 60 is it is it really still
full price i mean but my long-winded point with this was a lot of people were concerned when these
games started to become popular and i mean pre-patch for dan should should prove to you
that that kind of didn't matter and some of the bosses that are in the end of this game that
i've heard are un-fucking bearable so i still think it has the same charm i still think it
has the same uh pull i still think it's a very very difficult fun enjoyable interesting experience
need more balancing in the game i'm concerned about the spirit summons changing the balance for
non-users yeah but that is kind of hard mode isn't it if you don't use a summon and you're
you are the game is designed for you to be utilizing that stuff you can make this game
this game is hard or as easy as you want which is cool okay margit and um and godric back to back
after having no experience in the game and having not played a from software game in a while
what is that noise they were really really really hard for me they were very hard they
were very difficult um but i don't know from there there were summoning signs outside the
door in the other from software games as well you could summon a person to come help you
not just co-op like there would be a summoning sign and a lot of bosses in all the other from
software games so that's kind of the same thing isn't it margit is harder than 90 percent of the
bosses in this game i kind of think of who i besides radan which radan i thought was insane
godric was difficult but godric felt fair who hasn't felt i mean renala was all right once you
okay renala was bad until you figured out like kind of the gimmick behind it summons are way
tankier than some players ry card is pretty hard well we're about to find that out probably very
soon people will unironically say these things and still have stacked bugged buffs in the
fucking game and complain about bosses i mean there's a lot of crazy shit in it but that and
the point of all these games is they're unbelievably difficult until they're not
i was tearing my fucking hair out playing against margit and if you put me against margit right now
i would probably beat him in one or two tries like it's just it's just like i don't understand
what's happening i keep dying to this this is un-fucking-bearable this game sucks it's too hard
i would probably beat him first try maybe second try because i just know everything that he does
that's quite yeah that it's quite a comment your forehead looks sweaty it's because it is very
very much so wash your face it's it's because there's a piece of hair falling down it makes
me look like greasy there i fixed it but let me tell you i this game has so much content
that even okay what are you using as a weapon what even is this thing i get that this game has the
same amount of content i think is like all the dark souls games in the series have together
combined in all their dlc it's a little ridiculous all right these travel where does this go
what's your point my what do you mean what's my point you've i've been making it the whole time
game somebody said that they're they were they're afraid that this game is too easy or that with
the popularity comes a uh the game is going to be too easy and so from software is going to keep
making games and they're going to be simple and my point is that they've proven that that's not the
case 45 minute explanation it's a goddamn pod just title it podcast about from software okay
you have pointed ahead that last boss in securo though oh man that was the one of the most
unbearable experiences i think that took i took it took me like i think 50 to 60 attempts to beat
that guy and it was pain and suffering that was one of the hardest things i've ever had to do
he's easier than margit no no not a chance at help not in 100 million years you don't have to
parry every single move margit does to you you do with that other one all right there was a hold on
what is up here i had a lot of trouble with the ape yeah that was a that was bad too
oh what's that some of these bosses are harder than the last boss
imagine right i'm imagining that's probably the case what also do i think this game is nearly
as good as what everyone's saying no i think like dark souls 2 is probably better
dark souls one is probably better mario sunshine is probably better i think this probably sits at
like um i think the dark souls prepare to die edition on pc i think is a little bit more
polished than this game is all right i don't want to go that way yet no it's okay trying to take
my special baby bloodborne away from the number one spot it's gonna be really hard oh i fought
you on that bridge before i know what you do always the lock on i got it oh i still got it
oh panic stop panicking stop oh sorry shit what the fuck no i don't have any piano fuck damn it
oh oh my stamina oh i had it i just like figured oh god damn it i shouldn't have even drank the
potion i just was panicking because i was like fuck fuck oh it wasn't even greed it was just
fuck all right where where was that oh damn it i'm so mad oh i had it too oh i'm so frustrated
at myself why did i even i shouldn't have even drank it i could have killed it other bonfire
oh yeah the bridge the bridge right right right well i'm kind of fucked here and look now i'm
gonna get in my head and i'm gonna fucking lose over and over again shit all right which
bonfire this one here right first try oh the church oh you know now you know what really
fucked it up it was me doing the weapon art without any mana i just that that was that was
the big mistake because if i had known that i didn't have any mana if i'd even looked
i wouldn't have done it and i wouldn't have gotten hit that like third time all right let's do it
dude please change to your other hand you fucking idiot okay hey oh you can do it too through the
fucking wall all right stop tilting just fucking play come on fucking stop rolling oh shit oh wrong
button fuck fuck you the timing on that sucks absolute balls okay god skin stitcher noble
presence i feel like you made this boss in the sims serpents and what amnion from a womb that
bore unintended offspring it will never dry out remaining damp indefinitely that's kind of
disgusting okay just like your forehead shut up leave me alone that was the mcridler all right
what do we got for time uh all right it's getting late i think i'm gonna call it here about seven
hours oh i got this too where is it x and strength oh it's that thing okay this is a good time stop
so i am going to tentatively tell you and handle a full shift um i mean i my elden ring streams have
been like 10 hours nine to 12 some it's just i haven't been feeling that great so i kind of
don't want to push it more than like eight plus nine plus hours because i know i will
so i'm not gonna i've had stomach did you guys know colitis proctitis that shit it's back
it's flared up and i'm trying to take care of it i have medicine for it it usually takes like a
week or two sometimes to get rid of it uh to put it back into i guess you'd call it remission
uh let me i'm not let me clean some stuff up first uh let me see but let me let me see i don't
it's been pretty much tentative like if i can stream sitting here is really like not great i
really need to go do stuff with my body uh more than a few times so let me tentatively say
that the next stream will be on tuesday if i if i get up tomorrow and i'm fine i might just
stream tomorrow but let me tentatively just say tuesday um there's so much more left in the game
i can't wait so tuesday so 22nd if i'm filling up to it tomorrow then maybe but let's just say tuesday
same time around four yeah it's it's annoying but you know sometimes it has to be a thing that's
dealt with and it usually is dealt with very quickly let me level up first though all right
endurance is now at 20 that is exactly where i wanted it i don't need to do any more than that
that's perfect we still have a lot to do here and then there's even more to do here this is this
game's i just don't even know what to say is there more up here yeah have a great night thanks for
sticking around i don't these have been going late i know i start late and i go late so i apologize
if it's like three o'clock two o'clock in the morning for you right now uh but we will continue
we'll pick it up on tuesday right from here i'm assuming that i gotta go this way and maybe even
this way and then we're probably gonna get towards like the final finale of the game i would say
other two or three streams maybe total are you gonna do corn holio on tuesday well it depends
on if i die like 40 times in the same boss i'm gonna rest here call it there's still a ton more
left yeah there is there's a lot i'm really looking forward to it are gonna be like four
streams that's awesome that means i get to play more much love to you thanks for sticking around
keep an eye on the sus tuesday tentative tuesday the 22nd at four o'clock pacific more elden ring
we are going to be changing it up a little bit soon because uh ludwig and i are going to be doing
a stream together on the 29th that should be a fun time it's going to be kind of mayhem but
it'll be fun i'll probably break up elden ring again this week so if i stream elden ring on tuesday
then probably you know maybe on wednesday or thursday we'll do something else break it up
break it up a little bit go back to elden ring on the weekend and then the uh stream with me
and ludwig house flipper has new dlc well i mean that's i gotta play it right did you do a dos
night you know that actually is not a bad idea it sounds kind of fun we'll break it up because
i don't i don't want just every single stream to be elden ring because even for me i gotta break
it up too it's a no it's not till may oh okay avoid the adult dos games yeah it's been a week
since you put yeah but i mean the next i'm playing elden ring for at least another seven to eight
hours on tuesday so there'll be plenty more and i i have essentially committed to completing the
game on stream so i don't think that's going to be a scenario where that doesn't happen
eventually can we see auto next time yeah yeah i'll put auto on camera next time
the progress wise we kind of explored a lot i got through a little bit of the manner here
it's just so easy to sync just days into this game it's just ridiculous all progress
is good progress that's right yeah new map too i also want to go back out here i want to do the
assassination missions and i want to look around that the manner a little more i feel like i kind
of ran by it all right see you guys on tuesday keep an eye on sus make it to do list yeah i did that
a few streams ago and it was way way i was way more calculated i knew i knew the three or four
areas i was going to go on stream and i went there well i'll do that all right good night guys see
you tuesday take care yourselves bye