Hey, what is going on everybody? Jirba here with some more One in the Chamber, Call of Duty Black Ops 2, and away we go.
Oh Jesus, right off the bat I turned the corner. Oh, you bastard, he was lying on the ground.
I'll make a note of that. I'll make a mental note of that. You son of a bitch.
Something going on in this- Whoa, what the hell? That guy just teleported! That guy just teleported through my screen!
That guy, what the hell was that?
Alright, gotta get my bearings here.
That's a bad shot, I'm not taking that.
Let's find my way back downstairs.
They could be anywhere.
There's a guy up here. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come here.
Where the- Damn!
Don't shoot me!
Get it! No, there's another guy!
No, there's not. Yeah, there is!
Damn it! Damn it, crouch!
Here he comes, ready?
It actually worked!
It actually worked.
I can't even think.
Too many things going on in my brain.
Whoa, what the hell? I just like, panic knifed.
Oh boy.
Oh boy, oh.
What? He's still running.
The guy back here, I'm gonna try and just-
God, I didn't make one shot with-
I didn't make one shot with this freaking knife.
I mean, with this freaking gun.
I gotta- I need to- I could still win this.
Just gotta play smart. There's only two guys here.
Time to play smart. Here we go.
Smart German, here we go.
Wow, that guy's just sitting right there.
Oh, what do you know about that one?
Bastard.
Is that him? That's him!
What?
No! No!
I don't think I've played on this map yet.
This is one of the only ones that nobody ever plays on.
Maybe I have. Let's go.
This map is big, too. This is a big map.
This is gonna be tough.
Damn it. That guy's got a bullet.
Freak him out. It worked.
Wow. Hey, man. Whoa.
Big map. Big casualties.
I got ya. I still got ya.
I got ya. Whoa, a guy behind me.
No reason to freak out.
No reason to freak out. No reason to-
Geez! Louise!
Oh my goodness. People are everywhere.
Oh, there's a guy behind me, too.
Get out of my face!
Let's go down. I got three bullets here.
Just calm down, Jerma. Just calm down.
You don't gotta freak out.
You got three shots in this gun.
You got the upper hand. There we go.
See this guy right here? This guy's toast, too.
If I could- He's probably gonna-
I'm scared. I am legitimately scared to go around this corner.
Here's a guy right here. Come on.
Show yourself. Oh, this guy's doing a ring
around the Rosie with me.
Come on, man! Come on!
No! And he got the kill!
Oh!
Ashes, ashes. We all freakin'
fall down, apparently.
I'm gonna shoot that guy in his head
when I get the chance. Is anybody even over here?
There's only one dude. I got one life.
What? What is going on in this room?
Why are there two guys just, like, hanging out in here?
What the hell is going on in here?
What on earth-
What on earth is happening in this room?
Those two guys are just, like, sitting there
having tea. Alright.
I'm on my last life now.
I'm gonna die. There's one guy in here.
Yeah. Show your- Put your head
through that door. What?
Oh, man. Oh, man!
No! No! No!
Oh, I lose!
Well, not technically
no. Let's see. I got nine kills.
Yeah, nobody could pass that right now.
The next guy below me has three.
So, yeah, I'm going to win
this game. Let's think about one of the chamber.
You can kill, like, five or six
people in a row and then die three times in a row
and still win the game, so it's pretty cool.
Anyways, let's see how this ends. Let's go, man!
Hey, look, chickpeas!
I can't believe I died. I would have
been, like, 12 and 0 if I didn't screw up in one place.
But there was, like, two guys
camping in the same room. What the hell was that
all about? Ban them all, boot it, get them
out of here. Let's close it out on the cruise
level. Time to take a cruise.
Okay, we got a guy right here.
And we got a guy over there, too.
Two guys. Don't be too crazy.
Don't be too crazy.
Don't be too...
Why did I do that?
What the hell?
The knife went... Get up the stairs!
There's a guy coming up. Oh, God!
Oh, God! Oh, my God!
He's coming! No, he's not.
Oh, what? Come on!
Oh, Lord!
I don't know how those knives...
How are these knives not hitting?
I mean,
I have a three bar, but that's not
that bad.
Dude, those knives were going into, like,
the abyss. It's as if I wasn't even hitting
the button. It's alright.
We'll push through here. We'll push through.
Wow! I shouldn't even knife
anybody anymore.
I should just put the knife away.
Last guy, last guy, last guy.
Hello there!
Mr. Guy!
Moment of truth! The knife!
Alright, I'm gonna get this guy right now.
I'm not gonna use the knife.
Oh, it doesn't even matter.
The knife prevails!
Oh, my goodness.
Alright, well, that's gonna wrap it up here, guys.
Thank you so much for watching. I really do
appreciate it. And I'll see you all next time.
And of course, take care, everybody.
Connection interrupted!