What's up? What's up? What's up? Hey, how are you? How you doing?
Welcome back. Another day, day three. Elden Ring will be your host for the festivities today as we
continue to trek through the lands between. Horse? What? You like the title? Yeah. How's my day been?
It's been pretty good. I want to play this game so bad. I was talking to Holly last night and I was
like, hey, like, what if I made like another character just like I played like at the same
time? But then I realized if I were to play this game off stream, I wouldn't, there would be no
time for me to sleep or eat because I stopped the stream last night at what like 10, 11 p.m. 12,
something like that. The night before was like two o'clock in the morning. If I would play off stream
after that, there's no time for me to go to bed. Like I'm just going to bed, waking up,
doing some like morning routine, early afternoon routine stuff, and then like playing this game
for 10 straight hours. So I don't have time to make a new character. You're addicted. Yeah,
I mean it's a good feeling though. It's a really good feeling. It's hasn't, it's been a long time.
If you're going to get three streams that are eight to nine to 10 hours in a row on this channel,
you better believe that I'm very, very interested in the thing that I'm streaming.
When was the last time I streamed anything three times in a row?
Ever. Besides Dollhouse. It's been a very long time. House Flipper, was House Flipper three
streams in a row though? I don't think it was. Sometimes I'll do two and then I'll take like
three or four days and then do it again. But this is, it's been a while. How have I been feeling?
Um, I don't, I, I don't want to like concern anybody because if I say the wrong thing here
and people are going to get concerned. So without doing that, let me just tell you that I've been
fine. I've been monitoring and managing how my body feels. I'm doing all right. I'm doing good.
But I would be lying if I told you that it wasn't, um, I didn't feel it.
I have been taking a Tylenol pretty much every day here. One dose, uh, kind of right before I
start. I'm doing good. And it, it works. It helps enough for it to be like, I'm fine. He's addicted
to Tylenol. No, I'm not. It's been, it's literally, I, I've been taking Tylenol. The last time I took
Tylenol was probably like, I don't know, maybe like fucking two, a month or two ago, two months
ago. No, and we're talking, I, I, look, I, I know, I know that like, you're an idiot. He's gonna,
he's gonna take too much Tylenol. Trust me when I say like medical shit, I'm very, very much aware
of everything. I'm very much in tune with how like what you should and shouldn't be doing. Trust me.
I know the exact amount of milligrams of, uh, acetaminophen that you really can't take in a 24
hour period, but trust me, I'm very aware of my body. And I am taking on a daily basis here
well below 50% of what is even addressed on the bottle. So don't worry. I'm going to be fine.
But I know people might've been concerned about, dude, do you really think you should be doing
this? Like 10 hour streams, three days in a row, like 30 hours of streaming in a row. And you have
very, you have a right to be concerned, right? Cause obviously like over the years it's been like,
Hey, I have a bunch of medical problems, but I'm good. I'm good. And we'll see how we feel tonight.
It's a very real chance that maybe tonight I'm like, let's go again tomorrow. We'll see.
There any updates on the medical stuff? No, not really. And I probably would rather not share it
anyways, because I feel like it's kind of, um, it's kind of like a downer. You haven't heard me talk
about it too much recently because it's just a downer. It just is. And I would rather like
have the mood of these streams be a place where like, I can just have fun and we can just kind of
chill and just do whatever and have a good time and have to like, you know, every week or two
kind of tell you guys like how I'm feeling and how like my back hurts and my chest hurts.
Cause I did that for a little while. I did, I did that for like, I don't know, there was a period
where like a few months in a row, it's like, it felt like that was kind of half the shit that I
talked about. So I would rather just kind of not have to talk about it really, just deal with it
on my own. And if there's something significant that I would ever tell you about, obviously I
would. Um, especially if it was going to affect the streams and you know, if I was going to need
to take time or something, but it's kind of downer and I don't want to make it a downer
because it's something I really don't like to focus on anyways. Uh, that's it guys. Every hour
he's going to actually, I thought about making the title, uh, guaranteed loud sound every 30
minutes. Please adjust your volume. Um, but I kind of feel like that would be like a deterrent for
people like to not even click on the stream because that means that doesn't mean what you
guys think it means, right? Oh, he's going to scream. He's going to yell to me as somebody
that's an outside viewer that might not know this channel. That could mean like, I'm going to just
do like an ear blast sound every 30 minutes to be funny and yeah, air horns. And I feel like, yeah,
I don't think I would want to click on that stream because if you click on that stream and you're in
that period where it's like 10 seconds until a noise, what if you're not ready? Yeah, it would
be a good bit. Yeah, but good bits are only funny. You know, if everybody can enjoy them, right? Uh,
I think that having a bit that's funny and that look, people would come in maybe and they'd be
like, okay, this way there's no like going to be like air horns in my ears. Make a loud sound now
Bicycle honk every time a runes are lost. Anyways, yeah, there you go. Life update. It's time to uh,
play Elden Ring. Ready. Very excitable. And yeah, look what I got right here. I'll show you right
now. Take a quick look. You'll see it. Got, I'm prepared. Very prepared. God, of course. What,
what would a 10 hour stream be without my fucking magical macho powder? What would a stream be
without my magical macho powder? Green shirt. It's a dollar shirt. These actually fit really
well and they're really comfortable. I was just saying that because it's my own merch.
You look uncanny valley today. Respectful. Where have you been hiding? I took you for
now. All right. So what were we doing? Your arms then uncanny and handsome way. I'm just fucking
around. Okay. There are some things that I, I, the last thing I did was I beat that, um, that like
sewer boss. I need to start focusing on mind because I don't have enough. I beat that boss
so early. I don't even have enough mana to summon the guy that you get for a reward for beating that
boss. So, uh, I have to, I want to get mind up because I feel like that could be a huge,
huge game changer and you beat the game already. This is pain. Also, please permanently ban me.
Hmm. I'm thinking about it. I'm thinking about if you should get permanently banned or not.
Probably, but I'm going to do the thing you don't want and that's not do anything. Yeah.
You just, yeah. Okay. You just get to sit here and like just chat and chill and have a good time.
Fucking idiot. You just get to like hang out and like talk and like enjoy like the like company
of the other community members. Hmm. Fucking moron. Can't fucking believe it. Got them.
Yeah. Get rid of them. Yeah. Got them. All right. I need to go here. There's a few spots.
I like, I don't know what the hell happened over here, but like I ended up over here and I don't,
I like, look at the map. It's cut in half. I'm not supposed to be over here. And like,
I was doing shit over here. So I definitely have to be like over here or like here.
I'm not supposed to be there. The game's like, what are you doing, dude? It was rejected.
Wait, what? What did Holly say? I have to go, I have to wash some shirts. He's been sweating
through them all. I've gone through like, I mean, I'll be honest. I've gone through probably like
seven t-shirts, like six t-shirts in the last like three days, two days. I can't help it. I'm
fucking disgusting. What do you want me to tell you? My room is hot. The shirts are like
suffocating. I, this is why I don't have, I don't have the balls to do this, but like imagine if I
was just sitting here with no shirt on, just sitting here. I would be doing that right now.
I really would be, but like, I don't think I, I can't do that at this point, right? Like I can't.
I would be sitting here like this and have like a cigarette just like hanging out of my mouth.
Oh shit, man. Fuck. I would do like huge burps and shit. If only I could just be the real me on camera.
We're going to go up this way. You can literally, I'm just kidding around. He's unleashed. No,
I don't want to have my fucking shirt off on camera. Like, oh yeah, let's just be comfy and
like have like just sit there with no shirt on. I can imagine the amount of people that would just
like zoom in on my fucking belly button. Like what? Get the fuck out of here. Like, you know
what I mean? Like, like I'm not doing, I don't, that's why. Yeah. Cause guess what? I, I have my
shirt off just like chilling comfortable, like on cam, whatever. And like some of you guys are
going to zoom into the, my belly button, crop it really close, draw eyes up above the belly button,
add some like, like a lip detail, like to the belly button and put a nose on it and be like,
oh, new German character, like belly button Andy or something. And it's, and that, that would be,
that would be on the front page of fucking every Reddit or something. Like that would be on my
Reddit. That would be on, there'd be everywhere. And like you, you would like make that a character
and I wouldn't have any control over it. You must've thought about this way too much.
Hey, he definitely will. Yeah, of course they will. Like, what do you mean?
He's going to show his belly button. Your character is ugly. Well, I mean, I mean,
I based it off of you. I need a glint stone key. I'm like just, I'm just doing burns today.
Elden Ring just kind of makes me like mean. Be a tank top streamer. Oh, I'm just going to wear
whatever makes me comfortable. He's wicked toxic today. All right, let's go. I want to, I need to
go up here. This is where the academy is, right? Cause this is where I need to go. This is the
sorcery place. We're going to go here. It's going to be a shitload of sorcery items because why would
he say, oh yes. Oh, the sorcery tower, the sorcery kingdom, all the academy of sorcerers. Like there's
going to be like a cool ass weapon here and I'm going to be able to use it. So this way, let's go
apologize right now. Or do the Goku. It's the same effect. Oh, I don't know. I'm really, I'm
really, I am so, you know, I'm really, I need to really, I need to really go through something to
you guys. I need to just, I'm very, very, I hope you got that. I hope that came through.
I hope it was genuine. Okay. Well, I can't go this way. So how the fuck do I get over there?
All right. There's a path over there. God, I love this game. That path connects. Where? Here.
Where is it? Is it like a, is it water in between? No, there's not like a lake or anything. All
right. It's like, I think I can drop down and not die. Please everybody pray. Will I die from this?
Yep. Okay. I prayed for you to die. Oh, I, this is one funny one guy moment that I saw after the
fact, uh, when I was dying over and over again, and I was complaining about all the gravestones,
the graveyard boss member, like all the gravestones, I specifically was really,
really pissed off. And I was saying, what the fuck is this? Why are there so many gravestones here?
How many people have died here? This is fucking ridiculous. Somebody in chat said, uh, they're
all your gravestones. And it was like, Holy shit. I wish I caught that. That was fucking hilarious.
My audio is delayed. I don't think it is audio like, wait, game audio. Or you mean like me.
I have a really weird way of talking. I think people like come to the stream and they, when I
have cam on, like my voice has its own mouth that makes like sounds like my down here. I can just
sit here like this. And my vocal cords are just actually, they're, they're, they're talking under
there. There's lips down here moving. Like I can actually do that. So when I talk, my blips don't
move maybe that much. Maybe as much as you think they should be. I don't know. There's people
always go, dude, your audio is like delayed. Like sometimes your mouth doesn't move. And it's like,
well, I don't know, man, I've got like, I've got like a mouth down here. I'm losing my mind.
He's, this dude is working. All right. Where do I go? Where do I go? I don't know where to go.
Okay. I'm fucking near, I need to settle down because like, I don't know why I act like this
when I play these games, like something about from software games, just like open up some weird
thing in my brain where like, I'm constantly just not being serious and just constantly just
fucking around. It never stops. It only stops when I go into a boss room and then I get like mad
and I hate everybody. We was weird. How the fuck do I get over there? He's having so much fucking
fun. Monka S I think that might be what it is. Wait. Oh, okay. All right. This is it right here.
Very good. Very good. Very good. Very good. By the way, the more the less that I move my lips,
the less calories that I burn in my like mouth. So it means I can talk way longer
because my mouth doesn't get like tired by like talking. So like I can rest my mouth and I can
really speak very, very clearly for a long period of time. All right. Finally, let's go.
Stream begins now. Okay. Microwave boy. Microwave boy. That sounds like a really,
stupid shitty superhero. Microwave boy to save the day. Oh, how did you get your powers?
I was making popcorn one day and I opened it up midway through and I breathed in too much of the
microwave radiation. Oh, I accidentally microwaved myself. Okay. What? How? He heats up too many hot
pockets. Yeah. I don't know how I got all you can like shoot like radio waves through his fingers.
And it's like, well, what happened, dude? I ate four hot pockets a day for 10 years. Oh no,
he's slipping into do watch out. Watch out. Get out of here. Whoa. We've got a sauce.
We must be getting close to the academy. Oh, gauntlets. This is going to be a big deal. I
actually can't wait to be here. I think that's it up there. The big castle looking thing. Oh,
fine. Let's go. Take them on. Oh, fine. Let's go. Take them on. And finally,
so I got my flasks refilled because I cleared the camp. Let's go explore. Do doofenshmirtz or riot.
I just, I offhandedly didn't do for it. I don't think I could even do it again if I really even
tried. Oh, I could probably do it. I can't do it. I need to hear it a few times. If I were to listen
to it, if I were to watch an episode of Phineas and Ferb, I would probably do a much better job
because I need to hear it. So anything else here? I don't think so. I got like that cookbook thing,
which I have to sit down. And I know like stalling stalling, hurry up and play the game.
But I do need to sit down and figure out that all the cooking cookbook crafting stuff.
That's something that needs to be done. This place is pretty narrow. So wait, oh, what's over here?
Can we move on to the academy? Or do I go look at the lake and get a dragon to drop on me again?
Go in the tent, please. Tent, please, please. The tent. Shut up. Sorry, I can't get it to stop.
It's like too much fun to just like pretend to like be mad at people. I don't know. I don't know
what this game is. It's weird to me. What tent? Tent? 139. I don't know what you mean by tent.
There's nothing in any of these tents. Oh, I was going to leave. You're pretending. I honestly got
it. I don't. I think you're just fucking with me. What's in one of the tents? Guys, I'm only
streaming for like 10 hours today. We don't have time for this. What? Where? In the tent.
How was I supposed to see that? There's nothing even in here. It's just a smoldering butterfly.
You guys are acting like it was a fucking great sword. I don't know how people see that shit.
How do you even see that? What? Wow. That looks cool. We're taking a second here. Wow. This is so
cool. This looks unbelievable. It does look so good. Oh, I can already see. I can already see
the VATI videos on this game, right? Like I can't wait. I can't wait to beat this game,
have no fucking idea what happened, have absolutely no idea who any of the characters' names are,
and then watch like four hours of VATI videos where he gets to tell me everything. He'll just
tell me literally everything I need to know. Okay, so what's over here? And then forget it again.
And then forget it again and come back a year later and watch the same VATI videos a year later
to be like, oh yeah, yeah, that game's great. That story was pretty cool. It's only like a
once a year rotation. Is that a crab or is it a turtle or is that one of those? Oh,
let's just go get it. That was one of those like pus bubbles. Okay, I know they've had a lot of
time to see what other like worlds look like and shit, but as much as I talk shit about like some
of the stuff that I don't like about, you know, like, oh, the boss is to delay the attack delays.
This is the first time that FromSoftware's made an open world game and it's the actual open world
is fucking unbelievable, like un fucking believable. How come companies that have been spending
two decades making open world games still can't seem to get it right? I don't get it. It seems
kind of empty. I don't, um, no, I don't think so. I think we see like random camps. We see random
shit happen all the time. Um, but just like art, like just artistically, right? Just like the
aesthetic of an open world everywhere feels really different and really interesting, but really
connected at the same time. It's just, it's, it's just beautiful. It's just amazingly put together,
like at least the actual like technical kind of artistic representation. Take a picture.
This is a screenshot game. It is. What is this? Glintstone firefly? What is that? Where is it?
Material used for crafting items. Glass, now that his tail is a glintstone, it can no longer be
eulie potential mates. So it's a, is it crafting material? Dude, whatever. It's a horse. All right,
I'm going to just explore. We're just looking. I know some people said Breath of the Wild. I know
I'm so stupidly just not interested in Zelda. I know, but Breath of the Wild, people are saying
like, dude, just please for the love of God, play it. If you think this is good, am I going to be
one of those people that plays Breath of the Wild eventually after this and is like, yeah, I'm,
that's like one of the best things ever. I don't know why I won't. Yes. Yes. Yes. Nah, nah, nah.
Okay. That was like song lyrics. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Okay. Got another firefly. Anything else here? There's got to be like a little dungeon or
something there. That's a fucking lobster. That is a lobster. That's crazy. There's a lobster.
There's always crabs in from software games, but there's never been a lobster.
This is freaking me out a little bit. It's weird. He's got a lot of health. That's crazy.
Oh my God. He's like a pistol sprint. Oh fuck, that hurt. Oh, I thought he was going to be longer
than that. Fuck, he's quick too. He's way faster than the crabs. I think I got to get off the
horse. I think I just got to fight him. Yep. I got to get off the horse. We got to go. You
are fast. Lobsters are not this fast. I'm out of, I'm out of juice. You are as fast as I am on a
horse as a fucking lobster. Get out of here. He's stuck in the ground. All right. We're good. Damn.
That was awesome. Oh, probably a fresh lobster claw. Drip of white flesh. Oh, it's actually a
lobster. Cheese lobster. I don't want to have to say this every time I stream this game.
Sorcery works until it doesn't. And when it doesn't work, good luck. Cause now you got to
fucking use your other weapons like the claw. How many, I would, all the naysayers I'd like to,
let's take a minute here. This is Copium. Is it though? I have fought five bosses so far. How
many of them did I use sorcery more than 10% of the time? How many bosses have I fought in this
game? And I used melee only and maybe sorcery, maybe like for one or two seconds. Thank you.
Thank you, bro. Stop ranting every 30 seconds. Did you see the title of the stream?
What is the title? Oh, right. It doesn't say meltdown every 30 seconds or every 30 minutes,
whatever. All right. I need to find a bonfire. Get off the ledge. It's going to fuck with me.
Just why did he, that was a weird scream. That was kind of like a goofy scream. Oh, come on. Get
out of here. You're going to really piss me off if you kill me. We're just going. Okay. Wait,
wait, wait. We can make them fight each other. Can we? All right. I'm going in a random direction
here. I need to take a second. Am I still being chased? Nice. Perfect. Somebody behind me. Perfect.
Awesome. All right. Let's get our bearings. There's the academy. And speaking of academies,
can we talk about education? So, verified ruins. Ooh, okay. I could probably go down there.
I'm going that way. We're going over here. We're going to the ruins. It's definitely like a little
dungeon or something here. Okay. All right. I understand your criticism, right? I get, like,
you, I, I get it. I understand. Like the people that are like, oh, you fucking sorcerer. Like,
okay. Right here, you can complain, but don't complain during a boss fight because you know how
it is. Okay. The ruins are down here. Verified ruins. All right. Let's get this guy out. Where
are you? Why does it sound like he's behind me? Where is he? All right. Let's go, dude. Come on.
Come on. What was that? This thing does crazy great damage. Too slow. Too slow again. Too slow
again, but I didn't get hit by it. I blocked that. I don't know how I blocked that. Is there the
backstab technique? Oh, what's the guard one? Maybe I should, should I take a second to figure
out how that works? There's a different parry in this game, right? There's like a guard parry.
How does that work? Yes, there is. Okay. So how does it work? R2 right after guarding.
What? So they gave, they made an easier parry. They made a parry that's like an easy parry.
Is that that reliable? Because if that's that reliable, then having a shield and being like
heavy armor guy just became like the best way to play this game. Let me try that again.
Okay. That's seriously, that's unbelievable. What? Okay. There's somebody behind her.
Why would you ever parry? What's the, why would you ever parry? Does that work on other?
Okay. There's no reason to parry in this game. At least normal enemies. If you have a shield.
That's ridiculous. Does it, does it only, wait, does it work on like,
what? I can't, I can't believe it. That's so much stronger than that. Because if you missed this
with the few frames that you can hit it, you're just fucked. It doesn't always break their stance
though. So it doesn't work on bosses though, right? There's a huge window for you to be able to do that.
What's the downside? There has to be a downside, right? Basic enemies are easy anyways. Yeah,
that's true. I guess that's, you know what? If you wanted kind of to block and be able to parry like
that on the kind of normal enemies, I guess that's, it only works really on basic enemies.
That's that, you know, that's cool. That's all right. Like maybe some of the harder
enemies you can't do it to. Does it take a bunch of stamina? I wasn't really paying attention.
Only good in a few circumstances. All right, well, I mean, now that I know that,
why would I ever try to parry a regular enemy ever again? You've seen me do it a bunch of
times in the last three days. There's no point. I'll fight the lobster. I already did. All right,
there's, this wouldn't be on the map if I couldn't go down somewhere. Use it on the lobster. You're
going to get mocked by everyone if you do it. Okay, so I only do guard parries and the most
OP sorcery move. Do I drop to like, do I drop like 80 percent viewership? I'm not going to do that.
I'm not going to do that. I'm going to use it if I need to. All right, so where I need to find a
place to go down. This looks promising. There's one of these statues here. What's this? Oh, no.
Come on, there's got to be something to do here. There's 100 million percent of place to go down.
What's that? Arry the shrimp or you're a journalist. Come out one and all from the
darkness underground and let us offer unto the maiden our eyes. Where are, he's looking for the
underground passage too. It's going to be like a weird spot. I didn't check over here yet. Runes?
Tell a joke, funny man. The crowd demands it. Don't demand things from me.
Don't, do not demand things from me. Okay, you can highly suggest things.
Do not demand things. Everyone here is allowed one question per year, which I will or will not
answer. If any other questions come up during the course of that year, you are using more than your
allocated question allowance. It's infuriating. Where is this cave? I'm still technically like in
the ruins. Maybe over here. There's got to be a cave. I have to find it. I can't leave without
knowing what's down there. Come on. Where is it? That would kill me, I think. God damn it. It's
right here. Come on. Here, purified ruins. Smashing stone, smithing stone. What are you doing?
I'm looking for it. Oh yeah. Yep, there it is. I just had to fall through the ground.
Hell yeah, let's go. Dangerous looking. What do I touch first?
The brewery grape. And this is going to be like a poet. It's going to be like poisonous.
Blue fingers heirloom. What is that? What is it? Is it an item? Oh, should I have a golden seed?
Hell yeah. All right, this is the glintstone craftsman expands crafting repertoire.
There it is. Oh, the talisman raises faith. Come on. Everything I've found so far has been for
faith. I'm playing the wrong character. Shit. I keep stumbling upon these ruins and I keep
finding items that are awesome and really cool for a different guy. Wait, shit, I need that.
Where is it? Are you being serious? It's literally here. Wait, hold on, dude. I need that item. Where
is it? Yeah, let me be your Wikipedia page. It's here. If you go on the loo near a highway
north, it's south, southwest cheater. Oh, come on. Some of you guys that haven't started playing
this game, are you really trying to tell me that after a week or two, you're not going to go find
the item you want to use? I want to make a two handed great sword, a claymore of the depths build.
And where is the claymore of the depths? I'd like to go get it right now. Of course you are. Of
course you are. You might, you might do like one or two playthroughs completely blind, right?
Right. But like on your second, third and fourth playthrough, you're definitely going to like
just look at where the claymore of the depths is. I opened the wiki before I opened the game.
There's no shame. No, there really isn't. All right. There's not. If you just want to like
play the game, there's no shame in that. But the wiki doesn't, hell, the wiki doesn't make
you fight the boss better. The wiki just lets you get an item that you know you want.
I could tell you where that item is, but I'm not guaranteeing your safety getting it.
Okay. We're almost there. Little bit turn around here this way. That's our destination is up there.
Yes, it is. Did you earn it? And did you earn it? I mean, these games are so particular
that if you want to build a like faith based character and have like the best,
nowhere like the coolest faith based stuff is you're either going to stumble upon it.
Like I just did after at least a handful of playthroughs, right? Or if it's like,
I just want to build a faith character and I want a faith item, where's the nearest faith item?
Shit, these shit, the boys are revolting. I got to get my, where are they? Oh, we just did that.
Oh my God. There's somebody up there with a fucking grenade launcher. Oh, fuck off. I'm
getting that guy right now. Get down, get down, get down, get down. They're going to kill you on
the ladder. These guys are going to shoot me on the ladder. Watch out for the guy on the top.
All right. We're good. All right. Let's go kill this guy. Maybe this is where I'm going to start
to see. So I forgot him. Ooh, come on, come on. Staff of the deep sea. Shit. Oh, this guy had
like a dragon fruit beard. Look at this guy. Whoa. Is that a, is that a mask or does he actually
have two heads? Oh, we got it. Yay. Oh, I'm so happy. This is fucking awesome. All right.
Boost glint blade sorcery staff embedded with a blue glint stone and one of two types of Karen
staff gifted to enchanted nights. It enhances a glint blade sorcery that we are. There's no skill
to use this. Oh, that's what I thought. That was making fun of me. Oh, by the way, no skill. If
you use this shit loser, I thought that's what that meant. This weapon has no skill, no skill.
You use this shit. Okay. All right. Let me see. This is, that's exciting because that's intelligence
C. Let me see what it looks like. We're going to take a look. Ooh, double staff. Hell yeah.
What's the difference? So this is, this has been upgraded three times though. So this boosts
sorcery. This doesn't, and this is going to start scaling way better. 22 intelligence needed. I'm
just going to take, this is one 26, one 22 for now, just until I go to the blacksmith.
We're going to keep using this until I upgrade it. That's really exciting. I'm really happy.
Finally, I got like an actual sorcery weapon. Oops, wrong hands. I gotta get rid of some of
this shit. They have too many items. Okay. So that's good. I have too many things in my inventory.
All right. For now we're going to keep it because this is still has better scaling because it has
upgrades. What is that? What is that down there? Just looking at me. All right. I'm very happy.
Let's go. I have to go investigate what that is. Remember you promised you'd never make that sound
ever again. Yeah. And I made it like four times in a row and they were deep and they were excited.
Fall on the horse and jump off. I was kind of scared to do that. I figured it was going to
hurt me. All right. Let me just take one more extra second here. There might be something else here.
Highway lookout tower. All right. I know what this is. I'm going to head back. I'm going to
upgrade the staff. He's really just embracing himself today, isn't he? Um, I don't know. I'm
just kind of hanging out. Oh, right. We're going to upgrade the hell out of this thing.
You know what else I have that I haven't looked at? I have that painting that I could examine.
Maybe I'll do that too after this. Okay. To the left of the fireplace is where the blacksmith is.
Otherwise, I'll forget it every time. Okay. Here we go. Where is it? What's wrong? Can I not?
Additional items required? I only have one smithing stone? Smithing stone one. I only have
one of the- one smithing stone one. Smithing stone two. What's going on? Smithing stone one.
I think stone three. Oh, I need more of the little ones. What does that number actually mean?
Smithing stone one. Smithing stone two. Apparently, I have five smithing stone twos, but I have
one smithing stone one. It's the level of the stone. Does he sell them? Like one of them or two of them?
No. Well, that's annoying. I'm gonna keep this on balance. Yeah. Okay. Well, oh well.
Sell all your gear. It'll be really funny. Well, we're just gonna keep doing what we're doing.
Different level stones. Do I have enough to level up, by the way? I might have enough of the crunchies.
I think I do have enough crunchies to level up. Yeah, I definitely do. It's about 8,000.
And I've got to use my flask sieve. That's right. Thanks for the reminder. I would have forgot.
I don't get there. I'll be very, very close. 8,000. What does it take? 8,200. Okay. Well,
I'll just go kill like two things. Wait, what? I thought I had one. I need two now? Oh, shit. Okay.
All right. Well, I need to kill like two things. What's going on here? Oh, they're fighting the
ghosts. They're having a fight with the ghosts. Oh, shit. Are they gonna attack me or am I not
priority? Holy shit. This is so, this is absolutely free. I'm such a fucking bad person.
Hell yeah. I got the souls I needed. Just coming in, just unloading. I'll take care of this.
I should have waited. I should have waited until everybody was, uh, oh no. They, oh no. They called
their friend. Hey, help in the barrens, please. There's a level 40 just like killing us. Oh,
all right. I'll handle this. I'm level 50. And then I beat the level 50 as like a 42
and it's a fucking huge embarrassment. The guy logs off. What am I doing? Oh, I don't even man
off. We're going to go to the bonfire. Where's the fire? Where is it? Oh man. He's got magic.
Okay. He's got magic. Where's the fire? Where's the bonfire? Where's the, where is the fire? I
don't even remember where it is. Person here. Oh, the puppets, the puppets besiege us.
There it is. All right. So now I'm not going to mess that up again. I'm going to maybe get health
to 18 or dexterity 22. HP probably or mind. What is it? What does it get to? God, to get to 100,
it's going to be three, six, nine, 12, 15, 18, 20. It's going to be seven fucking levels
before I can use that guy. You're talking about like 60 plus a thousand souls,
all just to summon Oleg to reach a hundred mana at 20. This is going to, I'm going to be so under
my character is going to be so underdeveloped and I'm going to summon this guy and he's going to,
okay, we're going to do this. I'm going to spend the next like 70,000 souls on mind
and Oleg is going to get one hit killed by the next fucking single enemy.
It's going to be such a disaster and it'll be your fault and mine 50 50. We'll split it. Okay.
Let's try this again. It's definitely not magic for that guy because he's a magic. He's made out
of the, he's made out of the goo that I shoot out of my staff. So there's no way it's magic. So we
have to just kill them with our special moves. I think I'm going to have to get the boys involved.
Let's just, let's just go aggro him because then there'll be a bunch of people here. It'll be an
absolute mess. Okay. It's going to be a mess. Here we go. Like the big guy that's about to
come over here. Dude, do you not see what's over there? Look behind you. Why would you come after
me? There's a guy right there. He's killing everyone. All right. Just follow me. I'm just
getting on the voice. All right, come on. Let's go. Is he fighting the other ghosts? He's got a lot
of health. What just happened? He's bumped into something. What's wrong with him? What happened?
What? He's just tripped. Oh my God. That was embarrassing. That was really embarrassing.
What happened? Somebody is parrying him. One of them keeps parrying him. No, he's not running
into the wall. He's, one of these guys is parrying his attack. It's this guy. It's this knight with
the shield. Yeah. He's like, come on, do it again. And then I'm going to sneak over there and just
hit him in the face. It's definitely a parry. It's absolutely a parry. No, don't kill him. He's
actually very useful. Lock it. Parry. Boys. Let's go. No. Shit. Parry. Come on. Parry him, dude.
Please. Parry him. Parry. Parry. Almost. He didn't parry him. Whoa. I had no stamina.
Fuck. I thought he was done with his moves. Why did he get off the fucking horse?
This left stick is bound to crouch, which is a horse left stick. Just
why is there just take the crouch out of the game. It's fucking left stick that I pressed
left stick accidentally. So come on, dude. What the fuck? Do I really have to unbind this shit
every time I start the game? What a pain in the ass. I'm not the only one that's saying this.
I'm not the only one. Oh, okay. Let's go. Stupid ass bullshit. I had it too. It was dumb. All right.
Bring him over here. I have an easy solution. I have an easy solution to the problem.
Have crouch be you hold the button for more than one second. Like hold like, okay, crouch, right?
Like that's so easy. Just make it a hold. Make it you make it you hold it for like half a second.
Get him. You'd accidentally press it. Yeah, but you wouldn't hold it. You'd tap it and it wouldn't
do anything. Let's go. Oh my god. He killed me in one fucking hit. I thought he was done with his
moves. I thought he only does one and then two, just three, just a third. This lumbering fuck.
First of all, I'm not going to be doing magic on him. So take care of that. First of all,
he jumped into the sword. Well, I jumped in the sword because I didn't know he was doing a third
attack. Spawn this idiot. What was that? Okay, let's go. No more bullshit. Do the strategy.
Did you just kill everybody already? There's so many people to, okay, this is going to be
a huge problem. There's so many people to target to lock onto that it's hard to actually get my
targetter on him. Harriet, Harriet. Got him nice. I'm just a seagull at the beach.
Any food? Any scraps? I'm just a vulture. Where are my souls? I did the same mistake. I thought he
was going to, okay, here he comes. Good job guys. Go get him. Let's go. Do not get hit by one of
those. Oh, I'm stuck in a rock. I'm on a rock. I'm on a rock. I'm on a rock. I'm on a rock.
This guy is that that boy right there doesn't even know where he is.
That's just Torch Boy. Get out of here. Okay, we get it. You and me. The one survivor.
All right, so what were you protecting down here? He logged out. Obviously, whatever you're protecting
in here, there's a reason why you're doing it. What is it? Is it the main road? We're still dark.
Let me take a quick look. Kind of scary. There's definitely going to be a bonfire right here.
All right, where are we? Raya Lucaria, hallowed hall dedicated to the study of magic. Why
shut your doors to me? Am I barred from donning the crown of stone? Oh, we're here. This is it.
This is all. This is it. This is the castle of magic is right here. Okay, I could explore,
but not yet. I need to get the bonfire so I don't have to fight that big giant guy again.
Oh, was this place like abandoned? I know. I just walked off the edge, but that doesn't matter.
There's somebody in what appears to be a hot air balloon. What? I don't lock on. It's harder.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, I'm dead. Oh, that's 5,000 souls. Just got R1 spammed. That's so,
wow, that's so pretty. Where's the big tree? I'm so close to the castle.
It looks like a painting. Are we just going to have to take over?
Well, I don't think so. I think I should be fine. Dude, what the fuck are you doing?
All right. Give me the souls before I die again. All right. So what is it? What the hell is this
thing? Just destroy this? Golden rune. A plus six golden rune. Holy shit. I don't know which way I
should go. There's so many ways to go. Who are these little guys? Who's that? Is that thing alive?
Is that thing alive? That thing's alive. Holy shit. They're aiming at me.
This guy's face looks like half of every twitch emote I've ever seen.
It's like a zoomed in face. God, is that your move? I think I kind of have to take care of this thing,
right? That's the only amount of damage I'm doing to this. I don't think I can really reliably kill
that. This is going to take a long time. They're killing us. What? They're killing us. What? All
right. Now I definitely can't get in there. I wonder if they drop anything. Maybe you're really
not supposed to. Maybe you're not supposed to fight it. I don't know. I think that's just kind
of an annoying thing that's here. There's a bunch of them too. Yeah, they're just scattered around.
All right. So I'm going to keep going this way. I'm going to explore over here from the academy
gate town. Is that the academy right there? No. The academy's over here. Lucerne. It's a dex weapon.
Scales mostly with dex. I need 15 strength though. All right. I'm going to go this way
because I'm just going to explore over here for a minute. All right. There's like a little weirdo
guys. All right. I'm going to go over here. I think it's firing the missiles at me right now.
Thankfully there's not that much tracking on it. All right. What's over here?
Little hut. What do you got here? I don't know. I got to look at the new armor that I have to.
Silver pickled foul foot. I'm going to keep just going around the perimeter.
And then when I get too far, I'm going to teleport back and level up again because I'm,
I don't want to die here. Garnished golden sunflower. Ooh, alive. No. Wait, what do you,
what's this pot? Why are you guys spamming pot? Is that like a he doesn't know here comes like
the big pot enemy. That's what that is. Yeah. Yeah. It comes up. Oh, he doesn't know. Don't
tell him. It comes like the pickles bought. There's going to be like pickled bird feathers
or something, whatever it is that comes out of his spot and it does like poison damage.
It's because you smoke pot. I don't smoke pot slander. Something definitely back here.
Ooh, I got them all. Madam Mano land squirt ashes. Ooh, that's a new, uh, war thing.
I want to just kill all these. Those are new friends. Really? Oh, there's no Mano. Sorry.
It's just free. There might be something else here. I don't care. Nevermind. I lost interest.
What's this potty? It's going to be like the boss or something, right? I'm going to walk over here
and the giant pots going to land up here and nothing. I feel like from software,
put something weird up here, right? It's just cool looking rock or perimeter checking. I'm
just checking the perimeter. I'm just going around the edge, just seeing if there's anything here,
any caves, any interesting structures. Okay. There's a new bonfire here all the way in the
edge of this perimeter down here. Okay. I, I'm going to go here in a second, but not right now
because there's so many wolves. You guys are going to get that emo band saying, let's take these
both. He's probably 3000 or a thousand. Hell yeah. All right. So that I might have enough to do it
twice. Oh, this is, I'm going to be so far behind. I'm going to mind. What else does mine do?
What does mine do? It determines FP and affects focus. What does focus do? The resistance to sleep
and bouts of madness. So if I, there's going to be one boss in this game that's a sleep boss and
it's going to be the one that I can actually handle. I don't know. I feel like I kind of need
to level up this after I beat a boss and get like 30,000, 40,000 souls. Imagine the amount of damage
I'm not going to be doing to end up to bosses and enemies though, because I want to have 20 mind.
I think it has to be decks or intelligence at some point as the game starts to snowball in
its difficulty. I can't be like 20 in every stat. Andy do intelligence. I actually might,
let me just go over here. Don't howl. Just come at me and attack me. You got a lot of health.
I don't want to fight any of you. I just want to come over and see if there's any jewels behind
that rock. We back, but what's the, what's the, we're going to figure out what it is and I'm
going to know what it is in like a minute. I don't want to fight you regarding something over here.
What was it? They didn't attack in the pack. I don't know. There's a bunch. All right. I don't
want to, I just want to get through. I don't want to go kill the, all these wolves for no reason.
Anything over here? This is another area. Holy shit. Okay. This is, this game is way bigger than
I thought it was. I thought it was like this here. This game is huge. It's huge. All right.
We got to go back. It comes weeks of Elden Ring. Um, I don't know how I'm going to handle this. I
wonder because the game is so massive and there's so much going on. I don't think I have to play
through the entire game in the first six or seven days it comes out. If this truly is a hundred plus
hour experience, I, what's this? I get in here. Well, you just saw as a less than half of the full
map. How did they make this game? How did they do this? This doesn't make any sense. This is
impossible. This is half the map, less than half. What are you talking about? I don't, I can't,
I don't believe it. What you're talking, what you're saying seems almost impossible. What is
this thing? Oh, here it comes guys. Here comes the pot, right? Big open area where nothing is here.
Pots going to land. He's going to put his hand out like, Oh, no, it's just a couple of lobsters.
What are these lights mean? It's just cool looking. Is that actually mean anything?
Where did it go? What? That's not it. That's not the pot. Okay. Well, I don't know where it is.
You guys, it's going to fall on me and it's going to be so anticlimactic now because of your
emote spam. Okay. Boiled prawn shack. This is okay. Cool. Who's this? He's just
boiling a bunch of prawns. What's going on? What are you trying to start something, mate?
Just kill him. What the hell is wrong with you? Can I start something?
Piss off before I crack you in half. What the hell is wrong with you? You're trying to start something.
Piss off. Okay. So prawn NPC is, uh, doesn't like me. Maybe I can show up later with something.
Okay. Prawn guy says piss off to me. He's at prawn shack and swamp before academy.
Okay. So what's the point of the bonfire being here? How much further? Okay. This goes this way.
Yeah, that's the academy. I'm kind of going the right way, but why would there be a bonfire
right there? These are alive. This area is so weird. I hate it, but I love it. I hate this.
So fucking weird. So unsettling. Okay. I think I can upgrade staff now. So unsettling to me.
Lobsters and shit. The huge lobsters. Crabs don't really do that to me, but these big lobsters do.
What about over here? Weird little place to go through here. All right. I see something.
Oh, okay. Another one of these. They've been so much better about putting these in places.
They're kind of everywhere. They're everywhere. And the fact that you can just fast travel to
any of them is really actually awesome. All right. More of these crystals.
Maybe I can get some more of these, uh, fireflies. Yeah. This reminds me of fraggled rock. I like it.
Something about shining light, light coming through crystals like this.
I just want to, I just want to eat these. I know what they taste like. It's like blue raspberry,
little crab. There's a lot of this shit over here. There's a huge one. Well, okay. Um,
who's this person? That person's hiding. They not going to stop. Three damage, seven damage.
I don't think I'm supposed to be here unless there's some other way to fight those guys.
Three damage, three damage on a swing, seven damage on sorcery. I want to get a better view.
But what is the purpose of that? Why is that here? That's such a weird thing to be. That's
such a weird thing. Right. That's, this is weird. Why is this here? Two really, really strong enemies
that have a ton of health and a ton of defense. What are they? What's the garden? What are they
guarding? Something here. I don't know. Maybe I'll find out later. Nice. Jesus. Jesus. Where,
where am I going? Geez. Okay. Up here. I don't know what to do. This is ridiculous.
So I don't know what to say. Where do I go? I'm going to go over here. I know I'm not supposed
to be here, but I just want to, what about the, there was a bear. Wasn't there like a bear looking
at me? Where was that? I want to go look at that. I forget what that was. It was near like the
watch tower. Let me see. Let me just check a little bit more over here. I'm going to check.
This is a weird building. I'm going to go in there. Wait, I want to look over here first.
This is not poison, right? Items. Here we go. Ice. I think stones. I need these bats. I'm glad I'm
finding them. That's getting angry because he's exploring an open world game. Well, okay. Here's
the thing. It's not just an open world game. It's a from software open world game. That means very
different things. If I was walking around turning on every little like watch tower thing in an
Ubisoft game, then yeah, I'd be like, all right, dude, what are you doing? This is very different
because you can find some pretty crazy shit if you go kind of off the path as we've been at least
proven at least a few times. So if I was walking around picking up like crafting materials and
dying light to be like, all right, like, dude, this is what are you doing? Like we're not going
to find a dungeon to go down and have like an insane encounter. One of the trap chests just sent
me to the final area of the game. Look, I'm just scouting. That's all this is there. And this is
why you scout. This is why you scout. This is going to be an item. It's going to be a weapon or
something. And that's why it's a faith weapon. Nevermind. Fuck this game. Go back here. Okay.
Back here. This is the statue. This is where it was. All right. So let me take a look. This is
where the academy is. That's where I want to go. So I think the play is go on the road,
go straight on the road and head towards the academy. You don't have to justify playing the
game how you want to play it. I mean, look, okay, look, I can understand. Here's the thing.
I can understand if you want to watch like if you want to watch a stream where it's like, all right,
like he's going to go kill the shit and he's going to it's going to be a big intense fight.
He's going to kill everything. Yeah, I know. I mean, the kind of the parts of these games where
you're just kind of like, ooh, a tree. Oh, the sun coming through the tree. What's over here?
Oh, there are weeds here. There are weeds here. Yeah, it's like, all right, dude, I fight somebody.
I get it. Right. But I mean, remember, this is everybody's first time experiencing this stuff.
Right. Obviously, I don't want to run to the next encounter as fast as I can. But I am heading
towards the main objective. Where are these crystals? They're going to have some kind of
significance. Is that OK? I will be really impressed if this actually is in just game space
and that is just there. Is that just kind of a background image or is that actually just
rendered there? And it's there. It's been there the whole time because we've seen that from
very far away. And it just was kind of like a painting. But that's just there.
All right. Finally, I can upgrade my class. Looks like Isaac is one of those statues.
Why is that here? OK, does work so much better. Summon the boys. No, I don't need them right now.
I don't need the boys right now. What's he aiming at? Oh, my God. That's a gun. That's a gun.
I break this so nobody can use it. It's just eating. What are you eating? Just checking. OK.
This is a bad guy up here. That guy looks important. So don't throw that shit at me.
All right, here he comes. Not quite yet. This is the guy. He's waiting for me to get to the top.
He looks dangerous, doesn't he? Let's go. I get that guy way wasn't a big deal. Let's hug the
outside edge here. So this is a main bridge NPC right there. I think that's an NPC. Wait, is that
a lady? I got to clean these notes up. Some of them are not accurate anymore because we
already did them. Snatched it from the big pot. Did you say where it was? Did you say where it was?
Nicholas, favor can be yours. Slaughter, slaughter, the all-hearing slaughter.
All you need to do is snatch it from the pot. You didn't say where it is. Where's the pot?
Where's the big pot then? You didn't tell me where it was.
Just said, oh, slaughter pity. I pity you for slaughtering the pot. It's in the pot.
Don't tell me where it is though. It just exists somewhere. Let's hide. Is that it? That's a unit
from Warhammer. That's like Warhammer 40k. That's an Orc mobile. Is that a guy right there? They're
going to see me do this. What? It's got a face. I can't hurt this thing. Okay, never mind. Can I
hit it in the head? Get the boys out here, please. What am I supposed to do about this thing? Jump on
its head? I don't think so. There's a guy right here. God damn, it's a plane jump rope. All right,
die. Can I get in this? Fire blossom. Very cool. All right, let's take a look. That was pretty cool.
You should go get up, Doug. What's up, Doug? They're aiming over here. I'm going to go around.
I'm going to do this very, very carefully because I think there's a couple people back here too.
Yeah, there is. So one by one, I'm going to get these guys from, I'm going to get them from behind.
Nobody else is here. Sneaking through. Wow. Okay, let's do it. Why was that on a backpack?
Fuck. Why? That was, that was clearly right there. That seriously is such a game-changing
thing that you can do. Cool brass shield. Make sure you're not holding forward. Yeah,
I thought I, I thought I was at a complete stop. All right, I'm at, I'm at a complete stop right
here. Maybe the guys that are, if you're holding onto something, maybe you can do it. I have a
talisman that buffs those counters. I actually think I do. Yeah, you're right. Might be worth
putting on probably animation loft. Yeah, that makes sense. Blue white wooden shield. All right.
Let me, I got some new stuff. This is okay. Blue white wooden shield. Small wooden round
shield that has been reinforced with metal. It is light and easy to handle, but cannot offer the
damage negation of a true metal shield. All right. This thing's kind of junk. It's junk.
Brass shield. Although this is better. Oh, I can't hold it. I don't have enough strength.
Wooden gray shield. I can't hold it. This thing has more magic, but I mean, this thing is still
good. A hundred percent. Oh, this is blood loss buildup. 50. Maybe I should have that on.
That good? Honestly, this one's still better. Wait, I got some more gear. Okay, let me look at these.
I'm in like magic town, right? So I'm probably going to need to have magic resistance.
What has magic resistance? This does. 10, 11, 12. All right. Let's see this one with this one.
I don't like how that's not, I think this is the one. This one looking for magic resistance,
which this has it. 0.7, 2.7. This one's fine. Look at these. All right. Magic 6.8. These are just
better. I'm going to put these on because this is just kind of better and you lose a little bit of
magic, but it's still pretty good. If you want specific directions to the pot, chat has them,
but it's up to you. Hmm. Let me wander around for another like 10 to 20 minutes and we'll see.
Follow your nose. I think that does it for here. The gate is the front gate. There is a bonfire
here as well. I have a lot of souls. Front door to the academy. Pretty cool. I'm going to level up
this. I finally have a new charge and that's five and two is fine. I want to look at those
new ashes though. Let's go this way. I think I'll have enough. It's going to be close.
What do I need? 9,000. It'll be close. All right. Should I just have chat telling me where it is?
So I don't have to look over here and see this goddamn emote. Okay. Let's check this first.
This looks like it's blocked. Meeting place map. Found a simple map. Check your inventory.
What would it be? Simple map found on a corpse. Seems to point to a meeting place.
Man, it came from surely desired one. The sole means of gaining entry into the academy. A glint
stone key. Bro, where is that? It's in the water somewhere. I can't go in here without a glint
stone key. Shit. All right. I need to find where that is. It looks like it's in a lake or in some
water. I don't have a map of this area. Shit. Wait, let me look at the other thing too. That
painting. Note sold by a merchant imparting knowledge. Someone lurks among the waypoint
ruins on the roads through Limgrave. Work of a wandering artist. Reminiscence of a painting
titled prophecy. Painter is said to have captured the landscapes seen during the last moments of
those welcomed to the death's embrace. So the painter and the vestiges of the dead's last
moments can be discovered by visiting the location depicted. What just ran by the screen? Did you see
that? That wasn't a player's soul. I'm not online. I'm not online. I'm offline. Something just like
went by the screen. Oh man, there's so much stuff. You could spend an eternity. It's like a single
player MMO. Okay. I don't have the map and I don't have the key, but I at least have the spawn point
right there. I have the Lucaria gate, which okay, that's how to get in. I need the key, but I don't
know where the key is because I need to find where the key is. The key is on a map, but I don't have
the map of the area. I'm going to find the map of this area. Interesting stuff. So I'm going to take
a guess that the academy gate town would have a map of the academy gate. I'm just going to guess.
That's where I'm going to go. It was raindrops. Really? I feel like getting like this probably
like a little town here that probably has a map. Let's see if I can find it. I don't think I like
really explored this area here because it's on the map for a reason, right? They wouldn't just
put this here with a marker on the map. Who's that? Is that an enemy? That's an NPC. Oh, it's this guy.
I remember this guy.
The tale of House Hoslo is told in blood. The house here. I, Dielos, swear to deliver the message.
They laid hands upon my servant, Lanya, and I refuse to let the insolent. There's a place to go here.
The tale of House Hoslo is told in blood. I, Dielos. All right, so there's one of these houses
has like a dungeon. Let's find it. Is that, somebody said the map fragments are actually
labeled. Is that, what did that mean? That's the map fragment. Are you serious? So that,
okay, that one's literally right next to the bonfire. That's the map. Yeah. Oh, shit.
They labeled that stone tablets. Where is it? Where is it? Oh, okay. All right. I get it.
A new map. Oh, all right. Okay. I understand that now. Hey, wait, you went to Wikipedia.
I didn't go to Wikipedia. So there's one here too. All right. I'm going to explore this because I
want to see what's here. I've got to find the dungeon in this area because I want to, and I'm
going to. It's going to be a little spot to go. And then he said, make these guys pay for what
they've done. Looking for an entrance of some kind or an underground passage of some kind or
thing of some kind to look at. It's labeled up here. That does not necessarily mean that's where
you go. Or maybe it does. I feel like I'm fairly close. Where are we at? They're underground
somewhere, right? They're under here. Are we here? This looks promising. Shit. Ooh, that's good. Nice.
Hmm. I guess it could be any one of these houses. Drain the lake. What's this? Uh, where's this go?
Holy shit. Okay. Oh, there's a map. Oh my goodness. Okay. So that took me all the way over here.
What is out this? It's a pirate ship. Can I swim? Is there a bonfire over here somewhere?
I want to go to the pirate ship. Wait, this is a bit of this. I feel like somebody made that
in like, I mean, I said a roller coaster tycoon. That's like a roller coaster tycoon setup.
Like, I like made that. Like I had a roller coaster and the roller coaster on top of another
roller coaster and I, I had to make an elevated passage with like a queue going up because like,
that's where the entrance is. That looks so weird. That doesn't look like it should be real. This
dude loves planet coaster. I'm just looking for like the bridge that comes out like this way,
this way, down, down, down, down, that way, that way, that way, down, down, down, that way, that
way, down, down, down. You know what I mean? Like, well, I can't show it to go over to that side.
You're not real. Yes, I am. Okay. So pirate ship. Can I even go over to it? Jesus.
Pirate ship is out here. That's not right. Where am I looking? Okay. Maybe there's a teleport to
it. Well, at least I'll be able to find the, uh, the key now. I don't, I don't care about any,
what is that? What are they pulling a wagon? Are they on the same team? What is that? It's like
the king inside of there. Oh shit. That's so many people. It's fucking terrible. Oh, you hurt. And
of course you jump off the goddamn thing. Of course you do. Yes, of course you do. Why wouldn't,
why wouldn't you accidentally press the left stick? That's cool. I want to, okay. I want to
go back over there because that's actually really cool. I want to see what's going on.
Yeah. This stream is explore stream. Explore until I want to fight a bad guy. I'm not going
to fight him though. I think would probably too low. I want to, I want to see what's going on
inside of that thing. There's probably a weapon or an item or something, right?
I think that has to be. It's so heavily guarded. That's so many people. Okay. Should I just call
the boys and just like run over there and open it? Why can't I call the boys? Why do I feel like the
sheep are part of the crew here? I'm just going to go for it. This is, I feel like I'm playing. Oh
my God. It really is. It really is. There's a chest there. There's actually a chest in the back.
This is worth dying for. Okay. I don't have any souls who gives a shit. I'm just going to jump
on there and open it. I didn't know they were all going to hear it. I thought I had a chance.
I thought I could slowly do the thing that everybody did on dust bowl. Open it. It has to
stop. All right. Stop moving. Come on. I got to rob this fucking thing. Oh my God. I'm going to
get it. Holy shit. It's carrying a night sword. Holy shit. I think that's intelligence. Oh, and
by the way, you thought you could fight me. I'm pretty much a goddamn superhero. Oh, fuck
everybody. Fuck everybody. Get him. Get him. He's hacking. He's a fucking hacker.
Somebody ban him. Ban that guy. Oh, you want to try and ban me? He's a fucking hacker. What the
fuck? He's not even supposed to have that move yet. I had to never have any souls. I don't care.
I got what I came for. Yes. Carrying a night's sword. It's a magic sword. It scales with
intelligence. Scales with intelligence. Say it again. Scales with intelligence.
Do you see that it scales with intelligence? Now I don't have to be Castor Andy anymore.
Well, I will, right? But this is perfect. Dex and int scaling. Keep that in mind. Oh my God. The run
is saved. Oh, look at how pretty it is too. Oh yes. It's actually just a regular ass weapon.
It's a weapon. It has a normal swinging pattern. It's gonna be perfect.
This is the weapon that I have to level up. This is it. This is the one.
Weapon art is that stupid piece of shit, but that's okay. We don't have to be that angry about that
considering. But wait a minute here. What was that? I did it three times. It's a bigger sword and it's
faster. It can block. It's got a big charge. It's just kind of a got a regular swinging pattern
and I can use spells while I use it. I can change it too. Yeah, but actually it might be kind of
good. All right. This is bathroom break time because I actually found the weapon. I'm actually gonna
upgrade. So you gotta make a choice eventually here. This thing looks cool. It's exactly,
exactly what I need for my build. This I'm going to upgrade this weapon to like plus 10.
This is it. Very happy. Finally found one. We would find in faith, faith, faith, fire, faith,
faith, fire, fire, strength, strength, strength, strength, faith, fire, strength, faith. Finally we
run into an int weapon. It's a good one. All right. Key break. I'll be right back. And I'm gonna refill
this. I'll upgrade this sword. Let's go. Please show where that is on the map. For those of you
that actually really want it. It might not be. The databases for the game might not even be there.
So if you really want to know. It was along this road here. I rode down this road. I was looking
for the pirate ship. So here's the pirate ship. So I got, I was up here and I went down this road
here and it was this area here, right? I actually kind of don't remember. Yeah, it was like here,
right here. This is where that is. You want to see it on the bigger map you can.
Right here. This island thing directly left of the island. There's two guys pulling the wagon.
Look at how pretty it is. I want to get like a close-up of it. I want it in the light too.
Okay, that would have been so fucking funny. Wait, I gotta get a screenshot for my guild.
No, no, I don't want to rain. Hey, fine. I'll go home. I'll be right back. I'm gonna go upgrade
this thing and I will see you guys in a minute. I won't forget to loop the music this time.
I'll be right back. See, it looped. Looped. All right, let's get back to it. Turn that down. Turn
this up. I want to upgrade. It's time to upgrade. Let's do it. Oh, my drink! Wait, give me a sec.
I left my drink on the counter. Okay, I'm back. I left my drink on the counter. Back to Elden Ring
and I'm gonna take a minute because I want to go upgrade this weapon. If you're just joining us.
Holy goodness, we got some good news. I finally found a weapon called the Carrion Knight Sword.
It scales with strength, dex, and intelligence, which eventually here after a few upgrades could
turn out to be a very big deal. Very cool sword. I wonder how the scaling changes after a few
stone upgrades. Let's go find out. What's on the shirt? It's an Andy Mark shirt. Whatever floats
your goat. Andy Mark. Okay, left in the fireplace. I remember this time. There's actually I think
is there a new NPC here? I swear I just saw one. The decision is final. I have to pick something.
I can't just bounce around anymore. Here we go. Upgrade this thing. I can't. Why?
Why not? I have zero dollars. Wait, come on. Why? I have to go sell something to that lady.
Where are you at? You're down here, right? Yeah. I'm gonna call them dollars.
I want to sell. Who can I sell to? Who can I sell to? Who's who can I sell to? Can I sell to the
blacksmith? Forget. I can. I'm an idiot. All right, I need I just need like a few hundred.
I don't know what any of this shit does. Crafting. I gotta learn this. All right,
we're taking a minute. I know this filler episode here. Okay. Field. It's time to get
rid of some of this stuff. I'm not going to use the short sword to sell it. I'm not going to use
the long sword. This thing. No, sell it. Touch that. I'm not going to. I have two daggers.
Just give me one. I'm not going to use the stock. Wait, wait, what? I'm not going to use the axe.
I'm not going to use the loose yarn. I'm not going to use this either. And it's worth a lot.
But I'm scared to delete it. Okay, here we go. So this is going to be 88. Now it's 100.
That's so much better. And go. I need somber smithing stones to keep this going.
Oh, yeah. So if you I gotta make sure I wait. No, I already have them, bro. I already got them.
Let's go. I just need runes. All right. All right. Just kill two people. I'm just gonna go just
lay these people out. It gives us an opportunity to test the sword as well.
See how much damage it does, because it's probably going to do a lot. All right. It's going to find
a group of people to kill. Shouldn't be too hard. Yeah, like this guy. 150 fucking seven
damage. And this shit ain't even upgraded. Over 100 damage. I need like probably two or three
thousand souls. Is that OP? Well, it's not necessarily because I'm build. I'm I'm look at
my build. This is exactly what I was looking for. This item was made for me. All right. How
is it on horseback? Awesome on horseback. Yep. Perfect. What is this thing? I don't know. It's
gonna die. Whatever it is. Feed my rune appetite. I can just doesn't matter. I can just be poisoned.
It's fine. Now I'm going to be a force to actually be reckoned with. Bosses now are not going to be
a weird combination of meeting to dance around and do like 40, 50 damage a swing to everybody.
I don't have this poison. No more meltdowns. Got it. Let's go kill a lobster.
Because once I get this a couple more like plus two plus three plus four,
it's going to be like where I'm supposed to be. Just spit me get that. What are you doing? What's
it? Why is he standing still? I mean, that's cool, but he's a lobster. So it didn't really hurt.
How would you ever fight this guy? Not on a horse.
Literally looking at chat in the middle of riding around on the horse.
Wrong spell. How much is that worth? It's like a thousand. All right. 500. That's it.
So it's 400. Then it's probably going to be like 800. So I need another like 500.
No skill. Oh, you could just go. Yeah. The giant dogs fight again. Yeah. I could go to the,
that's a good, uh, farm spot. I'll do that real quick. Where is it down here? Right. Where was
that? Which one of these was it? Not the crystal tunnel. It's this one down here. Yeah. There's a
map right there as well. I'll get them up. Yeah. All right. This is the farm zone right here.
Map is over here. Let's market and start the battle. Attack. Yes. I am the master of chaos.
I am the master of chaos. Muahaha. Muahaha. I am the master of chaos. Oh, big move.
I've got a question. How many of you guys hate watching me? But you're still here because you
think it's kind of fun to do that. What was that lunge dude? 11,000 hate watchers. Oh, that was
like, I would, I don't know. I don't want anybody to like hate me. That like sucks.
I got his shorts on. This is your prize for getting a nice parry. Damn. All right. That's
definitely enough. I can move. Yeah. That's good. Wait, actually, there's a little bit more over
here. How much health do they have? Yeah, I might as well. This is how I actually felt when I was
playing like MMO PVP, by the way, like I didn't even know what was happening. I didn't know what
I was doing. I would just cast like random moves. I would just attack random people.
I feel like I wasn't doing very much, but I was kind of there helping. I wonder like, okay,
altered Valley. That's because I played well. I think it was actually like five people actually
playing the game and then like 35 other people just, just walking in random directions.
I remember people being lost that just weren't even part of the fight. They were just like
walking around doing stuff. They didn't even know where they were. Odd. I remember. Oh, the map,
right? 40 man raids and wow. What a disaster. I remember there were cases of people showing
the DPS meter be like, um, Hey dude, like it says here on the DPS meter that you're only doing
just auto attacks. You're not even doing any moves like just completely just not even playing.
Like you're just there doing the encounter and just not playing like, Hey man, uh, it says you,
you did like 1400 damage across the whole fight, which is actually impossible unless you have only
been doing auto attacks. All right. I gotta go this way. Oh my God. I got an entire zoo behind me.
What the fuck? Give me the map. Oh my God. Get away from me. Stop guarding the thing. I want
get out of the way. I got it. It looks like a puppet. Looks like there's a hand in there.
Sesame Street. Okay, dude, that's enough. I've had enough. I teleport. No.
A new map has been found. Whoa. Those are my souls right there. Right. Where the fuck are they?
My souls are right there. Upgrade your flask. I already did. I did say goodbye to those souls.
They're not gone. They're right here. We should say goodbye to is that that attitude.
Where is it? I wasn't even an attitude. That was just telling me what was happening.
Get off my stop camping. Fine. You want to play that game? We can play that game. What is this?
I didn't want to give a camping my body. Let's get the hell out of here.
Good. I have enough souls. I can upgrade this probably three times. Maybe twice. Cheesing is
so fun. What is more cheese? Casting spells at somebody or somebody camping. 113. Here we go.
Boom. I can do it again. Boom. I can do it again. Oh, this is it. I've been saving these stones.
I have four. I have one somber smithing stone. Hell yeah. Look at that. This thing is good shit
now. Plus four. Boom. There it is. Boom. That's so funny. Should I start saying that? Should I
start saying that? Boom. There you go. I wonder if maybe does it stay at D? Will it scale D the
whole time? Sometimes they get higher. So maybe one of them will turn to C.
Now, I mean, it's not the stupidest idea now to put some points in strength,
but probably not because just have it scale with intelligence and dexterity.
Because that just makes my casting better too. What about the wand? Where is it? I'm going to
check out the other ashes thing. Okay. So I'm comfortable putting this on now. All right, dude.
And this gets to be scaling when I do this. Here we go. Boom. Have I been saying boom?
Have? I've been saying boom. I've already been doing that.
If I really know I have. I've been saying boom. So that should even out look at my cool stuff.
I still look like an asshole though. I need some better stuff. I need some cooler like
armor. I look like I look like trash. I look awful. I need to match these cool new items
that I have for this cool build. I'm ready to tackle this next part, which is we're going to
find the key, which if I look at the map that I have in my inventory, it's like in the middle
is an island to the left. There's a little island to the right. There's a small little
kind of peninsula that sticks out. It's underneath that. Okay. It's right here.
This is where the glint stone key is. We're going to go get it. What was this marked for?
I don't know. Get rid of it. This is better than Bloodborne. Bloodborne is like my favorite
single player game ever. Bloodborne is my favorite single player game ever. Besides maybe
all that thought. Hold on to it. All that thought because it's tough. I think it's hard to let go
of something that you find so dear, right? But how I about D. You've completed 8% of the game.
You can't rate it yet. That's kind of why I'm saying that.
Afts have since diverged, never again to cross. Though that's hardly an uncommon fate for two
friends. D. was telling me that he discovered the mark of the centipede. The centipede is an ancient
symbol of the curse mark. As long as whoever finds and uses it is not nefarious by nature,
then we may be able to form an alliance. Okay. If only I could speak to them in person and if they
were like you, all the better. I want your outfit. How hard is that? I want this person's outfit.
Okay. I have enough to get both of these, which I'm going to.
Just to have them. Let's take a look. I got to go to the blacksmith and see if I want to
put something else on this sword. Cause this is... All right. It's time for the ultimate
hot take. Well, not really. This is like actually probably not an unpopular opinion right now.
It's kind of feels like every from software game combined into one game. It's every single
from software game. They just mushed them all together and just kind of made it. They've
polished it up. The one thing that's missing that I like from Bloodborne is I like having a ton
of Bloodborne's heels were instant. Being able to just be like wham and you're and you're healed
like 30, 40% was just so I like that system. But I mean, I didn't really love the system of having
to go collect them if you didn't have any, but I like the speed of Bloodborne being able to,
my character being able to move around like crazy was one of my favorite parts of Bloodborne
and the trick weapons. Yeah. The trick trick weapons were probably, I mean, you can't really
do that with the probably a hundred plus items that are in this game. Trick weapons, the actual
theme and the story of Bloodborne and the speed. That's why it's above everything for me. But
I just, it's hard not to like this because it just how much stuff you can actually really do
is that when I play Bloodborne again, I know where I'm exactly where I'm going.
I know what I'm doing. I know I'm going to go to, okay, we're in central Yharnam. We're going to go
to now we're going to go. Okay. We're going to Bergen worth. Okay. Now we're doing the swamp.
Like it's the same exact game pretty much every single time. It's incredible. It's amazing. And
it's a ton of fun, but it's the same experience almost every time. I feel like this is going to
be a completely wildly different experience. No matter how you play this. I mean, I could just,
I mean, it's holy, but it doesn't, I can put it on if I wanted to standard or sacred.
All right. Can I not take it off my weapon? Is this on here permanently?
Can I not put a weapon on this? It's on there permanently. Okay. You can go sit down to change
it. Oh, cause it's like a, but yeah, I mean, it's the, uh, everything of every time. Okay.
Think about this. There are, from what I've been told, an absolutely unbelievable amount of things
to do in this game. There are spoiler alert because I heard this just by kind of browsing
around and seeing stuff. There are apparently, and there's a spoiler for this game, but not,
it's not really a spoiler, but it's just, it's like, it's about like the content of the game.
If you don't want to hear it mute for five seconds, there apparently are almost 100
fucking bosses in this game. A hundred, 100, not 15, not like 30, fucking a hundred. When I heard
that I, and then when people were saying, Oh dude, no, no, no, no, you're not even, this is like,
not even half the map. It's just like, really? Like I, I looked forward so much to like the game,
the DLCs for dark souls three, for bloodborne, they added like 10 to 20 hours of content and
like what, like six or seven bosses. It was like, holy shit. Yeah. Cause the main game had like,
what, 15 to like 20 actual bosses. Thinking about a hundred boss encounters and only like,
I believe only like five to 10 of them are reskins of like enemies are in the game.
They're all like unique encounters. It's 83. Come on, dude. I mean, still, you don't think
they're going to do DLC for this game and bring it to like 100, 110, way more than 10 are reskins.
Only 83. LOL. 83 is still, even if there is like slight reskins and stuff, but that's still,
I read that there's at least 50 unique encounters somewhere. 74 unique ones,
according to a chatter. That's ridiculous. That's more people that are in smash brothers.
That's, that's bigger than the smash brothers roster at this point. So that's, I mean,
that's crazy to think about that there's that much stuff to do. It's almost overwhelming,
which is why I'm trying to, we're taking a little bit of time here on this stream to kind of slow
it down a little because it's, it's very overwhelming being able to kind of go anywhere. And there's so
much stuff to explore that I kind of want to like, let's slow it down a little. Yeah, that's,
that's ridiculous. So anyways, there's my, as it stands right now, this is probably at this point
right now, I have to see some of the more, some more bosses, especially the main story ones.
But this is like, if you talk about the brackets, like Bloodborne is like really like desperately
like reaching to grab at the heels of this game right now, at least in the first like 10 to 20
hours of both experiences. Because I did not feel that way about Sekiro. Let me be really honest.
Sekiro was good, was really cool. But Sekiro was just a lot different. And it was kind of,
it was a little much for me too. I find Sekiro to be like the hardest game I think I've ever played.
Just because of the amount of like the parry, parry, parry, parry, parry, parry, parry, parry.
Like the bosses that had like five phases, it was really, really, really a lot.
So I think this kind of sits in a spot that I like. We'll see.
Are you the kind of person that tries and completes every dungeon and side quest in an area?
Not particularly, but I love the fact that it's there. Because if I play this game again,
which I'm absolutely going to, instead of doing like this, I could do like this, or like this,
or this. I don't have to follow the exact same path. Even if I want to come back here, right?
This stuff I haven't done. The fact that it's available means you can replay it more than a
few times and see stuff you've never seen before. I think it's great, but I'm holding my tongue a
little bit just because I don't want to be one of those people that's like, this is definitely the
best game ever made. It has to be. Nothing can compare. And then like the next three,
four main story bosses I talk about like, these suck. This game sucks. I don't want to like kind
of jump the gun on this a little, but it does kind of feel like it is one of the better single
player experiences I've ever had. Especially in the first like 10 to 20 hours. Because I know
how much there is to do. You do that for every game though. So that's okay. Yeah. Oh, Resident
Evil 8. I just make, I just talk shit about every game I play. It's a coping mechanism. Don't you
get it? You understand by now? Like I don't actually hate these games. It's just for my brain.
My like ego maniac brain is like, it's there's no way it's you're the problem. Tell them. Tell
them it's not you. Tell them to unbind left stick. Yeah, unbind left stick. And also tell them to
eat that broccoli too, because it's got full of vitamin K. Eat broccoli. It's good. And also
tell them that this boss is too slow. Like I, of course it's like, that's like ego, right? Like,
no, it's not me. It's fucking, it's not me. It's the game's fault that I wasn't able to do that.
But like it's, it's cope. You're coping with the fact that you're not doing something as fast as
you want to. Play the game already. I'm giving you, I've played the game for like 20 hours and I'm
giving you how I feel about the game. I'm a reviewer of video games. Play the game so much of you.
Play the game if you like it so much. I'm reviewing this game. People come to me and they look for
their, their, how they feel about games. This is where they come. They come in and they say,
what does he think about it? What does he have to say? How does he feel about this? We need to know.
Where are those ashes? There it is. No, I think that's on there permanently guys.
It is. I cannot take that off. That's the downside to that weapon. That's all right. Here we go.
We're going. We're going. We're going. We're going. Fine. Fine. Play the game. Play the game.
Play the game. Play the game. Play the game. Usually you play something like Fart Simulator
2013. We're not used to your like takes on video games. So let me test this out. What's the, how
do I get to do the weapon art for this? Can I, I can't cause it's in my hand. What about this?
Does it have to be my right hand? Cause that's like the spinning shield thing.
Y and L2. That was stupid. This is a magic trick.
See, there are no strings where I'm attached. There's nothing, no strings on my arms.
Okay. Well that was, that was dumb. It's a pretty cool party trick though. Yeah.
All right. Let's get on the horse. We're going. It's this way. We're going to marker number three,
play the game already. We don't want to hear you talk. We want to see you play and talk.
Do two things at once and hurry up. My food's almost here and I want to be able to eat
my cheese pizza while you're playing this game and you're wasting time.
I've been waiting, sitting with a pizza in front of me and it's getting cold.
I won't eat one bite until you start riding on the horse. Hurry up.
So you said I'm doing that now? Dude, my pizza is cold now.
You slam your fucking hands on your desk. All right. This is weird. What's going on here?
These are those things that give spells and ashes of work. This is actually just kind of like a
jackpot. It is not. Okay. I didn't know. I was thinking maybe this is like a jackpot.
There's something over there. I don't know what that is. Is it a dragon? That's a sleeping dragon.
Oh shit. Did you hear me? I didn't hear me. Smarg. Glintstone dragon smarg.
It's in that kind of like, in that dragon. What? Well, here we go. Another dragon fight. We all
love these ones. Actually, can I do this? Breathe fire. Oh, he breathes glintstone fire.
Holy shit. It's like super missiles. I have no mana. I have no, I have no, I have no run mana.
I can't call, I can't call the boys either. There's a fire right here too.
I think I'm going to try the punch. I'm going to try a right, right trigger attack. Heavy attack.
There he goes with this bullshit and he goes wham. I don't think it's much better. I think
he's going to stick with what I'm doing. Stick with it. You shoot behind him. Don't be greedy.
Wait, that's why I didn't want to do that. Does he have no eyes? Oh, that was an epic scene.
Oh, it's coming. Button press on my keyboard. Button press. Didn't unbind it.
Don't swipe your tail at me. Don't even think about it. Oh, you ugly.
Holy shit. He killed me in one hit. One hit. Well, maybe I need more health.
I don't get one hit killed by that. I'll come back to him. That's really cool. I'll come back to him.
There's the bear. I found the bear. That was such a shitty reveal. I wanted to like actually see the
bear. Is that too far? That's not. All right. Come here. Where are you? That was a cool thing
that we were just doing. There's a gorilla? No, it's a bear. It's like a bear gorilla.
I'm sneaking behind you. What's the point of a sneak in this game? Dude, there's so many
fucking giant creatures. Oh my God. Wait, where's that taking me? What the hell am I? I don't want
to be here. Oh, I was supposed to go get the key. All right. All right. Well, I mean, I literally
can't even hurt these people. So we're going to have to come back later. I need to go get the key
to go in this way. Okay. Very cool. Let's go. Pull the dragon's glint stone dragon.
I have a big feeling that that dragon drops something that I would be very interested in
acquiring. Can't sneak around. I don't really understand the appeal of souls games. We used
to have NSNES games where you had to try multiple strategies to beat a boss that
is still being able to be used today. I don't even know. I'm sorry. I missed it. It was going
too fast. My eyes. Okay. I do not wake the dragon. I'm not doing that right now. I think I have to
have a little bit more health and maybe some more magic resistance because I have a lot of it on
right now. Wait. Oh no. This is the guy that has the key. I have, I have to kill this guy
with the key because he's going to drop the key. Right. Unless it's behind him. He could be sleeping
on it. Maybe, maybe he's sleeping on it or something. There it is. I'm trying to sneak and
he can hear me. Flintstone Key Academy. Goodbye. That's terrifying. Okay. Goodbye. I just wanted
to steal your treasure. Thief. Oh, magnificent smarag. Your presence precedes you. Oh, isn't
that what a thief would say. Oh, terrifying and powerful smarag. The legends truly are
correct when they describe you. I always want you to take it so I could see the look on his face
when he sees them, when he goes into there, into the academy. He's way too underleveled.
Oh, great and powerful smarag. Okay. He's gone. I got it. That's, that was fun. Excuse me. Well,
okay. I'm going to investigate what's going on over here. Cause like, who are these people? And I'm
very curious. Who are you and what are you protecting? I love when I hit somebody with
this weapon. There's like a blue splash because it's magic damage. Hell yeah. What are they doing
over here? I'm curious how much damage this actually does. Let's find out. But I don't think
it's a, it justifies swinging it. It's a really bad ability. Yeah, it is. I could see that. That
would might be kind of cool when there's a huge group of enemies and they're all piled up before
we kill them all in one hit. But besides that kind of jump punish staggers. Ah, that's true.
So, okay. If I stagger someone, right? Let's say I stagger a boss or a boss is like in the middle
of changing to like phase two. Is that worth just charging that up? I wonder you got to find
gob. All right. I'm going to go open the door. I don't know where that is. Open the door. I have
a key. Let me in. That was a certified gob moment. I'm in here. Damn. All right. What was that?
I love how much of a gamer you are when it comes to Souls games, but everything else,
you're a clown man. Well, you have to understand. You can't, I can't, I can't like be clown guy
in the middle of some of these boss fights. It doesn't work. I have to, I have to really try
to play the game and really, I really have to, where am I going? Wait, is this back out?
You saw what happened when I was funny clown guy. What the fuck? Okay. Turn around. I need to be,
I got to go in the academy. Deliver the key to the apprentice now. The one that you bought spells.
Yeah, I was thinking about, I think, is that going to get rid of the key though?
If I give him the key, won't it expel it and I can't come back in here? Like I need to,
I want to do this. I clear this first. I'm going to Academy of Rhea Lucaria.
This is my hometown. This is my like home turf here. Blink your eyes a few times and let's go.
I actually really liked Bergenwerth in Bloodborne and I was sad that it was not that large.
Something about like a academy, like a magic academy, or like a, it is, I think it's really
interesting. Bergenwerth was awesome and this is kind of like Bergenwerth. It's a big, this is
big Bergenwerth because I'm going to love it. Oh, you want to play the casting game, huh?
All right, fellow wizards. Never mind. Never mind. Slice. I don't think, yeah, they probably have a
ton of magic resistance because they're wizards. I might not be as useful here as I think I am.
They're all the burger king. You just ruined this whole area, dude.
You ruined this whole game for me now. Come on.
Holy shit, that sucked. Run. Let's get 50 subs. Brock League, get 50 subs. What are you doing?
That's insane. Holy shit, dude. Thanks for the 50 subs. I love this area. I do. I love it. I'm
gonna, it's gonna be, okay. Here we go. This might be my favorite area of the game. I'm gonna make a
prediction. I'm gonna be sad if I'm wrong. I can upgrade the weapon again. We just got here 30
seconds ago, dude. Yeah, but I mean, come on. You hear like chimes? Burger King wizards? Weird
people that are like freaking out. I'm gonna do less mana potions here because I feel like,
feel like I'm not gonna be casting that often because they're casters and I would probably
rather just get up there and smash them. What's it saying? Burger King paintings? That's so dumb.
That's so dumb. That's so dumb that it makes me laugh. Okay, outside. I'm gonna assume we're
gonna go around. Smithing stone. Looks like a Dark Souls 3 area. Uh, what the? Wow, that's enormous.
These guys have a lot of health. That's not gonna work, is it? What, what? Oy, oy, oy, oy, oy.
How much damage does this do? Not very much at all. They're really slow though. Get off me. What?
Oh, he just sucked all my mana. Not worth doing. Get off of me. Where was he even coming from?
Oh my god, they're fucking everywhere. Get the fuck away from me. They're so fast and they want to
I gotta line them up so I can hit them more. I can do cleave. That cleave is good.
Okay, one more. He doesn't, he double taps. He can do it twice. Stop whining? Am I whining? I'm
like, what are you talking about? These are disgusting creatures. Hey, they're using magic
on magic eaters. Spell proof liver. The bridge now? This thing's going down, right? Like this
thing's, of course it's going down. This bridge is going down. Shit, that dog. I'm gonna accidentally
slice this and the bridge is gonna collapse. I'm just, I think that's what's gonna happen.
Don't dodge on a bridge, you fool. Alright, I can't dodge here. Get off of me. Don't dodge. Get away.
I hate this. Just do it. Do it. They're just so, they're so, they taunt you. They're just like,
I'm gonna do it. I'm gonna do it in a second and I'm gonna do it a few times in a row. I gotta
just go in now. It's just like, hey, hey, you know it's gonna happen. You know I'm gonna do it.
I'm out of potions. Just seeing what would happen. What the fuck happened? What was that?
Something just sprinted by my face. What was that? What was that? What was that? That was like a dust
ball. It was the Blair Witch. I'm probably gonna die here. These guys, you have to just attack them
over and over again. Do not let them even get one second of time. Not even a second.
There's a guy right behind me. He's over there. He's over here. He's over there. He's over there.
You just gotta, they're probably spawning behind me. What the, no. He was just ready.
I didn't even see him. I'm running by these chumps. The shield, will the shield, wait,
will the shield block that or is it, technically it's a grab, right? It's kind of far away. Isn't
that technically, it's a grab. Would that, would that work? Let me try it. Oh, it's a grab.
I don't want to lose those souls though. I was supposed to just run off the cliff. I was running.
What about you boys? I can't summon them here for some reason. Do I not have enough mana?
No, I can't summon them here. They're not allowed here. Yeah, fuck it. Let's just go.
Magic Grease and, uh, trouble here. He's spawning as I'm stuck here.
I gotta get in that goddamn building. How can we suck at this? Why do you suck so hard?
Man, that's a troll comment. I mean, I know that this is the first time I've ever seen this.
This isn't like my ninth playthrough of Dark Souls 2. What are you talking about? Get in the building.
Nope. Oh my God. Oh, on fire. Oh my, come on, man. Not like this. Not like this. Some of you
fucking fall off and die. Okay. So I just got swarmed. Use your shield. Guys, I can't,
you can't block the grab attack. They just grab you. It's not a thing you can do. I can't block it.
And how, you want me to hold the shield up where there's five dogs on every single,
acute angle of my body? Ooh, okay. I don't like this. I, what the fuck? I can't get it. I can't
reach that. I can't reach that. Whatever that is. Holy fucking smokes, dude. All right. Back up,
back up, back up, back up. That just like threw me off so hard. You know what? Eat shit. You know
what? Eat shit again. I know. I said we started up shit a third time. Ooh, what's that? This is
intelligence. Pulls foes forward towards caster. Pull. That actually might be really useful. Okay,
we found like the one enemy where that was actually useful to do it on, but how do I get up here?
The infamous triple decker. It sucks them up. Might be fun to play with. It actually could be,
actually. You never want to just kind of close gaps in this game, but I wonder if it's a stun.
I wonder if you pull them and they have like a second or so. Maybe it's like a,
I wonder if it's a, if it's a stagger. That would be huge if it was. Where's this end? Holy shit.
I almost just died. I almost just went all the way. I'm so glad I was facing the right way.
Get up there. 312 damage. That's so good. Those guys are so susceptible to it.
I saw something over here. What was it? Wait. All right. Hold on. Not doing that yet. Is
this a secret chest? Shit. Well, let me, there might be a bonfire up here. Yeah, there is. Okay.
Thank God. Weirdo over there. All right. I cannot level up yet. Let's walk over here first.
What the hell was that? Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Where's my parry? Oh, because I changed the
weapon art. It's not a parry anymore. It's like a holy thing. Right, right, right. Okay. Because
the parry is technically a weapon art. Right. Well, I kind of want to, I gotta fix that.
Where's parry? Parry the platypus? Oh, staggered. I'm going to put the pole on. Let's try. Did I
fight Godric? I did. What does it look like? It doesn't take too, too long. Let's see what it does.
It actually is really not bad. It is a stagger. It makes him kind of go like,
you're alive. It's not a bad move, especially in a one-on-one scenario. If it's a hard enemy,
you can just kind of stagger him for a second and get away. Oh my Lord. This is going to be fucking
hell. What the fuck? Hello. Oh, it's a pot guy. Everyone was looking for the pot. There he is.
All right. Well, I need to come here. It doesn't work on the pot, but magic. Oh my fucking Lord.
Run away. Magic. Didn't you say it was in the pot? Okay. They've, they've reset. Can I
get a backstab now? No. Cause he's right there. I got to, I just got to run it and start swinging
unless you could do magic versus magic. And I think that's the play here.
I got to get line of sight on that guy. Oh my God. This sucks. God damn it. Damn. Okay.
I got legendary chest. Ritual pot. What's that? Container required for crafting ritual pot items,
which I don't know. I got it again. I have to sit down and figure out what the hell crafting even
is. I've spent the entire game just not doing it at all and not paying any attention to it at all.
It's locked. Yeah. You think I'm dumb, but you think I'm dumb. It's a boss right here.
Okay. I was about to hit me with this book. Okay. Fuck. This is like a leader.
Nope. There's gotta be a bonfire right here, right? There always is. Is there not a bonfire?
Oh, you gotta be shitting me. It's not a bonfire. There has to be. I'm not done looking around.
Okay. Is there not actually a bonfire? It's actually really, really bad news. It's not
because this was a pain in the ass to get up here. It's going to have to run through every time.
Hmm. Really though, I don't, I don't buy it. I don't buy it. I don't buy it. I like actually
don't buy it because this is really far away. Yeah. This is like really far away. And this is
the way to get over here. Remember that spot where I could drop down on the other side of the
waterfall? I have a feeling that that opens the door back here. I remember the door. It was like,
Oh, this is shut. That one right there. I have to imagine that I could open that door
if I go on the other side of the waterfall, which is precisely what I'm going to do.
We want gob. I don't know what gob is. Yeah. I absolutely have to open that up from the inside.
Everything is dead here, so I'll be fine. Make sure I didn't miss it somehow.
Wait, this is not that bad. Is though. Ooh, more spells. Okay. I think I just have to run.
I think I just have to run. You missed the wall. What? What do you, does that have the wall?
Wait, so that means there must be more. We're checking every bookcase.
Illusory walls are confirmed to be in the game. It's been a while. It's actually been a long time.
Up the stairs right here. Oh, I went through it though. This one up the stairs. Maybe I just,
that's going to be such a huge pain in the ass to run through those guys because the amount of
times they cast. Come on. Let me be, let this be right. Really? Come on. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes.
Yes. There's no bonfire in here. That's good. What's in the chest? What's that? Comet requires
52 intelligence to use. Fires a great magical comet. It can be cast repeatedly and while in
motion, charging enhances the potency. 52 intelligence. Good luck. We're never getting
there. Oh, there's a ladder. Is it even mathematically possible for me to get to 52?
All the points I've been spending everywhere else. You don't just put this up for no reason. Why is
this? This has to be left. There's no way this is not a different reason. It's impossible that
there would be nothing here. Jump down. Other side. Wait, what the fuck am I? I don't, guys,
I don't know what's down here. What's down here? Am I dead? What is that? Oh my god. It's a
gigantic, this could be huge. I hear a person behind me. Stupid little jello containers. All
right. Don't die here. Don't die. Where am I? That's definitely a sorcery talisman. Absolutely.
That is a sorcery talisman without a single doubt. They give a lot of souls. Is there anything else
in here? No bonfire, though. But that, let's take a look. Is this, do we have one now?
Oh my god. Finally. Finally. Raises the potency of sorceries. I lost max equipment load, though.
It doesn't seem like it really matters that much in this game.
Because I'm not mid-rolling. I should be, shouldn't I? How forgiving is mid-rolling and
fat-rolling now? Because I am well over 50 percent. Fat-roll is 70 percent. You are
mid-rolling, but mid-rolling was buffed. What does it look like if you're not mid-rolling?
Interesting, okay. I want the highest magic defense. Four, five, five, eight, six, eight.
I really don't, I don't really even tell a difference. Maybe, is it, I think the,
the underneath, the regular naked roll? Maybe you go a little bit further? I don't know. Cool.
Nonetheless, it's the stamina difference. Oh, all right. Well, I wonder how much more potent
these sorceries are because I need to go back to the bonfire. It looks, I guess you just have to
run. I think you just have to run through, which is a huge pain in the ass, but it doesn't seem
to be that far. Just got to run. Are there more walls? Hit the crystal. Uh, we will in a minute.
I'm putting a point into intelligence. All right. Well, I got to kill some people anyways.
Let's see how much more damage my, well, it's hard to tell on these guys, but
I need like 10,000. Oh, hell yeah. That's a good drop. Mm-hmm. Magic defense.
There's not a chance in hell that I don't need it here.
I need like 10,000. Yeah, this room in particular, I use, how am I supposed to run through this room?
I just sprint by. I forgot about the pot. The pot's still here. I've got huge arms. I forgot.
All right. Almost to 10,000. I think one more guy and that should do it.
Somebody said hit the crystal. Let's see what happens if I hit the crystal.
Nothing happened. Time to level up intelligence. You know that's what we're doing. Then boss time.
I'm going to give it a try. No, not boss time. Uh, we're going to level up and I'm going to go.
How much is it to level up? Cause I want to make sure I have enough to upgrade the weapon.
9,500. Let me see how much it takes to do this. So I'm here. All right. Schoolhouse.
Uh, cause I have enough stones to do the weapon again. I believe. When is German going to notice
he has a health debuff? I do. What do you mean? Oh, it's somber smithing stone five.
Not what I have. Well, nevermind. Health debuff from getting hugged have to use the
blessing to cure it. What do you mean? This? My health is the same. Go get hugged. Wait, did it work?
I am pleased. Would you like me? Um, yeah. Okay. Come closer. It was because she hugged me.
You are so fucking secret. I was known as a deathbed companion after I received the warmth
and life figure from a number of champions. I lay with the remains of an exalted noble
to grant him another chance at life. To do so is the purpose of my being.
Maybe that was the difference from getting instantly killed by the dragon.
I was awakened by the guidance of grace and chased from my birthplace. Pray, be kind.
Despite all that, I still wish to be a deathbed companion. So please, let me hold you like this
as often as it takes and good day to you. Okay. So I'm, I currently have like a little blessing
curse thingy. Having the blessing in your inventory gives you a 5% debuff. It will wear off once you
use the blessing. That is weird. Okay. I don't, wait for it to, that's weird. That's weird.
All right. We're going to, we're going to do intelligence. Then we're going to do, uh,
vigor and then mind. And I need to get dexterity up to like 25 as well. Okay. I have, for now,
I'm going to keep my flasks the way they are because in case I need to do any sorceries.
But, um, let's go. Let's see what happens here. Uh, let me see if I can just run by.
Hmm. Goodbye. Goodbye. It's not that bad of a run. All right. Let's go. Red wolf of Rattagon.
Double headphones for this. Oh, he's so susceptible to this weapon.
Shit. I almost had a first try. Damn it. Okay. All right. All right. All right. I almost had a
first try. Damn it. Oh well. Uh, this weapon is really good against this guy. I probably would
have had it. The only problem was when he went to the back and started like putting the like,
I was kind of like, what does that do? I didn't know what was happening. I actually should probably
just do health. There's no, I mean, how am I going to cast the spell at this guy? There's no way.
All right, let's go reposition. Okay. I got to get the timing on that.
Shit. I didn't mean to press. I'm all right. I mean, like getting the fucking handle.
Like, you know, when you just like kind of stay there and like your hands are still on B and
you're just like, get, get off, get off of, get the fuck off of B. Don't get greedy. No, I'll be
good. Some of the little squirt guys. I don't think I need summons for this one. Again, I forgot to
fucking put the flasks on. And I also probably shouldn't be wearing, maybe I should cause the
magic damage. Oh, this guy's not too bad. Unless there's like a phase two after this, which they
very well might be. Let's just see what happens. All right. Focus. Okay. Delay on those things.
A lot longer. And I think it takes about three full seconds, puts them down and they sit there
like one, two, three. Then they go, but the, what does the Fox say on a 10 hour loop while you fight
this? Okay. I kind of gotten unlucky. He's done that like twice in a row now. All right. I got
to get in close. Holy shit. I kind of hope I too bad. I didn't beat him first drive. This guy's
actually kind of difficult. Almost had it. Why is the first try always the best? Cause the first
try is always the best because you always go in there and you just like, I don't give a shit. I
have no idea what the fuck is happening. And you just let your body just do it and not your brain.
Problem is now after being in there a couple of times, my brain has figured out what he's doing
and my brain is going, Jeremy, he's got that move, you know, and he's going to use it on you. You
got to be careful. He's got, he's got those moves, you know, you know what they do. I got it. I'm
all right. I'm turning my brain off. Christ. Especially when he dashes across the room and
the camera changes. So I can't see them. There's a battle mage set right outside the door.
Huh? Don't tell him that. I thought I've explored every area. Please for the love of God.
Relax. I'm fine. There's no way. What do you mean? There's a battle mage set right outside the door.
I don't need it. I don't need it. I can get it. I just got, you got, I got to die like
30,000 more times in my pants. Oh my God. He's fast. Okay. I keep. So when, when he, when he,
okay, he has like two distinct sets here. He has one where he just with his mouth,
but then sometimes he'll go sword. And it's, it's hard to, I'm trying to figure out when,
uh, like when he puts his mouth up, he's going to put the sword in his hand and you gotta wait.
He's got a really, really fast, uh, just like little rare. This weapon is I got,
I got to keep this weapon on though. It's definitely the best thing that I have against him.
Damn it, man. Fuck you. Fuck you. I just panicked. Oh fuck. I panicked so hard on that
last one. I was so scared. The dog, I just held down the dodge button when he did the,
he casted the fucking blue shit. I was like, fuck man, he's going to come in.
And I thought there was one more that didn't shoot yet. Sorry. Damn. I'm sorry. I thought
there was one more that didn't shoot. That's why I was like, when is it going to fucking fire?
I got too cocky. No, you gotta be cocky. That's how you beat this shit.
Nobody ever beat a dark souls from software game boss going, I, I'm not so sure. I don't
know somebody else. No, you gotta, you gotta get in there and I'm, I don't even need it. Let's go.
You see what I mean? Like what, how come those didn't fire? That's what happened last time.
Are they stuck in the wall? That move sucks. That move sucks. There's almost no delay on that move.
I got to dodge the right. Oh man. Damn. Okay. So when he goes like this, when he goes like,
move is so hard to fucking predict. I got to start dodging to the right because it's, it's so quick.
It's just like a wham. There's not much any, there's no time. I almost had him too. It's just like,
sometimes those things don't fire. I think they get like stuck behind a bookcase or something.
But when you hear him be like, here it comes, it's almost like, why have they not fired yet?
It's kind of, it fucks you up. Sometimes he'll stagger them out. Oh, this guy, you motherfucker.
I'll get it. Bad start. I thought he was going to do the other move.
God damn it. Oh, cause like this, there's such a small amount of time.
Cause those things are staggered. But if you dodge, you, you're probably going to get hit by the
magic. Fuck. He kind of attacks in like a half second or like a two tenths of a second, either
faster or slower than those things come out. So I wonder if you just run. I think you just run.
I don't think you dodge. I just think you actually just run to like the left or the right.
Just run away. I don't think you dodge those. I think you just run. Try it. That's not going to
happen. That's not going to happen. Okay. So it might work sometimes, but that was one of the
times when he was like, Hey, I know you're across the whole, uh, the whole level here, but I'd like
to just in, uh, and then a 10th of a second be in your face and bite, bite your throat. That's great.
Am I getting worse? I am, I am testing out theories, testing out theories. Were you not
in the room when I just said, I want to try running and that guy for fucking five minutes.
Oh, you motherfucker. Stop with this. Greedy motherfucker.
How do I fucking God, that stupid thing. Did you see right before he came in,
right before I screamed, right before I screamed, he was the greedy one, not me.
And you know what else I just, I just unbind it. I don't care. I'm not stealthing ever again.
Like, what the fuck is the point? It doesn't, it doesn't do anything anyways. Let's go on a chance
in hell, man. Not a chance. No, give me the fuck away from that. We haven't seen that move in five,
10 attempts. Stupid fucking crouch. You literally killed him the first try. Okay. If I bind crouch
again, I just leave it unbound the whole game. Like I, there's actually literally not a single
reason to have it bound. Not one solitary reason to use it in the whole game. I'm never binding
it again. He would have been dead. Crouch, crouch, crouch. He was dead too. And like,
I just couldn't fucking move. Just wait, just wait till you get this fucking game or your goddamn
PlayStation three, whatever the hell it is. Oh, what's it called? What if a console exists?
Just wait till you crouch accidentally and you get killed. And then I want, I want to see your
fucking 10 page essay about how much you can't believe it's in the game.
What the fuck are you talking about? What did he hit? What did he hit me with? The very end of that
at the very fucking end, right in the tiny little backswing. When he said, Jeremy, you're using an
Xbox controller. It's not, it's not the game's fault. So you're telling me that like 7 million
people that have to play this on Xbox should just buy a new console. Now I could have chosen,
but I like the Xbox controller. I like the Xbox controller cause it's big for my big ass hands.
I can't use the PlayStation 4 controller cause I can not, my thumbs knock into each other.
Quiet. He does a third time. Yeah. Unbind that shit and never bind it ever again.
Sweating. All right. That's fun. Yeah. I don't, I just really shouldn't even bind it.
Hmm. I have an idea. Here we go. You ready? Here's my idea. My idea. This is my, might not be,
you can't call the map in combat, right? What if I made select crouch and left stick the map?
I wonder if that's a good idea. No, that would fuck with me in the regular game. Switch the
map and crouch. I mean, I'll try it. Maybe let's see. I might just be running away from like enemies
and like I'll open the map. Select is the alt menu. Yeah. What about like, I wish I could do like
combo or something. I just wish it was hold. It's the easiest way to fix that problem.
It's just pressing stick, hold for one second. You crouch. Nobody is crouching during any fights.
It's like something you do to sneak around. All right. I want to do health and we'll go from there.
We need more buttons. Well, that's like the red, the red dead way to do it, right? Is to like pick
up items or there were things tied to the same button, right? And, but you had to hold it.
And I complained about that too. You're the only one with this problem. I'm not. I've seen at least
three or four other streamers talk about this exact issue and other players. I've been scouring the
forums. I've been scouring the forums. Okay. So what do I want to do this again? That is a
brilliant idea, but I don't know if I don't think I can do it. That's absolutely brilliant. I don't
think it's going to work. Nope. I can't do keyboard. That's annoying. I cannot do a combo.
I mean, what, hold on. What is it? It's X and I just press. Hey, it's fucking game. I've got
damn it. Give me a break. You gotta be kidding me. Problem is officially officially fixed.
I do want to go back because I want to check out that wheel. This is going into the cringe
collection. I want to go to the wheel. Where's the wheel of the church? Where is it? Like right
here? Like right here. Right. How did that fix it? Cause I'm pressing X on the keyboard
and it's unbound. All right. Attention. All players that have the problem of accidentally
crouching all the time, a very simple solution X on your keyboard. If you're playing on PC is
bound to crouch. You can safely unbind left stick crouch and just hit X when you want to
crouch around. Let this be a public service announcement to you all. All right. Where's the
wheel? It's outside here. If you weren't dodging around like you're moving away from a moving car,
you'd be fine. This is one of the most intense video games that's available for you to play.
Of course people are going to get intense and grip their controllers harder and move around
faster. Well, I'm not playing Mario paint. Like I said last night. All right. Where's the wheel?
Oh, this is wrong. I just killed this idiot. Okay. Where I should have marked it. Graveyard.
Yeah. That was up in there, right? Look, just because I have an intensified gamer grip does
not mean that I should have to suffer because it's bound to the same button that is walk.
Where is it here? I should have marked it. I don't remember which one it is.
It's one of these a parlor right here on gate. I like this intense. No, it's not that one.
Is it actually the classroom? Just walk out of the classroom. I don't remember.
What do I do about this very important crouch issue? If I'm playing on a PS4,
I can't help you there. I'm, what am I doing? This dude's got a gorilla grip. I'm just saying
like that going from, okay, listen to me. I'm going to, it's time for the guy to spam the
email. Let's see the email. Spam the email. There is such a huge difference when you're playing a
game like this, but when you are, when you are moving at a speed that, you know, how many
nauticals per second, whatever it is, when it changes to this, that slight change is enough for
you. It's such a drastic change because your muscle memory is wrong. Okay. So where is it?
Down here or is it over here? It was a way I could drop down. It wasn't over there.
I'm so glad that that is a complete solution though. That is an absolute 100% solution on PC.
Perfect. Where was that other? I swear it was like I could drop down. What was it here? Remember I
was looking at it and I was going, Oh, I can go down there. Or do I just have to ride the
thing down? I swear. Where was it? Don't tell them. Not only there were platforms on the wheel.
I know I, yeah, but I mean, like I'm, I thought there was another way to do this.
I thought there was another, um, thing to drop down. When do I get off?
When am I supposed to get off? Oh shit. I was supposed to get off right there. Oh no. Can I
jump on anything? Where's it taking me? Oh, I'm alive. That hurt. Wow.
There's so many of these little fireflies down here that you got dodged through.
What is that? What are you doing? It's not that bad. There's a shitload of help.
All right. Drop anything? No, but I can freely. Oh, wow. This is cool. Okay. Look at all these
fireflies. Firefly city down here. Is he ever going to use magic? I am. His weapon scales with
magic. Long tail cat talisman. You're immune to fall damage. That's fucking huge. How much health
does that give though? Raises max HP. Okay. So this is at the point. I'm going to put it right
at the tip to the crystal right there. Right at the tip, the tip of that crystal. How much do I
lose? Hmm. I mean, that's kind of significant. It's not that big of a deal, but all right. No
more fall jokes. Sad. It's like 7%. It actually is a lot. Okay. So that's what's down here.
Anything else down here? These are so red. Greedy motherfucker. Greedy motherfucker.
Let's stick. Let's stick. Let's stick. Let's stick. Maybe that's why I'm so red. I don't think. Wait,
what's this? Wait, should I, can I test it? Huh? Uh, I think, I believe I just fell off of a clip.
Excuse me? Stop. That's not funny. Do you see the weapon? The item that I have equipped right now
renders the wearer immune to fall damage and I jump off to test to see if it works and I'm not
immune to fall damage. Excuse me. That's, that's a scam. Where are my souls? Maybe if it's too far,
it doesn't matter. I don't, that's not even worth putting on then. It's down further. Yeah,
I just think I'm assuming. Um, that's not worth putting on because all the times that you care
about falling in these games is to, is if you die by falling in these games. Nobody cares about
falling a little bit and like, Ooh, I took like 30% damage. Where's this magical set that you guys
told me was down here? Right there. How do I get up there? Oh, the mechanical thing is back.
Where are my souls? Where are they? Are they up on the, they're up on the goddamn cliff?
How do I get the fuck out of here? All right. There's a place I can run up. Where is it? Right
there. That is, that thing is hard. Fine. All right. So, so how do I get over there? I don't
understand. How do I get over there? Um, but where do I go from here? Where do I go from here?
Fucking God. Okay. Um, how do I get over there? Like that house is, it's like a weird house in
the distance. Where was that? I gotta see. Okay. Is there another ledge I can jump to?
Is it up there? I'm going to sell this to a fucking vendor. I wasn't even that far.
Okay. So I got to go up all the way. What is up there? Oh dude, check this out. What's this?
Rune? Hell yeah. I could have just walked up there. Okay. So this is the first wheel. I got to go all
the way up on the second wheel. Do I have that? Am I understanding that correctly? I'm going to
get my souls, which are on a ledge over here. Or they're right there, right? Where do I, where,
where do I go? Is this the right way? That just makes me back up that way. I go all the way up
that way. I'm going to get all the way up. All right. All right. And then this will go all the
way up to the top of this. Yeah. Yeah. Gets me here, which no, I'm no, this is back up where this guy
was. Did he even hire? I think it's even higher. Huh? Wait, I'm back at the top. Where is this
thing? I've been all the way to the bottom. I've been all the way to the top. You guys said this
like a super awesome magical item on the wheel. Where am I going? In this foggy ass place.
Oh, down the wheel. There's a ledge. Yeah. But there's, wait, the ledges I just jumped off onto.
Isn't that take me back around? Ledge is a ledge. This, you mean this ledge here. You're talking
about right here. You're talking about right there. You're talking, you're talking about right there.
I'm a writer and then I've run this way. I, that was so fucking holy shit. Okay. I'm fine.
And then you talk about this way, but I feel like, isn't this the same place where I just was?
Oh, God damn it. Okay. I honestly, I've been hit like three times. I didn't realize whatever
shit you do to those. You're out of your league. No, just can't just kill, just kill, kill, kill,
kill. What are you doing over here? Are you a Disney channel bully? I dare you. You're out of
your league or like a Sonic character. Ooh, it's those guys. Okay. That's where that is. So now
this is not what you were talking about though. There's more. I'm going to jump off the ledge.
You mean what? You mean there's more down there? I don't think I can make it today. I wonder,
can I jump from here to there? Maybe not. Maybe it might be possible. I don't think so.
I forgot about the jump. Jump invisible platform ahead. I'm going to paint crystals to the house
if we go down there. That's what I mean. Like, I wonder if I can jump from here.
Is it like something I can jump onto from here? Like with a running jump?
Try it. That's gotta be another way to get up there. Here we go. Oh hell yeah. Lost ashes of war.
Nice. What does those do? He used to duplicate an ash of war so I can put it in two different items.
That's still not what you guys are talking about. All right, let me take a look here.
You're talking about that ledge right there? It's the only other ledge that I've seen.
Is that the one? So I gotta get... It's when you're going down. It's that crystal right there.
I've never played this. I cannot call the whole thing. All the way over here. Congratulations.
A little bit higher, but I just... I could get on this. I was seeing what was here.
I was seeing what was here. Relax. I was seeing what was there. There's another one right next to it.
Dude, what the fuck? Really? What? It's higher than this? I'm getting fucked with this. No,
there's nothing else here. Where is this magical ledge? You guys, I've been fucking with for like
30 minutes. I think you guys, have you guys actually just been messing with me? Don't even
tell me you've actually just been messing with me. You might have been. No way. It's higher?
Is it on the same side? No, that's not it. That's where... That's what the... I just was
fighting people there. The school room. Go inside the left room where there's a balcony.
Jump to the far left side of the balcony. Okay, I don't know... Stop telling me to get on the
elevator. What the fuck? I have to jump on the ledge off the elevator? It was by the elevator.
Come on. Oh, I'm gonna look so cool. Let's fucking go. Now I look really cool. I look so... I look
sick. Look at how cool this looks. All right, for all the haters, I'll take the helmet off.
Not even a thank you. Thank you for... Now it actually is Captain Hook. Thank you for telling me
where that was. Although, if you remember, I would like you to rewind when I looked over here and I
said, there's a ledge down there. I could probably jump onto that. And then a million screaming
haters were saying, get on the elevator. Dude, up the elevator. Look over at the elevator. Get on
the elevator. A million screaming haters. How do I get out of here? Is there anything else I can do
here? What about down there? Oh, look at that. Facts. I think down there is something cool down there.
Facts. Now let's teleport out. So, uh, uh, so I killed the boss here. Like, what did I get?
Oh my god, what the fuck just happened? Jesus. My microphone stand just like broke.
Hold on, I'll mute this. That was weird. I just, yeah, my like thing just popped off.
Still another boss here. Yeah, let me, I gotta keep going this way. I like it with the helmet on.
All right. Uh, cool. Did everything I needed to do. We're best here. Go through the door. Cool,
cool, cool, cool, cool. Although do I have any crunchies? Cause I probably need. I don't,
so I have to be careful. Is there another boss like right now? I need the souls. I have to go
kill these crabs. Give me 10,000. 10,000. I'll be happy. I need people here to get souls.
They hit me in the tail and hit me with that. Another one of these mechanical people.
Are you susceptible to magic? Probably not, right? Get away from me. Oh, you got me. Oh no.
Whatever. I'm not going to get mad. That was, that was terrifying. I got two of these now,
which wasn't there. Okay. After castle skip, foggy door needs a key. Remember that?
I can remember where that was, but there was a little, uh, dungeon I could go in.
Oh, you just, he's killing it. Just kill everything. That's fine.
Shit dude. What in the name of God are you doing? I get a little up. I think I should have enough.
200 more. And what am I going to put it into? Mind probably.
No, dexterity. I've not put a point in dexterity in a long time. Hey, one more for good luck.
Haley message. See if you, if you've gone insane. Uh, I think I'm doing okay.
What's the damage on this thing now? 39 plus 28 139 plus 26. Okay. Continue. Now I'm not
terrified of dying anywhere. So let me go up here first. It's quite a few things to see here. I
think. By the way, another cracked pot, which I haven't used yet. Living Josh odd. Fun to say
those words. Nothing else, right? Doesn't look like it. Uh, let me kill this guy out here. This
thing on it. Wait, dude, how it's fucking aim. What is this aim? How are you shooting me through
that? What a punk. Seriously, what a punk. Flintstone wet blade. Dude, can you stop this
raining hell for a second? How many people are standing over here? This is like a thousand people.
Paul is actually pretty good. Rune fragment. Rune fragment. Grab this guy too.
You guys up here. I live right next to me. Ristocrat garb. All right. There's an aristocrat
garb for me. You got invaded by a burger king. I don't think this is even what you said out
magic by the burger king guy. I'm fine. I don't know why that's making me. It's pissing me off.
Why is that making me so angry? That's funny. I'm like pissed that you said that.
I wonder if I can cheese this and just sit on the balcony. Probably can.
Song sounds like it's from Majora's Mask. So far I've really liked the music.
It's been really good. Doesn't open on this side. Really. That's a good move. I like it.
It's staying on the bar. I'm not taking it off. Okay. Is this a decent, decent skip?
To just run in here? Cool. Apologize to Burger King. What? All right. But I don't. Okay. Maybe
I'll go the other way first. I got to kill this guy. It's time for cheese ball incorporated.
Hello. Welcome to cheese ball incorporated. Welcome to the first meeting.
Crab. Okay. Let's explore over here for a minute. I did not get a chance to look over here. I got
the thing in the fountain. What about this? Illusory wall. Come on. Really?
You're getting minus karma. Oh, my head doesn't hurt. Um, it kind of does. This does a lot of
damage to crabs. What is that bar? Is it sleep? Cool move. Crab eggs. What's wrong with this guy?
What was that? What was wrong with that guy? Why was he doing that? It was infected with sleep.
Ah, okay. So I get it. I get it. Where did that crab even come from? Nothing this way.
See an item over on the ledge. Very interested in. There's some scary sounds coming from over here.
Golden seed. I probably need two at least. How about over here? There's a balcony that goes up
that way too. Back over here. I don't think you're high enough for this next area. But do you mean
like, what do you mean by that? I get to be the Burger King now. Increases intelligence? Wait,
increases intelligence with the detriment of stamina? I have 27 intelligence now. I actually
am Burger King. So how much did my- so my stamina is 91 now. That's actually kind of bad. Oh,
do the dance. All right, let's keep going. I'll keep it on for now. If the stamina is too much
of a problem, I'll pick it up. Why am I sleeping? I have resistance to sleep because I have so much
intelligence. That was pretty good timing, I will say. Whoa, cool. All right, I can get that in a
minute. Somebody little trinkets and little things to do. This game is so cool. Where's my
stuff over here? You two fight each other. All right, time to kill this guy. I'm gonna do a super
Q. Ready? Oh, I fell asleep. I don't understand what it even does. I woke right up. Go talk to
the sorcerer about the gate key. Yeah, I am, but I need to make sure I can get back in here. I'm
afraid of going to talk to that guy because he'll take the key or something and then I can't get
back in here, which would be a disaster. It'd be horrible. All right, let me try to get this item
over here. You got me. Really? You just fish-hooked me. All right, let's get it. Oh,
oh, good thing I decided to get that item. Oh,
there's an item down there too. Am I safe here?
Is it fucking me so many times? I was so far away. I was so far away. It didn't hit me the
other times. It must roll a certain way. Hold on. Let me go look. Shit. I definitely want whatever
that is, so I'm gonna get it. It must be a different way I can go. The ball looks like
it has some like a trajectory, right? It like rolls that way and then curves this way. Bounces
against this wall. Wait, let me see. Where does that bounce? I'm safe like right here.
Bounce. Okay, I'm safe right here. So from here, how do I get down there?
How do I go that way? I'm safe right here. I think. I looked like I was safe right here.
That's the exact one that I need to upgrade this weapon. Yeah, just run up. I just have to
weave. Wait. Should be able to get in without too much trouble, I hope. A teleporter.
There's a port here. I don't want to take this. No, I don't want to take that right now.
It might. Let me see if there's a bonfire here. I want to be able to come back.
Moon grum carrion night. He just parried me, you fucking weirdo. We've thinking. Are you dumb?
Wait, why does he parry? I'm alive. Really? It's so. Look at that.
No, look at how far away I am too. That's such a pain in the absolute dick. I gotta run up
the stupid thing again. That guy. I'm so pissed. That guy's dead. Yeah, guess what? I can do that
too, you know. No, I'm going to fucking pull his ass. I need to use it. I will. It's so embarrassing
when you get parried, especially when it's from a non playable character. Same moves that I do.
Fucking parried again. It's a fucking what the fuck? I'm doing it. I'm getting up there and I'm
going to do the same thing to this goddamn asshole. I'm going to parry you now. You're getting parried
now. It's your turn. Where are my souls? Okay, right. You're just getting outplayed. Yeah,
I feel like this is what happens when I play online. If I ever go invade anybody, I just get
embarrassed. I would much rather be the purple guy during an invasion that just kind of runs around
and just like swings and stuff and hurts somebody once and then just runs off a cliff. That's the
kind of support invader I am. Purple guy from Dark Souls. You know, you can be a purple phantom.
All right, dick. Let's go. Look at how predictable your swings are too.
See how good you handle this shit. Mr. Predictable. Oh look, it's Mr. Predictable. There you are.
I can do the same move. So this guy, you don't just don't swing your weapon out. Just don't
swing at him because he's going to parry every single R1. Oh, that hurts big time. I can't. Okay,
so just do not R1 ever. Uh, I was expecting that, but if I knocked him down when he got up,
he wasn't going to immediately just parry. Usually you have like a few seconds to swing.
Just lead him into the ball. No, I want to beat him one on one because I want to embarrass him
on stream. I want this guy to lose and then go look at the chat. What are they saying about me?
Like open up, open German 95. Everyone's like, omega low, omega low shit on him. Omega low. Wow.
Like omega low. Like, you know, that kind of stuff. Like, wow, you lost a German. Holy shit.
Like fucking delete your fucking save file. Let's go. You can't parry those. Stop trying.
Oh, my mom. That was definitely a good time to do that. You're not listening to NPC. Quiet.
Holy shit. That probably was an instant kill. Don't do it. Don't do it. This guy's going to
get crushed by a fucking bowling ball in five minutes. What the fuck? No, what? What are you
talking about? You don't have the mana to do that move. I kind of want that move though. It's
actually really good. He probably drops it. All right. New strategy. It's called stand in this.
I got it. I know what I'm doing. I'm going to stand in a safe place and just like fucking
dodge around. And again, he's going to get hit by the bowling ball like three times.
I'm just going to block. Thankfully, my souls are right here. What was wrong with that? Like I'm so
tilted that that didn't parry. What happened? What was wrong with that? I don't understand.
That was like almost perfect. He's spamming now. Crush him. He just taunted me.
Intelligence scaling. What? Excel's been facing magic or holy attacks. Just who were these knights
to prepare fight for? I don't get it. What does it mean? It's like a magic shield. Okay.
Okay, you've lost to Jerma. Is he in chat right now? Dude, like, fuck you, dude.
Like, I like playing against people and shit, but like taunting like in the middle of a match.
Like you're a fucking shitty. Like, I don't know. I don't think I need to tell you that.
Blocks magic. That seems like it's going to be pretty useful. All right. Wait, is this a shortcut?
Yes, that was an NPC. Yes, it was an NPC. That's not a real person. Is this a shortcut to something?
Where am I? I'm scared to open this door. I'm kind of afraid to open this. Let me try the other way
first. Yeah, that feels like a boss door. A big one. So I'm not going there yet. There's another
way to go this way. I still have enough. I still have plenty of health. I'm not scared. I've got a
lot of runes too. I'll be able to level up one more time. Probably putting in into endurance.
Maybe. Or vitality again. I need to get vitality to at least 20. There's also the portal. Yeah.
Well, if I get a new bonfire, then yeah, obviously. I don't want to get teleported
across the whole game. Well, I guess it's not that far. Oh, okay. No, get me out of here because
this is... I know where this is. Wait, I've been here before, right? Have I been here before? Yes,
I have. Okay. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Well, that's a skip to get back there quickly. All right. I'm
glad I got that. Cool. Okay. I'm going to put it into vitality or get intelligence to 25. What do
you think? 25 intelligence. Let's do it. Into mind for OLED. Still don't have enough. Pinball
route actually might be better. Yeah, it actually might be because this seems very dangerous. Let's
try it. Yeah, I'll get into 25. Oh my... And then I'll stop intelligent. I'm going to stop putting
points into intelligence now. Now I'm going to focus on vigor, mind, and maybe a little bit of
endurance. That's where it goes there. So let's try this skip and see what it looks like. I could
do the portal, but let me just see what's in that room so I can have the boss revealed maybe.
See how hard this is to do. This kind of seems like a horrible way to go. I mean, I guess if
you get through there, it's a little bit, maybe a tiny bit faster. Not really though. Not really
at all. What are you going to do with this bullshit right here? Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
leave me alone for a second. Uh, I can jump to that. What's this? Interesting.
Uh, I'm confused. What's the... That brings a bowling ball actually turns out to be faster
potentially. What if I go up the ladder? Hey, say it's my brother's birthday. My cousin's birthday.
Your favorite. Say his name. Ball sack. There's no backstab. I gotta get up there. Yeah, this is
definitely the better way to go. It's just not really that dangerous. Onion head. I would call
that a clam head. That's definitely a clam head. You gotta hug the crap. Let's try that again.
Only this time. Not mess it up. I think I'm going to kill one of the sorcerers first.
You know what I mean? Just like sneak up right here and just go with this.
Ooh, that's a new staff, but I don't know. Who's casting? Dude, that came out of his penis. What?
What? Where did this person come from? Where did you come from? Did you climb up the ladder?
Sanctuary stone. All right, we got some stuff to look at.
Lintstone scarab. A helmet? Blue green scarab worn directly on the head. Slightly reduced the
FB cost of sorcery increases damage taken. Oh my God. You're gonna be like a bug head.
This is weird. Okay, but just take damage taken. I don't know about that.
I think I like the Burger King helmet better. This is just intelligence. Which helps my weapon
too, not just my sorceries. I think it's better overall. Any secret rooms? I don't even know
where the fuck that guy came from. I think that's it. Okay, carrying glint blade staff or academy
staff. Staff of the academy embedded with a turquoise glint stone. Only a recognized sorcerer
is permitted to wield this staff. Damage? It's a little heavier. It has B scaling.
This is plus one and it's 131. This is zero and it's 130. I don't know. Just look at this one
though. Boost glint blade sorcery? This doesn't do anything. Scaling is all that matters. How
much does this boost sorcery though? That's a good question. I'll have to do a little bit of testing
on that. Oh man, I can go down here. Golden rune. Okay, and there's the teleporter. All right,
I'm going in. Marina of the lakes. This supported me here. Okay. Ooh, all right. Well, I got a new
school. Rest here. This game is too big. I mean, this game is very large. It's very big. All right,
what is this? Church of vows. What's this place? Is this an NPC? Is this an NPC? Is this a pope
turtle? I have no idea.
That the great houses of the earth tree and the moon by the matrimonial red-haired
radican and so our church holds in view the monuments of both houses the earth tree of the
capital and the academy are one are one are one are one are one was there something you yourself
around would serve as your guide only my legs aren't what used to be free to take it with you
really unless perhaps you are in search of instruction in which case i will share all
that i know probably faith you got oh my goodness gracious oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my god
i have scrolls to give you but wait did i magic lint blade creates a sigil that forms a projectile
i already have that arian greatsword forms a sweeping slash using magical greatsword
that thing's good 10 000 souls give scroll academy scroll what have we let us both learn
together heresy is not native to the world it is but a contrivance awesome this guy's a summon
this can be swift glintstone swiftly fires magic rate glintstone oh we got red flintstone
jesus our shower i just got chills i'm fucking excited all right hold on
old sewing needle golden tailoring tools all right anything else here that i can take
no all right so i gotta remember where this guy is so this over here yeah the church of vows is
where i gotta go uh because some of those are probably really powerful let me ask about uh
radigan wish to know more was a great champ possessed of flowing the wolf he came to these
lands at the head of a great ghost when he met lady ranana in battle he soon repented his
aggressions there became husband to the car first
radigan left renala coming queen marika's second husband and king consort taking the title of
second elden lord mystery endures to this day as to why lord radigan would cast lady renala
people are turning into animals or something because that was a wolf person this guy's a
for the seat of dalton she is queen or family the academy of that's definitely the boss
eight and beautiful full moon which sadly her heart was broken when lord radigan left her
when the academy rebelled against them yeah that's definitely the door okay all right uh i did buy
this one so let's go let's go get it put on the bar and let's test it
right against the brown mushrooms of adult is free alter garments what did i just do
i don't know do that all right what it takes the cloak off just taking off the cloak and reducing
the defense why would you do that it seems kind of like a bad idea all right this is i need 52
intelligence for this and there's no way i'm going to be able to have that now but i can do great
glint stone shard test it that is big slow but let's how much damage does it do it's short range
346 fucking damage okay i'll keep it there for now that's a lot of mana so i can also upgrade
my weapon i believe so here's what we're gonna do i'm just gonna go kill some stuff actually no
i don't have to i have uh crushies crunchies whatever then i'm gonna go see if i can fight
whatever the boss whatever that is in there should be able to do this i wanted to use that
souls there we go 1200 should do it really i thought i got a five
didn't
that's horseshit isn't it already no matter thought i got one did you watch over a broad rica
are you out of your mind who would stay with an ugly brute who only knows how to score and you have
zero absurd besides she'd never agree to it that's what she wants i refuse to believe it i don't doubt
you but i know when something's too good to be true um i mean i
go talk to rod rica okay who's rod rica
no it's not you not you oh wait rod rica's over here is the guy gonna talk to me yet no
it's about time i headed off i'll see you again warrior that aren't wait that's not
was it about time i'll see you again that was her you just have to wait oh
how come this person won't talk to me i got some new items that i weren't wasn't sure what the hell
they were this one here found material used for crafting in stone key got all these cookbooks
this yeah in detailing sewing needle grants choice of affinity upgrade to weapon
when applying an affinity using physical and magic type ashes of war and infinity
there's no affinity and magical frost can be chosen how do i do that leave and come back and
you can talk to her again those who live in death should be left okay i'll just come back
let's go to a random place adding the ash will prompt you okay so now i can talk to her and she
can upgrade stuff if she's gone uh she in the room with him where'd she go you know where she
is where'd she go she has a gift for spirit tuning so i told her everything i'm indebted to a
spirit tuner i met long ago it was all i could do to honor her i'm sorry i doubted you okay which
where is she oh i mean right next to him it's just so unassuming it's just so i'm so blind to it it's
just i'm just like oh that one has like a bunch of books that was a clothes and books that wasn't
even a person to see you again baby master hugh that he has taught me what of spirit tuning i'm
unsure of what i might be able to accomplish spirit tuning if i might be able to help you all
i'd certainly like to try and if there's any chance to ease the suffering of my dear men who were
grafted well i certainly must try boderica the spirit tune apprentice pleased to make your
acquaintance with the spirit tuning menu you can spend runes and grave glove wards to strengthen
the spirits you summon what oh man upgrade the boys boys suck i should upgrade the knight
if the boys to plus 10 or we riot i don't know what i want to do yet i don't know i don't know
what i want to do i'll have to come back i don't know yet i know i have to make a decision on this
the boys are trash off the boys the boys out of their misery
with the boys upgrade the ghastly crew um we'll come back to that we'll come back i need to think
about that for a minute because i'm either gonna upgrade the boys to plus 10 or i'm gonna have a
super bro that's gonna be able to come in and kill everybody in like two hits
let's go ahead i want to come back here where is it no no no where is it not the church um
the school where's the classroom right no where is it where is it the debate parlor
then you walk out yeah okay i just want to go in and see what this boss is i'm curious
we'll take another break we'll take one more break and then we will continue to play
and then conclude we will conclude for today i'm going to confirm right now yes i will be
streaming tomorrow elden ring but you'll die i'm not gonna die all right so then it was out
here whatever happened to el ballo okay here we go let's take a gander
absolutely a boss room no doubt in anybody's mind oh face what the fuck
oh it's the deacons it's the new deacons okay deacons of the deep let's go yeah it's deacons
i'll soon birth be a new a sweeting fresh pure
you got fire coming out of your mouth what is this horseshit
i got a feeling you gotta kill all of them and then the bubble will break boys a chandelier
dropped on him the shit dropped on him fuck god damn it it's cracking cracking somebody
okay they pass it around just like the deacons this is actually deacons i can't believe they're
crushed i'm so sad that i didn't get that on camera though you know what i mean like seriously
that would have been unbelievably funny hey what the fuck was that crack all right now get out get
out get out get out now get out now get out now get out now get out oh this is so easy
don't say that you'll probably lose you got it over there you just killed your own friend
you fucking lose them panic here we go well that didn't do anything what a waste i forgot
she's a mage who has it oh no that just reminded me of the boys
that just reminded me of the boys wow where is the last one over there this might be phase one
because this is actually really not a big deal phase one or is that just the deacons yeah of
course it is
well not gonna be fun is it upon my name is rani the witch
mother's rich slumber shall not be disturbed by thee
of course let's go
that's gonna be such a pain in the ass i have to do that bullshit run around smack people let's
just beat her first try which that means magic that means panic dodging of the last queen of karya
loves the of the night she conjured
holy shit she's got a power beam oh that's slow as shit bro all right okay i'm sure she's a spammer
right use the magic shield i wonder how much that eats damage though i was i was i kind of
want to see what you did well that phase one is gonna be such a pain in the ass to do over and
over again there's some of the boys for that one okay well i i can do that much quicker though
because you don't have to kill them just to walk around and break walk around break break break
break break i feel like once you depending on how much that eats damage those slow ones might i
might be able to eat them all what about the break oh shit that's right i i'll do it after this
unless okay if she does not do anything more ridiculous than that this might not be that big
of a problem let's try this again this time i know exactly what has to happen in the first
phase just kind of run around i really shouldn't need to get hit that much here let's find out
greedy where are you where are you where where is it oh my god where are you you piece of crap
you idiot i have to do a full cycle after this bullshit aren't i i'm so pissed you can't i can't
lock on to her you can't lock on to her when she's down there dumb dumb like i'm thinking r1
like right stick r1 right it won't work that's so annoying you would have been dead can't lock on
to the lady in the bubble oh my god stupid god damn deacon bullshit where is the oh yeah i'm
hiding behind him oh can't see me yeah you can't lock on to her although you can but sorry there's
like 30 people in the world do you want to walk in lock on or what are the other 40 people that
all right let's go okay running is good for that what does this do what does this do what does that
do why is there like a moon here now how much does it defend it's not that great i don't know
i'm not i'm not a fan i'm not a fan god you're so fucking annoying should i attack that i don't i
have no idea it's running left the strategy kind of you said get i'm gonna get in close
i'm gonna get in close she goes oh flasks yeah that's a good call flask and p yeah yep yep yep
yep absolutely i'll be right back i'm gonna be really quick i'm not gonna be long i'll be right
back i didn't put any music on oops all right let's do it i told you that was gonna be quick
i got a refill of water all right can somebody tell me how many runes this is how many do i get
i don't know this is golden rune seven is it 10k 2200 maybe 2500 you know all right let's do it
oh it tells you if you sell it a merchant okay so the next strategy that i'm gonna try is i'm
gonna stay just as close as possible i'm just gonna go i'm just gonna run sprint directly like
right into her stomach stay there i ain't going anywhere i'm gonna try to just just keep the gap
closed just kind of just pivot around her dodge around how much longer you're gonna be streaming
after the last break probably an hour or two maybe somewhere on like the eight hour mark maybe it
depends it depends on how long this takes it depends on if i can beat this tonight if i beat
this this will probably be the last thing i do if i win so if whenever this happens uh that's
probably gonna be the end stream but i mean i spent like an hour and 20 minutes on the first
boss of the game so we'll see how long that takes stream tomorrow or rest day i'll be live tomorrow
okay no dumb mistakes let's go
close the gap i wish it didn't take so long to load you're getting me out of my rhythm
what is your hitbox are you serious you're like all clothing this i'm i don't know what this is
i wonder if i should hit it okay all right so now i know what that fucking thing is it's a big bomb
if you touch it it explodes all right she does okay spins she'll throw it out all right watch out
for this goddamn thing come on boys what the fuck are you talking about oh fuck you i'm not dealing
with this bullshit what the fuck come here you're the one doing the incantation what the fuck is
happening i don't know if i would qualify in this fair fight get her okay that was fucking
horseshit hit them once they'll go down in one hit if i hit her do they disappear i feel like that
might be a better idea no okay they're all one hit kills and you have to dodge all of her other
bullshit that she does because she still casts spells okay well i now i understand what's going
on here you had the boys you're summoning giants i have a guy i have okay three guys with torches
and two guys with rusty shovels i don't think is the equivalent of a gigantic 55 foot tall
monster with a club so that first phase though was that was the absolutely the play
all that projectile spam as long as you just close the gap and you and you get right
right up kind of right in her um none of it will hit you the second phase though that's
a different story because you have to dodge all the other bullshit from the people she summons
dude i i fucking the lock on is gonna make me shit my pants i can't tell what's better r2
or just r1 spin it's hard to tell oh my god this this is so fucking annoying why
does that go through walls the thing that she does watch out
from software loves these like wicked annoying fights in the game oh i have an idea what's that
first phase be like just run around in circles while shit spams at you and you break the bubble
and now the lady comes out and then you fight the real boss then you fight the real fucking
boss i'm tilted i'm tilted right now i used two flasks already this is a disaster all right you
can't hit her more than once i'm worth trying oh my god they hit me twice fucker
hey i'm running fucking through you and she turns i thought she stays in the same spot
i thought it was one hit i thought it was one hit i don't think that's accurate inaccurate
inaccurate testing inaccurate testing you just have to avoid it god damn it can't even go near
this motherfucker it's such a random dog shit where does it there's no scenery on this second
stage why are you losing god damn it how dare you that's exactly what you wanted oh sorry but um
she spawns she spawns random ghouls and ghosts that will just attack you and you just have to
avoid them and attack her she spawned that guy that huge guy came and clubbed me in the back of
the skull from behind me i didn't even know where he was i gotta keep i gotta send this back down
hitting them once is true i hit that dragon like four times and he was still there should we go
casting versus casting it's worth a shot it's probably worth a shot see what happens although
i gotta stand still for a lot of that which is probably not gonna happen they disappear after a
moment yeah but they still exist which is like oh my god i can't hear anything sleep tidal lullabies
are scary lullabies are spooky probably hiding behind a goddamn bench somewhere over here
where something in my nose and i'm gonna pick it out in a second where is this person
god that throw dice in the fucking air where is this person where the fuck is this person
god kill me kill me kill me i can't use a flask here kill me i really okay i really wish i could
just beat this part like 30 times and then it was just like okay you've done it sir you can just go
to you can just do the actual fight now we just go right to the fight do you have a crossbow or
something um i i mean it's it's just orangey right it's like okay you're gonna get a good
roll here and is is it gonna is one of them gonna be behind a bookshelf with it or is it gonna be
like one of the thousand and a half people that are in the middle use the big wide range spell
i'm curious if the big one will hurt a lot because there are moments where i get like a second to
cast it i'm curious if it would get if it does a lot i would not last one fight in this game
without crying magic doesn't i would imagine magic probably is not that great considering uh
her repertoire of abilities now i got what i need i you know the could i probably get this to plus
five weapon maybe i'm not giving up yet i think our one's better i think our one's better i really
do all right before she does the move sleep tight you fucking wanker i tried to dodge but he went it
instead boys i'm like blood wig i'm like blood wig no stop putting my hand up to go i don't have to
do it i don't have to call them in real life i don't have to go like this stop fucking putting
my hands up i'm like i can't stop though i don't know why because i here's the thing listen
ah it takes like one two three anyways so that's like me going like let's go boys
is the same it doesn't not like i'm actively not playing it it has to cast so it's not like it's a
problem it's just like i don't know i just have to do it every time you're a clown at heart i was
doing pretty good that time though but the that's the problem calling out the summons it takes so
long that you just in a bad position pretty much no matter what i keep calling i keep calling out
boys like ludwig i swear to god i didn't even realize that's what's been happening this whole
time okay come on man that was a pretty good run that was not a bad one so i'm gonna right before
the phase change they'll come really all right that's good to know yeah our one's way better
people that put the fire on the ground buried behind a fucking wall somewhere where are you
you piece of shit does this block it does this block it will it actually block does this block
does this block does this block will it will line of sight block the stupid holy fire thing
that she's about to do why did i just get steam notifications you got it can't you can't get it
into past you can't get it into i just tried to get it into nope get out of the way before
she kills me with that stupid move sleep time sleep time reset mother fucker hold on i got why
am i in steam why why am i logged into fucking steam i'm not i'm not even logged into steam
that was a throw i had to why stop because i got i i can't lose a health flask you had seven
heals yeah but i had a full health bar gone it was gonna take one and a half to get rid of it
no i cannot use a flask on that phase i can't i can't use flask you're getting bodied by the
easiest main boss i'll time that person off for 10 minutes because they haven't seen phase two
how dare you come in here and say that without seeing phase two phase two stupid phase two
oh i know phase two is doable it's annoying but it's doable i just hate it doesn't matter how much
i go on on i go on the fucking from software forums and i say hey look i'm just i'm a gamer
and i'm a big fan i what i would really like to see is is no more of these free boss fight boss
fights where just random shit happens and then you fight the boss i i would appreciate if that
would never show up in one of these from software games again otherwise i will withhold my money
you just got downvoted you have negative they had negative like 400 upvotes i am telling you right
now i don't know why it has to be the same color i thought that was a person and i turned over here
immediately and what ended up happening is i got hit by the chandelier because i walked initially
this way because it's a yellow fucking thing on my screen just reset reset reset reset i'm
not wasting two fucking potions see what i mean oh you're not going to say i'm a big fan of like
when like you just throw random shit on every fucking inch of the screen and you know be careful
though you get up you can't memorize it because it just goes everywhere and then by the way i'd
love a boss that summons other bosses and other enemies at the same time that you're fighting
which can she can do in less than a tenth of a second but you take for you to summon the
the boys uh it's really annoying it takes me four seconds to do that when it should be pretty much
instant you said you wanted the other story bosses to be different no i know i think it's
not a bad encounter no i think i think this is actually one of like the you know i love like
rng throat dice in the air bullshit this is i i think this is like i think this is probably
my favorite encounter of the game so far i think this is like my favorite encounter so far
you know i'm i'm pretty sure he hates every main story boss no i don't i'm just kidding
just reminded you said you're gonna love this area i do love this area i don't hate this boss
i just hate everything they stand for god you really have to motherfucker where are you
where are you where are you where that killed me i would have screamed you bumped me two potions
down and this stupid shit fucking god i hate this place this is just stupid it's just fucking
dumb this is dumb what the fuck dude where the fuck are you i'm just killing you because i wanna
oh no i'm dead i'm dead i'm actually dead i gotta i gotta start over like i can't dude
like where even is this person where the fuck is this person and by the way um what's going on
with your house why is your house just collapsing what are you doing why are chandeliers just falling
from the ceiling huh maybe screw them in a little tighter wait listen for the lullaby it comes from
directional audio i feel like that person's just trying to get me to dive out into the chandelier
it's real yeah but this they're all clumped up in the same zone anyways
all the way the books are coming from mono audio andy it's the one that fires the books
it's not are you sure it's not coming from random rng random directions make it look good in front
of 10 000 people this is the motherfucker with the books it's the fuckers with the books and i'm
my brain just couldn't what happened there
i don't hear anything i don't hear any singing i don't hear any i don't hear any singing
just stuck in the corner down here oh my god you had to be in the stupidest fucking possible
stupid stupid all right you just the boys just gotta fuck that up and now they're all dead
bye guys the boys are actually fucking this up i don't the patterns are weird it goes around
her left side get it right what is it hey i dodged it you fool giant giant giant giant
get that balloon shit out of here god damn it the fucking it's so stressful that the
fucking dog's behind me i got it i got it i got it i got it i got it it's just like
trying to fucking find the right spot to be in when you're just somebody's just running behind
you i want to fight the boss not the dickheads that she summons to the party all right all right
let's go let's go let's go let's go let's go use your spells they'll do negative damage
so okay there's four things that she brings out unless there's something i haven't seen
there's a giant which spawns right behind you and swings down two or three seconds after she
spawns it it's always behind you you literally can't see it the dogs are probably the worst one
or the dragon because the dragons are so huge the dragon flies up in the air making it like a huge
pain in the ass you have to like just try to dodge that i think the dogs and the dragon are the worst
ones i don't know if it's rng or not a little like slimy like squirrely guy that is on the
ground with the blades you just have to run away i could try i could try a different summon yeah
that one was close how do you already have the bubble on you good rng right there your stupid
your stupid fucking voice line is talking over the singing behind something what new plan
the boys are gonna get summoned when she goes into the moon for the first time when she goes
into the moon boom i do say boom what a dip shit what the fuck was that homing missile it's
just fucking holding myself get her oh no dragon all right where is he you got come on dude like
you can't even see where the fucking where he goes it's like you i have to i have to look at
him i can't just guess that was a good one too i could hear her casting but like it's either she's
gonna cast a spell and i have to dodge it or i'm gonna dodge the spell and this guy that just goes
into the fucking skybox is gonna land on me and kill me can you use your horse no unfortunately
i would love to get on the horse i thought i thought that was gonna be the one i really did
ignore the dragon when he goes up but if i ignore the dragon when he goes up he's gonna come down
and land and it's gonna it does like i think 70 or 80 percent of your health bar and then i'm like
in a bad position she might already have a spell out dragon won't land on her i think it already
has the wolves are more aggressive i'll try the wolves that same exact strategy is going to apply
though he goes into the little thing wait till she goes in and then go for it bro just run when the
dragon crumbs yeah but the dragon the dragon the dragon's like as big as the whole screen
like it don't really matter where he lands he's gonna land he's probably gonna land on
you can't see him god you bastard don't do it don't do it don't do it don't do it
don't do it i want to use the heal but i have to
aggression get her get her no moves don't let her do any moves call it out what is it why can i hit
these fucking things he just ate that whole thing get that fucking thing away from me okay i need to
be able to see both of your asses you don't get two right oh please you can't even do that
giant dudes just stop do fucking something else god i haven't been able to go even near her
piece of shit i'm dead like dude like she kept spawning people one after the other after the
other after the other after the other it's like how am i supposed how you supposed to fight this
just fucking random dice roll bullshit you can interrupt the summons she does it so fast that
like it is a knockback on it it's just okay she spawned another thing when the dragon was
just still there i wonder if that's just a thing that she can just do maybe bleed weapons i mean
it's too late for that it really is i've already spent all my stones upgrading this thing i am
she's close okay here's what's gonna have to happen i have to get favorable rng no like dragon
then giant then dragon then dogs then guy like i need like at least a two or three moves in
between she did that like stupid beam thing and i couldn't get close to her and you hop over the
summoning circle you probably can but i she still summons it i wonder if there's maybe there is a
way to stagger maybe try r2 i'll give it a try that's gonna explode oh come the fuck on with
your stupid phase one eat my ass i want stamina yeah rolling probably is worse than juking i'll
stop rolling and this i'm telling you right now like that shit takes you out like that takes too
long i thought that was the moon holy fucking shit okay you can't but what the fuck am i locking on
to dude dogs are getting in the fucking way get out of the fucking way the giant where is she
oh my gosh she's inside of the snow globe don't don't don't don't don't i'm coming for you bitch
i was killed really glad for all this uh soundproofing screaming like no no don't
oh god i'm coming for you this is bad i can't scream it oh that was horrible
that wasn't even that bad it was okay all right all right okay 40 000 souls by the way
cheater and i hate you you're a dumb boss and yeah i'll take that orange and fucking you can
throw that orange in the ocean that like whatever that is a little like cutie orange like the
clementines you fucking peel it let me make sure i don't die here so what's the pro what's going
on now let me do this don't don't don't don't don't i'm coming for you bitch my god if that
killed me can you fucking imagine if that killed me because it doesn't count it doesn't count if
you die during a boss fight i would have been so awful but look this is what i'm talking about
ready like okay so hold on let me put it on screen so look when check this shit out i did
a full heal right before this because i remember i i rose right after the giant came out and i said
like oh shit i better be at full health for this oh i kill her so i kill her right i get i have
almost full health i'm coming for you bitch look at this move that's still there can you imagine
if i did not have that face that's fucking embarrassing it was embarrassing okay so
there's a chest right here i already sat at that right where did he flee my sweet things i'm right
here i'm opening up the treasure chest it's locked
i just kill her reborn of my beloved egg i just realized that her hat is like a snake or a bird
or something that has eyes rebirth cosmetics okay so i can redo this rebirth should i do that
i'm kind of afraid to do that because that's probably just part of the story right
it's a respec they added respecs to really no way it's a stat refresh has there always been
a respec i don't remember you lose 10 you're great ruins oh right i would imagine i probably
got something from her take the power we gotta go okay yeah this is gonna be huge
all right well i don't want to do that let's level up no i'm not gonna level up yet because
i want to maybe get one of those uh spells okay let's i can teleport here whenever i want this
is the uh grand library let's go back here there's a jet it's a lock chest i want to see
what this is i'm gonna go talk to the finger lady this is the creepiest thing in this whole
game by the way it's so weird you have earned the right to become elder lord have i now seek
the earth tree and an audience with queen marika to become elder lord and restore the golden order
i'm not done streaming yet because i want to i think i want to go to that castle skip foggy door
more talismans
become okay what is that 60 intelligence full moon sorcery 70 intelligence guys i don't think
we're getting there 60 and this is uh this is astrologer yeah uh this is definitely for
astrology because i don't think it's reliable that i'm going with this character with this kind of
like battle mage i don't think i get to 60 intelligence i don't want to go full
sorcery it it sucks with bosses full sorcery is really fun to try to like cheese bosses and stuff
but it for first playthrough it's like it's hard because you really you have to kind of stand
really still i don't like sorcery for the first time that's so goddamn cool looking though is
it a sword it's a staff right it's a scepter just i could just consume the soul too this is really
awesome but i think for the first playthrough i kind of have to stick with what i'm doing here
and that's spells light spell casting battle mage with like the decks in scaling weapons
this looks insane though doing like a full complete just astrology or just dumping every
single point you get into sorcery or intelligence i think probably you probably want to kill bosses
with this it looks like a sword but it says the staff down i also want to look at this too where
is it okay this is godric's great rune did i get a great rune okay great rune of the unborn used to
perfect rebirth oh so you use it okay so this is the great rune so once i respect this is gone
this is the great rune okay cool go back to the turtle yeah uh i'm gonna break it i know it's sad
and that those items look so cool but it's just not gonna work with what i'm working with
so i'm gonna crush it unfortunate but we're gonna be like at 35 40 and
30 decks yeah 60 and 70 intelligence means i have to redo the whole character
which i i mean i this thing is awesome never don't forget don't forget what we have equipped right
now this thing is awesome it scales off of int decks and strength but we're doing pretty much
int index bring some water got you covered right here you should just do full sorcery
i would be pretty bad at full sorcery because folks like i said full sorcery requires you to
essentially stand still which i don't like doing i'm not confident enough to do it maybe like
another two or three playthroughs and i'll do like yeah i'll do a full just caster caster no melee
weapon no swinging at all all right let me go to the turtle and this is this will be it uh wait i
want to look at that i'm gonna go to the castle skip because i want to see what those uh keys do
the foggy door all right lindstone comet this is in 36 which will get there will definitely star
shower sounds cool our six shooting stars that pursue foes so that's like the ring and they
the thing the dog was doing to us there's also this thing i can afford them all but i don't
know if i really want to buy them all this is probably the best one to get because this is
melee i believe this is melee so i'm gonna get it this one is kind of cool too i kind of want
the comet though let me go check and see how this one looks because if this is the one that i think
it is i can incorporate this into a rotation you know what i mean i can like slash slash with the
magic uh weapon which is exactly the kind of character that i'm trying to make you look like
an scp oh i sound like one too is this what i think it is yeah it is so i could be like wham
wham it's kind of it's a good potential i wonder if it uh it staggers it is really slow but that is
precisely thank you for bringing that up there's a really good point that's why we're putting
points into dexterity so if i want dexterity up too because if you don't know let's explanation
dexterity reduces casting time of spells so eventually this thing could actually be faster
way faster let's see how much damage it does how was the scale i wonder does it have a three
swing or is it just two it can just be chained it's got a massive arc too look at that arc
that's pretty useful now we're going to do decks we have to make sure we can get some decks
so i don't think i'm going to buy the other shit i'm going to level up 25 25 and then we'll do
endurance mind maybe i could get this over with but that's i'm just so that's so many points to
not put into something else i want 25 25 i think it's actually really really important see how fast
this is now that is way faster that is uh at least 10 to 15 faster than it was before no it
absolutely it definitely is what about oleg well now i can focus on oleg but i can't just let my
damage fall off completely i have to like be able to beat stuff in the game too there's no difference
where there has to be i don't know if this is realistic i think it's all right look i have a
respect if this doesn't work out let me buy this other one too this is like the little one swift
this actually could be useful too copium this could be what what it ends up being right because
i have the pole oh just a lot faster so it could be like when wham dodge wham lightning bolt
lightning bolt yeah i need mana flasks really cool though really cool let's see how much
damage this stuff does because i this little swift one this could be a little just pick people off
and like kind of poke at people let's check the one that i really care about this one here i mean
that's a lot considering my regular swing is it's got huge range too that one i don't really like
so much but i think this is a bad indicator because these guys work so hard there's nothing
in there all right well i'm just done all right well i'm just playing around um i kind of want
to kill that guy he's that's just like a regular enemy it's kind of bad i don't know if that's
going to be amazing if there's more than one person right can i hold the button down let's see you
cannot hold the button down oh they're not here anymore they come out at night i get it all right
let's fight a group with it all right it's showing its usefulness because that can really make or
break anything this one's not bad but it's kind of the other one hits a little harder
it's really good against groups and some of the toughest shit in this game is when three or four
people are all in front of you i'll leave it on for now so here's an interesting question does
this scale do my sorcery moves scale with the staff or are they just based off of intelligence
and that's it i wonder both so i really should be upgrading the step too if i can this is good for
stutter i'll try it for now all right we're not done almost done i need to go back here and i
believe it's it's like right here somewhere right here i want to do that castle skip drop down
and then there it is the misty door for the keys is it this way not this one
bro please i'm begging you craft man two main bosses down i believe it's three main bosses down
as of right this moment unless that wasn't a main boss i think it was though because that was the
academy lady bro please oh it's one of these right main gate left side i think it's main gate
i just don't remember no it's up there i wrote after castle skip foggy door needs a key
and i but i don't i should have told myself where the castle skip was
and i played too many from software games i think you have to travel from the bonfire
rampart tower does anybody remember this is what i wrote down tower i this is it yep okay
so we go here i think it's potentially a mcdonald's night time is it oh shit
it's late my god it's late it's too late shit it's late i did it now it's down here right right here
i don't i wonder what's in here let's check it out here we go okay what is this
is iron wet blade and ockcrest wooden shield miss misery miss record me sorry miss record
oh it's a dagger art and sharpening critical hits especially potent that's cool looking that's
cool that's insane crit yeah that's cool i got one of those whetstone things too
not entirely certain of what they are
ranch wish me a happy birthday my mom forgot about it and i thought you could fill in for her
happy birthday yes that doesn't sound good
i remember looking in here from there okay well cool that's what that do i have any more keys
i think i think it's two to get in there yeah that was one okay um iron grants choice of trinity
every keen or quality can be chosen so this you can put this on a weapon right and it'll scale it
for intelligence imagining right or vice versa you can change the scaling of the weapon okay
i think that's it 12 30 it's late been about eight hours i want to keep playing all right i have a
proposition for you i have a proposition for everybody here here's my proposition two options
option one is just keep going i'm gonna eat like i'll just go figure out what i'm gonna eat
no this is a bad idea because then it'll get too late and i'll fuck up my whole sleep schedule
no that's it we're done i want to play okay uh that's it that was awesome it was an intense
session uh we'll be live tomorrow tomorrow starting at the same time about four o'clock
pacific i cannot guarantee we're gonna do five days in a row but you know i want to play elden
ring i just want to play it so if i'm not gonna here's the thing i'm not gonna play this game
off stream realistically until i get to a point where i've seen a lot of the game already
so i'm just playing it as i stream it which makes sense right so i'll be left tomorrow four o'clock
aim rating update it's still a 9.4 it has not changed although it actually it went down to
like a 9.3 and then ticked back up to a 9.4 so it hasn't it hasn't gone anywhere look at how much
of this shit is this is ridiculous how long have i been playing this total hours 20 30 25 it was
like 10 hours the first day eight nine hours the second day you know it's been like 27 28
when i was my first playthrough of bloodborne and dark souls 3 i don't think was more than
35 to 40 i i beat dark souls 3 in like what four five streams five streams maybe four like five
yeah i'm not even remotely close to be even touching the surface of this game it was eight
streams with the plus the dlc okay so what like five or six without it i feel like after 30 hours
in dark souls 3 you're getting close to like the last arc of the game it's insane all right this
is uh yeah i will catch you guys tomorrow at four let's get the credits we'll just chill for a
little bit thanks for watching as always i know that i can be a little much sometimes my um rage
but no i think the game is fantastic it's just it's it's crazy and i will see you later i gotta
figure out what i'm gonna do for food though which i'm not sure because it's very very late
we'll figure something out uh let's see i'm hungry but what what's even available i wonder
figure it out uh we're gonna raid box box i don't know where box box is in the game they're also
playing elden ring let's see where he is yeah do you guys do the same thing where it's a get you
want to see where people are so you almost like open one eye and like you look down at the health
bar and you kind of just see what the area looks like and you click click on for two seconds look
away i don't know where box box is in the game but it could be way further ahead than i am or
it could be way before where i am right now so just be aware there may be spoilers ahead
be aware good night goodbye go say hi to box box see you soon