This shirt is like wet with sweat.
All right, let me set this up. See, we're just fine. Everything's fine. Put that over here.
There's seven fucking thousand people here. I'm gonna change it off from IRL. We're gonna go back
to Lifeline. I'm gonna try to finish Lifeline. Or I'm gonna try at least a handful of times.
Let's see. Trying to finish talk at game. Game. You look kind of pale. I feel uh, I kind of feel
I feel pretty good. Trying to finish to finish. That's a good title. Trying to finish
to finish. Right, that's literally what's going on. Lifeline. This is joke on a joke. Okay,
by the way, if you were participating only for the festivities of,
well it wasn't really festivities, it was more along the lines of just me sitting here with
like a bunch of goofy dumb shit on, panicking and nothing happening. So if you enjoyed that,
I'm glad you did. But we're gonna transition to a stupid PlayStation 2 game where you
have to yell at the microphone. If you want to see what it looks like, here it is.
Yeah! That's unfortunate. This is the microphone I have to use. It goes like this. And you have
to talk to the lady on the screen. Oh, but somebody's saying uh, big bits came in.
Ta-bunk. I might not have the right hairstyle for that. All right, let me turn on the
PlayStation 2. Let's boot it up. Reset transformation on that. We're gonna try to
just go right where we left off. Why is this so small? It shouldn't be like that.
The PlayStation 1 sound is better. Uh, Brolok. Brolok, you are at the 24-hour cool-off period,
man. That's a hundred dollars from Brolok. You are actually at the cool-off period.
It hasn't even been 24 hours. We got nine hundred dollars now. Nine hundred and fifty bucks.
Oh, nine hundred and five. God. Holy shit, man. Nearly a fucking thousand dollars.
Let's go. Make sure I get my tabs open because I just started here. Let's bring the volume down
a little. That belongs over here. But, Brolok, honestly, I really hope that you're
taking care of yourself first. That's an extreme amount of money to give anyone.
I really hope that you are within the means to give or do so. Thank you so much for the
ridiculous amount of money. Trying to finish to finish. We are updated with the correct information.
Hold on. I gotta get to the screen first. I should have all my tabs. I do. Lifeline.
No. Sweat check. It's the whole shirt. We can't do a check on it. It's the entire article of
clothing. So I have to go here. All right. We're ready to start. If you don't know what's going
on, Lifeline is a game where you have to speak instructions to a girl on the screen
and she you can't control it any other way. It's only through that. This is
a spoiler for this game because literally we're at the last hour or two of the game.
I might not even complete it because the game is a fucking mess and sometimes does not listen
to a goddamn thing you say. But I'm going to try. Wrong. Well, it is not wrong. It's my
opinion. I'm fine. I think it's a great game. I think it's a great idea. I'm not. I'm fine.
Make sure they can hear me. So we're at the last portion of the game. Just Broluck. Broluck. Bro.
Hey. Bro. Bro. Bro. Bro. You just. Broluck. That's a thousand dollars. A thousand. One
thousand in one day. A thousand dollars in a day. One thousand dollars in a day.
Broluck just donated a thousand dollars. Get up. Okay. I got it already.
They say, all right, man, that's it. That's it for me for a while.
Just letting you know that this amount is okay for me to donate.
Been watching you since I was in high school and you helped me along the way.
The tragic part is, in Australian dollars, a hundred bits is two dollars.
Enjoy. Oh my god. Did you. That's a. That's thousands. I hope. I hope you got some like
Monopoly man money because holy shit. Case three. Case three. Run. Yes. Was it 15? 50? 15?
It's not here. Someone's taken it already. We need to find Alan Honda.
You don't need to see this shit anyways. Operator, hold on a sec.
This cord, what is this? So many people already have no idea what's going on.
But it's all right. This can't be. Listen, can you analyze this device?
There's no time limit on here anyways.
Is that a good place for me to be? We're racing against time. Hurry, analyze it.
Okay. There's no mistake. It's a bomb. Yes, I know what it is. I've seen it like 10 times
now. I know it's a bomb. The sum of the last digits of today's date. Okay, you found the
right instructions to defuse it. Can you read them to me? Out of sync? We'll think it
through. Oh yeah, the webcam is. What's the first one? Now we're going. Enter the sum of
the last digits of today's date. Okay, yes, that's easy. Today is December 24th, 2029.
So the last digit of each one would be 249.
15, 50, 15, right?
Game is too loud? Yes. I got it. I got it. The music blasting.
All right, let's get to the part where I need to get to.
Enter the number of guests checked into the hotel.
It's not 13. She's going to stop me. She goes, wait.
All right, let's go. I know what it is.
Somebody's saying emulate this and get it to this part. Just so I'm able
to just go through this part. There's no other save point until you'll see what happens here.
50. Okay, what's the next step for diffusing this? I'm going to move some of these windows
around. That's back. That's a better spot for all my windows. All right. Enter the sum
of the last digits of PM Takayama's birthday. How old is she in the game? I actually
don't know. That's a good question. You need to keep moving. You need to keep moving.
Did he? I don't remember. I only saw it last night. I have no idea how old this girl is.
I don't know. This part takes 20 minutes and the part where you die
takes five. I know it's hell. It's hell doing this. Yes, I know. It's 15.
So it's left soldier, right soldier. I got to be very clear.
And the fact that I only have one little health bar, it sucks. No, it's not seven. 15.
Okay, I'm going to, I got to move this because this is old and I don't want to
drink out of this. This is the part that I've died out like seven or eight times last night.
Remember, this takes 20 minutes or so to do this part. Oh, I got to get it ready.
Do you like to take a break? There we go. She's going to do the whole thing with,
can we be friends when I get out of here? Can we be relatives or something?
Well, whatever the fuck she says. Yeah. Unskippable. It's crazy because select
skips cutscenes, but not this one and not any of the ones leading up to where I need to be.
For some reason they decided that that was a good idea. What am I going to say this time?
What do you think? Ready? I feel like I never went to bed. Is that weird? I feel like I'm
still here from yesterday. And you know, it's funny. It was today. It was this morning.
If we get back to earth safely, you think we could actually meet somewhere
like normal friends? Yeah. On Facebook, add me on Facebook. Look, you don't need to be a jerk.
I was being serious and now you make me feel like an idiot.
We really have to find her. We've got to Facebook. That isn't very insulting.
Actually, that's extraordinarily insulting. Facebook. Yeah, I'll add you on Facebook, I guess.
All right. Left soldier, right soldier, red lever, yellow lever, red lever, yellow lever,
red lever, red, shoot red, shoot red lever. Left soldier, right soldier, red lever, shoot
yellow, shoot yellow lever. I got it. Red lever, shoot red, shoot yellow. That's as clear
as I could possibly make it. Shoot yellow. Left soldier. Here we go. All right, here we go.
Come on. Come on. We're going to get that first try. It's not lever. That's a soap company.
Lever 2000.
Shoot yellow. Left soldier. What? Soldier. It's soldier. Red lever, red lever, left soldier.
No, I'm not faxing you my feet. Okay. Pay attention. Here we go. Left soldier.
Shoot red. Shoot, shoot, shoot red. Shoot yellow. Left soldier. Right soldier.
Shoot. I'm not saying shoot. Shoot red. Left soldier. Right soldier. Hide. Shoot red.
Hide. Hide. Shoot red. Hide. Shoot left. Shoot red. Shoot red. The right soldier. Red lever.
But I said shoot red. Oh my god. And when you shoot the soldier, it doesn't even do anything.
You shoot them, they go, oh, and then they keep fighting you. What? It doesn't do anything.
It doesn't do anything when you shoot them. I can't fucking believe this,
that you have to do this whole thing again. Somebody just fell asleep at the at the fucking
computer to like have this be a reality. This is the only save point. You have to do the whole
entire cut scene again. Somebody fell asleep making this game. Get up. Okay, I got it already.
Case three. Case three. Okay. How do I fast forward the stream? Run. Yes. What are you
doing? What's going on with this fucking audio and video? And I don't have any health.
They made the health packs like Resident Evil 1 in this game. Like if you don't, if you run
out of them, you lose. Somebody look up those cheats for the PlayStation 2 version. No click
through the fucking wall. I don't care. I need to get a game shark. The fact that you have
to do this again. What were you doing when you made this portion? How did you think that this
was a good? How? How is it? Why would you make not have a save point? Why would you make this
the part that can't skip it? Can you read them to me? Well, we will we do it. Why would you
sit in the office? What's the first? And you would you run it? Did you run out of time?
Enter the sum of the last digits of today's date. Okay, yes. Nobody but me got to this
point. This is a speedrun of this game. Skip cutscenes with L2 and select.
Didn't I do that already? Select worked before. I used L2. No, they don't work.
Enter the number of guests checked into the hotel. Thanks for the save point.
Careful with this. Safe point. Wait a second. It's not 13. It's neither. It's the number of
checked in guests. Use the speedrun as a walkthrough. And enter that number.
I'm gonna see. I'm gonna mimic exactly what this person says. Okay, what's the next step?
I don't think there even is. Does it even exist? Enter the sum of the last digits of
PM Takeyama's birthday. What's going on with this fucking thing? What the fuck is happening?
It just got dark. Yeah, this is how it ends. It ends with me fucking snapping. I'm gonna put the
disk in my shredder. This is how what's gonna happen here. Holy shit. This cable's broken,
I think. No, it's not. I think we're good. Shred the disk. Shred this fucking disk.
You're right. Didn't he say something about that at some point? I know. I am right.
Big coffee cup. It is. I'm a streamer. We drink coffee, you know. We drink coffee and
sip on it for two, four hours straight, dude. That was a huge vein. Did you see that?
The blood pressure is rising. All right, should I? Stop talking, lady.
All right, here's what I'm gonna try. I think I'm just gonna not even worry about the fucking
soldiers. I'm just gonna shoot. I'm gonna... Red lever. Yellow lever. Red lever. Red lever.
I'm just gonna hide and shoot. Every time I try to deal with the soldiers, I say like,
left shoulder, right soldier, right soldier, left soldier, and she just doesn't shoot in
the right direction. We've seen it like five times now. You have to say shoot red. I just,
I tried that. Shoot red. Shoot red. And then everyone got mad because they're saying red
lever. And then when I do that, people get mad because they're saying shoot red.
I don't want to see this again. You can't just, while you're talking, walk over to the kiosk
and punch in the code to do the safe point. It's because I have a Boston accent. It's,
but it's, it's not... Red lever is... It's not like I'm going, ah, red lever. Open up the
red lever, dude. Red lever. Red lever. Shoot red. Red lever. That's not what I'm saying.
Oh yeah, by the way, uh, pick me up with some clam chowder while you got a chance.
Sorry my fucking Boston accent is really screwing this game up. I fucking can't help it. I say
like ahs and hs and ahs. I have not said like ah the whole playthrough. Listen to the,
listen to the sound of my voice. This is the way I've been talking the whole time.
Some of you guys are making it sound like I'm like, hey, can you like go over there
and pick up some of the thing on the ground? Don't make me make my fucking chin bigger.
You can skip it with select. Sometimes you gotta prove it on the webcam.
Is it bootleg controller? No, it's not. This is an officially licensed controller.
All right. Red lever. Red lever. I'm stuck in a time loop right now and I have to get out of
it. I'm stuck in a time loop. I'm stuck in a time loop right now. Licensed by mad cats.
I'm just gonna do it with a Boston accent. Speedrun strat is just say red,
but wouldn't that she spuck that up sometimes and think I'm saying right?
Take a med kit. I don't have any med kits. There are no med kits. There are zero.
Red. Red. Red. Shoot. Red. Red lever. Hide. Right soldier. Hide. Yellow lever.
Hide. Yellow lever. Yellow lever. Hide. You fucking assholes. Red lever.
Yellow lever. Yes. What does it say in the walkthrough? What does it say in the
walkthrough? Somebody please. I need this. I can't do this again. Please give me a save point.
What happens now? What happens now? You have to say run. Say run. Right? It was save run
when I got the opportunity. Save run. Run. Is that enough to have an accent for you?
Run. Run. Run.
Run.
Is that? Is that? Worst ending? I don't care. That took like four and a half hours to do that.
More than that. I have to let the others know. Give me a save point please.
I don't. Do you have? Why would you do this to me? There's got to be a safe point in this
room. What do I do now? What should I do? Something terrible is happening.
Run again? Should I run again? Somebody look it up for me. I don't have a computer in front of me.
I have a PlayStation 2 computer monitor screen. I don't have an actual computer.
Run. Run. Calm down. Corridor open. Wait. Hold on. Okay. Run. R.I.P. Gino. I understand.
I feel the same way. He should have been in Smash. But you got to give me the actual
thing I need to do. So it's calm down. I don't care about cheating right now because I don't
care about a thing about this. We're not doing another fucking 42 minute cut scene
scenario. It's literally sexy pose. No it's not. I'm not getting baited that hard.
No no no. Somebody just had it. You just put it in there. I can't look it up. I have no
spam to keep the advice away. I'm trying to cheat here and you're making it very
difficult for me. Okay here we go. This is I gotta I gotta walk through here.
Let's go all the way to the bottom. If it's not sexy pose. I just want to make sure you
guys are aware of this. If it's not sexy pose. I'm turning off the stream. All you're gonna
do is make a threat. Bring back the music. Okay trying to find a walkthrough of this
game is like it's not like easy to find a real one. Lifeline PS2. Well I got my
computer here. I was lying. Okay here we go. Here's a walkthrough. I don't care. I'm
gonna read this. Here's a full walkthrough. All the way to the bottom here because this
is the end of the game. There's so much more to the game. This this is like another two
and a half hours to this game. Okay use the door. Press case three. All right.
There's the shootout. The Marines show up. It's stuck. Later run when Geno fights the
alien. If you decide to stay behind and help you'll be killed. Thank god. Trust me when I
say you don't want to do this part. They actually wrote that in the walkthrough of
the game. Trust me when I say you don't want to do this part again. UGH exclamation
point. Even in the walkthrough they hate it. After it's all over tell Rio to cheer
up and on you go to the testing ward. There's been an unfortunate incident.
We set an explosive but it seems that one of your people has diffused it. What is that
supposed to mean? I never gave you orders to blow up the station.
We don't take orders from you. What? Aren't you here to rescue us? Rescue?
How presumptuous. Who on earth told you that? We are soldiers for a new world order.
Our sole purpose here is to obtain a relic with incredible power.
Having accomplished our objective we are now leaving. Alan you're with these terrorists as
well? I but I this being Christmas my gift to you is a quick painless death by one very
impressive explosion. I need to be ready to do exactly what this thing tells me to do.
Now I have no choice but to dispose of you. I just happen to do this whole thing again like
they said UGH exclamation point. Wait take me as your hostage.
What? Are you sure that I just have to cheer up while running into the fire?
Trust me to say the then witness the after it's all over tell her to cheer up.
You monsters you herded them here to kill them not for rescue.
Hey exactly and you've conveniently returned to die as well.
Cheer up tell her to cheer up. I curse you killed a great man. Curse you. I'll finish her.
Oh she's the alien. She's the alien. That's the climax of the story. I curse you.
Oh sexy pose yeah I'm sure it is.
I brew my own coffee. I brew my own coffee with my own percolator.
Only real only real coffee enthusiasts do that. I used to drink Dunkin' Donuts every
fucking day. What are you talking about? In fact I think this might even be Doug.
This is there's okay then I'm gonna return this. I'm gonna return wherever I got this
coffee. That's a hair. There's a hair in my coffee and that's a big hair. Any more hairs?
I knew it. I'm ignoring the plot. Who am I? Um okay I'm a descendant of Paracelsus
the scientist from Alan's disc. The story of Paracelsus and the philosopher's stone is more
than just a legend. It's real. It's the stone that I've been trying to find. It's an heirloom
that my family has guarded since Paracelsus time. It began to influence my life when I was
only a child. I told you guys that she was like coming to steal it. The geologist's name was
Joseph Kraft. Those two spent years researching the stone and they eventually uncovered the
secret nature of it. Physically the philosopher's stone is pretty much your basic rock but what's
uncanny about it is the composition. Completely uniform throughout. Whether stone or metal it's
impossible to manufacture solids of entirely uniform composition on earth. Why you ask?
It was a dog hair. Because of gravity. The same night they concluded their analysis of the stone
Kraft shot my dad. It was one of your nose hairs like this fucking huge. He also shot me.
I survived but my mom and dad weren't so lucky. No save point yet by the way. Kraft was trying to
steal the philosopher's stone but dad had it protected. Fearing for my safety I fled to Japan.
I just wanted to forget everything. Kraft back in cheese. But then I saw it on the news.
Oh I gotta my does my tweet say I'm doing an IRL hang up? The channel's negative or positive
emotion from spoken words. With the stone you can heal or corrupt. If I die I get to sit this I
know I don't want to sit through this again. At least according to research data taken by
Joseph Kraft. From what I can tell he used the stolen research to build a replica of the
stone in the lab on this space station. I guess with all the chaos going on he was
planning to steal the real stone and blame it on the aliens. Right I mean this is what we're
seeing. Even if that means killing everyone in the hotel to ensure their silence.
But why does he want the stone so much? I don't get it. What was he gonna do with it?
He does stop that. Turn people into hideous monsters. He would use the stone for that.
The infinity stones. Use the stone for that. Cheer up. Got it. What we need to do is find
Alan's stone and dispose of it. Actually that can wait. I'm sorry I've been so caught up in
the stone I still have to get you out of there. And Naomi too. To make super mac and cheese.
But listen in spite of all our searching we haven't found your girlfriend.
Yeah that's right. You know what's happening. I mean I know the philosophy of stone and
all that but my girlfriend is missing. That alien. Is it some kind of mutated person that's chasing us?
Could it be? Sorry. I'm sorry. What am I saying? Good you should be. There's still the testing
ward left. That's it she must be in the testing ward. The monitor room you're in it's in the
testing ward. She's in the oh she's in the room I'm in? She's been here the whole time?
Naomi. What? Oh yeah she is. She's in a fucking cryogenic lab behind me. The three of us can
leave this place together. Go get her now. I can get to the testing ward on that elevator.
Wait for me. Save point please. Please god. If an enemy spawns right here we'll get another
cutscene too. Another one. Is there no save point? Is this the end of the game and if we
fuck up we go all the way back? There's only the testing ward left. This is it I think.
There's no gravity but I can use an air shooter for moving. No problem. One hp.
No save points. 27 full minutes of cutscenes. If we lose. Shredding disc on stream.
This is pretty much what it is. Can you open this case? Get. Grab it. That just gave me so much anxiety.
Thanks. This solves the problem of zero gravity. Wait. Stop. Yep. Where's the save point? There's
no save point. Hatch three has hp. The guide says there is a there is one. If I'm getting
baited into opening up a hatch I'm looking at my own goddamn walkthrough. I don't trust
a soul here. Not in a million years right now. A million. We're talking about a million
years. I don't trust what you guys are saying right now. There is a heal. Hatch five. Hatch five.
Run. Oh you can't run. You can just do you can just do the the uh all right.
I have to make this reference and I have to make this joke. If you haven't seen the last
jedi just delete your computer okay? Because here comes the last jedi reference. Here it
comes. So you're ready? If you haven't seen the last jedi then mute for the next 30 seconds.
Good. You good? What does this remind you of? It's the princess Leia like thing right? With
she flying back. That's the same exact everything. All right you can you're good.
Unmute now. Read my lips. You can unmute. How is that a spoiler? Because if it that's a
major plot device there. Unmute. Yeah you're you're good. I already I gave the ultimate
star wars reference. Well I did. There are two hatches. Hatch two is straight ahead.
Hatch five leads below. Which way should I go? Hatch five. Hatch five okay. I don't think I
can go any further. I'm turning back. Oh a heal capsule. Jerma go to hatch three.
Jerma go to hatch three. Jerma go to hatch three. Jerma go to hatch three.
Jerma go to hatch three. Jerma go to hatch three. Jerma go to hatch three. Jerma go to hatch three.
Which way should I go? Recover. Yes. What's the save point? I did I x out of my
fucking walkthrough. Hatch two. Hatch two okay. The hatch is closed. You have to analyze and
open it i i hold on oh uh uh uh ugh there's a save point in here
jerma go to hatch three this is the laboratory go to hatch three
jerma go to hatch three were they studying how to make the philosopher's
stone here right save point the save point
okay it's right in front of us oh i can finally take a sigh of god
relief ah great canadian fuck club 50 fucking community subs how many
community subs do you have now are you over like five or six
fucking hundred fifty oh my god did that
that's what is with the money the last few days
it's been i don't i don't i don't have any words that's
that's a lot of money god all right so we're going to go to
thank you so much thank you so much for the 50 community subs
sample cases the sample case run okay quickly
okay how much money was 50 and 50 community subs
is is five times 50 uh check glass are you talking about that
that is check sample case if you don't say which case i can't help you
check top right sample case this don't open that it's one of those
monsters don't open that this is evidence of
illegal experimentation all right don't open that
experiment rack one experiment rack one
okay run smash the glass and eat the monster run
quickly okay these look like test systems
everything around this pillar fly check control panel
it's the panel for controlling the robotic arm at least that's what i
think wiggle it around and try to win the teddy bear
wiggle ah control panel it's a panel for controlling an experiment
stop grab control panel it's a panel for
controlling an experiment rack operate control panel the control
panel wrecking it is pointless what else
should i do use control panel using a huge machine
like this is way out of my league okay it's all you
it's all oh it's inoperable set to emergency mode storage boots
the storage boots okay i can't even see any of this shit
activate do what with what check wall panel what should i check
ghost busters one ghost containing machine that's all it took let me see
oh i guess you exchange experiment racks using this
so the storage and extraction experiment rack okay
operate experiment rack experiment rack three
okay run quickly okay it's the same thing
experiment rack two experiment rack two okay
run run run slowly oh that's not what i said
where is my walkthrough look at floating purple object
okay i'll leave no that's not what i wanted you to do
walkthrough is cheating not at this point where did you just know leave
like she's leaving the whole place why are you doing this
no stop don't go through two different places
that's hatch three hatch four turn around turn around
what are you doing stop stop stop stop stop i know you're having a lot of
fun and zero gravity is really interesting
but listen stop what you're doing stop floating around
where are you going hat stop yep hatch tow hatch five
hatch two hatch two hatch hatch two okay one two three months like four
hatches this is why how dare you use a walkthrough
that was at least how many blinks was that i don't know
just admit that you're bad at the game stop
yep experiment experiment gum rack two
experiment rack two okay shoe check shoe huh what are you talking about
that's a shoe up there there's nothing like that here
check purple shoe what are you talking about
look at the shoe there's nothing like that here look above
to see shoe okay i'll leave no stay stop yep
experiment rack two experiment rack two
okay run look above were they using this for animal testing
look above robot arm is it a tool for experiments
i don't really know check purple object is it a tool for experiments i don't
really know look up what should i check
look up at floating object the save point okay stop
stop stop stop yep experiment rack two
experiment rack two run okay quickly okay look top left
what should i check check top left what should i check check up
what should i check what the fuck does the walkthrough say
check up up holy shit you fucking can't be serious
it's a shoe what is this i told you guys didn't know it was a shoe
hey can you analyze this for me how am i supposed to analyze a shoe
leather product past inspection was naomi here
there's something like a tunnel in the back could she be beyond there
i can't get in there unless the gap is widened
what are you doing she's gonna smash your face it's an auto emergent it
can't be directly operated we need to find another way of
lowering this device all right storage boots the storage
boots okay run quickly okay check
what should i okay check other panel check left panel
check left panel check input panel check input panel check control
device experiment rack jettison that's it
if we get rid of the experiment rack i'll be able to enter that corridor
so do it yeah it's okay the system appears to operate even in an emergency
yeah okay let's give it a shot i feel like you're operating the machine to
scream operate to jettison experiment rack
into space the operator must enter the disengagement code number within a
set time frame hello busy mode the experiment rack
insert the shoe in the machine the shoe was just a big key
i get it i read some numbers and you enter them
that's easy and we'll get it done in the jiffy read numbers
entering release code let's see two one oh no it's
three one four what the fuck please proceed let's see
six four and seven seven pound five let's see
three eight uh seven and five and stop saying and why are you saying
and three four and seven and two five star you motherfucker
two five uh star two five four eight five one
we have to get it together slow why do you have to
self-destruct initiated sixty six and yep
six six four 66 and uh six six four get it together
66 and uh yep uh six it's like four numbers
you don't have to stop in the middle you just say the numbers
you look at it if it's six six six four
you don't have to go six uh yep uh six
six um and four have you ever read a sequence of numbers before in your
entire life two uh and uh uh three four two five uh
star and uh and that's it can i just have to start
can i just fucking get it together activate this and like put her into
space let's see seven two and
it's seven one eight five release code please try again
get it together how am i supposed to know
if you say it wrong first seven two no seven uh one but you're just
reading a sequence of numbers see nine five and one that's it
see three eight uh seven
let's see pound star five star and nine pounds what was it
pound star what pound star five and one
pound star and five and one five and nine
pound star five nine pound and start nine and five and nine
pound star five star nine pound star five star nine
there's more let's see three four six uh five eight star
four two is that it oh my see
two five star uh four five star and six one
let's see star star pound star pound pound and star star
it seems to have worked hang on for a second
uh pound pound star five pound star uh yep uh uh two no uh how did you make
it this far it's because of you that's true
that's actually true maybe naomi will be all right safe point
no you think the two of us are becoming a great team safe point
stop we don't get a safe point i don't think
somebody's brain hooked up to a computer i sense you
i feel you who's there alan could it be joe this thing's
alive i think i can communicate with it
using this keyboard please isn't this enough turn off the
machine let me fuck you
of all the times to do it i try to queue it up
god i tried to skip the cutscenes and work as we can scientists have
experienced i'm sorry it was fun i was happening i couldn't
find a way to get out turn off the machine i beg you
you what do you want would have been a great a joke i know
i tried no i'm just a waitress i'm jsl i sensed some sort of crisis in
the hotel the stone this station yes i see
i was a fool i thought that the stone would bring happiness to the world
may it had done for our everywhere the evils of jealousy and greed have
corrupted and this is the world that they would produce
more of the stones for beg you this machine all right who is this
supposed to be thank you this is me there is one last
thing i wish you could do yes in japan there is a woman named
rio hona i want you to find her and tell her
her mother still lives tell her to find her the swiss union bank
enough money there so she can have a good life
will you do this for me it's i was gonna scream dad in the mic no
i beg you to do this it's
thank you controls organism sustenance system
it is absolutely forbidden to turn off this device whatever the situation
may be
good wait does that does that destroy the whole
complex attention attention
i had somebody's urges to sneeze lately i don't know why
i couldn't sneeze before and now actually just they're just coming out
of me for a second oh no
get out fly get out fly fly fly the station's falling to earth
what should we do um escape the hatch is open save point okay
i'll come get you right now save point
save point no no give no god damn it
you you're please
yes
so this is naomi
fucking electric hands stop stop my health is dropping stop say her
name say her name sexy pose
sexy pose
it worked naomi
i just did a sexy pose
i did i can't hear
naomi listen
that was it did i just beat the game operator
no too late cursed they all died the man i couldn't
save anyone itchy nose get everything
i'm gonna sneeze now it'll be because of me this time i'm gonna mute and get
off the fucking camera what did you just say tell me
everything's all my fault we're gonna get out of here
you and me we're gonna get out of this you really believe
yes yes i do yes yes i believe that
yes yes i do yes yes yes i think we can get out
yes yes we can get out of here yes yes i believe that
that is the truth i believe that i'm telling you the truth
i'm we're gonna get out of here tell me the truth we will get out of here
tell me the truth we're going to get out of here
tell me the truth everything it's all my fault no it's not your fault
there's no way it wouldn't let me say yes we're gonna get out of here
save you happen you save me nope nope i'm out of here
will you believe me i am out of here thank you
i don't know if you realize this maybe you already know
these monsters some are actually people who've mutated
but not naomi she lived and died a beautiful woman
uh welcome to the we did it joe power hold it don't try anything you'll
regret later you didn't hear me coming down the
hall because i floated you like to know what you've done
you and the operator you killed the girl that you were
searching for
oh wait he's got it he's got the nerve ball he's gonna crush it and he's
gonna turn into the final boss wasn't enough i hope he eats it
always in search of exactly what play it play it please play the other
audio clip you used her for some twisted experiment
you need to kill anyone this is by the way everyone's saying what's wrong with
the cameraman this is me i'm the cameraman unaware of the
threat she posed to those around her i don't know where this camera is
supposed to be in this space he's been your operator correct
he's been poisoned by the toxin from a mutated caterpillar
he'll surely die i'm the one who locked him in the monitor room
well it's too late to save so it was you who altered the station's orbit
that's correct rio howner still find it puzzling
i was certain i'd shot you in the what what just happened
did he not the the blowback from the
shotgun or did the disc protect me that's got shot point blank with a
shotgun such a brilliant man i'm amazed at how stupid you are
joseph craft my german birth name translates to joe
powers in english well i'd better be off with the philosopher's stone
craft
i think you got him where do you get the gun
wait hold on how what you didn't see her
pulling the gun up you were too busy talking about how your english
translated craft name is already translated into english
you didn't miss many years ago you shot me through the heart
and i really did die my father took the stone pressed it into my wound
it revived me and i escaped didn't fucking revive your
brain it's been keeping me alive ever since
that's why what you have there is only it's a fake
so she is a philosopher's stone at this point i'm gonna be like lady
you saw it i'm not i don't want i don't want to cease communication
nothing i could do i swear it you die i promise
using the real stone i can keep you alive and get you to a hospital that
guy's dead my english name craft
translated it to powers like what the fuck was that
i have control again hatch three hatch three is a save okay
save for the love of fuck i know if hopefully is there a
save point the save point run okay we did it quickly okay no save run you
gotta be kidding me i would never in a million years do
something like that is this the streamer that was supposed
to die today i i protected myself i got some duct tape
got some padding i was good to go all right
where do i go now hatch three no three
okay all right exit okay i'll leave the speed run is no safe
so we got hatch six can i talk yet i i this is another
scenario where i'm gonna get hit one time and die
but what this is is there anything else to do
hatch six hatch six run okay quickly okay how's las vegas it's great vegas
is great place did you finish the star wars
spoiler yet yeah you could you could unmute you're good
i gotta pee i'm just gonna pee now i'll be right back
i'm just gonna go pee all right let's finish this thing
all right that was a long pee yeah i've been holding it
i had to pee since we first got to that spot
so you know since we first got to the spot from last night i've had to go
i've got to go to the bathroom run you mean go faster don't expect
the impossible i did i save it i did right yeah
uh there it's full of stones isn't it
it can't be yeah did i say i did right
this can't be it's all phony philosopher stones
this station will crash on a populated earth do
don't breathe the philosopher stone dust don't breathe this
upward what am i doing the station should have a self-destruct system
we'll blow up the station and these stones before they can be used on earth
okay wait for me i'll be right there credits
there's more to do this is it the monitor room there's no mistake
i finally made it am i in there you're inside of here
oh this is me this is big reveal am i the final boss
can you see me sure can yep yeah it's okay it doesn't matter if you
can't see me on camera you'll see me soon enough is it all
right if i come in i don't like the way that she's talking
here what's the matter operator are you also feeling nervous
my pulse is racing this is like when the vampire comes to your front door
and pretends to be like a door to door vacuum salesman i'm coming
hey who's this why so surprised rio was it not you who taught me that if
we die near the stone it'll bring us back to life
joe craft is back realized it yet don't you get it you became a
monster long ago you liar believe me
i will save you
become dust the only thing that's becoming dust
is you uh-oh he's they're all gonna get attached to him he's gonna turn
into a giant alien
i've got an idea okay you've got an idea just let's get out of it let's go on an
escape pod press the button and blow the place up
thank god i saved it because this is another one of those unbearable
full cutscenes i can't skip this is gonna this is not even gonna be
just this is the very end of the game there's gonna be
one little gimmick that i gotta do to take out the monster and then we
leave that's it
grab operator listen to me turn the engine's power on full
fry that monster once and for all engines power on full
this is it our last stand head wink time to settle things all right
thrusters full wasn't i supposed to get up to
always done need to give me instructions it's okay don't worry so i
don't get to get out i'll destroy that thing soon then go get you
all right okay this is getting bigger this motherfucker just leveled up
again twice again all right i think we have to
for the health bars full power use the left thrusters right left
left right left down left up right i need the
i can't control the other one right down up left left left thruster right
down right up left left left up how do i use
the left thruster are you serious right right down
up left down left up up oh
up right up right right right what right left
down left left left left dude okay the reason why
this is horrendous is because i have to use
left stick to move mine i have to hold
trot hold circle tell her a command and then let go of circle every time
left down right up left down right up left
down left double beam him right down right up
left left down left up up right left
left left left you fucking idiot left down
up left right right up down left left right
right down up left left right left left
left how do you fuck that up how do you get that wrong
low right down up left left where's the damage what right
down up left left down right up left
down down right up left left right down
left up right left left right left down
right up up down right what a fucking mess
what a fucking mess of an encounter so you got these two thrusters which
by the way block the whole screen so when he spawns the stupid fucking
underseen mines half of them you can't even see where
they are oh by the way oh i'm gonna complain about
that what a piece of fucking crap can't wait to watch the four and a half
full minutes of cutscenes exit okay i'll leave hatch six hatch six
okay left left left left up up left left left right
go can't be hard the fuck up here fast
quickly okay doesn't do anything you just have to float
it does it does it to float to the fucking cutscenes these better be
skippable you're gonna watch me fucking have a
real meltdown thank fucking god this is it the monitor room
there's no mistake i finally made it you are inside of here
hi can you see me yes we can finally meet yes yeah just keep
talking is it all right if i come in just play the cutscene
huh what i couldn't quite catch that oh operator are you also feeling
nervous i'm gonna get a second this pops up
even though i don't have a heart watch this
okay i'm coming here we go i'm so fucking glad you can skip that shit
put them to the end of the game to figure it out all right
i'm gonna get it this time because now i didn't even know i could
control it the whole game you can't control i'm not gonna talk
left right bottom right top left let's go get rid of the barrier
bottom right top left left up right up down
up up oh my fucking god i hate this game
left up left up up up up i what the fuck is going on
up up left what the fuck are you doing top right
upright left i can't even fucking believe it
left down right right she doesn't understand the word right now
i'm watching a fucking youtube video at the end of this game this is
dumb this is d-u-m-b dumb lower right right right
right down adjust the mic there is no adjusting the mic
it doesn't exist it's not a feature there's no feature to adjust the mic
there's not a you can check the mic and she goes i can hear you
i can hear you just fine we did it last night
i gotta i have to start over piece of fucking crap
this is the last encounter of the game why did i reset it because
last time i reset it we could remember weren't you just sitting on the ground
last night and wouldn't listen to anything
your mic's not on my i'm it hasn't moved
no don't do a new game i tried to that made some noise i'm not gonna
have a corrupted save file i mean i did the thing you're never
supposed to do we'll just turn off the we're fine
move the mic away from your butt it this is where it's been the whole time
the game says keep it very very close it's obviously not not a problem
because when i was saying left it would go left
microphone check your voice that's coming over the microphone
your voice is easy to distinguish i like your voice
those of you that are wondering that's the that's the microphone
calibration in the game it's just can i hear you
yes or no that's it mic works leave leave hallway okay i'll leave
and i gotta watch her float around jerma's hair looks like candy floss
band fast yep speed up okay it's because i had a helmet on
if i can't get her to move in the directions that i say
at at least a 50 percentile 60 percentile
i'm putting a video of the end of the game on the screen you
wouldn't i i wouldn't but i would today this is it the monitor room the foam on
the wall is doing something i finally made it you're inside of
here you keep trying to fast forward the
stream me too i i'm in control of it hi can you see me
yes we can finally meet is it all right if i come in
sure come in all right i wow my pulse is pounding even though i don't have a
heart hey hey all right i'm ready i'm ready to
put the nail in the coffin that is this game
let's go get it use the light i'm like i'm like
blinking too much here down up right
left
right down lower right upper right upper right left
right down right right down left
up up down
upper right left down left right right right left right left
up lower right left up right down sorry right left
here we go for right the fuck out of here get out of here
it's on a ds somebody's playing the ds finally we meet
what do i look like she's coming in for a hug what do i do what do i do do i do
the hug or do i just like put up my hand and shake the hand
for bananas thanks for 10 community subs fort bernandes
thank you there's only the two of us left now thank you so much
that cursed stone will blow it up with the station
and let me borrow your seat for a moment awesome sauce with 50 bucks 5000
bits it was here the whole time mr streamer you missed a spot upper
left please thank you for your 50 dollars awesome
sauce thank you so much operator escape i'm
initiating the self-destruct sequence
please evacuate from this time is that it
no this
wait operator can you take a look at this
what's wrong the escape hatch won't open there's a high security lock on
the escape hatch the shuttle cannot be launched
tutorial escape hatch i'm not doing this
come on open password my frigid heart the only thing that melts it is just
your just your fuck uh dick balls please
shit it's a swear everybody's password is this where
please tell me the password for the escape hatch
frigid heart the only thing that melts it is just your kiss
that's so sweet i'm not typing in that fe word
love my frigid heart the only thing that melts it is
just your trust that's a good word
operator take a closer look it's five letters
the missing word is four letters long love
my frigid heart the only thing that melts it is
just your life that's a good word if i failed this
love my frigid heart the only thing that melts it is
just your life oh my god if this actually ruins the cut scene
i'm not gonna say it love my frigid heart the only just your life
that's so sweet i'm trying the same password
over and over again at what point fire my frigid heart the only thing that
melts it is just your fire how do you get that
not love
that's not it say feet i'm not gonna all right
yes my frigid i didn't say anything that
melts it is just your kiss that's so sweet
i didn't say anything life my frigid heart the only thing that
melts it is just your life that's a good word
i was thinking it was gonna be love why did i say life because i keep
i keep saying love and she says life i'm thinking of trying to turn it
around on her love my frigid heart just your passion
that's a good word dove my frigid heart the only thing that
melts it is just your eyes that's so sweet
no that's not it of my frigid heart the only thing that
melts it is just your life that's a good word
that's not it love my frigid heart the only thing that
melts it is just your memory that's a good word
closer look the input space the missing word is four letters long
feet my frigid heart the only just your sex
operator take a closer look the input space
the missing word is four letters loaf loaf
my frigid heart the only thing that melts it is
just your life we're never gonna be able to beat this
no that's not it say lobe lobe my frigid heart the only thing that
melts it is just your life that's a good word
no that's not it l o v e my frigid heart the only thing that
melts it is just your pity uh sure no that's not it
what do we do here love my frigid heart the only thing that
melts it is just your life that's a good word i'm
gonna scream it as loud as i can my frigid heart the only thing that
melts it is just your passion that's a good word
oh my fucking god operator take a closer look
the input space the missing word is four letters long
self my frigid heart the only thing that melts it is
just your soul that's a good word no operator that's not it
wait everybody hold on shout out what's wrong just say what you think
no say it go oh my god damn it the only thing that melts it is
just your words that was a that was a really nice i need to pronounce the how
to pronounce love the missing word is four letters long
how to pronounce this my frigid heart the only thing that
melts it is just your sex huh operator take a closer look
the input space the missing word is four letters long
american accent love portuguese accent my frigid heart the only thing that
melts it is just your trust that's a good word
why did she listen to that one and not any of the other ones
the input space oh my god to pronounce this
accent my frigid heart the only thing that melts it is
just your passion that's a good word writer take a closer look
the input space the missing word is four letters long
here we go how to pronounce this american accent
my frigid heart the only thing that melts it is
just your love what's wrong with my voice
love love love you gotta be kidding me that's it come on hurry we have to
escape boston accent too strong bullshit love love i've been doing it
game done completed i went beat the game
stop saying the light good luck oh no is that me
this ending is just a white screen is that me
are we gonna get a face reveal get a hand reveal
let's get on it's okay i'll get a sound time
live inside me now
we made it back to earth we go and i'll pronounce you man and wife
right listen operator can i say one last thing
thank you no we never you know i was thinking we don't show the face
because it could be anyone leave it up to the viewer
and the moviegoer to dissect and figure out who that could actually be
is it them or was it enough was it somebody else
entirely different because obviously it's not you
because it's not from a first person perspective
but who who is that mysterious figure it wasn't us
we're in space right now floating around that was not even the operator
that was some random fucking guy that just happened to still be alive as a
guest in the hotel i was i'm still the perspective we're
floating around in space we die there it is all right final thoughts
on lifeline bad awful not good why did i stream
that for fucking like 16 straight hours almost
worst thing i've ever done in my life worst thing i've ever done in my adult
life and it was a very fun experience very
good game now all jokes aside it was really cool
really fun uh except for the poor portions with it you didn't really
listen to you and how broken sometimes it was and
the unskippable cutscenes i'm not gonna give it a letter grade
but i'm gonna tell you right now if you have a playstation 2
make sure you have the one or two specific headsets that will even work
with the game because you can't just plug in anything
it has to be a very specific headset who's gonna buy this
i'm acting like this is a game that's on steam right now you can't just go
get this that was a fun experience that was a
good that was a fun no no no hold on let's rephrase that that was a
good stream that was a fun super stream was it 12 13 14
about like 15 hours or so in the last 24 hours
that look at like sometimes we play these fucked up weird games
this stream doesn't happen unless this game exists it was great
so um the purpose of today's stream last night because we went so late
into the morning if you weren't around yesterday i
streamed until like three or four a.m pacific
so i didn't get a whole lot of sleep and obviously i wanted to get up
and do the irl stream so what we're gonna do and i
want to finish this game obviously too because
i just kept it going from yesterday or this this morning
end of the stream yeah so last night there was a ton of bits
and there was a lot of messages and i didn't do any of them because the
stream was so late into the morning that what we're gonna do right now
we're gonna just kind of relax we're gonna
just hang out gonna go over the bits from yesterday
and do the obviously the bits from today
and just chill for a little while and then the stream will end
and on top of that the next time you'll see me what's today today is
today's the 23rd wednesday you will see me again
on friday and saturday and friday and saturday
we have a lot of random things we can do there's tons of shit to do
that could be finally the day of dreamcast because i have all the games
i have all the stuff or maybe i don't know it really depends
on what i feel like doing so you'll see me again on friday if
you're taking off thank you for if you were here
yesterday too thank you for joining me on this um weird schedule here
stream part one yesterday into today stream part two
today also so have a good rest of your night i'll see you guys on
friday and let's do the bits and i'm gonna
just kind of i'm gonna just like hang out here
oh i gotta save the game dragon's dog but
that's also definitely something to do i'm probably gonna go friday saturday
sunday this weekend just because i've been
kind of all over the place with streams i missed i pushed a stream
back because i wasn't feeling that great last week so
i don't see why i wouldn't be able to do it unless something else comes
up which i don't think it will open the safe there's an easter egg
so let's go through the bits from today actually no no no no no no
that's probably not a good idea because uh some might trickle in over
the land next little while complete data i need to open that
bits website it's the germa mustard one
i have that in my favorites don't i the hell is it why do i not have it
in 16th century europe there lived a physician
let's go so what's what's easter egg for start
what's easter egg come in please oh she's in a
is this different costume new costume finally my efforts pay off
one glove is the con link still live operator can you say something
what's with the casual attitude sexy pose
you don't sound like the regular guy you don't sound like the regular guy
listen will you please undo the lock uh so we saw that looks good let me
just um go and queue in this up engage the lock on this door so this
is where are we at here if you operate the door panel it will open
the door operate all right here let her out let
her out so we got let me do
maximum time lock me up in there for over an hour
jeez i didn't know what was gonna happen
so what's your story this is the wrong timeline are you trapped inside that
monitor room so we share the same dilemma and now
sexy pose don't worry i'll try it i will try
okay so i have the bits from yesterday
it's not in here it's not i'm not saying that show that
we already know what that is it's just bullshit
please disengage the smock all right we're not even it doesn't even matter
we're just gonna do the bits while we hang out here this is from yesterday
by the way so we're gonna go through them in a
fairly timely manner but i want to make sure i cover most of them
uh thank you peter p327 are for the 25 dollars yesterday
fat bussion thanks for the one dollar sad vega thanks for the one
dollar it was the best of times it was the
worst of times it was the age of wisdom the age of foolishness
it was the epoch of belief it was the epoch of imperability it was the season
of light season of darkness it was the spring of
hope this is just a whole paragraph look i'm in a bit of a hurry just wait
there to be rescued thank you bake me home for the one
dollar tingy for the one dollar no message
uh thank you itras gara for the one dollar
end of the screamer voice did this happen in the other game
i don't remember this happening oh it did happen right
uh me and machines thanks for the one dollar mr kassadin thanks for the one
dollar can i have your gamer v portable when
you die no that's coming with bears i'm gonna get
buried right eye middle eye left eye right eye middle eye left eye left eye
left eye dodge left i can't play this right now
i can't play this and i can't talk game and read bits it's just not
gonna happen so here's what we're gonna do i'm just
gonna go on the camera like this get this thing off go over
there okay god that helmet really look at look
what that helmet did to me it just fucked me up so bad okay
i'm just like weird guy in the middle of the screen but that's okay
so let's go back to what we were doing shave
i shaved like two days ago i shaved like every three or four days
uh mr kassadin thanks for the one dollar divas
thank you divas for the two dollars am clockwork thanks for five dollars
agent pigeon thanks for one dollar sorry i'm not richer but i just want to say
thank you for being there for me without knowing it also sorry about
your death tomorrow today today is tomorrow today's tomorrow
and i'm just fine i'm still here uh the only guy ever
thanks for the one dollar germa a friend i would greatly appreciate if you
could treat chat to your humorous reading
of this post from your subreddit i was working at a mcdonald's
drive-through in las vegas i just like stretched my whatever uh i
was working the night shift at mcdonald's when the first customer in
hours pulled up to the window as my headphones sputtered to life
hey idiot see i've been dealing with anxiety issues for a while mainly
because i'm fresh out of college and i'm stuck working the graveyard at a
fast food joint so this actually hit me pretty hard this
didn't happen but alas the customer is always right so i had to power
through it welcome to mcdonald's what can i get
you i said with corporate forced joy yeah can i get a
whopper dummy i was taken aback not just by his
rudeness but by the slurring of words i can tell that he was either
intoxicated or at a new new eastern new england
accent excuse me sir but we don't have those
here but can i interest you in a big mac
shut up doofus say something funny already clown at this point there
were tears streaming down my cheeks from the barrage of insults
and it felt worse when i heard the laughing and another man in the car
as well as a synthesized noise coming from some sort of instrument
i couldn't handle it anymore in my current state being i just got it a
it's the yeah this this is like a whopper fucking chat is the
this is a chat thing why are you turning this on me so i had just
missed my mother's funeral so i snapped
hey i've had enough of this can you just go asshole
as a response to this i heard boy boisterous laughter coming from the
two men and the sounds of my manager coming down
the hall to talk to me he shoved me and took my headset
and told me to go to the second window and get ready to give them their order
i apologized for him may i take your order after a minute or two
and an order appeared on the screen two small coffees
two ten piece chicken wings four limited edition cheeto sauces
i prepared their order and waited in the window and looked down through the
the drive to take a look at their car what i saw was a car smaller than
a volkswagen beetle painted white with red blue green and yellow
spots all over it in the words german 985 emblazoned in fluorescent purple
across the hood swerving down the road hitting the
wall multiple times in a 10-foot journey to the window
how long is this this is like a whole story the one driving
appeared to be an older man and was flushed red
hold i didn't do this this is not this is a this is a
this is a copie pasta this is a copy posto
hey loser the short man slurred as the passenger giggled and played the
instrument the driver elbowed him and said hey
was that a good one cheeto a real lol moment huh
and the automaton played some high notes seemingly meant to signify a
chortle he finally actually looked at me and
saw my distraught state and shrieked with laughter
at this point i couldn't look at them and i turned away sobbing holding
out the drink tray with their coffee and the brown paper sack
containing their cheetos and chicken
the older looking man had to jump out of his seat to grab and snatch the goods
from my tear stained hands i was still for a i was still for a
while until i heard their car finally drive off
and when i finally looked forward once more i could make out a small
card left on the counter in front of me
through my tear clouded vision i took the slip of paper and
locked myself in the bathroom to cry and about an hour the emotion had
passed and my sight was clear again so i
looked at the card subscribe to germa 985 on twitch
i i didn't do this i didn't make this but if you want to read i did not make
this i did not do that that was a somebody
made a reference to the stream from a couple days ago
where i was talking about how chat was ordering me to do things and
calling me names so that's where that came from i
didn't do any of that i would never do something like that
dummy but thank you the only guy i think you plastic glue for the one
dollar thank you ace jealous for the one the ten dollars actually from last
night i've been watching your videos for over
eight years thanks for all the great times i know
you don't usually watch videos on stream
but find time to watch this one find time to watch
this one let's see uh i think did we watch this one
i think we watched the this is like the reunion german star reunion
right i think we already i think we watched this already
no it's not it's there's no gnome here there you go
yeah we we it is very touching um i'm pretty sure we we watched that uh
while ago but thank you for it nonetheless check it out
15 minutes until death no no that was eastern time we already did it
if it's a gnome i unsaid it's not a gnome i don't want to be mean and
maybe it's just some weird lighting but you look like a corpse right now
uh it's i think it's yeah here it's the what it's the it's
i don't understand why that would be i feel fucking fine
i'm gonna change this you look like a corpse
i don't i don't understand somebody's linked a clip
i don't know what it is should i click this am i gonna get in trouble if i
click this yeah it was it's the white balance here
what the fuck is going on um okay the webcam the webcam is broken
why did that happen what i clicked on white balance
and the thing crap fucking watch tech man here comes a
joke don't there ain't there's no joke i don't have a joke i actually have to
like unplug the webcam and plug it back in
see if that fixes it i'm gonna change this to
just hanging out for a little bit and put it on just chatting right
because that's what we're doing all right can this work please
add camera there it is what the fuck is wrong with this thing
yeah i have no idea what's going on this this thing sucks
uh it made the resolution even worse some
insane way i couldn't tell you why this is happening
zoom in on your ear why now i'm desynced
yeah fucking computer has been i should be that
we should be good at least we should be i've been wrong before
fixed good and why is the resolution like
an 800 by 600 where's the 16 by 9
don't ever buy a computer just like fucking read a book
seriously just read a book just read a book
uh but anyways thank you to novi333 for the
three dollars and 33 cents since you blatantly ignored my bits last
dream i'll say it again you must play seaman for the dreamcast
already bought it it's already here so don't worry you will see it very
soon uh i had i did purchase seaman
and the mic talked about how expensive it was it was an incredibly
stupidly expensive piece of product and uh it it's uh it's here
dreamcast is back there all the game actually the games are downstairs look
at this fucking hair worst here fucking 2020
but thank you nonetheless really appreciate it it's fake
it's not fake it's not fake but thank you novi thank you demphay for
the one dollar hey germa my boyfriend is a big fan but i wanted
to let you know that every time i watch your streams videos i have the
strong urge to vomit thanks for the one dollar uh thank you
sexy cowleg for the four dollars uh demphay for the four dollars again
i actually puked to your green screen stream i got pretty bad motion sickness
and i was drunk just thought you i just thought you'd know
you didn't puke on the green screen stream you did not
why would you how would you get motion sickness on a there was no
first person stuff i did i did you didn't puke
nobody puked none of you puked can guarantee that
but thank you for the four dollars thank you to demonic cucumber for the one
dollar it's a clip let's go ahead and click
it and see what it is if it's a snort i'm turning the stream off
i'm reaching for the fucking coconut that's up there i'm not reaching for
the banana what i don't get it what happened
they said germa furry gave the grossie thanks for the four dollars
uh not a lot but i hope to join streams as often as i used to man good
to see you still good to see you still are community-based
i love it yeah why not why not of course i'd be community-based it's the whole
reason why the stream exists so thank you thanks for being in the
community thank you gave to grossie for turning into
glue man all those years ago and thanks for the four dollars
uh certainly not tom thank you for the ten dollars certainly not tom germa
i had a dream that you were a teacher
and tried to give me detention but then the rest of the class bullied you
and made fun of the things you said until you stopped and i think that
was a metaphor for chat in my dream okay good speed by uh other than that
you're an incredible streamer and i wanted to show my support
well um chat can be a little wild sometimes
but 99.9 percent of the time they're great but there's a 0.01 percent
of the time but they're very very mean to me
and it makes me say the heck it's definitely more than
0.01 percent it's like 40 now i'm kidding somebody in chat wrote that and
i was just making it you guys are amazing don't worry
thank you uh for the funny dream that seems like a fucked up dream
we suck no you don't don't say that you don't hey pin thanks for the one
dollar fucking go to the wicked room dude you're making
fun of my boston accent i don't even have listen
this is not a boston accent this is a
i just got a regular accent there's no boston here
hey ydna thanks for the ten dollars ten dollars from ydna hey german we want
you for two plus years just want to say that you're literally my favorite
content creator ever thank you for all that you do
thank you that's it means a lot thank you so much
thank you thank you thank you thank you thank you um
floored by the amount of money and the amount of support people give
this channel there's not much else i can say besides
thank you so fucking much that's fucking incredible that's
incredible that does not i can't i have trouble
with this because i i can't believe it sometimes
thank you all of you uh thank you effect tater thank you effect tater for
the five dollars according to your bio inc redemption
stream you're set to die tomorrow which is
today which also is me and my partner's anniversary
can our present be that you don't die i need editing jobs to pay for
food here i am still here nothing even happened
that's fine uh thank you chess master for the one
dollar friendly reminder that you're due to die tomorrow
a lot of people harping on that fact i don't even know where that came from
some video game or something thank you uh drummage door for the
one dollar thanks for introducing me to vis for cleanup detail
i've almost done all the levels of over 95 completion
what a simple but fun game are you going to stream it more greetings from
finland ps try to pronounce i don't know i don't know i don't do
pronunciations i don't know i could be saying
anything but thank you so much and yeah viscera is
awesome viscera is a really really really
really fun game really really interesting
really really chill and of course i would love to play it again next
time i think i want to bring a troop in there i want to bring some
friends in there and try to cause uh cause some fun
you know it's a great game uh smelly boy thanks to the one dollar creepy
pasta contest when um that's not a bad idea
creepy pasta contest is like some of you guys are really really creative
judging by half the shit that was even on this stream at any given
moment anything you guys say half the
shit you guys say half the shit you do it's like
there's a lot of fucking talented fun interesting people here that could
probably come up with some really great stuff
and bugleberry reads them that's true 742 pacific 743 is it's coming up
it's not gonna matter though because it was eastern so don't worry but we'll
see maybe it's an interesting idea alec four
by four thanks for the one dollar hey germa
i'm 15 have 1500 bucks so far from working at my job is a gaming
desktop a good investment well that depends on what you mean by
that uh you don't have to spend 1500
dollars to get a gaming pc a gaming pc does not have to cost that
much fun you could get something that's very
capable 743 oh no
happy new year uh you don't need a gamer pc
you just need a decent video card a good amount of ram and a good like a
decent cpu you don't have to have top of the line stuff
to play games you can probably get a decent gaming computer for like
somewhere in between like five to seven hundred bucks
you could you could do it somewhere under a thousand i think is you could
actually absolutely make it happen and don't buy expensive shit just
because it's expensive some of the stuff that you can buy is
oh yeah but it's 10 faster than the
than the latest and greatest and it's two grand you don't that doesn't
matter 700 700 is really all you need somebody
said yeah that's really all you need unless you really are planning on
doing something that requires a ton of power
like if you're doing a lot of computations
heavy editing heavy photo manipulation heavy video manipulation then of course
you need a computer that can do it but if you're just playing pc games
and you don't care about playing at the
ultra ultra ultra settings and you don't care about being on like just
high and medium then you're fine you don't need to yeah like witcher
three modded 4k textures with two c gpus and sli it's it's it's not
necessary to just kind of play a game there are
a shitload of people that are in the discord that are around that
would probably love to talk to you about it so good luck
and good luck on your uh on your job too
thanks a lot aleph freudian weapon thanks for the one dollar you need to
use your car salesman voice sometimes i do bream bin thanks for
the ten dollars don't be mean to her she's trying her best to pick up
the half eaten meal no she's she was just i could i could i could not even
tolerate half the stuff that happened when when she was
doing things no i'm sorry when it got to the point where she was reading
numbers in the worst possible way to read a
sequence of numbers it's just like come on
what am i supposed to do there but thank you so much bream bin for the
ten dollars c4g thanks for the one dollar shito
shito be like like what be like i just feel i think i just i think i feel
like i just got a note uh thank you timmy tim tan for the one
dollar the girl in this game talks like one of these videos
traffic rules sarah you can't park here it's a bus stop
oh we'll be back in a few minutes it's okay oh no it isn't
you'll get a parking ticket if you leave it here no i won't it's half
past five all the traffic wardens have gone home
sarah yes is this your car ma'am
traffic rules sarah you can't park here it's a bus stop
oh we'll be back in a few minutes it's okay oh no it isn't
you'll get a parking ticket if you leave it here no i won't it's half
past five all the traffic wardens have gone home
sarah yes is this your car ma'am left right left right left right
right getting hungry hungry hungry panda say i love you
autoplay uh played uh ancient for uh animal vines but thank you for that
timmy tim tan thank you hack it fast for the one dollar thank
you the wombat from hell for the one dollar
the 700 000 game stream give me an idea you should have chat play
i spy spooky mansion with the clicking extension
that game is actually good unlike those crappy stolen asset ones from
the stream we talked about that doing a hidden
object chat plays hidden object game that'd be pretty fun i definitely want to
do it i'll look into it you know in quotes
that hair just got in my eye oh yeah i'm reading fits
hey thank you hall of one zombie for the one dollar donate dollar thank you
techno toast thanks to the one dollar germa i love this meta stream
you've got here where you get mad and shout commands at someone on screen
great cosplay of chat rc martinez thanks for the one dollar
can i get uh hi hey yeah in chat can you
and then this is this is where bro luck gave
like the 700 trillion fucking dollars just seeing all these
red symbols here red red red red red and
rounded it up to a thousand jesus uh carlos the clam also last night gave
24 i think we grabbed it but they said the game
can be beaten in under three hours which there's no wasp in the room
that's ridiculous to me that somebody could even let this
you must have to you must phonetically figure out exact
mumbles to get the the game to do what you want it to do
hack it fast thanks for three bucks no message thank you mostly lost
for the one dollar today we learned bribing germa to say something works
but it's because he's afraid of getting more money
from you and feels bad we yeah we talked about it last night robbie
thanks for the one dollar thank you hack it fast again for the
two bucks eat the whole ass or whatever thank you for the two bucks
uh mostly lost thank you for 30 dollars
don't make me do it 30 bucks for mostly lost
thank you hey pin thanks for the one dollar just pretend there is a few
more zeros on these bits pin thanks for the fucking 10,000 bits
dude are you are you fucking kidding me
it's a lot of money was that good did i get the job
hey grill master x barbecue that's not right that's grill master bbx
bb it's grill max grill master bbqx uh pro tip of the day next time
you're looking for a tasty spin on the classic cheeseburger
try grilling your beef with the skin still on it adds a unique
furry texture that can spice up don't do that don't eat don't eat like
that don't do that that's a very bad idea don't ever do
that eat officially licensed nintendo brand
you know it doesn't have the nintendo seal on it
don't eat it uh pizza bot thanks for the 10 bucks
bit stream thank you pizza bot thank you so much for the 10 dollars
uh ck luck thanks for the five dollars five bucks towards the clown card joke
eventually at some point before i stop
streaming and doing anything to do with online stuff
i'm going to have a clown card it's gonna happen it will happen eventually
i promise uh thank you the unraveling for the two bucks
mouth mouth uh thank you dave pita squared peter pito
and they said uh vr isca made me do this
give a dollar thank you uh thank you
to senho senho for the one dollar superintendent chalmers thanks for the
one dollar hello mr jeremy can you please do a microsoft sam
impression and then say panther in the same voice
you can't do a microsoft sam impression that's
how you just uh no you can't it's a it's a computer you can't do a
computer voice there's no computer voices that can be
done uh thank you dr epic frag for the five dollars
here's some for the earthworm jim's suit fund
hawkeye of mine thanks for ten dollars let's give germ a mscrooge mcduck
swimming pool dr epic frag again for the one dollar
what's where's the pokemon soccer reveal
uh it space got space
lost space in space uh t h e space uh ma
il space period that is your microsoft sam voice
right there thank you future gamer thanks for the one dollar if you do
get a vibe i recommend playing payday 2 vr jet island or fallout 4 if it still
comes with the vibe google earth vr and waltz of the wizard
i actually am once they put out the new one
is what i'm gonna do it once i put out the new one once i put i have
nothing to do with vibes development once they put out the new one i'll
buy it because then the other ones would
probably be a little cheaper because the new one will come out and
you don't know what happens with the fucking iphone so i'm sure it'll
happen uh thank you to bro luck for the one
dollar not a thousand no this this is on top of the
thousand let me explain myself i only was
actually planning on donating like two hundred dollars your stubbornness
led me down that expensive road i recently picked up a lot of hours
at work and i'll be fine without the money
enjoy my stubbornness you wanted me to say that i was bad at the game
only 200 only 200 that's so much fucking money thank you
thank you for the fucking two only 200 bucks
first of all yeah that's what what are you talking about that's a huge amount
of money that's 200 fucking dollars that you
gave me and then he turned it into a thousand
god damn it i'm gonna fucking cut it uh bro luck
fucking thank you thank you thank you thank you thank you thank you thank
you uh we have broccoli bert adala hey
germa you're one of my favorite people i know five dollars is in law but it's
all i got thank you uh vivian thank you vivian for
the ten dollars germa say trans rights thanks germ we love you and shito and
love catching the streams and we can sorry to hear you dying so soon but
it happens to the best of us yeah well i'm still here i'm still
here i'm still good end of the life voice
it's star wait star is here i can't believe germ is dead
is it what is this something i'm not picking up on here what am i missing
here i just heard a door close some there's
people that live here dr phil germa is in the closet there
i'm dr phil's not here all right well regardless whatever thank you for the
ten dollars uh i really appreciate the ten bucks
and i'm still here i did not die i'm good to go
i am good to go for the rest of my life and i'll be able to drink
this is he this is actually really comically huge
this is almost embarrassing to have this near me but thank you thank you
broccoli bert for the one dollar germa you one of my favorite people
got you a bar but you got another dollar here
i always wanted to donate but never had the money you're the best you've
honestly given gotten me through some tough shit
thank you happy to do so thank you so much broccoli bird
much love to you for real large mug or it's not an
look now this one is oversized too they're both oversized okay
that one's like a three this is a four oh yeah yeah that's a that's like a
triple if this hair goes in my eye again i'm
going to eat it on stream i'm going to fucking pull it out i'm going to
consume it okay it almost happened again hey hack it
fast thanks for the two dollars uh bum stick a bum bum thank you
colonel crackers for the dollar hey germa are you going to make the
green screen stream a yearly stream it was an amazing stream probably not
i probably would want to do it once or twice not that much
because i feel like it loses its magic if you do it too many times
that's why a lot of people say oh why don't you do a do a germa rumble
event like every once a month or something
loses its flavor and it gives enough time to have
obviously more characters and more stuff and more references it's it's
better to space it out much further but
once a year i would really have to get in front
of the camera more than once because i'm not going to just put up
the same footage where hey yeah remember that footage i recorded
i'd want to get in front of the screen and do a lot more to give you
more to use so not with that footage no but there
will be another night that we watch i really have to get on top of that
because i want it to happen soon but uh how where are we okay we are
almost at the end of yesterday and then we'll just power right in
to today do a germa rumple every stream uh thank you to bet three
for the five dollars thank you so much for the videos and streams germa
you've helped so many people along the way with your humor and optimism
also thank you for the constant support of your lgbt fans
yeah you got you guys you guys know where i always stand
on these things you know i mean you know
you do whatever you want to do i can't tell you to do anything
you know i my philosophy has always been
you know you be the best person that you want to be
that's it that's it it's it's as simple as that
and i am not going to tell somebody how to run their life
you know because i wouldn't want somebody to tell me to run mine and
politicals uh should aside i have a lot of beliefs that are from all
over the political spectrum we don't talk about them because i
don't i don't want this to be a politics stream
there's no i don't think there's a reason to do it because i i'd like to
keep this stream and this community kind of away from
all that not good enough oh he's such a he's such a
neutral no yeah we you can read between the lines here over the last few years
i have a lot of i think a lot of people are dynamic
radical centrist no you're not allowed to like everyone there's nothing to do
with liking everyone and everybody has their own opinions
and i don't need to share them i don't have to talk about them
i don't feel like i have very many extreme positions on very much
stream and it's slow mode please politics are polarizing
and that's why i don't talk about them because
that's not what this community is for it's not what this community is about
it's about us hanging out getting together and not
worrying about that shit for a little while world's a crazy fucking
place world is a crazy fucking place but
i'd rather us just be able to hang out and
have a good time so people that say what's your opinion on this what's
your opinion on that how do you feel about that say this say that how
do you feel about that it's like it's tough because i don't want i don't
want a bunch of people to you know using certain things that i
say as examples to not want to listen to what i have to say not
want to like me don't want to talk to me don't want to listen to
my streams oh now fuck that guy he said that fuck him
i'd rather just remove it entirely at least in this space
if you wanted to have a private conversation with me about something
like that you know so be it right like i've had
private conversations before with some people in this community about
you know political stuff before but not in like a form like this
which is why that jokey but also very serious
uh i don't we don't talk about politics on the stream is still there
i feel like people are trying to bait germa into talking politics so they
can meme about it at his expense no i don't i don't think so i think
everything's just fine and even if they are then that's
okay it doesn't because i i'm not i'm not going to give
i'm not going to give any there's not going to be a stream where i sit up
here and i talk about let me tell you this and let me tell you
that because that's not how i am anyways what is the camera resolution
very bad i've never gotten the vibe that the chat is malicious and it's
trolling no i don't think so either but to close the book on that we
don't even need to open it at least here uh resident evil 2 on
friday it really comes out on fucking friday
holy shit politics ruins streams please never do it that's i'm not gonna
i'm not gonna i'll say a few things but not anything to i'm not going to
have like any political arguments like why would i want to do
that here there's no reason for me to do
that here i want you to have fun i don't want you to feel like you're
being targeted or you know yelled at or told you to
like stupid or something like why would i want to do that i want you to fucking
come here and have fun but move on jay see you in three
minutes i think it's the reason why there's
such a long slow mode right now is because
we're on a topic that's you know really people uh kind of you know
what i'm saying careful because because you said it
yeah but it that's you know i don't want it to derail everything which
kind of already has so we're gonna just here we go thank you too
plus w plus for the ten dollars hello i'm drunk and sad have you ever been
drunk and sad yeah that sucks i'm sorry to hear that
that's not cool i'm really really fucking sorry that
whatever you're going through is making you feel like that and you're
drinking and you're sad that sucks hopefully you get through it that was
plus w plus for the ten bucks that was last night hey clueless
sniper thanks for the one dollar hey jerma guess this is the last
chance to donate before the big day tomorrow
can't give as much as these oil tycoons in chat but i hope this is enough to
get shito a treat i'll get shito a treat thank you
clueless sniper almost at the end of last night i told you
if it went in my eye again i was gonna rip it up
thank you shogo thank you shogo for the
or shugo for the one dollar hey jerma been a fan for a long time
ever since i stumbled on your tf2 videos way back when
every stream and every video are always an incredible joy for me lately
i've been involved a lot in the community and it really is something
special you and your community are a massive
part of my childhood and now my adulthood
anyway i just wanted to say thank you to broluck
and gil my man both of whom offer to gift me subscriptions
personally nothing but love hell yeah thank you
thank you shugo uh i'm so thrilled that people can come together here
and have fun and can make friends and can play
games together that's what it's for that's what it's
for having a discord having a community that's
it's just it's great to know that people have
meeting each other and hanging out it's awesome thank you for the one
dollar and thanks for being part of the community
thank you stop having fun stop having fun this instant
when's the stream gonna end uh like probably 30 or 40 minutes we're
almost done with the bits here uh kill gannon thanks for the one
dollar hey jerma please reconsider checking out psyops the mind gate
conspiracy cool physics based combat superpower
game on the ps2 i know you i know you'll love it
yeah that is true you did mention that somebody did mention that before too
hey yellow kuru thanks for the five dollars good job
man running from it talking about last night running from the monster i
believe never trust purple thanks for the
ten dollars you cleared the platforming puzzle incredibly fast by
contrast um lobos jr the guy who does dark
souls challenge runs for fun took hours to get through it
genuinely impressed damn that's fucking wow sure he had a
lot of uh triumphs over my times in other
places in the game so that's pretty cool thank you for
the uh ten dollars purple pinwheel the pinwheel
shit it's all right you can die to pinwheel at
least four times and you still have a good playthrough
hey thank you yellow kuru for the four dollars never for free
never for free if you're good at something never do it for free
and finally no no no no no not finally errorless thanks for the one dollar joke
society one of the most favorite people alive
i always love catching your streams whether silly or chill
keep up the good stuff germ thank you thanks a lot
glad you have fun glad you think it's a good time thank you dr epic frag
for the one dollar this alien looks like something out of the movies game
every cut scene in this game felt like something something out of the
movies game they were not very good hey frody and weapon
thanks for the one dollar i was watching the stream before i went to bed
seven hours ago now i'm up getting ready for work and
you're still kicking ass that's one way to put it kudos for
seeing this game through we did cheated a little bit but still
did uh so sretto thanks for the one dollar
good night i tried to stay awake for the whole stream but my left eye
right eye middle eyes are closing that was really good that was very
good dr epic frag thanks for the one
dollar last stream oh wait that's not a good thing
he's still here in the shirt he's still here
they didn't go anywhere whole of one zombie thanks for the one dollar go to
bed go to bed i said go to bed thank you whole of one zombie
and then i am monk i said i would and i did
thanks for the one dollar i am monk that was all the bits from last
night which takes us to today which i should
be able to go like this i should and i can let's go down
to a couple hours ago to fat boy sunt for the one dollar i
don't know if you'll see this message but unless you actually had the memory
to remember the death joke i hope reminding you was
worth it death joke i'm not entirely certain
superintendent chalmers thanks for the one dollar it's a clip
let's see what the clip is on his fax machine
say my sweet sweet germo you were neat you had nice feet
good night sweet prince bye bye he would have done the same to me i'm
sure yeah probably yeah fucking feet man
thank you joel uh for the kind words appreciate
uh thank you to superintendent chalmers for showing the clip
hey nipple thanks for the one dollar i love you papa hey
thanks kiddo uh retro wave thanks for the bits
marvosh magali thanks for the one dollar chat can get pretty wild
sometimes but you always manage to keep it cool
but has there ever been a time when you wish you were allowed to say
fuck you chat out loud not really maybe a little maybe a little bit
maybe i can't really give you an exact memory
but this been maybe like out of the hundreds and hundreds of times i've
streamed and probably probably yeah there's
probably been one time when i was just like
at least i'm just looking over here like you don't
fucking know anything you want to talk to me about knowing shit but you don't
fucking know a thing you don't know what it's like to say
like yeah there's probably been maybe three or four times total maybe like
twice two point hospital two point hospital
i'm looking the wrong way oh yeah like chats that way
let me tell you something you bunch of fucking idiots
uh no no no no no no no i've ruined your footage i've ruined your
footage you can't use it chat confirmed no no that was that
was a joke that was a routine i was doing
but the answer is maybe maybe sometimes not
very often joel ray too uh joel came in right at the end of the stream here
right when i'm talking about the the the routine that i was doing
but thanks joel we just listened to your clip
of you talking about uh give me that that nice those nice send off
words uh you know about about uh the stuff that the things that are
lower than your ankles so welcome everybody from joe we're just
kind of hanging out uh going over the bits from the day
and a little bit from last night too hope you had a great stream there joel
and you probably did because you always do you got a great fucking
stream there and welcome everybody follow joe if you
haven't i mean he said it in a word started with an f and ended with
t and like it was two e's in the middle
it was four letter word so i mean you do the math
but yeah and then i'm gonna end the stream so
not much going on after this thank you to
uh solid milk for the one dollar germa have you not seen final
destination you avoided death but it will come back another day
yeah but that's when the next this when the next movie comes out
which they come out like once every few years
uh great canadian fuck club added to his hundreds hundreds of
gift subscriptions hundreds of them thank you great canadian fuck club
just just adding to to to the ridiculous amount of people that you
have subbed to this channel now 507 gift subs you are you are a
significant portion of every single sub on this stream
that's 507 gifted subs that's a sick that's a very
significant portion of the amount of people that are totally subbed it is
holy shit and you just see you seem to just keep
going you okay you like cross that threshold
of holy shit you that you never expected any more than that
and you you cross that threshold and and you still go
my god uh yeah an actual oil tycoon wow thank you thank you so much great
canadian fuck club that's a lot that's an insane amount
but moving on to the bits here we had uh what does this say look at all of
these all coming in and last night too last night like
i forget this morning how many subs came in this morning and last night
do you see what's going on right now do you see what's happening
do you see what's going on right now you thought i was making it up
i want to prove that i'm not making up shit it's
in my eye i'm not making it up do you see okay but did it like
transport dirt into my eye i don't understand why is that dirt on my
hair i have dirty hair do i have dirty hair
okay thank you to solid milk code man thanks for the two bucks if
any streamer would could come back from the dead
i knew it would be you don't i don't know what you're talking about but
i was fine today everything was good uh thank you for the two dollars thank
you uh to errorless for the 10 bucks thank you errorless your death ghost
scene may have been one of the most well executed gags you've ever done
and thank you for duct taping the pillows on your body that could have
been couldn't have been more perfect the death ghost scene um
i don't you might have had a tv on in the background you know you might
there might have been a there might have been a scary movie you a while
on the tv behind you or something but thanks for the 10 bucks i
appreciate it thank you it means a lot thank you and
somebody somebody just gave fucking a ton of money literally a huge a massive
amount just came in again from like did let
keep the like three or four thousand dollars in 24 hour stream thing going
apparently that's fucking insane so um tempest just gave a hundred and
five dollars holy shit and tempest says hey germa
just want to tell you about a year ago today i had a major depressive
meltdown in the lowest point in my life
and your videos were one of the only things to help get me through it
thank you that is a that is a powerful fucking thing to say
i'm really really really happy that you that you're getting through it
and it's that's that is like a i can't even fucking believe it like
that's such a powerful fucking thing to say
to somebody really really happy that you're doing better
hell yeah stay strong keep fucking going
thank you for the hundred dollars thank you the one hundred dollars
and a message that i will never forget i won't so
it's just that's thank you back a couple hours ago here
thank you so much like i still i it's i'm
fucking floored every time this happens somebody says something like
that sometimes i'm like lying lying down
in the bed i told you like i'm just like that you're talking about me
me like you're talking about me that's fucking
and i can't even explain the feeling i'm so fucking happy that you're doing
better i really am thank you for everything
we had demonic cucumber for one dollar uh it said who made this who made
this that's fucking great who did that
who made this hey anybody anybody want a fucking
boxing helmet anybody need like hockey pads for a
14 year old the pillow makes it it just it does
you get fucking fined if you had that on in a football game
thank you for that hey flames thanks for the five dollars happy birthday
happy birthday flames uh six dollars actually from flames
hey jerma could you say the name ethan for me my friend's birthday is coming
up and i want to edit his name into the rats mix tape
sure i'll make it easy for you and ethan it's your birthday today
and ethan's been such a good boy so you can like really feed that in
you know you can really feed that into the song
see happy birthday ethan and thank you to
uh flames for the six dollars and the birthday the special birthday
surprise for ethan i heard he's a great great ethan
happy birthday hey pilot guy thanks for the 15
dollars pilot guy cheer cheer cheer cheer 25 and 66
no 61 65 that was so dumb it really was thank you for the
15 that was the worst part of the game probably no it wasn't it was like three
or four sections where i could have attributed that to but thank you for
the 15 pilot guy freudian weapon thanks for
the one dollar jerma hart right back at you thank you wild fox
thanks for the one dollar hey jerma the old games
are always the best to watch you play hope you do more of the odd ones
there's still a shitload of ps2 games back there the one less shit load
i mean like probably eight but they're all going to be worth
playing eventually on days like today and yesterday i always have a lot of fun
the streams are always some of my favorites when we
tap into an odd old game they really are a shitload
eight also thank you to scar for the one dollar jerma i think the reason
this game's plot is so asinine is because they never expected anyone to
get this far maybe possible but thank you for the
one dollar thank you dork cube for the one dollar
tell me the truth do you believe that tell me the truth do you believe
that tell me the truth do you believe that uh george thank you
george maca for the one dollar with the philosopher stone and hoenheim
lifeline turned out to be just like full metal alchemist in space
at least edward was never as i wait this is spoilers
i'm not gonna get i don't want to give animated cartoon television show
spoilers so thank you for the one dollar george
i do see what you're saying i do see what you mean also i'm
gonna move some windows here because it's it's better to be facing this way
in my opinion whole of one zombie thanks with one do you dream about
voice commands yesterday no i was too tired i just crashed
i took the headset off i fucking jumped in the shower just to rinse my
body and i fell asleep it was i was too
tired too tired to dream yeah it really was like that
excalibur thanks to the one dollar once this game is done germa shall
return to the heavens and make his final judgment on humanity
i'm not a god clueless sniper thanks for the one dollar turn your germa off
and on again to activate jex mode i tried to turn the camera off and on it
it didn't work so i can't activate it thank you for the one dollar
you guys if it doesn't happen to you guys i'm sure it does
when i like sit on a computer screen and more than like two or three
hours go by i feel like like my i like my eyes
start to water and even when i take break and i you know throw some
water on my face and just hang out it's like
it's annoying i need to get like gamer goggles
you might need to turn down your brightness i think it's actually pretty
low it's like on the 30 to 40 percent side it's not
that high i don't think maybe i'll try that i'll get gamer goggles and i'll
turn the brightness down like another 10 percent and see if that helps
because sometimes it's just like i have really sensitive eyes though
anyways if i go outside in the wind for even five seconds but there's a
little breeze of wind and it hits my face
what tears just stream down my cheeks it looks bad it looks like i'm just
crying streaming down my face i walk into like a like a coffee
shop or something out of the wind and it's like
can i get a latte and they're just like holy shit okay
Nvidia swag bag what hey that shepherd thanks for the 10 bucks
is this that streamer that beat death
and lifeline in the same stream yeah i don't know about the death part but the
life part sure thank you the shepherd for the 10
dollars thank you canadian dynamite for the one dollar i haven't had this much
fun watching your stream since the sims 4
nice to see you stream a day before my birthday thanks for the good
memories canadian dynamite happy birthday thank
you for watching i'm glad that you enjoyed this stream
as much as you enjoyed that stream which is arguably
one of my favorite times sitting in this chair
the sims 4 mod streams especially the first one was probably the
the most fun i've ever had sitting in a chair with a game
probably talking about tears streaming down my face that
happened that actually happened during that stream
i will never be able to replicate or replace how fun that stream was
but you can do other things we got a lot of other plans so don't worry
don't worry but thanks for the one dollar thank you dork cube for the
one dollar my frigid heart the only thing that melts it is your labo
uh dr epic frag thanks for the one dollar next game is kenshi right
no not anymore it's a great game but i think i got my stream time out of it
so thank you though double d thanks for the
one dollar hey germa any update on the t-shirts
do you have an exact date or is it up in the year it is done
the shirt design is complete it's final uh i'm just gonna get the
raw pdf files from ashley probably either tonight or tomorrow
and then over the next few days i would assume some point probably
i would probably say after this weekend so
expect somewhere on monday or tuesday maybe
for me to have a link in this and you to uh
be able to buy a shirt two shirts glue man's coming back the original glue
manager will be back and the uh solar system shirt will also
be available to purchase on that day for the next if i can do
it forever i will because i don't there's no reason for me to do a
limited uh run i don't think we'll see don't hold me to that let me
find that out first but uh yes next week thank you to
door cube talking about me looking like a corpse
i don't know why that would be but thank you rocko forto thanks for the
one dollar hey germ just want to say congrats on not dying today
the new semester started this week and i would not last till finals
finals without your wacky epic gameplay commentary
keep wearing that goalie gear and stay safe
i will and good luck on the new semester
thank you good luck much love to you wow epic gamer
what that's what's wrong with epic gamer
i'll take the title of epic gamer that's fine
i can't wear germa shirts what if i'm associated what
what if you do crimes if you commit a crime with my t-shirt on they're
not going to think that i committed the crime too
it's like there he is he robbed a bank and he's wearing a metallica shirt
go arrest metallica too they must have had something to do with this
he told don't stop that stop it uh thank you soys awc for the three
bucks hey germa you're a genius when it
comes to entertaining me i want you to be part of a major
decision in my life okay and i want to quit this job
because i'm not respected for my hard work
input and input because i refuse to twiddle my thumbs just to clock in hours
i'm carrying this project but we're probably getting none of the credit
well want me to be a part of a major decision what's the decision
to stop working on the project or quitting or leaving or should you stay
or should you leave um there's a there's a couple of
scenarios i'm not a professional when it comes to stuff like this but
i would say if you're not happy what you're doing and you're putting in a
lot of work and you're not getting what you think
out what you should be getting out of it
then you need to start kind of looking for something else something
maybe try looking for another job try looking for another place in the
same field and if you're able to you know get
a job and leave the one you're currently at now that's way easier said
than done i know that and i understand that
but you don't want to put yourself into a position where you
are going to essentially regret what you did you know if you quit your job today
and you're like fuck this place i'm out of here and then i'm going to
go look for something if you can't find something then you
don't you got to be careful are you financially able to do that maybe you
are if you are financially able to do that
maybe that is something that you want to do it really depends on your
specific scenario but unless you have a lot of money
i don't think that's a great idea personally i would say the route of
looking for to interview other places and looking to find other stuff to do
while you're still working and then once you know that you've got a
solid lead and you're going to be able to work somewhere else
maybe go through on that route instead it's
it's rough there's no real correct answer here i don't think
because everybody's so different and everybody has such wildly different
lives and jobs and i don't know how essentially you
are as an employee to this project and if you leave are you
negatively affecting other people i don't know i don't know that's for you to
decide but the safest route is is definitely
to try to find something else that's great don't jump from the
plane without a parachute that is a great point yes that is pretty much
exactly what we're talking about that's just my opinion and that's just
the way that i see things other people might see it differently but
got to think about the future you do but i wish you the best of luck
sorry to hear about the hardships at work hopefully you get it figured out
real soon thank you uh soy's awc did my eyes just
change color no i don't think so i think they're only
one color hey sam thanks for the one dollars sam k
hey germa been watching since the early tf2 days you've always been my
favorite and your hilarious shit has helped me through some tough times
best wishes seems good seems good thank you
thank you so much for sticking around this long solid milk thanks for the
ten dollars hey germa you and star the reason that i like what i do
i was saving for a pc but i wanted to give to my favorite
streamer love you germa hart i really appreciate the ten dollars
thank you take care of yourself save for that pc
you don't have to give me a bunch of money if you guys if you want to
save for something you want to buy something
do it take care of yourself treat yourself
thank you so much for the ten dollars solid milk keep saving
you'll get something good uh coco ronis thanks for the one dollar hey
germa i did this rat movie fan art back in 2006
but i don't know if you ever saw it uh anyway thought
yeah i'd link it just in case you never did see it let's see
well it's beautiful uh i'll give you a link i think i did see this a long
time ago 2016 not 2006
back in 2006 remember that one now here's a link to the art
and that's that's fucking really cool i know i have seen this i have
the rat movie what does it say on the bottom
william defoe hugh jackman morgan freeman those are a lot of
a-listers in this one uh modest narcissist thanks for the five
community subs i got one did you get one
good thank you thank you for the five community subs
and thank you to um coco ronis for the artwork thank you
good shit thanks a lot i didn't get one pogchamp
maybe next time there are a ton of incredibly generous people
that have been giving out hundreds and hundreds and hundreds of them so
thank you thank you uh probably lc for the four dollars we talked about
the um the this topic already so but
thank you so much for the four dollars i really appreciate it
thank you to i am tony for the one dollar spent like three minutes
trying to come up with a message and got nothing have a good night
thank you you have a great night too did it again
five more community subs from modest narcissist
10 community subs i survived like the community subs are bad i didn't
get hit with one no community sub here thank you so
much for the 10 community subs ah and there
comes another 10 from your boy 10 community subs
right now my god uh take cover you guys are fucking hilarious thank you
for the 10 community subs your boy really appreciate it thank you so much
everybody you've been giving so many community subs
there's so many it's thousands a lot a huge a lot thank you
and look at here they come community subpocalypse
a huge pogchamp thank you to firestorm for the one dollar turn on
the screen click thing you lost all your privileges
forever because you kept on drawing penile shaped things
sorry you can't come back uh thank you to
trenty trenty enough for the one dollar you only have well will you
why do you only have one earbud at all times and no headset
i've seen you all these years with that one earbud
well i'll explain it i'll explain it again when i have
two headphones in or two earphones on
it fucks with me it's hard right now it's hard for me to concentrate hard
for me to really talk i get like speech jammed i need to
be able to hear myself and my surroundings
and 10 more from your boy and five from the space butterfly just
dropping community subs everywhere 20 30 40
five five blue comet drawn flats five five everybody's gonna have a sub
this is gonna happen is every single viewer gonna have a subscription
eventually soon here is that even possible
holy shit thank you guys modest narcissist again with five
do i get a sub too i'm automatically subbed my own channel so
that's how twitch does it i automatically have the highest sub
uh but thank you modest narcissist again for five five five ten ten ten
jesus you guys are fucking you guys are fucking ridiculous i can't believe
that this is many people that are getting committed that kid here it
comes again another one another fucking like sub commute
another community sub missile is like just coming over to chat
pin man one two three ten community subs thank you
you guys are too kind thank you so much seriously
and why not your boy why not your boy's gonna come in with another
five community subs oh shit thank you so much everybody
i said has it been like there's been almost a thousand
subs added in the last three days seven eight hundred or something how
many subs were added in the last 48 hours
oh my god tempest five community subs drawn flats five community subs
missiles are coming in shoot red lever shoot yellow lever
anonymous five subs anonymous gifter five
concrete car five community subs are you guys trying to put me into
like the top fucking hundred subs channels on twitch
my god you guys are gonna put me on a yacht
dear murdy five community subs visual warlock five community subs
we just did this yet we just did this yesterday great canadian
another nine community subs that's too many i can't read them
visual warlock another five great canadian ten
it's too many it's too many to read this too many of them
ydna five oh my fucking god magellan five this little like
timer that comes down five from magellan five from ydna
okay that was fun that was fucking pretty cool that was pretty awesome
and now there's another five from don dingle i don't know what to say
you guys are you guys are gonna break a record at least on this
channel yeah you brought i think let's see oh
y'all holy shit you guys blew right through it
this is the most subs i've ever had you guys blew right through the old record
this is the oldest that i and i don't like to talk about
subs and how many subs i have or give i don't want to have a huge amount of
like incentive for people to give subs i just i
this is fucking ridiculous you want to know how many people have
subscribed to this channel i don't put it on like the screen i
don't at least two yeah well the highest sub count i
like i think i ever had it was like a month ago would you like
to know the number and why i'm able to go into the studio
all the time and why i can potentially try to put up elaborate streams and
elaborate things is because there are 6200 fucking
subscribers on this channel right now do you understand
you understand how fucking and an uncountable amount of money that is
i'm gonna use it you bet your ass i'm gonna use it
and this all happened in the last in the last like
10 months drawing flats another five remember i talked about the channel
like like growing in in numbers and money
and shit this all happened in the last year
like six months ago or so my subscriber count fucking
like doubled more than that more than doubled it like
almost like one and a half almost if you bet your ass i'm gonna fucking use
every goddamn cent of this as best as i can
thank you all so much like i i can i i really i'm i'm speechless i got
nothing else to fucking i got nothing else to say
i hope you think it's fun hope you enjoy your time here i think you hope you
p another five from peachy thank you so much peachy chew for the five
community subs on top of everybody else i never i never thought that that was
this was ever gonna happen i really didn't
a couple like maybe two years ago well no no like a year and a half
ago hitting something like even two or three
thousand subscribers was like a huge fucking deal dabs for dinner thanks for
five community subs another five that was a huge deal when
it happened and there's been a huge influx of
new people and a bunch of people that have been around for a long time
silk uh thank you silk for the five subs
there's been a lot of support from a lot of other people too
i mean think about other streamers that you know other youtubers and shit
that have like sent people over here i that
it's unbelievable i can't fucking believe it so and that's another huge amount
of money came in but i don't want this stream to be
about that you know i don't want the stream to be like
oh i'm making money can't wait to make more money
i want to make some more on top of that too that's not my intention
and having that many subscribers i want to keep the channel the way
that i intended it to be even before making a huge amount of
fucking money larz bloodaxe thanks for the thanks for the
111 dollars 111 dollars uh thank you first of all
hey jerma i've been watching you since around 2013 you've always had an
immensely positive impact on my life i'm in community college now and the
last semester was the worst but your streams never failed to help
me out and keep you smiling i hope to contribute more when i
get a steady income because i genuinely love what you do thank you
oh and i'm glad you survived today me too uh thank you for the
ridiculous amount of money that means a lot i hope you just
just know everybody like i'm repeating it a hundred times
but like how do you think that some of the stuff that i want to do will
happen you know uh fucking jerma rumble live
too streamed you know i mean that type of shit
i've talked about it a couple times other stuff there's a couple there's
one thing i was talking to my my buddy that does a lot of producing
work with me about um i could choose your
own adventure stream where you guys get to like go places
and look at stuff it is like the other stuff that i've talked about it it's
all that's all fucking that's all possible
that's all very possible now it just is just talking about thousands and
thousands and thousands of dollars that are that are ready to go
jump another hundred dollars tempered cucumber thanks for the hundred
dollars uh how do i cheer i think you figured it out
but holy shit my god guys will you just cry already and get it
over with blowing through fucking every ready every
record i've ever had and i don't want to use that i don't
want to use the word record because it's not a record
60 fucking 200 60 500 10 000 20 fucking thousand subs doesn't matter
100 subs 10 000 subs i don't want it to be a record
because that's i don't want to see it like that i don't want to have
that be uh hey well you know we broke our sub record but that's
that's that's not for me to tell you that's not for me to tell you
to do uh thank you adventure mf dan for the five subs
five community subs your humbleness is just compelling people to donate more
true another 50 dollars just came in from great canadian fuck rub cry damn
it you big baby i'm not gonna cry i'm not gonna you're
stuck in a feedback loop oh my god great canadian gave 50
dollars lacrosse to 50 dollars i can't afford the hundred but here's
my chump change don't no no no no no no don't see it
that way don't see it that way it's okay if
you don't if you never sub or never give a
cent to this channel that's completely fucking perfectly fine
it's all right don't worry don't don't worry about giving me a
hundred dollars on stream don't worry about it don't have that be a thing
in the back of your mind that you think that you have to do
but my fucking god thank you cassie five community subs
chump change it's not chump change it's 50 dollars
50 dollars somebody said longest stream in the last 48 hours and
broke every monetary fucking financial and more money than i've ever made it
in one period on twitch or on youtube ever in my
in my whole life thank you everybody you've given me
way more than i could possibly ever ever want or ever ask
anybody for anything ever in my entire life my entire fucking living adult life
ever i hope you enjoy the things that i'm gonna try to do
thank you all of you much love to you all you're all fucking so
god if i could like if like if like if like 17 or 18 year old me
could like look into the future and like have seen this shit
it'd be impossible like i can't even fucking believe it every day
50 more dollars just came in from ben thank you ben for the 50 dollars
uh ben add benado bros thanks for the 50 bucks
thank you germa for everything you're a great human so are you
thank you for your 50 fucking dollars 50
my god another 50 from ben thank you so much ben 50
oh okay all right that's uh 50 from lacronda do it or lose it brother
50 dollars from lacronda all right this is done
that's it thank you everybody for the five that was five community subs from
dr shrug 50 dollars from divas all right i'm gonna
have to let turn stream off okay i'm trying thank you i'm broken
i think i might be broken you think you broke me
divas thank you for the 50 fucking dollars
thank you hey germa wanted to ask you something that has been bothering me
lately lately i feel like i don't really have a purpose
in life other than just to live and be there for other people either that or
i'm just living for dreams and opportunities that i
know are never going to happen but i keep giving it a chance as an
excuse to live longer it's just so many
expectations and pressure from other people and i don't know what to do
with my own life and that's on top of depression so
much other shit and that says one out of two i will
tell you very very very much i mentioned uh lobster five community
subs thank you i mentioned something uh not even five
ten minutes ago about if 18 year old me could look into the
future they would think it was a lie um the
thing about opportunity is you never you never know when it's
going to happen the reason why it is why it is called
opportunity is because it could just fucking happen and
you'll never know you just you just try to be ready for it
it doesn't matter if you're talking about something in work or relationship
or school there's there's no real way to
to prepare for it i was not prepared for it i was not ready for it
i was just like a lot of you fucking guys
all of you guys when i was like 18 19 20 i'd you know you just kind of
you're just doing you you're trying to figure out what you want to do
into your 20s into your 30s you're just trying to figure out what the
fuck you want to do and sometimes an opportunity will knock
and you just happen to do it and you can't really foresee that it's going
to happen but on top of that though there there
is no secret formula i i think people will ask well how
do you do this how do you do that what's the secret what's the what
there really is no secret it's just kind of uh
passion a little a little bit of uh talent in the right areas a lot of
luck you know that's what opportunity really
kind of is is those a handful of things and
i really wish there was a way for me to
tell you all the secrets and give you all these things and hey let me
tell you this this is the exact thing you have to do
with your life but i can't do that you know i can't uh i i can't give
you the answers because i don't have them
as much as uh yeah life is very complex
but to put a cap on something like that try to find a few things that you
like to do a few things that you're good at
and just make your life however you can from those handful of
things everybody's good at something everybody's
good at fucking something you just might not know what it is
yet and even if you do work on it all the time a lot of
people say i'm not good at anything
you yes you are there's at least a handful of things that you could
reliably do that you know that you can and if you don't if you really don't
think you do you might try to take up some more
hobbies try to take up some more things that you might want to try to
get better at i wish i had the secrets everybody's good at something
if you don't here's another thing you don't have to be an astronaut you
know what i mean you don't have to be
like a fucking personal chef like you don't you can be
whatever you're good at find it you will
soon enough keep gifting until he cries on stream
i'm good at not being noticed in chat but again i'm not i'm not
an expert i'm not qualified to have to tell you these things these are just
just kind of stuff that i believe but i want to be an astronaut go for
it try it learn about space learn about
all these things get into it get involved in community projects get
involved with whatever nasa's got some shit right
get involved with it get make it something that you care about every day
and if you are still doing well and you still like it
and you're doing good go for it just go to nasa
this is still going tl dw too long didn't watch
you shape the person that you are in your late teens into your 20s
you think i knew what the fuck i was doing my life even like six or
seven years ago not even like 10 years ago not even
i'm 33 we got any goddamn idea what the hell i was doing when i was like
25 i was like i wanted to do some
i was making wedding videos and i kind of didn't really like it
i wasn't that great at it i thought i was okay at it but i
just did you know what i mean like i didn't have any idea
a growing boomer you shape the person that you are
and the things that you know that you like and the things that you're good at
from those teen years into your mid early to mid
into late 20s that's what i believe that's how i feel
you'll find it thank you thank you so much
and a ton more fucking money came in joe dirt gave 50 oh my god joe dirt
gave 50 dollars love everything you do have part of my student loans
don't give me student loan money thank you joe dirt for the 50 dollars
thank you drawn flats for the 50 dollars germy you're a great human
just uh just willing to being able to make people laugh and do that without
stopping you deserve every single penny and bit you get thank you
i hope you feel that way i'm just going to continue to try to do the
things that i want to do thank you anyways let's go and
go back before this huge amount of money
and let's go let's go talk about some of the other messages that we've
received and then colonel zero comes up with another 50
dollars from colonel zero thanks for making me happy and for giving me the
pep talked to pick a new hobby you'll find it you'll find it y'all
everybody finds something thank you so much for the 50 dollars
good luck i wish you the fucking best good luck to you
good luck my goodness we were down here
uh not that much more well yeah there is
my god there's so much money i'm gonna build a fucking i'm gonna build
a higher like real higher like a fucking actor
to come and like squeeze juice for me on camera
and we'll talk about like acting uh hot take alert thanks for the five
community subs hire an actor to stream for me let's go
back here we were down here everybody that was fucking ridiculous
thank you everybody thank you so fucking much
let's continue after that my god thank you thank you solid milk for
the one dollar uh hey again germa i spent a dollar
sixty this week and i set myself back so far from a pc so i'm just going to
give my last of my bits don't make sure you take care of
yourself first it's very important very very very
important if you have some disposable expendable income
and it's something that you'd like or that you want to do for yourself
do it for you first i should be way way down on that
list of things that you want to give money to if you still have some
leftover sure absolutely but make sure you take care
of your fucking self first take care of you first thank you
uh dr epic frag thanks for the one dollar
uh when's the stream where we finished that one good item finding game
uh we didn't somebody mention a better one one that was
more interesting that we were gonna take a look at in quotes
i spy okay yeah we'll do it drawn flats thank you ten dollars
earlier uh you're a great streamer thanks for
all your content still brings a smile to my face
i'm fucking really happy to think that thank you so much drawn flats
for your huge amount of money thank you whence rind did i
tim allen is still here there's so many whence rind thanks for the two
bucks hey jim i want to let you know that
working on animation uh homework while listening to you yell
stomach head stomach last night was like being in purgatory
but like in a fun way did somebody give even more
tempered cucumber a hundred dollars a hundred from tempered cucumber again
i am in 22 000 in debt now i hope that's not true
i hope that's not true thank you though germa debt
thank you tempered cucumber so fucking much
make sure you can pay your bills and you pay your debts don't worry
about giving me a fucking huge amount of money i appreciate you
fucking hanging out thank you oh my goodness gracious
i'm gonna do something with this money you better like when when this
payment comes in you're gonna see some fucking which
you probably you're gonna you're gonna see a fucking stream
with this blow it all in vegas why would i do such a thing
take all the money from the last two days and put it all on black
no fucking way no way my god thank you too i i got lost here
there's been so many some so much money thank you for
five dollars from graveyard ghoul i found this on
cropped boomer images and i feel like it perfectly sums up how you feel after
beating yell at lady game cropped boomer images i'm fucking tired
hey uh zir zilly writer thanks for the
ten dollars jeremy please do a sexy pose
thanks for the ten dollars thank you thank you for the ten dollars uh
ziller ziller eater uh leto thanks for the one dollar how much for dirty
socks in the merch store i'm not even thank you for the one dollar thank you
ty thank you thank you thank you ty go maniac
for the one dollar germ bowl thanks for being awesome love you
you've helped me through many a hard time and you're a great inspiration
for me thanks for being amazing thank you thank you so much base
grandpa thanks for five dollars look mario tennis went bad but at
any point in time will you do one stream in smash ultimate please
no no i can't i can't do smash ultimate
it's too much for my fucking germa old brain
it's a great game but i can't i can't do it i tried
thank you though uh thank you nick for the
ten dollars hey germa a girl i thought i was going to spend the rest of my
life with ended our relationship tonight
but going on to twitch and realizing you were streaming brought a
smile to my face it means so much to me and the rest
of your fans just want to let you know that we love you
i'm terribly sorry to hear that that's always incredibly fucking difficult
breakups are fucking hard oh my god breakups are really fucking hard to
do and especially if you thought it was
going to be something much more long-term
take care of yourself i'm really sorry to hear that glad you can hang
out here and have some fun thank you i wish you the best
another hundred dollars did another hundred dollars just come in
or was that from is this is this thing
is this thing just counting from like fucking an hour ago then another 50
from ben this stream is not serendipity you deserve every penny my
man thanks for getting me through law school
lawyer law school i told you that there's a ton of smart
fucking cookies here i don't you guys know them all
all of my viewers are either doctors lawyers astronauts
that's great to hear uh thank you so much for the 50 dollars
you guys are fucking great thank you thank you fucking ben
so much for the hundreds of fucking dollars thank you
we also had some come in from look at all these
i'm scrolling through hundreds of fucking community subs
hundreds of them i can't even tell where they begin or where they end
this is too much holy shit this is too much new account thank you
for the five dollars hey germans want to tell you about
a year ago today uh no no no sorry that's a different
message it's scrolled up right when i read it but
that new account thanks for the five dollars what's the eta of germa rumble
live action 2 that's gonna get me hey thanks thanks a lot that was from an
hour ago an hour ago that means it has an
hour to catch up oh my fucking god uh i don't have an
eta on it there's no eta ever on anything that i ever try to plan so
you'll see it eventually john horns thanks for the two bucks
hey germ any probability of a crash insane trilogy stream
um probably not probably not there's an overwhelming amount of money here
i don't even know what to say it's like thousands of dollars in bits and
messages and uh hold on i need to open this back
up where is that fucking okay hold on
uh the the the messages and the bits were coming in so fast
that i actually have to like load up the other page so let me see where
we were i think we were right here holy shit hydrate i need to hydrate
you're right i'm still alive i'm still here don't worry
let me see how many how much is left there are there are
hundreds there are like probably hundreds of messages here
holy fucking god yeah i there's so there's so many more messages and so
many more bits you guys are fucking you guys are
unbelievable i don't even know what to do
i don't even know what to say this was gonna be just a little end of the
end of the stream thing 50 bucks just came in right now
from no it didn't i have to like turn off
stream labs i think good thing you announced it as a hangout that's true
uh i'm i'm gonna go get some water so give
give me just a moment uh i will return very shortly
just gonna get some water be right back he's crying off stream
i'm ready for the purposes of trying to get through
this extreme amount of money and messages and donations and everything
it's an overwhelming amount of money uh i'm just going to try to go
through them and thank everybody let me move this where even is this
oh okay so for the purposes of getting through this
uh thank you everybody we're gonna go through them
i'm not gonna skip any bits but uh this would probably probably gonna take
another two to three plus hours to go through these
it's a lot it's an un-fucking-believable amount
did he put in eye drops no so let's see uh if we can get through these
in one stream thank you to uh thank you to Lando Bando for the dollar
hey i'm the guy who wrote the drive-through story
this is important what's your review of the story it was a solid
it was a solid i didn't do it but no it was very well
written storyline thank you Lando Bando for the one dollar thank you so much
cosmic moses i'm sick of your lies germa
free whale lord
at this time by this time next week
on the day of Jeremy's death i don't like to even say that i don't
i'm just gonna say the 23rd okay i'm gonna okay the goalie stream where
i'm dressed up as a goalie all right so on the goalie stream
i will be wearing the sock what's wearing the what
let my audio cut out song i'll be singing a song
song wearing it keeps cutting out on me wearing song
uh the audio keeps cutting out sorry thanks for that though sorry i don't
know what's going on there thanks for the one dollar uh thank you
hola one zombie for the one dollar somebody linked an old video of you
acting i'd never seen it's fucking funny
um acting you've seen me in such things as
made up stuff on my imdb page that people have a lot of fun with
i don't do that by the way it's not all right you can't do that it's
not it's not it's against the rules uh thank you whole of one zombie
thank you uh probably at least again for the one dollar
thanks for being wholesome thank you for being here
thanks for giving me a dollar thanks for the money thanks for fucking
watching thanks for everything teapink thanks for the 10 bucks hey
germa i've been a big fan of your content for like five or six years
now and love every second of it make
merch i want to wear glue man you'll be there next week
next week you'll see the new shirt as well
so you'll be by glue man and that also for ten dollars thank you
error 4044 for the ten dollars germa i desperately ran around my room
looking for a working credit card oh anyways i'm here to thank you for
this channel and your lovely community it's been a while since i feel
have felt so supported also you look magnificent today all the love in the
world from brazil thank you thank you for the ten dollars
error some guy thanks for the five dollars my donation got shat on
yesterday so i'm donating five bucks to make you watch this video
i think we already did i'm about to okay uh i think we did did we did we
watch this already arf arf arf uh thank you for the five
dollars thank you platadonius for the three dollars
here's a nice little video on your sub made about today's events museum of
art in new york like a relic i can't get over that
and streamer come face to face at the metropolitan museum of art in new
york actor this is like a relic i can't get
over that and streamer come face to face once upon a time and another time
he was right here you know william defoe
studies a portrait of germa and i see the marks you know i laugh
when people say you look like him he looks very different it's a
remarkable close encounter that's fucking great that was really
good it was very good thank you for that uh
platadonius for putting that to our attention
peaceful hailey thanks for the one dollar hey germa just want to say hi and
you seem like such a nice guy thanks for being a chaotic neutral i
love you germa and love you chap uh uh awful stupid is the uh actual
disciplined emotional right i'm a disciplined emotional
but thank you uh thank you hailey also thank you to uh
lanad for the ten dollars i've been watching you for a long time germa just
want to tell you that you seem like someone that gives super good high fives
nope i missed and i just hurt my hand so you were wrong
uh i'll miss every time thank you for the ten dollars
uh timmy tim tam thanks for the one dollar okay so you said a little bit
about politics earlier and i don't really want to bring that back up
but what's your favorite pringles flavor it's not pizza it's not sour
cream it's not cheddar it's not original original is the
worst original is disgusting my favorite pringles flavor is
can i get a drum roll please i don't i can't remember the last time i
actually ate pringles so i don't think i know i don't i
actually don't know i don't think i i haven't eaten pringles in like
fucking four years i don't know i'm sure i liked one
you still i'm still here yeah i'm good i was just searching so i was
going look my my brain is in hard drive from like 2001
something you know like that
i have to search through the records uh thank you dinky duper for the one
dollar hey germy you seem like pretty good with advice so i was wondering if
you could help me you could say i'm one of those i
guess uh melodramatic fools you could even say neurotic to the
bone so doubt about it sometimes i get myself the creeps and
sometimes mind plays tricks on me it just keeps adding up i feel like i'm
cracking up as paranoid am i just it's uh green day that's a green day
lyric thank you uh john horns thanks for the two
bucks hey germy any probability of a crash insane trilogy i don't know why
that's here again it just popped up twice
thank you john horns and thank you do new account
wait what we already we got this one already we did thank you we phone for
the one dollar you're a great person it's amazing how much you help all of
us thank you we fun i'm happy that this
community is a positive fun one thank you uh
taeyeon thank you taeyeon for the one dollar hey germy you got any
interesting stories specifically from the eighth grade
not much of a storyteller not much of a storyteller
when's the pepsi man stream what do you think i'm gonna do pepsi man
pepsi man uh thank you target ape for the
ten dollars and eleven cents can you tell my friend uh zander to buy a
computer uh it depends do they have enough
money or they do they want a computer i can't just tell somebody to
do something hey zander if you want a computer
and you have enough money for a computer then yeah get a computer there's
no they're pretty cool they work they do
things i'm not gonna tell them to buy what if
they don't want one you know what i'm saying uh but thank
you mutant abyss mutants abyss for the one dollar and fifty
cents hey germy my grandma passed away this morning
and your stream tonight has really helped me out so thank you so much
you are easily the most creative streamer on the platform and i
absolutely love every stream you do you make a difference in our lives and i
want you to know that you're genuinely my favorite streamer and you've
helped me out so much just by being you
thank you so much from all of us it's my pleasure thank you
thank you so much that default all right scream
thank you mutants abyss i'm really sorry about um
sorry about your loss thank you for sticking around thanks for watching
take care take care squirrel assault thank you for the ten
dollars been watching since 2013 i love
everything you do another rat birthday request can you do
uh elena my girl and i sing that song all the time
elena elena or elena elena yeah elena it's your birthday today and
elena you know you can add it me in uh thank you so much
squirrel assault but happy birthday happy birthday elena
uh burgers by the way thanks for the three dollars i'm still waiting for my
nvidia swag bag i use the code fat fuck and i still
haven't gotten it that's not my that's not on me
that's uh that's not on me that's not a company you know thanks for
the one dollar superintendent charlmer's raid vinny ha ha
uh we'll take a look and see who's who's going here still
well when we get to the end of these bits here hey gray thank you
grave for the nine dollars and 47 cents hey germ
well that shirt you put on during the new year's stream the fireman
shirt would that ever be some kind of merch
i'd absolutely wear that in public the shirt is currently purchasable from
the jackbox uh app thing it's like a website
as for fireman merch everything is a possibility
but i really don't want to load up a shitload of shirt like for instance it
was like three or four shirts oh yeah hey by the way tomorrow it's
20 bucks a shirt and it's like five of them like i
don't i'd rather trickle out stuff like that
and not just dump out like three or four pieces of merchandise at once
so everything is open everything's up for the future
i i can't tell you exactly but it's been it's been talked about
mostly lost thanks for the one dollar that poster art reminded me
since i have no idea what boo actually looks like i just imagine he looks
like the guy he voiced in rat movie he might you never know he might
look just like that guy from rat movie demonic cucumber thanks
for the one dollar i don't think any of my bits came up today which is a
shame because i made a really good joke
about today actually being the death of the main channel
it's a pretty good uh pretty good joke pretty good joke
hey superman thanks for the one dollar it is a youtube link
it's celery man we've already we've already talked about celery man we've
seen celery man with paul rudd thank you superman
for the one dollar and the celery man
dork cube thanks for the one dollar linkedin here's ron
uh here's the ron troutman's uh the cheers to you guys linkedin
i don't want i don't want it no that's okay
thank you for the one dollar uh thank you mostly lost for the one dollar this is
the stream where people actively dislike being gifted nice things streamer
included i don't think it's it's not that it's
about dislike it's about it's just kind of one of those
overwhelming things that you're never really prepared for
as much as i can try to look like and pretend like i am otherwise
if that makes any sense thank you for the one dollar though most of the
loss i really appreciate it thank you jules for the one dollar
thank you hack it fast for the one dollar am i going to pax east this year
i am not going to pax east i don't think it's in the cards
something on this side of the united states probably
but not pax east i don't think i'll be able to make it
thank you most of the loss for the one dollar i love how you were saying
i don't want there to be any incentives for subbing
while chat was in sub only mode well chat goes into sub only mode
sometimes when there's a problem or there's a there's a reason for it to
go on it's not on it's on maybe for a couple minutes
maybe um sub only mode is as is like a way
to potentially help or corral when
there's like an issue it's not you know paying to
the chat is open almost 100 percent of the time so
uh that's not going to happen i'm not going to turn on sub only mode
forever it's it's just only there for very specific
reasons right when it gets too gassy it's a good way to put it but thanks
for the one dollar and yeah that's why the face cam i don't like having
it on because you see me do like fucking
quelled burps it's great uh techno toast thanks for the one dollar
germa i can honestly genuinely say that you're one of my favorite
streamers and youtubers ever you deserve all the subs and more
because i know you'll put it towards amazing uses
and make even more ambitious entertaining streams
love you my dude that's i'm gonna try
i'm gonna try that's all i can do is try
but thank you so much thank you we than for the four dollars
germa glad to see that switching to twitch has worked out so well for you
keep up the good work it's been great twitch has been
incredibly kind to me so it's great um
couldn't be happier so thank you uh goops
goops natch thanks for the ten dollars already sub so i thought i'd
give you more money thanks for being a funny dummy
funny dummy thank you goop really appreciate it
thanks for the ten dollars no soup for you thanks for the one dollar so when do
we get to play twitch plays the stock market with all this money
i would not do something like that we would lose that account
that account would go to zero in roughly fucking three days
uh thank you tagora for the five community subs
tagora five community subs on top of the fucking hundreds that have
happened today the last 24 hours uh ivy caz tv thanks for the five dollars
germa my friend it's been some time remember me hope you have a wonderful
day and thank you for all you do for everyone and they have the party
the party popper thing going pop pop pop thank you ivy caz
thank you for the five dollars and welcome back to the stream
where were you at this point not being a sub was an anomaly here
yeah yeah it's wild to think about that
robbie revolver thanks for the one dollar congrats germa congrats
thank you kill again and one dollar from kill again and we want to thank you
for all your hard work you're the one who steps things up and
gets things done around here you keep your word you deliver what you
promise and then you go the extra mile you're doing a great job
a great job 10 more fucking community subs
what the hell is happening fly for shy thanks for 10 community subs
thank you for 10 fucking more subs dr epic frag thanks for a dollar our big
boy is gonna cry i think we're breaking him no i'm gonna i'm all
right noob king thanks for three dollars
it's my birthday thanks for the great stream happy birthday new king
happy birthday to you to you spuds thanks for the dollar 25 spuds i can't
sub but you can have these ad bits smiley face love you the fact that
anybody would have ad bits and watch ads and give the money to me
is thank you thanks for fucking suffering through ads to give me money
and then health packs five community subs from health packs
these gifted subs i don't even know what to say anymore
it's fucking it's remarkable it's great it's
you guys are paying for literally everything
and you're taking fucking such good goddamn care of me
i don't even know what to say ads germa pluto
ads uh i'd ever agree thanks for the five dollars i'd hey germa i've been
watching your streams for a long time you never failed to make me laugh till
my stomach hurts also have you checked out a game called
oxen free i have not heard of oxen free oxen free what's it about
a thriller about a group of friends it's a thriller about a group of
friends uh who unwittingly open a ghostly
rift just bookmark it bookmarked we'll look at that
see if it's worth something that's fun to do i have now looked at it
so i'll give it i'll give it a closer look hey tingy thanks for the one
dollar this is chump change right here don't say that but what you don't know
is i'm almost at a hundred dollars donated you see i didn't give it all
at once i've broken it down into a ton of
messages germa iq yeah i mean no one's expected to
fucking just give that much money in that short amount of time
tons of you guys have given like ten five dollars dollar two dollars
every single stream it adds up a lot it adds up over time to a point where
you you have given potentially hundreds of
dollars over the years bottom left what's in the bottom
left pillow with duct tape on it yeah if
you're just if you're just joining us we
i finished um lifeline and there were a lot of messages and a lot of bits
and stuff that i didn't read from yesterday and i'm just kind of
going through the massive amount of bits and
subs and donations that were given over the last 48 hours so
we're just kind of hanging up for a while just chilling up what chat am i
reading from the what are we talking about hangout
stream i too like to hang out with my friends by watching us shower money
on one lucky friend for five hours straight
well two because we i beat i beat the lifeline i beat lifeline at about three
and a half to four hours in sounds like my kind of party my three
thousand friends watching watching us give one person
money um but this doesn't happen that often
this is this is an anomaly for sure this is a lot of fucking money
and a lot of messages over the last couple of days this
does not happen all the time so i obviously want to give the
attention that i think it deserves but we'll we are getting we're getting
there not very much left not like a it's probably not going to
take more than an hour or so but this is also another conversation
to have because a part of me does not want to
have this conversation but kind of have to at some point
if remember how when we it used to be
it was 25 cents and i would read everything
right and then we move that to a dollar and i'm still trying to read as much as
i can what happens is when there's so many
people giving money and so many people
donating and it becomes it becomes hard to do this
with a channel that is growing at the size that we are
so with a one dollar minimum it actually
as much as i don't want to say this and i'm not really i'm not sure
ready to do it yet the threshold may have to increase
it might have to for the end of the streams
50 dollar minimum what the hell are you talking about no way
i wanted to wait as long as i could i wanted to see how
how far it could go but when there's when there's this many people it just
it becomes nearly impossible you know sometimes the end of the
streams will be two three plus potentially hours long
and that's why we moved it in the first place
10 to 15 dollars no no it wouldn't be that high
it would it would not be more than that not no not in a million years
but it just that's just kind of what happens when
there's this much to read and i want to give everybody the attention that
they deserve but the stream needs to function too
that's been one of my biggest philosophies with doing streaming and
twitch and everything is having a stream that is a stream
and that's why i stopped reading stuff in the middle of the streams that's why
i moved it to the end so we could kind of have a little session where we hang
out and i'm gonna think about what it would
possibly be i need to buy the season pass no it's
just for um end of the stream messages to make
it easier for us to read them so it doesn't potentially go on for hours at
a time like that fucking sound but for the
purposes of uh this stream the one guy vip dlc
no let's keep going just figured i would bring it up
and sort of keeping that in here for a while
because i didn't want to really talk about it because i didn't want to bring
it up because i didn't want to do it but sometimes it's necessary as much as
it pains me to say but thank you kill ganon uh for the
one dollar we we want to thank you for all your hard work oh that's just
the fucking cheers to you guy we got that already uh dr epic frag
thanks for the one dollar our big boy is crying we're breaking him why
are these popping up twice then we get we got them right uh happy
birthday to noob king we got new king right
oh some of these are coming back hey hey heat miser thanks for the five
dollars kind of broke because i'm in high school
but i can't fucking wait to see what you do with all this
so cool to see you doing this well germa love you we'll see
i have a few projects in mind that i think this money would do very well
in so i will use it i'll put it to good use
space butterfly thanks for the ten dollars thank you for your fantastic
streams germa you're one of the funniest most genuine guys on the internet
and you deserve all the money you earn really appreciate that space butterfly
thank you for the ten bucks the ace's chase thanks for ten dollars
i got a community sub right now letting me be subscribed for the first time
to any streamer well and i don't have money to give
subs in return but i got a few free bits that i want to give you
thank you first time to any streamer a sub
ace's chase thank you for the ten dollars and thanks for
thanks for being here solid gold bathroom hey i got the solid gold on either side
the toilet is going to be the cheapest one at home depot
but thank you ace uh dr epic frag thanks for the 10 bucks here jeremy
buy yourself a pizza pie on me 18 dollars actually from dr epic frag
thank you i will buy a pizza very soon within the next few days
and i will be thinking about dr epic frag when i eat it
solid gold toilet water thank you burger by the way for the two dollars keep it
rolling we are thank you auto hinds thanks for
the one dollar been watching you since 2015 you've been one of the content
creators who i've enjoyed always consistently make me laugh i'd like
to give more but i need to save some cash
since i'm in school keep it up keep up the school
save your money save it up to buy a gold bathroom because that's what i'm
doing hey glyph bin thanks for the four
dollars germa rumble live action turned out to be a brilliant investment good
call and as you're aware of the amount of
money they were making here now the amount of money that i have now
going to be in my bank account this year
i that was like almost 10 grand to do germa rumble live one
imagine what the fuck is possible with like
30 i got some fucking ideas your accountant is going to go through hell
don't waste it all on one video no i'm just obviously
pulling out random numbers but i'm gonna use it
i'm gonna use it thank you glyph bin again for four dollars
hey divas thanks for the two dollars on top of that huge amount of money
from earlier uh i don't want to make this feel like
a therapy session but do you have any any advice
we talked about it for a little while uh hopefully you can get it sorted
out we extensively went over it if you're
still here uh divas hopefully you were there when
we talked about it thank you so much for the two bucks
and the huge amount of money before that and also thanks to
star wolf star wolf ken for one dollar give until he gets mad
why would i ever get mad from someone giving me money
mad no no i wouldn't get mad at that a band bro like but that was i was
just trying to it was a joke though that was not
for real i was just trying to say that he gave a lot of money very
quickly and i and i mean i'm looking at the
shit that you guys are writing right now everybody
everybody everybody's doing the fucking rage mutant thing
the sun the sun yeah fuming because booming uh thank you
lelemo for the five dollars hey jeremy i've been watching for around two
years and have never donated so now it
seems like a good time uh seems trite to say at this point
but your streams and videos have helped me at my lowest love you
bud thank you it's a lot of positivity
here a lot of positive shit which is great
you know there's not very much negativity at least i don't believe so
and it's really really great to see all this positive stuff so
thank you lelemo lelemo for the five dollars and your incredibly nice
message thank you brand dinghy brand dinghy for 10 bucks hey jeremy i've
watched since 2013 and you brought a lot of joy into my life
really do put a lot into your stream and i think we appreciate what you do
i'm glad thank you thank you future gamer for the one dollar you deserve
every goddamn cent you're the best streamer on twitch
and it's been amazing watching you grow from some sort of shitty tf2 videos
to having the first live truly amazing
my first live i didn't i'm fine i didn't i'm still here
thank you future gamer leather jacket 10 books from leather jacket are we
having a give germ a money party seriously though all this generosity
you deserve it all honored to wield a sword for the chat
for all these years thank you fucking honored to have you here
that was leather jacket for 10 dollars one of the first mods
one of the first mods on the channel that was leather jacket 10 bucks
and then that was future gamer before that thank you you guys are
fucking awesome and jessa everybody realizes that we are
getting close to the end i'm gonna put on the outro
because i don't really i'd rather not have people stumble into the
stream and just be like what's going on in here
this guy's just like accepting payments and
you know what i mean i don't want people to think that uh
end of the stream music uh where is it there we go
i literally just got here see so there you go
payment stream yeah but i don't that's not
you know what i mean that's not that's not you know what i'm saying
cheeseburger thanks to the seven dollars here's all my biddies i'll
take them thank you uh five tiger thanks for the five
dollars germa facetat thanks for the five dollars
uh scrap shrapnel thanks for the 10 bucks shrapnel
hey germa uh love you thanks for these real talks at the end of the stream
sometimes hearing you say some motivational
things in your way being so much so much to me
hope you have a good night also love all of chat yeah how can you
not love chat i mean when they say fucking boomer you
know you kind of want to like hey thank you shrapnel clink thanks for
the 15 dollars germa isn't going to be the one crying
i am don't cry you don't have to there's there's no you don't have to
cry but thanks for the 15 dollars anyways
clink it's a lot of money uh thank you
shinjo thank you shinji no for the four dollars and 60 cents
been watching since 2012 your stuff has always been a highlight when i
see it i hope you can keep doing this for
the rest of your life because i'll be right there with you
i'm going to do it as long as i can and as long as i'm still having a good
time and as long as i'm still interested
if i'm if i'm still interested you will see me forever
but i have to keep myself interested thank you
i appreciate that the long-term dedicated support there
thank you that means a lot mr shadow man thanks for the 10 bucks hey
germa according to twitch stats you have more subs than top streamers
like tufu and ninja i do not have more subs than
i don't think either one of those i don't i don't think that that's real
whatever website you're looking at it's it is definitely not
correct but uh just search for sub counts
no that's not that's not no no no way
i don't have that many subs number one streamer
no but uh also this first time i've cheered hope it works it worked
mr shadow man thank you for the 10 dollars and uh
thanks for thinking that i've got some of the most subs
on the site but i don't think i do i have a fucking lot though
uh natty thanks for the 15 dollars natty
just a heart no message 15 bucks thank you
steward synod thanks for the five bucks thanks for making
me laugh keep up the good shit thank you steward
clueless sniper thanks for the one dollar germa died and went to heaven
where he receives a never-ending supply of bits
dr stein one dollar hire an actor to be you on stream for five hours no jokes
that's the whole stream even have him end it the same way
we thought about we were in the chat uh in the pre-stream chat like a few
weeks ago and we were coming up with stupid ideas
like that and i think somebody said hire an actor to be you and then it
was like just a british person like a british actor
that looks like me and it's just a full-on like
just english accent except it looks like me it's just a british actor
i'm not even close like why would i even say why would i do that
but that would be funny maybe one day i just come in i like fucking like
like point to a couple things and i leave with like a plate of food
i'm like i'm watching downstairs i'm watching the stream just like hanging
out eating that'd be kind of fun uh riant
delir deliration thanks for the 10 bucks
this is for people who want to donate but can't and then it's a
cheeseburger thank you for the 10 bucks and thank
you for uh paying for people that can't do it
when no one's ever expected to pay which is why stuff like this sometimes
is fucking wild um we don't do this very often i don't just sit here for
like four hours and talk about money and but
when shit like this does happen i just uh
i'm glad you all fucking find it fun to be here ow
my whole hand i went like i put my hand down like this onto like the
spike that's on the desk i mean you kind of do yeah but oh but
but at the end of a stream if i stream for six seven hours
and then we do this then yeah but this stream really has been
a majority of this so you know if i stream for six or seven hours
straight and then there's like an hour or two of this then that's
that's a little different he slapped him why is there a spike
on the desk it's part of my monitor it's something
broke right here and it is like a spike there
but i got like a chest bubble okay uh never trust purple thanks for
twenty dollars never trust purple haven't been around much in the last
few months i've been going through a lot of
upheaval in my personal life and a lot
kind of lost a sense of direction uh sometimes there are so many choices
as to what you can do it's impossible
you just have to pick one and just go and see what happens
that's a great way to put it sometimes just pick one and just go
yeah we're just humans we're just a couple of humans
you don't get that much time right you've got this time
this never stopping always moving thing
try something we're just a couple of humans that's all that is
pop the chest bubble uh rudolph thanks for the one dollar don't you hate it
when a sentence doesn't end how you
they wrote testicles at the end here thank you
thank you lando bando for the one dollar hey i'm back thought you
would be sick of stories of anxiety and stuff
no i don't know sick of those stories no but about a year ago i was
hospitalized for depression and anxiety and the somewhat routine of your
streams has actually really helped me over the past year
currently attending attending a therapeutic school now but your
streams help me forget i'm in a literal
loony bin for my schooling don't think it like that
no don't look at it like that i uh i wish you well hopefully that you can
kind of power through it sounds like you you're doing just that
uh but you know give yourself you give yourself a little credit you know
don't you don't have to don't i wouldn't
classify that classify yourself like that
but any time that you want to hang out here
and if this stream helps you that's more than i could ever ask
i'm very very happy that somebody somewhere in the world gets something
out of these streams thank you take care of yourself and i wish
you the best i good luck on getting through what
you're going through it's not a fucking easy fight but fight it
sir enigma thanks for the five dollars awesome stream awesome streamer
always watch your content on here on youtube and i laugh my ass off thanks
again thanks for five dollars sir enigma
thank you uh let's talk about a 50 dollars that i missed in the in the
chaos of money uh toshi toto shiro toshiro.tv
gave 50 bucks not that long ago they said let's take a minute to talk about
how well germa has aged as a comedian back in your tf2 days you
demonstrated that you had what it took to be an internet personality
and those who recognized it stuck with you and now in a platform that has
so many possibilities for entertainer you've delivered every single bit
back to us tenfold in the form of the finest red blend comedy
i've ever seen you deserve every dollar coming your way here's to you kid
i'm glad you think it's funny because if you didn't
i don't know i'm not sure i would be doing it for as long as i have
you know i'm i'm glad that people fucking think this is fun
i had this like certain idea when i was younger and
you know years a couple years ago three years ago of like what i want to
do how do i want to make this happen
how do i want to continue to move because it wasn't kind of a different
thing right like i went from doing team fortress gameplay commentaries
about like the spy knife to i want to do other stuff like this
is it worth doing will i alienate some people if i say something
fucking like this i don't know but i'm i'm glad that
people think it's fun i think a lot of people go through
that though if you do any type type of doesn't matter what you
do if you're doing something that uses some type of mental energy and
you start to change the way that you do things or
pivot to something else you almost kind of worry about if it was the right call
but i'm glad that people like think it's funny
thank you for the 50 dollars to shiro and the incredible amount of support
thank you spicy cues thanks for the one dollar
dub skew dude thanks for the one dollar i'm currently one dollar in debt
and may have to file for bankruptcy because of it i'm giving you this
dollar to you instead hope you feel awful because you did
this hey novi 333 thanks for the three dollars and 33 cents
hey germa given how generous this community is do you think we could
have a charity night i think we could raise some serious
money to help people in need yeah i've i've thought about charity
nights before and how to run them and how to make them
work i think of uh years ago the once a year you know the tip of
the hats was always something that i wanted to be a part of uh but
probably that is a nice idea yeah i would want to have that logistically
make sense right because uh pretty much like i said
once a year or so i would be part of somebody else's
stream or somebody else's event or charity event and i would kind of go
and or do or show up and promote and um but not nothing just like
personally for me in this stream in this community it's always been
something else or somebody else's uh event but i'll do some research on that
figure what i'd want to do and take a lot of time to research
charities though a lot of actually kind of shady
yeah that's another thing too is it's hard i i'm not the greatest on
trying to pick stuff out like that that's why i've always
felt more comfortable supporting ones that people have already done the
research on so and maybe it would be another
thing where i would just support another one and be on another
event stream or do something like that rather than my own
but i do agree how um how just how generous this community is
it's very very very generous but something to think about for sure
let's move on to thin rue for one dollar hey jerma i used to think i
was useless but then i found out i can draw
porn kind of well kind of find something you're good at
i don't i don't i don't know what you want to tell you we're good
at something and great but that's good that you found
something that you think you that you can do
you know thank you thin rue for the one dollar and good luck
thank you great canadian fuck club for the five dollars if you wear the
same pair of socks for long enough do they become
hard enough to be shoes what what is this what is this twitch thing
with like socks and thank you uh moon thanks for the five dollars
hey jermis want you know my biggest new year's resolution was to catch
more of your streams and while i've failed mostly so far i
am thankful to catch whatever i can you are great in every way that matters
love you glad you can catch some streams if you can't catch streams
there's a couple avenues to catch up with if you if you feel the need to
there is the second channel which has obviously
edited highlights there's the archive channel that is independently run that
i don't have really anything to do with but
is independently uploading archives nobody can make it to every stream
it's a lot of time even like a five six hour stream like this one is going to
be it's a very significant portion of
somebody's day so glad to have you while you're here
thank you uh crazy dude josh thanks for the 15
dollars just want to say thank you for helping me through hard times
i recently started working in a sushi restaurant here in vegas
and just thank you for helping me with your comedy
really i have to pay you a visit i fucking love sushi
go to place go to place no that's awesome
uh that's awesome that's fucking cool you probably i'll probably show up
i'm like i'm you think i'm fucking around and i'm gonna order a bunch of
fucking weird shit i'm gonna be like i want you to take that i want you to
dip in an oil i'm gonna be really like i'm gonna be
like you you're gonna have like one of those fucking las vegas
mcdonald's copy pasta stories about me he's testing you but that's awesome
crazy dude josh thanks for the 15 bucks and eventually maybe maybe i'll take a
trip down to that restaurant thank you so much uh keith thank you
keith ward for the one dollar can i borrow 500 dollars
i i don't i i don't i i don't do loans
and only a little bit more we're almost at the end
ten dollars from damon x thank you for everything germa you're wonderful
funny and inspiring you've helped me laugh in the darkest
moments of my life and i can't thank you enough for that you absolutely deserve
the world sending you love now and always a lot of fucking nice things
people say a lot of nice things to me almost to a point where i i never
want i just don't want ever anyone to ever think that i'm just kind of
trying to power through your messages talking about how
fucking nice you're being to me a ton of people give a lot of money
and say a lot of fucking really nice things
i just hope collectively you understand that it's i
i'm forever grateful forever grateful and there were some new ones that came
in we had shimmy sham for five dollars uh while
we're getting sentimental you're one of the most positive influences in my
life i'd like to revisit old tf2 videos
uh thank you for being such a good boy thank you shimmy sham for the five
dollars and that's that channel is never
going away i i love that channel i love every
video i've made on that channel except for the bottom warfare 3 kill
confirmed 17 and 4 games like commentary and some of the minecraft
videos and some of the grandpa videos that i did
think were very funny and probably um at least four or five
of the let's play videos that i made like one or two episodes of and
have deleted them uh of auto videos um
maybe like 60 videos on that channel that i don't really think of i don't
like five nets at freddy's uh demon lord video yeah that's another one
but for real thank you uh for being around for that long and for enjoying
the videos thank you following snail for the 20
dollars have missed so many of your streams still try to catch the vods
here are some bits for support it's been a lot of that recently
thank you for the 20 dollars and thank you for hanging out and thank
you for catching a stream when you can
really appreciate it that just kind of scared me
that like you didn't even hear it but i heard it
uh thank you thank you uh hunter d for the 10 bucks hey germa you deserve
every penny of what you've gotten tonight
and have changed the lives of many and i hope you keep this up for many more
years thanks for all these memories move means smooth thanks for the 15
dollars i haven't been able to catch much of
the stream tonight but i wanted to thank you for all you do and that you
deserve every penny you're given you're a hard worker and a great guy
i can't even imagine what my life would be like if i hadn't found this
community of great people to get me through
tougher times and to habitually pop in and say
hi to when things are good love you all
and all this wouldn't be possible without you germa take care
no it wouldn't be it wouldn't be possible there's
a ton of people here that just a community doesn't exist without the
community the stream doesn't exist without
the community without people here to watch it doesn't
it's not gonna happen thank you thank you so
goddamn much for everything also thank you to
uh thank you to door cube for the three bucks
uh since we're getting sincere i should mention that just two weeks ago this
semester i can already tell it's gonna be tough
i was late to my second class and my computer science professor spoke
condescendingly to the whole class because none of us were taught a
specific part of coding in the previous course
then when i got home i had to do 20 sketches for my art class
so when i saw you streaming i literally jumped out of my chair and
yelled yes i can't imagine i have that kind of
effect on you and i'm happy i'm happy that you do i'm happy i do
stick with it it can be fucking tough thank you so much for being around
you've been around a long time you've been around for 700 000 years
so thank you door cube uh b e c p n g thanks for the one dollar hey germ i
know tonight's got a lot of feels and it feels like the right time to
say that even as a new viewer i can see you've got something really
special going on here you're a real genuine clown uh you
also just gave that pep talk of the century
i really needed that much love to you also i don't know if you like
sloppy fan art but i made some the other week
sloppy fan art this is fucking beautiful what are you talking about
that's very that's look does it pretty fucking good
that's not sloppy at all that's like the reverse of sloppy
good work and new viewer thank you thanks for somehow stumbling upon the
channel and i'm glad you stayed thank you
beck uh and great art avon star killer thanks
for the one dollar germa i'm a very old fan so we got back to back
you're a new fan and old fan i used to watch your tf3 spy videos i'm
so heartwarming to see you're still making a living off your funny voices
and great attitude i look forward to watching your streams
as an adult like i did as a teen let us view the art wait didn't didn't
post it i i posted it did it not go through
it should have no oh one one guy said that oh okay
uh thank you k-link for the 15 dollars to follow up my original bits
i'm moving to atlanta to look for a new job in a few weeks
and leaving behind all my stuff at my parents house i'm incredibly nervous and
have and i haven't i'm not really looking
forward to it new chapters have a blank page
you already wrote the old one felt the same when i when i moved to vegas i
had my whole life back in massachusetts everything my entire life
was massachusetts the whole thing you got a new page what's that uh
when i did the people flowing when it's instant that's going
this is when where your bit begins the fucking stream is dying that was so
awful that cox just decided to close my
internet off they took emergency measures they like
turn that fucking stream off that is so bad he's embarrassing himself again
turn it off turn his stream off that was genuine shame it was
because i didn't know the lyrics and i just knew that one that one part
but you get the idea cox has got you back
but uh for real when moving anywhere you really just kind of start a new life
for yourself you leave everything behind you start
something new you keep going you gotta you gotta write the book
like i didn't but you know the life book
you gotta write the life book thank you k link for the 15 dollars thank
you uh deaf phyrex for the two dollars
63 cents hey germa this is all the money i got while begging outside on
the subway i hope this helps but for real you're
one of the only streamers that have been able to make
uh writhing that i've been made to writhe in pain from laughter
much love oh are we gonna be good here they're turning me off hey demonic
cucumber thanks for the dollar read your own eulogy i'm not doing that
it's too scary i can't do that that's like that's
like that's except i'm not gonna do i don't like that uh dark
thank you dark angel avon thanks the one dollar germa very old
subscriber yours from youtube i used to watch your countless videos
of tf2 spy tutorials i'm heartwarming to see you're still
surviving off of using why is this i got an like this this popped
up like twice with a different name no it's the same name
yeah what the fuck cocks come on are we good
are we good here uh oh but thank you dark angel uh for the
one dollar there uh thank you vance for the one dollar germa please play
the song uh fig leaf by carbonate from mf doom the
guy in the beginning sounds exactly like you well i might not be able to
huh well anyway you may be saying about now
how in the world is that old mf doom's a great rapper
uh thank you vance thank you mr shadow man for the one dollar not sure if
my early bits went through but it's possibly a large backlog uh
anyways i don't and i don't remember if you said 62 000 or 6200 subs
it's not 62 000 that's not i don't have 62 000 subs
i would be that would be i would be literal like billionaire
that that's like 100 millionaire 62 000 subs is not that high
uh come on cox what the fuck is this uh if not forget i said anything
well uh thank you mr shadow man for the one dollar and
that would be crazy if there were that many people it already is crazy now
but that would be beyond ludicrous uh good luck i found out of you because a
star let me see good buddy of mine uh good
luck and taylor from lifeline better be in the next germa rumble with the
lowest stats accurate representation of her character
end of the stream for two hours i can't ivy cast tv thanks for the
three bucks doing my job saving lives given the
chance thanks for being you and calling me out
ha ha ha they said ha ha calling you out no what
i'm just kidding with you just messing around thank you
ivy cast uh let's see thank you to uh giga meme supreme
for the ten dollars hey germany no it's not bro lock money don't worry you
don't you can't compare yourself that's that's a huge amount of money
to be comparing yourself to uh but i'm watching you stuff for a
long time i want to say thank you for all the happiness you brought us
over the years we love you you fucking dunce thank you giga meme supreme for 10
bucks bro luck money tv table thanks for the
dollar watching you stream for a long time you
don't fail to make me laugh thank you tv table hope to be as
entertaining as you one day that's that's a fucking really nice
thing to say thank you so much uh vance thank you again for the
one dollar this is hilarious it's literally you in the song
well anyway oh that we just heard it
thank you vance uh thank you also too uh we had fly for shy had the 50
dollars unfortunately going through a rough
breakup really sorry really terrible to fucking hear that fly for shy but
thank you again for the 50 dollars uh what else we have we're at the
end we have made it to the end of the
hyper money stream so well not quite
uh thank you to chi way for the three dollars fifty cents
uh love you how much care you put into your work pursue those crazy stream
ideas and get creative oh yeah i also remember that you being
you and having fun is all we could ask for
if you're still reading these i hope your eyes are all right man
geezer or i think he said man geez yeah and we're still going through
the little uh rough internet patch here for some
reason somehow street fighter six hyper money stream
thank you chi thank you also to jess homeboy for the one dollar just came in
here and you say you need to put up the bit limit but really don't want
to show so much you care about interacting with your fans
and it's so touching to hear also the paintings coming along
nicely i'll buy as many bits as i need so i can show you when it's done
it's always that's a it's always a tough decision to make because i
don't want to alienate people from thinking oh well now i'm not going to
give any money i can't give any money
i want to but he's not going to read the thing that i want to tell him you know
what i mean it's a it's a it's a rough place like rock in a
hard place because at one point i don't want to alienate people from
well i can't tell him anything now because now he's
he like sold out and he's like a three or four dollar minimum to say
anything now and it's like i hate that fucking feeling i don't
like that feeling and but on the other hand
you know sometimes the ends of the stream with this many people can
can go on for hours and hours i want everyone to feel like that
a dollar to a thousand dollars that that
i i think that you all fucking matter here you know what i mean it's not
just like well those of you that don't have five
dollars tonight i'm sorry but you can't say shit
i've never liked that but we gotta do what you gotta do
i'm still struggling with the internet here for some strange reason
it's does it doesn't want to work right now
but thank you we will do what what i think needs to be done
i can k-ling thanks for the one dollar congrats on surviving your
genital warts oh that oh okay from the
that's how that was from the year ago stream
that was the thing that from bio inc whatever it was
but thank you for the 10 bucks bro lock thanks for the one dollar hey
mate check the top 10 cheers on the bits leaderboard
yeah can you believe that's what people are willing to give you
i bet never thought clicking that upload button and start stream button
would mean so much to people no never but i'm happy it does
thank you evoip tv thanks for the five bucks been watching you for a long
time you're one of the people who inspired me to start becoming a
content creator and seeing you be so humble like this is exactly the type
of person i want to be if i ever blew up
so keep making the great content good luck to you evoip
it's a it's a it's a tough world in the content creation
landscape i wish you the best stream do what you want have fun and we're still
dropping frames this just kind of came on like that
huh we've been we've been pretty solid for
like a couple months i don't know uh superman thanks for the one dollar
since you've already seen celery man here's another tim and i've seen
pretty much all of them eric where i'm here
oh i've seen them all yeah this is the internet yeah i've watched almost
every tim and eric skit that's ever been done
there are they're very very good they're very funny and they're very
have you never seen it before but eric where i'm here definitely you
definitely need to watch this the internet caught up with the
youtube channel here it comes uh thank you though superman uh do you
needs thanks for the one dollar grapple mace thanks for the four
dollars uh hey germa i was kind of sad today
and watching you cheered me right up as always does
thank you so much we all love you very much thank you grapple mace
i'm currently reading the current bits we did the old ones though
another reason why this this end of the stream has been more than two three
hours is because i pushed the bits from
this morning to now so that's another reason why it's been a
little longer than usual uh but thank you grapple mace uh sick
vic thanks for the two bucks hope this worked my boyfriend introduced
me to your streams and your youtube a while back and i've loved you stuff
ever since keep on trucking thank you i'm gonna
keep going i'm gonna keep trying uh only a few more left thank you
christ vilgen for the ten dollars love you man now that you have
millions of dollars i want to see germa live germa noble life 2
on defo's imdb page i don't know if i'm gonna have that much money
but i really appreciate the ten dollars and it's
that's a it's a good idea uh thank you dark angel avan
for a dollar i'm an old subscriber who used to die laughing watching
chiefs of spy tutorials i'm am i was this what this is
hap this was earlier or i i have no idea what's going on
my brain is like this is there was two
other ones those four bits are the same i was confused i'm sorry skip oh okay
i thought i was like did i am i like read did i read these
but thank you for the four dollars dark angel uh and then you also see
people say people that say youtube and twitch and video games and comedy
isn't worth people's money uh but it's more for a personality
and attitude like yours i aspire to be you
and look up to you as a role model uh you've been a huge influence on my
life that's if really i i can't believe
people see me as a role model i don't know i mean i thank you for
looking up to me i don't know i'm not sure i what
pedestal i i would put myself on i wouldn't
but thank you nonetheless happy to be there
and then a couple more just a couple more
just a few more here we are we got we got palasonic one dollar
missed the stream today looking forward to watching this one on youtube
i just jumped in a lot of people are saying how much you've helped them
mentally it's a great it's great man really warms my heart
you're doing a great fucking thing a lot of entertainers don't do that
i can just i just i just try i can just try
i'm glad that you fucking like here being here i'm happy that you think
it's a lot of fun it's all that matters thank you
dr stein one dollar are you still interested in voice acting not so much
anymore i think like stuff like twitch has
just taken up all of my time so focusing on it completely is
i think more important to me at this point but i still think it's a great
craft i still love it but not anymore i don't think not
currently not now hey mostly lost thanks for the one dollar for real
though i harass you all the time through bits
but you're really such a huge inspiration for everything i do
you're an incredible model of positivity in a world that desperately
needs more of it thanks for everything you do for us
you really do deserve every bit and sub you've ever gotten
tonight and forever thank you mostly lost
thank you lee roy for the five dollars thank you for being such a positive
influence in my life through a crappy high school
an abusive relationship and trying and failing out of college three times
over in the last seven to eight years you
inspire me to never give up in this community it's just a wonderful
wellspring of creative joy much love i mean the one thing here
here's one thing though right tried and failed college three
times three times you're still trying you know
keep trying keep going don't don't give up
thank you so much for the five dollars and thank you for being part of this
community good luck 50 more dollars from the
mick rib is back yo germa man keep up the hustle
peace 50 dollars at the end here thank you mick rib is back for the
50 fucking bucks mick rib is not even back the mick rib
is not even back you're not you're not gonna be able to
get your like piece of mystery meat that got ran over by a car
it's not there but boy is it fucking is it delicious
it's not but for real uh the mick rib is not back oh what the hell
i wanted the mick rib it's my favorite sandwich
it's not there thank you for the 50 dollars though for real discord b thanks
for the one dollar germa i missed you reading my other
bit donation i felt awful about it so i will spend more money
but i'm an old tf2 fan and was a fan ever since is there a way to
private message you if not i understand it just really wanted to know
how much you really helped me through the years i just don't like have any
money for bit donations i'm sorry about that don't
don't apologize for giving me money but
i don't do private message i don't have dms open or anything like that i
don't because it can get overwhelming it can
get very overwhelming and instead of focusing on this stream
and this collective gathering of stuff to do
it's i don't i i don't read i can't it's it's it's it's too much and then
if you know let's say a bunch of people want to talk to me or ask me
things and then i add they i give them a response and then i you
know a couple days go by maybe i don't respond and i'm doing
something else it's just it's too much i can't spread
myself that thin so because i know the kind of person
that i am and that bill bow baggins quote
spreading yourself too thin um like butter on toast
toast ends up being fucking disgusting and you don't want to eat it anymore
gandalf but thank you i really appreciate the
fact that you'd even want to talk to me in the first place
demonic cucumber one dollar it's a meme read the comments
yeah but here okay here's the thing about i don't i don't want to like
brigade a post that just maybe doesn't belong
you know what i mean i can't like officially condone something
that maybe somebody's doing on like a website you know what i mean
that's maybe doesn't necessarily it's just the germa craft uh it's just the
germa craft intro these comments yeah i i don't
because here's the thing i i don't want it's it's that's funny
it is but i also don't want to i i'm not sure what that way if that
website is a um i'm not sure what that website is
i've never really gone to it but i don't want to make
like a funny joke about you know a place where people maybe
put stuff where they lose loved ones and you know i that's
that that doesn't really sit that you know what i mean so i don't
want that to necessarily be something that i say oh yeah
look it out you know i'm saying it's funny in our
it's funny in our context here because we know
we know we're in we have the joke here but
i don't want to cause a problem for somebody else i don't want to cause
an issue or it i like to stay away from that kind of stuff
so it's funny it is funny because like we
like i said we know what it is but you understand
interesting stuff and then finally at the end here we've got
here we go ready last few uh we've got dark angel for one dollar getting
late ps i would love to become an active
streamer like you starting out reading every donations they won't have many
uh fans to begin with as you did transferring from youtube do you think
being a twitch streamer is a stable job with enough stop you right there
i'm gonna stop you right there very important you cannot go into a new
venture like this with the idea of money being there
that's not it is i think that is the absolute wrong way to do this
it's not a stable job it's not something to go into
hey that's what i'm gonna do for work and that's what i'm gonna do for
money that's that's that's a that's not the best attitude to have here
you have to do it and do it because you want to do it because you
want to not because you want something from it you know what i mean
you don't money i'm talking monetarily you
can't go into it thinking it's a job
because it requires other people to watch to for it to become
a job so as long as you have an attitude that's not
there is money but just germa took it all but if you said i was good
at something never do it for free yeah but you can't have that mentality
when you start out if you have a goal a monetary goal
that is let's say a stable income from twitch
you are preparing you are setting you're setting yourself up for
disappointment because if you don't get to that
point that you want to get to that that's a problem because that i
wanted to do this for work but that's not how it works you
you can't go into it like that whatever whoever wants to stream if you want to
be a streamer and you want to be a youtuber
good fucking luck to you i hope you make great content i hope you put out
stuff that you're proud of that you think is interesting
but you can't go into it with the mindset of this is my job
and i'm gonna do this for money it's i think it's it's it's an attitude
you have to leave at the door bro luck money but good luck uh
oogla goob thanks for three bucks not so fast jeremy one more you deserve all
the love there's more than one there's more
than one more three dollars though thank you uh
netscape navigator that's an old one thanks for five dollars netscape
i used you back in 1995 uh carlos the clan thanks for six
dollars i've given you 30 bucks this week and i'm a third of the way to
get in the leaderboard but seriously love you jeremy love my
gloom and t-shirt thank you i love it too i think it's a
great shirt it's one of my favorite shirts ancient meme in the chat uh atos
thanks for the one dollar you ever gonna stream
my lethal league germa mod yeah i was gonna do like a game night thing
there's so much other stuff that just started happening uh that's
it'll i probably i was gonna make like a discord channel too
it's talking about spreading the butter you know what i mean that's what
i'm talking spreading the butter you gotta have just a pat of butter on
the pancake uh eventually there's something i do
want to do so yes but thank you for making that thank you
for the one dollar i look forward to seeing you again soon
he's still in streamo lando honey chain thanks for the one dollar hey
germa ever since since everyone's doing it i want to take a minute to say
how much i appreciate you you've been a bright spot during dark
times thank you oh speaking of speaking of
no it's good we're good we're good just buy more butter
uh i'm vinnie just kidding thanks for the two bucks love you dad
thanks a lot son uh eight dollars from joe zilla i realized you would die one
day and i got really sad uh well i've got i've got some news for
you here and i happen to everybody eventually
but live the life you have now and take care of those that you love
and do as best you can that's all you can do but thank you for the
eight dollars thank you chino for the one dollar joel said
he'd like to do a vine wrestle germa rumble collab with you someday
would you oh and he would get destroyed think of the fucking german universe
you got glue man you've got dr roker oh it would be it would be a no contest
they'd be getting thrown over the fucking ropes yeah that'd be fun
i think that'd be fun maybe we'll figure that out uh yep so five dollars
thank you yep so hey what's up this vaude gang
thanks for the hours and hours of content for my degenerate
active hours thanks germa thank you yep so
and i changed get your sleep schedule fixed is that that's what you mean
thank you huge man thanks for the one dollar love you germa been watching you
for a long ass time first time watching you live
and had to slam a donation your way thank you so much
bingo sunshine five dollars hey germa can
can can i what that's it it cuts off there
maybe we'll see later hey cas cas tv thanks for two dollars
it's absolutely wild to me to see this amazing community consistently be
on the verge of clearing out their bank accounts
to come and support you uh loving me and we all do wear the
support beams with the great tower you built
yeah it's a very very very strong foundation
one that i am immensely proud of so thank you all of you
you've all you've all done so much how do you guys have this much money
where where is this money from uh thank you chicky for the one dollar you
and star were a huge part of my childhood and i want to thank you for
that thank you for watching sure he would say the same thing
anti tau on thanks for the one dollar wish i could say more but for now thank
you for doing what you do thank you uh something or other thanks
for the one dollar yo germs good to see you're still kicking
still am for now you know because eventually
like i said before you got this you got like everyone has like 185 years
can you imagine like in the future are people going to live to be like
500 in like 100 years you know no no i'm saying like the
people that are born in 100 years are they going to live to be a 500
maybe depends uh but dio needs thanks to the one dollar hello from sydney
hello from las vegas nevada bingo sunshine five dollars very end
flat finger the last one watched your videos for years and years has brought
me and my brother closer together and eventually my wife came
around as a big fan you're awesome rats rats motherfucker
bringing family together that's fucking amazing thank you
something about the family one like that something i don't know something
about the family one thank you so much bingo sunshine and
then finally here let's what no that's old right
it's almost in three and a half hours of fucking like ridiculous hyper
money support like do you understand let me put the
credits on because there's a ton of subscribers
too many to count more than i will ever be able to count
take a look at this do it again the software counts for you but that's
what i'm saying i would never be able to count
i wouldn't be able to jesus thank you uh g-a-g-y-h-d-gid
hefei that's what i'm gonna call you 50 dollars
hey germ i think you missed my hundred all the bits during those bro
like hundred thousand donations but don't worry i'll repeat the
question what's your fetishes is it is this a is this a uh
i'm not sure this is the place to discuss that
what hey twitch.tv germa985 let's talk about sex
no that's no no no no no no no thank you for the fucking huge amount of
money and bro luck thanks for the dollar how
does it feel that your most profitable stream was a fucking talking game
it could be any stream and it would be like i can't fucking believe it
huge man thanks for the one dollar germa just donated before don't know
if you missed out or not but thanks for the laughs over the years you
better keep the hustle up i'm gonna thank you all so much
that's the end of the stream that's the end of the
long long list of money and subs it's been the the i know some people may
have trickled in here and just probably had no idea what was going on
and they were like what the fuck is going on here what does it get doing
long story short i mean it's just an insanely supportive community
of tons of generous fucking people that all
collectively build up the tower like somebody said
i wish you all the best thank you for continuing to put
support beams down for this channel couldn't do it without you i could not
do this without everybody fucking here thanks for watching the end of uh
lifeline a little while ago we had more community subs come in five from
mr space i think we had others too yeah mr space
gave mr space gave 10 community subs
holy shit i'll see you guys on friday take care of yourselves and thanks for
continuing to be a part of this fucking stream have a great
night i'm gonna get friday prepared and we'll have fun on friday too don't
worry until then good night it's the wrong
button that's the right button see you all very soon