Hey, what is going on everybody? Jiruma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary.
And tonight, gonna be playing as the Pyro with the default flamethrower, the reserve shooter of all things, and the extinguisher.
And tonight, gonna do just a casual commentary, sitting back relaxing, gonna talk about a couple things that happened on the screen,
And, most importantly, we're gonna talk about the super snowstorm that's on its way here tomorrow afternoon.
If you're from the northeast of the United States, you probably already know this.
We're gonna get hammered tomorrow with snow. We're probably gonna get like two feet of snow in Boston.
So I assume my front door is not gonna be able to open. It's gonna be completely blocked from the outside with snow.
And, you know, whatever. I might actually do a stream during this whole thing, like a snowed-in stream.
We'll see if that happens or not. I don't know. I might lose power, too.
So if you don't see a video here in the next couple days, it's because my house is under snow and we can't get out.
And please send help! It actually kind of reminds me.
Back when I was younger, I know a lot of you guys are pretty young.
Some of you guys are even under the age of 16, 15 years old.
So you'll be able to relate to this when I talk about this.
But snow days, back when I was a younger kid, snow days were like the best thing on planet Earth.
I would pray to all the gods that existed to get a snow day.
I remember me, my brother, and my sister just huddling around the TV at our local news station,
waiting to see our school's name pop up and have it say, closed.
Because by God, if it said two-hour delay or one-hour delay, a vase would go across the room and smash into the wall.
That's the worst possible outcome of having snow come down, because you still have to go to school.
It's just a tease. It's almost like the board of directors at the school was like,
you know, how can we screw with these kids?
I know. How about a two-hour delay?
That's what I picture when I think of the board of directors of a school system.
But the point still stands. It's a tease. Maybe you get an extra 45 minutes of sleep.
Oh, cool. You still got to get up and go to math class. It sucks.
And the town next over, the town next over maybe doesn't even have school, so it's even worse.
That's happened to me so many times.
When I see my list, my school come up with a one-hour delay, and the next town over, they don't have school.
And they can do whatever they want. They can throw snowballs at old man Whitless' house,
have him come out and yell at him, everybody laughs and runs away.
I don't get to experience that on that day, and it sucks, because I want to do that too.
But that's going to wrap up talking about the snow storm coming in.
Again, I might try to livestream tomorrow night or tomorrow evening,
and maybe I can get like a webcam to show outside how much snow is actually on the ground.
I don't know, maybe I'll do something like that. The stream might not even turn on.
I'm not going to guarantee I'm going to do this tomorrow, because like I said, I might be out of power.
But anyways, we're going to move on now and talk about some stuff in the gameplay.
Most notably, the fact that I'm using the reserve shooter for the first time in a long time,
and I've been having way more luck with this thing.
I can't seem to use the flare gun like I used to anymore, trying to time those crits, trying to time those hits.
It's way easier to just blow somebody in the air and get that guaranteed hit scan shot right on their body.
I've been able to do that a lot more frequently than I used to.
Also, for the new subscribers that have never seen me use the reserve shooter before,
the reason why I'm not using the degreaser with this thing is I feel like the 15% that you get with the reserve shooter is enough.
I feel like it's just about enough to land at least one good shot on somebody.
And with the degreaser equipped, it's such an instant switch that it really screws up my head,
and I cannot get the plants that I want to plant, and I just shoot around wildly, it seems.
I miss every single shot, because I'm too focused on the switch.
The switch happens, and I'm almost not ready for it.
It's almost like I'm sitting there, and we're like, okay, time to switch the gun.
And the animation doesn't even happen.
When you have the degreaser and the reserve shooter, there's no animation.
It almost looks like the game glitches out, because it switches so damn fast.
But that's the reason why I don't use the degreaser with this thing.
I always have the default on with the reserve shooter.
One tip I will give you with the reserve shooter, and I've actually gone against this tip multiple times in this gameplay already,
but it's when you blow somebody in the air, try not to shoot them more than once or twice,
because you only have three rounds or three shots in this thing, so you have to reload it very, very frequently.
And if you miss one or two times, you are screwed.
You do not have any more bullets in your secondary.
All you can really do is light them on fire or hope you can load more shots in before they kill you.
So make sure when you blow somebody in the air again, try to land just one shot before they come down again,
because again, you can blow them in the air again.
Once they land, blow them in the air again, shoot the second shot.
That's pretty much how you should be using this weapon.
But that is going to wrap up the video, guys.
Thank you all so much for watching. I really do appreciate it.
And I'll see you guys all next time.
Again, maybe look for a live stream tomorrow afternoon.
Weather permitting, I guess.
So I'll see you guys all next time, and of course, take care, everybody.