I don't even know. No, we're gonna do is we're gonna the video has to start with us doing the crazy frog theme song
You know how it goes? Doh, doh, doh, doh, doh. No, no, it goes
Ding ding so yeah when I say ding ding you have to say ding ding as well, okay
Do it again
You fucked it up. Hold on see so stand up. So you so Joe. Hold on. Let me just get the
So which one even which one am I?
How do you move
Which one is who I'm the one on the left so why am I just
Like the fucking living room. I don't know stand up
Oh wait, this is like another room. Oh, you're just sort of a beach ball. I pick you up. I don't think so
Let's go. Okay this way. It says this way
Alright, where are you? I don't know. I'm dead. Oh, we were actually like gonna play the game now. I want to get the cannon
No, I want to get in the cannon. No, I'm getting the cannon
Again
I'm in it. Oh, how'd you you just go in the front of it? I guess I jump
Can I like just shoot you guys? No, I feel like if I jump we're just never gonna find each other again. Oh
God stand in front of it
I'd love to
By the way, the doors are not closed. That's a jump. That's a jump. That's a jump. That is a jump. Do it
Oh
There's like actual car damage look at this thing Wow, what I picked up
Hey, I've got some for you
Look, I'm the car
You're the car. I'm the car. I'm the real one. I just want to pick this up and remember what the throw button even was
What did he do there
What was the point of that?
That guy sirs just walked into me. He's looking he's doing it again. This guy's a fucking idiot
Here take this car door and you'd go to hell. Where are we going? I don't know
Oh, okay. We're gonna have to try to get on. Okay. I got a plan. We're gonna stack these boxes
What the fuck?
What?
Are you dead? I am I dead?
There's life in him yet
Boombox
Jumpy house when you get over here, we're gonna listen to some rockin tunes and we're gonna rock out in the jumpy house
I hope you're ready. I'm
You just realized that I'm just realizing right now this is really fucking stupid
We're just fighting all over each other with this stupid song in this bouncy house. Oh, it's going from left to right. You're so bad
One second, it's oh god
So if I score one point on you, then I'm the master. Okay
I'm the master of the basketball. Okay, which which one are you gonna score in the one that's behind you?
I if I score on the one behind you then I win. Okay. Yes, and if I score on you I win
Yes, if you score on me with the dumpster then
As a gun you just got the most excited I've ever seen in my life
Is a fucking gun on the ground?
First jump, okay
Are you serious? What is going on?
What?
No, I'm just throwing it good give me the gun it's running away
This music is so loud
This is the loudest thing ever
The playground don't really flip this already. Okay, I see the play if you can spin me on one of these things
So that you went to the right?
No, no, no get that box out here throw that boombox in the dumpster
thing as far away as possible
I don't want to do with any of that slowly slowly
Down the slide just walk down it. No, I want to slide down the fucking slide
This doesn't look that hard. It is trust me. It is. There we go. Just wiggle on to it. There we go. Come on
harder
Harder
And you come in butter so we can get out it
I
Breaking this look it's dented. There's a dent in this bus. You're really like messing it up
We like fucked up that bus
Can you get in here can you I'm gonna push you
Are you gonna push me up?
My body was doing all kinds of you get in the bus. Hold on inside the bush
I
Figured two people would be better to fight that. Oh, so you can't can you not even can you get not get hurt?
No, it's just a mosh pit
I can't get out. I can't get out. I'm out. I can't get out. I don't even know where I am
You just mash up just mash jump get in the mosh pit play some heavy metal
They're all going on top of one person. This is Katamari. Yeah, it really is
They're like farting people like shitting on each other. What the hell is going on?
you