720p for the win. Starting in 15 minutes. Exactly. Let's do it. Alright, ladies and germs.
And let us go into a new server. Let's try and see how many people are in my server right now.
My server is currently full, but it's okay. We can fill up an empty one.
Just because that's what I typically do anyways. So let's fill up an empty server.
Just because I feel like a lot of you guys would rather be able to see where we're playing and you guys in the stream would like to play.
So here is the IP. If you can see it on the screen, I'm also going to put it in here.
It's going to be... Oh god, I have a lot of tight balls in that statement.
And there you go. Posting it right now.
Funda Mountain.
Germany needs a catchphrase like Chibi's chocolate sauce.
How long am I going to be streaming Diablo 3?
At least a couple hours. At least.
At least that.
Oh, and is the stream running okay? There's a 360 and a 720 option.
Are both of them looking okay? Or is it... How does it look? Are we good?
Hopefully we're good.
Because this is the first time I've ever streamed in 720 and I think the test went...
The test went okay. I don't know if it's perfect, but it should be better than before.
Let's watch the...
And while I think about it, let me turn up my fans here.
How is that even possible?
Diablo 3 looks... Oh no, Diablo 3 is fun, man.
I got a lot of problems I have with it, but they are overshadowed by the fact that the game is really good.
So I can't really complain.
I have a major, major problem with it though, and it's something I can't get over.
I'll probably talk about it in...
The video I do when I review the game.
When I actually review the game, I will talk about it.
Where is everybody?
Somebody want to post the IP again? In the chat?
Oh, make sure, if you haven't already done it, select update automatically.
For your stream thing on the chat window.
Yah, yah.
It's going to be 1v1. There's a lot of spots in this server.
I'll do this, so you guys can see.
Because maybe the chat is lagging or something.
This is the server.
63.146.183.23.27015.
If you take a look at it right now, write it down maybe.
That's where we're going to be for a little while.
And hopefully you guys got it by now, so I'm going to close it, and here we go.
The only problem with Diablo 3 is the constant...
That's another thing that's kind of shaky in my opinion as well.
What's up, ZCS? How you doing, bro?
The combat is incredible though.
It is one of the most satisfying combat games.
At least action RPG combat games ever played.
Playing a barbarian if you didn't see the video.
Man, what's going on? Is this...
Are we getting like a crash or something? No one's really joining.
What is going on with this server?
People should be able to join.
Yah, I'll go online. That makes more sense.
Alright, you can join off me.
You can join off me.
You can, and in fact will join off me.
Yah, I gotta go over to Twitch and say it's not going to be there.
The only reason why it's not on Twitch is because I wanted 720.
And I don't have a partnership with Twitch.
I never plan on really getting a partnership because I of course have a machinima contract with live streaming, so...
I need to utilize it a little bit.
Can somebody do me a favor?
One of the mods I have in my typical Twitch stream.
Can somebody go over there and just tell them that the stream is over here?
Because my window is currently closed.
How?
Yah, I'll...
Somebody please go over there.
Streaming on the YouTubes.
I'm going to be streaming for a long time, so...
People will figure it out sooner or later I guess, right?
I'll probably be streaming for maybe half an hour, maybe 20 minutes.
Couple of rounds. I want to get a couple of good rounds though, that's the most important thing.
Let me get this thing rolling now.
Let's not tryharden as a scout.
Let's get this rolling. Here we go.
Nah, I mean Diablo 3 is taking over the streams.
By a large margin.
Well when I say taking over, I don't mean like...
It's not like taking over, but...
I got a bob. Bobarian.
Oh! Oh god.
Speaking of jag, I'm getting lag.
What rhymes with jag?
Oh, you see that? I threw the milk and it didn't even come out of my hand.
Oh, let's go.
Candy cake.
Yah, TwitchTV has a better chat system.
But this is 720.
And no, I just wanted my Diablo 3 videos to be in 720.
For the most part at least.
Oh!
Oh, where you going? Where you going?
Nah, we're doing it. Nah, we're doing it.
Oh!
That was like a goomba stomp with the scouter gun. You guys see that?
Ow.
Jerma, killer of steam, is back.
Yeah, it's not a...
Everyone's pings look okay.
I think it's the server we're on.
Yeah, it's definitely too many people at the same time.
Hey, we gotta stop it.
Damn.
I can see the YouTube comments. I have a little pop-up window that comes up where I can see whatever you guys are saying.
Say something in this video that could become a real viral saying.
Umm...
I want Burger Boy to go viral.
I want Burger Boy's entire presence to be viral.
But I don't know if that'll ever happen.
Yes, this will all be uploaded to YouTube. Probably tomorrow afternoon.
Oh, God.
That lag.
Alright, I'm gonna appear offline now.
I think it's just too many people trying to join at the same time.
But yes, Burger Boy 2012.
Actually, no, let me rephrase that. It's Burger Boy 2012.
Emperor of Earth.
That's the hashtag.
Alright, let's see if we can get a good string of non-lag here.
God, they're gonna push it. We're dead.
No, this is not good.
That's a dead ring for sure.
We all okay up there?
You are a spy.
We don't have a medic, do we? I might have to go medic.
Germa, say...what do you want me to say?
Alpha...I missed it. Alpha something, something, something.
God, that's such a laggy shot. I shot him five seconds later he got hit.
Oh, God. Oh, God.
Oh, God, I'm dead.
Oh, my word.
I'm watching Germa and eating brownies.
Brownies are good, man. I love brownies.
So, if Burger Boy was president of the United States of America,
what do you think his first legislature would be?
Spy over here. I just saw him.
Oh, no, is it soldier actually?
That guy just floated.
So, reserve shooter is becoming my default.
I love this thing.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, God, this is bad.
He's gonna kill me.
God, give me the health.
Oh, good spy, good spy.
Good backstab.
Oh, good medic, good medic.
Oh, heal me, help me.
Oh, I'm gonna die.
Too many things going on at the same time.
Do some market gardening.
I'm so bad with the market gardener. I'm terrible.
Me, market gardening is like...
I'd rather watch paint dry. I'm terrible. I'm like so bad.
Stand on the freaking point, you moron. Stand on it.
I didn't get the kill, did I?
Oh, shoot it at me again.
Damn.
Where's grandpa?
Grandpa, you want me to get him?
I'll get grandpa after this round.
The heavy.
That would be the heavy.
Oh, random crits. Ow.
My body.
Gamer class is engineer.
I haven't been playing a whole lot of engineer though.
I've not been playing really any engineer.
I don't know why either.
And we're gonna lose the game.
I'm ready. People are gonna walk right by me. Watch this.
People are gonna walk right by me.
Hey.
Oh my god.
That kill feed.
Oh, so by the way, those of you that were at the stream a couple weeks ago,
during the whole debacle where people can see through the backpack, the game show event,
I wanted to clarify that Optimus Prime, he could see the backpack,
and he wanted to make sure that it didn't get stolen,
because he's obviously a mod on the stream.
Optimus Prime is not a thief.
Oh god, I'm lagging.
He is not a thief.
He did that in the merits of his own heart to try and protect the unusual hat.
Oh my god, I can't even walk.
Yeah, I can't even walk either. What the hell is going on?
Maybe if we all crouch, the lag will go away.
If you're wondering, I am working on a new solution
to figure out how to do another stream like that and have it work.
I mean, it worked. It was okay after the first 15 or 20 minutes,
but there were a lot of issues, and I will figure them out.
And I'm gonna get overcharged right out the gate, and I'm gonna mess something up here.
I'm gonna be like Sir Derpington.
When you hit this on me, if you're gonna hit it on me...
Actually, don't do it yet. Sit right here.
Sit right here. We're gonna hide.
We're gonna hide right here.
We're gonna eat cookies and pancakes until they come out.
No, no, hold it. Hold it. Hold it.
Okay, go! Woohoo!
Oh dear god.
Oh, how is he not dead?
How many Ubers did we just have out the gate? You kidding me?
That was like... Holy crap, that was a lot of people.
Soup can!
Oh god.
So after this round, I'm probably gonna move on to my own server,
because it's just like chaos.
I think too many people are trying to connect at the same time.
What is it?
Every time I hear... Let me tell you...
Agree in the comments if you agree with this.
So every time I hear the ambassador shot,
that like boom, boom, I always think it's not on our team.
Oh my god.
I like broke his legs.
Oh, this is gonna be bad. Bad news for everybody on the cot.
Oh, good backstab. Good backstab.
Come at you.
Oh god!
Hide.
He's still alive. He's right here.
Oh, dead ring and bastard.
Well, that was... Okay.
Ugh!
Don't let him get away!
He's gonna get away.
Oh god, it's like lagging all over the place.
Alright.
Run!
Run away!
Alright.
Now they think we're running away?
Oh god.
No!
Hey, it was a good run.
It was a good run.
Ambassador.
Or backstab too.
Whenever I hear the backstab sound, that...
I always go...
I freak out and I turn around and look around all over the place.
And he spies over there.
Oh god, spam everywhere.
What just happened?
Did I kill that guy?
What?
Oh, Optimus Prime backstabbed him. Okay.
Oh, you need one more shot and you're dead.
No, get out of my face!
Ugh!
Thank you.
For healing me.
That's a spy.
That's definitely a spy.
Aw, I'm trying to reflect it.
Get this help over here, bro.
There you go, buddy.
Oh, they know we're in here. This is not good.
That's a spy.
No, it's not.
Oh lord!
Oh no.
Uber charge.
Oh, just die.
No, just...
Die!
All I cared about was killing that guy and I didn't even get him.
Aw, damn.
Aw, at least I got the pyro.
At least I got the pyro.
Let's go, let's go sniper.
He'll never get me.
Spy.
Sappin Mountain Spencer.
Favorite weapon in Team Fortress 2?
Probably... uh-oh.
Let us take a moment to mourn the loss of this sniper.
He was a good man and all he wanted to do was just snipe
and kill and melee.
I was actually hoping I was gonna get backstabbed.
That was like the whole point there.
I was hoping I was gonna get backstabbed.
Fire, fire, fire.
I just heard it.
Where is he?
Ah, I thought I was gonna run into that.
Oh god, they're everywhere.
Oh, get away from me.
Crush him, crush him.
Strategy that I never really talk about is the freak out melee.
It actually works more times than you'd think.
Oh god.
Ow.
Hello.
Hold on, that came from Optimus Prime.
What the hell was that?
Optimus Prime just like morphed into a woman for a minute there.
Yeah.
Did you?
You son of a... you bastard.
Oh, I thought that was actually a spy.
That was funny.
You ducked from my arrow.
Ah.
Kill him.
Chaos.
Ah.
I lost.
I lose.
He's been a woman the whole time.
Where am I?
I'm actually not doing too terribly.
For as laggy as this is being.
Doctor!
Don't worry.
Oh my god.
Oh god.
It is so scary when I just bump into spies.
Then I bump into a second one.
Give me a headshot.
I refuse to put this thing away until I get a headshot.
Come on.
Aw.
Damn.
Alright, you want the Boston Basher on there?
I don't even think I have it.
No, I don't even have the Boston Basher.
I don't even have the Boston Basher.
I'm not used to it.
Oh my word.
Wait a second.
I just shot by him.
And killed the spy that was behind him.
Alright, there we go.
That's three.
Let me get a quad.
No, no, no, no.
Damn.
I just freaked out right there.
Medic.
Freak out, smash.
It always works.
I told you.
As long as you just freak out.
If you freak the hell out and start swinging at somebody, you probably will kill him.
Oh, that's a crit screen.
Chaos.
It's going to be, it's going to work.
When all else fails.
Chaos.
Smash.
When all else fails.
Chaos.
Smash.
No, no, hear me.
What's up, potato fryer?
How you doing, my man?
You can't beat the chaos.
Smash.
Alright, one more, one more little life here with this huntsman.
And wait, is somebody on the cart?
Going up top.
I'm going up top.
Yeah.
Just shoot down this hallway, man.
I'll kill somebody.
I'm bumping into a spy, too.
I don't have Jurati.
There he is.
Oh, god.
What?
How many spies do they have on their team?
Alright, I think I'm going to try.
See, here's like the big joke.
See, listen to this, ready?
So my server is full right now, right?
And I can't even get into it.
I have reserve slots set up for myself, but apparently it doesn't work.
I guess not.
So I'm going to try and do this again and see if it works.
And let's see what happens.
Yeah, see, server is full.
I have a reserve slot.
I'm probably doing it wrong.
Who knows?
But I'm changing servers.
We're going to go somewhere else.
I would go in my server, but there's no way I'm going to get in.
I can't even get into my own server.
No, this is like, I'm knocking on the door to my own house.
And there's like a party going on in my house.
That's pretty much the equivalent of this.
There is like a crazy party going on in my house right now.
They're like breaking vases.
Somebody's like puking in the bathroom.
And I'm outside just staring at the house.
That's pretty much what's going on.
I can't get it.
Wait, I can't get it.
Wait, connect, you rip?
What is that?
Oh, your IP.
Yeah, I just tried it.
I don't know.
I have it set up.
It doesn't work.
I'll try it one more time.
Ready?
Connect.
Here's the IP.
Server is full.
And I have a reserve slot.
I don't want to be a jerk.
That's my own fault for not having it set up right.
Party at Jerma's, but he's not invited.
I'm not invited to my own party.
Oh, I want to check something.
I got to drop that down.
I do play on Shibby's server.
I mean, now that I have my server, I kind of...
I try to stay on that as much as I can.
Who's on here?
Is anybody on there that I know?
Nope.
All right, new server.
So what's going to happen now is because my house is full of people at a party.
We're going to go to somebody else's house that is not having a party right now.
So let's go.
Let's see.
No, not RTD.
After this, I'm probably going to play some Diablo 3.
So here's the IP.
If somebody wants to paste that into the chat, it's right there.
Because if I do it, it's going to get swarmed.
So post that into the chat.
By the way, turn on automatic updates for the chat.
That'll help it with the reload time.
But that is the IP.
If somebody want to link that, I would be appreciated.
I would be appreciative, not appreciated.
I bet you Burger Boy the dump machine is there.
Oh, yeah, I forgot.
Let me get Grandpa.
Hold on.
Hey, yo, Grandpa.
Get down here.
We want to talk to you.
Who wants to talk to me?
Let me sit here.
Sit down.
I'm sitting.
I told you I'm already sitting.
Okay.
All right.
It's question and answer time with Grandpa.
So what do you want to ask me?
In the comment section, make sure you ask a good question,
or I'm going to punch you in the face,
and you're going to bleed.
Let's play some Red Team.
Wait, how come I'm not invited to the party?
Where's there a party?
Who didn't invite me to the party?
I'm the best son of a bitch here.
I'm going to play engineer for a second here.
Put this down.
Put it right here against the wall.
Because you never know, there could be a spy
that's going to come around this corner here
and try and get the spawn.
So I'm going to put that at the spawn door
to make sure no spies get it.
What the hell is going on with this lag?
Oh!
What the hell is going on here?
This is the laggiest piece of crap server
I've ever played out of my entire life.
Oh!
How old am I?
Somebody want to know how old I am?
I am...
You'll never know.
You're never going to find out how old I am.
Let me get this century...
Help me get this century to level three.
While the lags...
While the server lags out.
What?
How does that actually work?
Oh, he's right there.
Get him.
You want me to high five you?
You're not getting a high five from me.
Well, my birthday is June 15th, 1918.
So if you can figure that out for yourself, go ahead.
What is this game?
Why is it even happening?
Where do I go?
I don't even know where to go in this game.
I just know you build a century here to protect the spawn
from those bastard spies.
And I'm thirsty, too.
What the hell is on this guy's head?
What is that?
You look like a freaking Nordic god or something.
Get away from me.
You're freaking me out.
All right, well, this server lags too much.
So I'll pull this over here.
And he's going to...
Right here is a good spot for the century.
Century going up over here, boys.
It's a good spot for it.
And then the dispenser is going to go, like, over here.
Ah!
Suspect, you're going to go right there.
And then the century shoot people.
And I'm lagging out way too bad.
This is the worst server ever.
Do I get all the bitches?
Yes.
Absolutely yes.
You might think because I'm old, I don't have any, uh...
I don't have any Lubino left,
but you'd be totally wrong when you put that statement.
So if I kill two people, then I leave.
And I've already killed one, so let's get another kill.
Come on.
What are you...
Get out of here!
You're making me show up on the radar.
This is like Modern Warfare, right?
The more you shoot, the more you show up on the radar, right?
Where is the radar?
What are you two doing?
Go fight the battle!
You guys need to fight the war!
What are you doing hitting the thing around here?
Somebody challenge you to a duel.
What is that?
What's that do?
Second kill!
I got a second kill.
That means I can leave and put this century down here
for a suicide century.
There we go.
This is the best part of the game right here.
This is where you get all the kills.
Come at me!
Somebody come at me!
Look at this century doing work.
You're a F-U-C-K-I-N-G spy.
I'm not allowed to swear on these streams.
Jeremy told me I'd get in trouble, so I can't do that.
Grandpa, have you ever gone to the bathroom two times a day before?
Yes.
I actually go to the bathroom...
What's going on?
What's going on with that century gun?
Yeah, look out for that bastard spy.
He's a Frenchman.
All Frenchmen are bastards.
We all know that.
They're all sneaky, and they steal your stuff,
and they love your women.
What the hell just happened?
What just happened to me?
Oh, I'm out of here.
I'm getting the fuck out of here.
This game sucks.
Not playing this game again, Jeremy.
You need to go take a nap, anyways.
You've been up a little too long.
You've been up a little too long, Grandpa.
Somebody keeps repairing that century, by the way.
I didn't even know I was in a duel.
I think you're a spy, but I could...
Yeah, I was right.
I was right.
I was right all along,
and I cannot land a shot to save my life right now.
There you go.
Are you a spy?
No, but I'll high-five you anyways.
Yeah.
Whoa.
How did he even get me?
I was too busy choking on my own throat.
Is the lag in the game unbearable to watch in the stream,
or is it okay?
How does it look in the actual stream window?
Oh, my God.
Chaos.
Remember what I taught you guys.
Unlapped.
I'm just going to go wrench.
I'm just going to wrench people in the face.
That's all I'm going to do.
There's a guy right here.
I'm not going to get that scout, ever.
Ugh.
I'm waiting.
I'm waiting for someone to jump over here
so I can just...
I'm going to freak somebody out.
Ready?
Let's do this.
I want someone to walk out and land on this.
Oh, my God.
Ugh.
It's coward killing time.
I am a derpington.
I really am.
Whenever I do these live streams,
my brain shuts off,
because I'm looking at the chat talking,
and I'm doing like...
Like, where's your head?
I feel like I just bought the game.
Bring back those memories.
Let's get this sentry up.
At least a little bit.
I'm not even protecting it.
I'm just running away from it
every time it goes up.
There we go.
I really do think...
If you're watching this on YouTube right now,
did I get more melee kills
than...
Are you serious?
I'm getting...
I don't think I've killed anybody
with anything else besides melee
this entire time.
Maybe I killed, like,
four people with the Huntsman.
Did I kill anybody
with anything else besides melee?
Medic!
Why am I not streaming on Twitch?
Because...
I can't do 720 on Twitch.
And we're lagging again.
So I'm gonna disconnect from this server.
So I'm gonna go on a random server
so that nobody can see the IP,
because I think what the problem
is happening right now
is we keep on crashing servers out,
because too many people are getting the IP.
So let's just go to...
I'm gonna take it off screen.
I'm gonna take it off of this screen.
What's going on here?
Let's see.
Let's find a map I like.
We'll play in some gravel pit.
No, we won't. Yes, we will.
What is that hat with the Eiffel Tower?
We are all highly intrigued.
And I looked, I can't find it in the store.
Oh, yeah, the...
Eiffel Tower hat from Kritzkast.
If you don't know Kritzkast,
it's a Team Fortress 2 podcast they do every week.
And every week they give out Player of the Week.
And I guess it's like a thing they do
where they find somebody that's doing
a lot of cool stuff,
or they're doing well, or something with competitive.
I'm not really exactly sure.
But I do know they give it out pretty much
every week, I think, to somebody else.
And I happen to get Player of the Week,
which that's awesome, and thank you to the Kritzkast guys
if you're watching this or if you're seeing this at some point.
Thank you for that, I much appreciate it,
that's awesome, thank you so much.
But that's where that hat came from, it's from the Kritzkast guys.
Alright, let's go to...
Gold Rush, this one, whatever it is.
Yeah, I want to get at least one
good non-laggy Team Fortress 2 game.
And it seems like every time we're...
I don't know, recently I don't know what's been going on.
Every time it's been...
The streams from a long time ago,
I've been doing streams for the last
four or five months. I've never seen
this problem before, and I used to give out IPs
like crazy. We would always just flood a server
and that stuff would never happen.
So I'm wondering, I'm wondering if something else is going on.
Who knows? But
I'm going to try and play a little bit of one more session
here with the...
Demoman.
I am appearing offline.
So I don't want to kill this person's
server. Thank you, doctor.
I've got my strange lock and load.
Oh, I thought he was going to back up into that.
Whoa, just barely.
Just barely.
Oh, I didn't get him. Almost got him.
Oh my god, I just barely dodged that crit rocket.
There's a sentry right there.
Oh, and
goodbye, sentry.
Oh, I'm going to be in trouble.
I need that medic, there's still stuff over there.
What happened to that medic?
Oh god.
I hate when that happens.
Bumped right into him,
shot him right in the face, instantly blew up myself.
I do that far too often,
by the way.
I do that more often than not.
Alright, let's go. I want to kill
at least ten people in a row.
Doctor.
No!
I saved him.
Oh my god, more spies!
Oh, that's crit, someone's going to walk over that.
Someone's going to walk over that.
I don't feel bad for them.
Oh, this is not good.
I forgot I had this equipped.
It's fine, that's fine. Oh, great.
Come on, somebody walk over here.
Somebody touch that cart.
There he is. Oh, I thought I was going to blow somebody up.
Let's see, let's see if I can't ambush
somebody. Come on,
you coming? Oh, okay, okay, we got a medic, we got a medic,
we got a medic. Coming out this way,
buddy, where you going?
I think I'm running into a spy.
Alright, alright, alright.
Stalk the prey, just like you would
in the jungle.
Random crit, random crit.
Random crit! Yes!
Yes! Oh,
I can't believe it.
Oh, let's be a real jerk.
Oh, I'm being a real
bad person right now, I'm out of here.
Oh, get that
spy! I keep pulling this
stupid thing out. I'm going to be
playing Diablo 3 in like
15 minutes or so.
Here we go, same guy, same guy.
Round 2? Round 2.
Come on. Oh, round
2. Round 2.
I got him. Oh,
now I'm a lot sober.
That pyro has to be very, very upset
with me. You got to imagine
that that pyro is probably not happy right
now. Well,
I would be quite upset as well.
Oh, I'm hitting into the stupid thing.
One heavy down.
Come on, somebody get on that. Cut!
I need some health.
I need some health, man. Help me!
Please help me.
Thank you.
Oh, come on. I got it.
Spencer down. Come on,
walk out that front door.
Oh, come on. Walk right into a crit
rocket. Crap. Damn it.
God dang.
That pyro is your friend?
Oh my god.
I'm going demo night. 7 and 3?
What'd I say? 1 of 10 kills?
Alright, I'll get it all right now. Here's 1.
No, that's no spy.
They're getting locked in the spawn, man. I feel bad
for these guys. Hey, spy.
I just ran into you. Don't know where you are, but it's okay.
Oh, there he is.
Prey number 1.
Yikes.
Oh, how did they know? How did they know?
Did you win that duel,
Justin? I don't even remember.
You probably did.
Medic, medic, medic.
All you have now
is that crit's cast hat.
Uh, no, I have other
hats. I just recently got it, so I haven't put it...
Oh, this is it, by the way, if you want to see it.
Vintage lo-fi
longwave. I just have it on
all my classes right now, just
for fun, because I just got it recently.
And it can be equipped on anybody, so...
Oh,
no.
I totally did not time
that right. Totally didn't time that
right.
HalBlobberFatty, what's up, man?
I play Diablo 3 with
Star, Shibby, MLC Stealth, and
Burger Boy. Alright, let's start
the chain here. Let's start the chain here.
This guy's gonna kill me.
I have no health at all.
Come on, stay alive until I get charged!
Yes.
Alright, let's do it.
Let's go for this.
Somebody, like, walk up here.
Oh, crap.
Suicide
for the win.
Alright, one more kill, and I'm gonna
probably move on to Diablo 3.
Let's all ask him
if he's a Brony.
I...
I don't think so, no.
That's somebody that really likes watching that
show, right? That My Little Pony show.
I've never watched one episode, I've never
seen one episode.
I don't really watch any TV. The only TV
I really watch is... I mean, I
watch a lot of YouTube, if you count that.
I can't believe I missed. Thank God
El Scorcho just sniped him, because that was
awful.
Ah.
I'm sorry, did you just say suicide for the win?
Fake in-game
suicide for the win. We'll put it that way.
I got the kill, though. That's what I wanted.
Never seen one of my streams? Well, welcome.
Thanks for coming, man.
Oh, super trick!
Alright, let me see...
Is anybody even online?
Do I have to play some Diablo 3?
I'm not even in Skype.
Let's see if anyone's
online.
Burger Boy is online.
No sign of Brett with Shibby.
Shibby is online.
And Star is online, too.
Alright, we can make something happen here.
Oh, not a new game. Yeah!
So, I have to get Diablo 3 in a window.
So, if you came here for the TF2,
thanks for coming.
Glad you stopped by.
And yeah, thank you.
If you want to stick around for Diablo 3, I'm going to be streaming Diablo 3 for
probably
quite a long time. And when I say quite a long time,
I mean at least an hour or two.
So, yeah.
Let me get that rolling here.
First, let me write a heart.
The screen is going to go black
for a minute
or so here.
Whoa! Streamception.
The screen is going to go black. But I'm still here.
Don't worry.
I have not left. I'm still kicking.
So, what can I talk about while I do this?
Oh, Diablo 3.
Because I'm going to play Diablo 3 right now.
Loading up Diablo 3.
So, what I can talk about while this is
kind of a black screen right now is
yes, I'm still a barbarian.
I'm having fun with this new build, and I'll try and talk about it.
What I'm doing is
I've got to show it on the screen before
any of that
good stuff happens.
So, hold on a second, guys.
It's probably going to be a whole lot of
nonsense in the background.
Windowed.
80 by 720.
Why can't I make it to window?
Well, that's weird.
Why can't I change it to...
What's the deal? There we go.
All right. Windowed. There's the window.
I believe that's
correct.
There we go.
Okay. I'm coming back.
Coming back. Coming back.
Are we back?
No, that's not quite what I wanted.
Not quite. Hold on, guys. Sorry about this.
Not quite what I was
looking for, but it's okay.
All right. Okay. Now I've got to do this.
Hello.
Ah!
Inception. Inception.
Inception.
Hold on. I'm going to try one more thing here.
Just black bars on the side.
I don't want that.
I don't want that at all.
Now let's try this again.
Okay. I got it this time.
I got it this time.
Add screen region. Screen region.
Hello.
And let's do it.
Okay. We're back.
I'm actually going to turn some of these down.
The purposes of...
The purposes of streaming.
And there we go.
Watch if you like servers are down.
So now I want to show you guys my...
This is my barbarian.
Look at him. He's like, cool.
Oh, Burger Boy is in the game right now.
I'll go play with Burger Boy.
He's in Act 1.
Oh, so I've got to say this is going to have...
Actually, this is not going to have any spoilers.
Let's go join him.
He's going to be so confused.
He's going to be like, what are you doing in here?
I just said, sup, Burger. I'm streaming.
Where is he right now?
So this is what I wanted to show you my build.
This is the build I'm working on right now for the barbarian.
So I have right now...
See this thing right here?
Berserker Rage.
You inflict an additional 25% damage while at maximum fury.
So what I'm trying to do is
I'm trying to use as many moves as I can
that are not
consumers of fury.
Because obviously these ones are not.
As a barbarian, if you don't know,
you have moves that build fury.
And you have moves that
use it, remove it.
So what I'm trying to do is
I'm trying to do this kind of build where
I'm always at maximum fury, at least for the most part.
So I get 25% damage from that
just by having the fury
as high as it can go.
And then this,
Enter a Rage, which increases damage done by 15%
and critical hit chance by 3%
for 30 seconds. So it's a buff, right?
And of course I have this rune
where it makes it so
it increases that damage bonus to 30%.
So, if you can do the math,
what I'm trying to do is have this be at 30%
and have this be full all the time
so it's at 25%.
So you're talking
55% more damage if I have
full fury. And I'm trying to stay there
as much as I can.
So let's go
find Burger Boy. Burger Boy!
Actually I want to turn up
I'll just join off him.
I'm not sure where he is right now.
I think he's in the Old Ruins.
Barbarian, someone's asking?
Oh god, lag.
Why Barbarian? Because Barbarian,
I don't know, I remember the Barbarian from
Diablo 2.
Let me turn the sound down a little bit.
The Barbarian in Diablo 2 is just a classic.
And I'm a huge fan of the classic
Diablo. So of course
I'm going to try and pick it and play.
This is on Nightmare by the way.
We have already completed this game at least once.
And it's probably going to lag for the first
few seconds or minutes
or so of the game.
Only because
it does that for some reason. I don't know why.
Diablo 3 is very, very buggy right now.
What quest are you on
right now?
I'm going to show you what I'm talking about though.
So I have Frenzy, right?
Frenzy speeds up the more I hit people.
Like speeds up my attack speed.
So what I'm trying to do is just be like an absolute
psycho and swing like 100 miles per hour.
See if I can't show what I'm talking about here.
So see, the more I hit people
the faster I'm going to swing.
And those yellow letters, those are crits.
Yeah, let me get Burger Boy in the Skype call.
Burger Boy, I'm going to
call you. Where are you, Burger?
Actually Burger Boy,
can you call me?
Just call me Burger Boy.
Because I'm a bit used to much of my bandwidth.
Oh, he just started Act 1
Nightmare. So for those of you
watching, this is the very beginning of Act 1.
And it's on Nightmare difficulty.
You just started Burger Boy.
Where are you, Burger?
That's where I am.
I'm trying to remember what quest he's even on.
Oh, Burger Boy has to come in here.
Because he has the quest person.
So you want to see my stuff?
Before we get going here?
Before Burger Boy gives me a ring-a-ding-ding.
Burger. Look at that face,
by the way. Look at like Burger Boy's
face. Someone's asking
what is Diablo 3 about?
It's kind of a difficult thing to explain,
but pretty much it's an action RPG
where you run around and you kill
literally hundreds and hundreds
of monsters at the same time.
And hold on, Burger Boy is actually calling.
What's up, Burger?
Oh, hold on, I gotta change something.
You know you guys can't hear, am I gonna make it so he's coming through the right
line? Line 1.
There we go. Burger Boy, close
your windows.
Oh yeah. Sorry. Hold on.
Burger Boy like lives like on a
highway.
Alright, let's do this
thing, man. Bring a
Leia. Oh, she's actually right here.
You want me to grab
my 42 and you want to continue
where we left off?
No, it's alright. It doesn't matter. We gotta catch up
a little bit anyways, cause Shibby and
all them, Breton, they're all
a little higher. It's a beautiful
face, somebody said, about your face.
Oh, sweet.
But somebody was asking what this game's about.
Pretty much loot. It's about picking up
stuff. It's about
collecting gear.
And I'll show you my character. This is my
character's stuff. It's about
collecting gems and rares and uniques
and there's literally thousands and thousands
and thousands of different items in the game.
And right now we're in the middle of
the Act 1 quest where we're supposed to be killing,
I think we're supposed to be finding somebody actually.
So let's start whooping butt.
So Burger Boy, I'm a barbarian.
Burger Boy is a monk.
Oh god, freeze.
Yeah, killing stuff. That's pretty much what
it is, killing stuff. Killing
bosses, trying to get better gear, trying to have...
For you TF2 guys, I'll
explain it like this. So you
have unusual hats in
Team Fortress, right? So unusual
hats, pretty much think of it,
every time we kill a boss in this game,
or any time you kill a major enemy or
a very rare enemy, it's like opening
a crate. It's like opening
a Team Fortress crate. And there's
items that are really, really incredible
they're called Legendary.
And the chance of getting one of those is like
probably 1-2% per
major enemy you kill.
So it's a very
big like treasure box game where you want to get
like as many cool pieces of gear, you want to get all the awesome stuff.
That's the best way
to describe this game. It's all about making your character
better. And I'm level
32. I'm 42.
I should probably not even be here with you. I'm probably not going to get
rid of that much experience. Yeah, I'll roll on my 42.
That's fine, staying game. Okay.
It's just very addicting.
Everything about it is addicting.
There's an auction house. You can sell stuff. You can...
There's a whole trading atmosphere to it.
It's very, very interesting.
But I've been waiting for this game for over 10 years.
Just about 10 years.
2,000...1999?
Yeah, exactly, Shaxx. Exactly.
It is unboxing a boss.
And even just
regular enemies too. If you notice when I kill some of
these guys, they'll just drop stuff.
They randomly will drop stuff on the ground.
And there's a big storyline to it.
There's a whole lot of cool stuff to read about.
Just interesting.
Excuse me.
Oh, the Puke spell. Puke spell.
I'll give you guys this buff.
That's still recharging.
But if you are a fan of action RPGs,
this is pretty much the series that started
it all. Diablo 1.
I'm not going to
give up my battle tag.
For the main purposes of...
It's very easy just to join off of
anybody's game. So I'm going to
keep that probably private for now.
Because as you know, if
anybody joins your game,
the game just gets harder.
I gotta get a water. Hold on.
I'm starting to get froggy.
But if anybody joins your game,
the game just gets harder. Everything just
gets harder. Oh, this is where it gets nuts.
Going to Super Saiyan mode.
See, I can turn into this
giant barbarian. Smash.
Get smashed.
Enemy drop.
And you get bonus experience.
You get bonus experience
for killing a certain amount
of enemies in a row. It's very, very addicting.
Everything about this game is addicting.
I'm going to go this way. Just split up so we can
fight it easier, I guess.
I got 144
killstreak earlier. It was
insane. Oh my god.
144?
Yeah, the monk's nasty.
Oh, I gotta turn you up a little bit.
There you go. People are probably having trouble
hearing you now. They can hear you probably.
Can you guys hear Burger Boy okay? Or should I lower him?
Drop him? Oh, here we go.
This is what I'm talking about. This is a room. This is like a
room full of enemies I want to fight. Bang.
I'm at the
point where we need to be.
Just... I'll TP off you in a second.
Yeah. Yeah, I will.
This will all be
uploaded to YouTube.
Tomorrow, probably afternoon.
Yeah, you can just take it. I'll just accept off you.
So, just skip everything.
Because I don't want to, you know, the story.
People might not want to see it. Yep.
And skip!
Get him, minions.
Deckard Cain.
It's Deckard Cain. This is on Nightmare, right?
Yep. Yep.
I think it is. Yeah, it is.
We got a big boy right here. What's he going to drop?
Legendary. He just keeps
dropping, like, vintage items.
Skip, skip, skip, skip.
How much is the game? The game is
60 bucks. It is
60 dollars. It's a brand new AAA release.
Kind of expensive, but
for the amount of time that we've been
playing this for...
Skip. Yeah, skip it.
For the amount of time we've been playing this for, like, I'll just show you.
I think I can show you.
I guess I can't. But I've been playing this game
on this character for probably 25, 30 hours already.
I'm almost level 43, too.
This is good stuff.
Alright, get the next quest.
Yeah, Burgerboy, he just changed classes.
He's a witch doctor now. He was on
his monk, but now he's playing as the witch doctor.
Let me sell some of this stuff.
And as you can see, he's
like 37.7 DPS, and the thing I have
on is 75.6.
And you can look at the stats, too, and you kind of go
stat crazy, and you get all nuts.
It's a lot of fun.
I don't need any of this stuff, really, though.
And I want money.
So I'm just going to sell it.
I want dat money.
Oh, no, it is not monthly. It is not
monthly. You just buy it once,
and you have it forever. You don't have to ever pay anything ever again.
Yeah, that's the best part about this game.
It was monthly, man.
I hate that,
monthly stuff.
No, I wouldn't do it if it was monthly.
Maybe for like a month or so, maybe, I don't know.
It would be tough, because the game is really fun.
Oktoberfest!
But it can get really crazy.
When you get a group of four people,
because the maximum amount of people you can have in a
lobby is four,
you get four people in this game, and it gets pretty
ridiculous.
Do we have to kill this lady, or no?
Yeah, we gotta kill this lady.
Get her. Super Saiyan mode.
Oh, she went down.
I'll just grow up all over.
Nothing good.
The major points of the quest is to
make the story keep going,
progress the story, get some more gold, get some more loot.
But the real
treasure chest is the bosses.
There's like
15 major bosses in this game, maybe a little bit more.
That's like the real joy
of this game.
It's killing a boss and crossing your fingers that you're going to get a legendary.
Or like a good rare or something.
Somebody wrote,
doesn't Burger Boy only buy games
when they're $10
when they're $10?
Wow, that says a lot about this game.
Yeah, that is true.
Watch out, we got some dudes over here.
Oh, we got a lot of people over here.
Oh, God.
Let's just smash them.
Smash them.
I love that move so much. Cleave is so much fun.
You can just swipe at everybody
and just crush them.
Yep, bosses are treasure boxes.
When you kill a boss,
a ton of stuff just jumps out
into the screen.
And you see what you want to pick up,
what you don't want to pick up, what you want to trade to people,
what you want to sell.
We'll be at one of those bosses
probably in the next 25 minutes or so.
The Skeleton King.
This way.
Burger Boy. Get out of town.
Pick up all the money is important.
Waypoint.
You found the waypoint, nice.
Is there a way?
Just trying to see when people were online last.
Always check the...
Oh, I thought, oh my God.
I almost just lost my mind.
I thought my brain just collapsed right there.
I thought that was a set item or something.
You want to go down one of those doors
and I'll go down another
since we're a little ahead on the level here?
Yep. Sounds like a plan.
Get that speed.
Jerma, are you grandpa?
That mystery will never be solved.
I can neither confirm nor deny
that statement.
I'll check this one.
If you need help, just call it out.
Yeah, I'll be good. I got my minions.
That's right, you are.
You are a witch doctor.
I do forget that sometimes.
Technically Diablo 3 is not an MMO,
but I guess you could classify it as one.
With the trading and the items
and the multiplayer.
But it is at the heart
of a single player game.
For the most part.
Oh, a treasure bandit.
Oh man, I wish you were down here right now.
It's alright, I'll try and kill him.
Oh, die you little bastard.
Yes, nice.
I got to check that out.
So what I just did right there, guys,
is there was a little dude and he carries around
like a knapsack.
Burger Boy immediately
came to where the Treasure Goblin was.
And if you kill that guy, he drops
a lot of stuff, as you can see. Look at the ground.
It's covered with things.
See, these are rare.
This is like the uncreating thing I was talking about, guys.
It's not a legendary, but it's still a rare.
Let's see what it is like.
The thing I have is better.
Vitality, 3 health per second.
I can sell that, though.
I can sell it.
I'll grab some more of this stuff.
Yeah, I think there will be DLC.
Oh, got an event down here.
They already confirmed that there was going to be
at least one expansion.
Oh boy, there's a couple lords.
Lords and ladies.
Yeah, these guys got nothing.
We're a little bit high level for this.
But, I mean, it's good just to
clean through everything.
If you wanted to bring your witch, I mean, your monk in here,
when we get to the boss, you could.
Just, like, speed level him.
Hmm.
Good idea.
I'm pretty sure that's how it works.
Yeah, we'll try it.
What do you mean, when we get to the skeleton king?
Yeah, yeah.
What do you think, like, you don't have to complete
the quest before?
I don't think so.
I could be wrong, but I don't think so.
Level 43.
Ow.
A new rune.
Gotta check that.
These guys, these little bastards are running around like crazy.
I'm a melee class, I can't keep up.
Oh, damn.
Kill this guy.
Speed hack, speed hack.
I don't even need to use my cooldown.
Anything?
No.
Oh, that is good to know.
Good to know. Thanks for whoever said that.
Let me see what his name was.
Thank you for that.
This guy just said, if you hold down control while you hover over an item,
you can see the stats on it.
Oh, wow. That's awesome.
I didn't even realize that.
What an idiot both of us are.
Oh, man.
Rare shoulder plates.
Let's identify these babies.
Oh, a shibby's gonna want these.
74 intelligence.
82 vitality.
I'll hold on to those for the shibster.
Alright, so it wasn't in here.
Yeah, it wasn't that one.
It might be the one you were at.
Let me check this one.
What's my favorite type of cheese?
Swiss cheese.
If you want, we can try and do...
If you want to go to Act 2 and try and farm the boss, maybe.
Yeah, let's do it.
If you want to do that after we...
I want to go through a more little dungeon first.
Yeah, because I don't even have to complete this.
I already did this on this character.
See, the cool part about this game, guys,
is you can literally
just keep opening crates.
You just keep killing the same boss over and over again
to try and get cool stuff.
Yeah, we'll do that.
Let's do that. I'll make the game.
Alright, is that a new perk?
TF2 was before this.
If you missed it, it's gonna be uploaded tomorrow to YouTube.
Okay, change quest.
Act 2.
We'll do...
The Lord of Lies Belial.
Act 2.
You can join off me when you're ready.
What we just were playing right there
was kind of the beginning of Act 1
because Burger Boy was on it with another character
and I was just coming to help him out.
But now that he's on his actual character
and I'm on my main character too,
we're gonna do the boss of Act 2 again.
Just because he's
a very major boss,
cool to farm,
maybe get some good stuff.
No, getting good items does not cost $2.50.
It costs nothing.
Unless, of course,
the real money auction house is coming out at some point.
We don't know when in the next few days.
Okay, this is what I'm talking about.
This is gonna get difficult.
So all about being prepared.
With that cleave.
Let's get this sped up. Frenzy mode.
I love frenzy.
Stop them!
Oh, I'm taking some hits now.
That's what I'm talking about.
I want to take that pain, take that suffering.
No, don't stand on the poison.
Yeah! Nice.
Do I think the real money auction house is a good idea?
Tough to say.
Well, I gotta go activate this.
Tough to say, because
it's one of those things where
Diablo is supposed to be all about finding the loot.
And, oh, you found this, you found that.
But with the auction house,
it kind of makes it
oh, let me just go buy
whatever I want from the auction house.
I don't have to find anything.
And to me, that kind of takes away from the game a little bit.
But most people probably aren't going to
really use it that often.
I'm not sure.
But yeah, that's my opinion. I think that a real money
auction house makes it so you can just buy whatever you want.
And have the best gear in the game
and you really maybe didn't even play.
You didn't even like try and get it.
I'm an old school Diablo guy.
I was all about farming the same boss over and over and over
and over again until you got that one item you wanted.
But it's cool.
It's something new. Something interesting
that they added.
That kid's going to like
get way better gear than you.
It's going to piss you off, isn't it?
No, I don't care.
Just me personally,
I probably won't use the real money auction house.
At least right off the bat.
Oh god, don't stand in that.
Get over here.
Don't stand in that lighting.
It'll be your demise.
Besides the barbarian, the wizard.
I have a level 17 wizard I haven't really been playing with lately.
But probably the wizard.
I gotta run away from that.
See the problem with this build?
Oh boy, we got, oh boy, oh boy, oh boy.
We got a couple of
elite creatures over here.
Oh, they're all doing that
lightning thing.
I can't even stand near them.
Oh god, I gotta try and single them out.
I keep doing that mirror thing too.
That's annoying.
Get out of here.
Alright, I'm going Super Saiyan.
You got nothing on me.
Super Saiyan mode.
Any good drops?
Sick. What'd you get?
Oh, nothing. That was just a
destructive...
If you buy too much stuff, won't it defeat the purpose of
Diablo?
Yeah, that's my opinion.
A lot of people share the same opinion.
But there's also a lot of people that say,
and it's very warranted,
they say, I don't have time to grind
the same boss over and over and over and over again.
Oh by the way, we're about to
you're about to see a boss, a major boss,
so if you don't want to see it, then you don't want to see it.
So I recommend clicking
away from the screen for a second,
because you're about to see a major Act boss.
Oh, we're skipping the scene anyways, right?
Yeah, we're skipping it, but still, it doesn't really matter.
Spoiler alert!
But this
guy is probably going to be incredibly
difficult with just me and you.
This is Act 2.
What was your question, Brunden? Sorry, I'll answer it.
Ask it again. I apologize.
I'm trying to pay attention to
five different things at once here, so sorry.
Got to get rid of his snake ads.
Yeah, we're
definitely going to wipe. There's no way we're going to do this.
Maybe we will.
This guy's quite difficult.
Actually, we can show
this. Oh, no, we don't.
It doesn't matter.
Get him!
Sick of minion!
I only have one potion,
dude. This is going to be really bad.
This is going to be really, really bad.
Getting annihilated already.
We are going to get
so owned, it's not even funny.
Oh, he's almost like
Half-Life. Not bad.
Are you forgetting the most important
thing? I don't.
Crush him. I'm saving my Super Saiyan
for when we really need it, because we're really
going to need it.
He's just about to give up.
Kill that ad. We don't want this guy here.
We want this guy gone.
Let's see...
Am I going to Dreamhack?
Uh, it's
probably not. It's across the world, and I don't really have
the funds, I guess,
to travel across the world.
Okay, this is where it gets nuts.
Oh, god. Oh, god. I'm literally
scared. We're going to wipe right in the first two seconds.
We're going to wipe in the first two seconds.
Probably.
Oh, god.
I have like half health.
We're dead.
Oh, me too.
Alright, let's go Super Saiyan. Give me that health, yes.
Oh, come on.
We got to burn up as quick as we can.
He's crushing me right now.
He's going to do the poison thing.
When he does it, make a run for it.
Try not to stand in it. There it is.
Don't stand in it. Oh, no!
Oh, that was so close.
I get the orb.
Get away.
That was so close. He does this
for so long on Nightmare.
Alright, come on. Here we go.
Come on, come on, come on.
Pick up that health.
There's a health right in front of you. Don't get it yet.
Oh, dear.
I didn't hold shift.
There's another health there. We'll be okay.
I'm going to grab it. I need it.
Watch out.
Oh, crap.
Get that health globe. I'm alright.
Here he goes. Here he goes. Run.
Run around. Don't stand in it.
Oh, no.
I'm so dead. I died.
Are you dead? Oh, no.
Can I revive you? Can I revive you?
Come on. Come on.
Oh, this is bad.
This is bad.
Oh, no. It's over.
Get that health.
You know what I have to do? I have to do it
right now.
Right now. Come on.
Come on, you son of a bitch. Yes.
Alright, run.
We got to do some damage to him.
He's not dropping any globes.
There's one. There's one.
Alright, good. Smoke him. Smoke him.
Watch out. Watch out. Watch out.
Oh, I'm stuck in the corner over here.
I just died again.
No.
Oh, my God.
No, don't die.
Oh, I'm so dead. It is over.
Super Saiyan mode.
Go. Go. Smash him. Smash him. Smash him. Smash him.
No.
Oh, it's over. We're dead.
Oh, it's going to hit me and I'm going to die.
I need to get a globe out of him.
It's over, regardless.
That was disappointing.
Yeah, it was a little too hard.
A little too hard.
I just got to go repair.
We know what we need.
We need to get potions.
I didn't have any potions.
I had like one potion. Going back to Tom.
Damn.
We got him down to half.
Sorry, I was paying attention to that craziness.
When you die, you don't lose your character.
No, you don't. That's hardcore mode only.
If we just lost our characters right there,
I would have peed my pants and then like
pooed my pants immediately after peeing.
I would have never played this game again.
All right.
The potion person is down here in town.
And yeah, I absolutely will do arenas.
Absolutely.
I can't wait for them to come out to be honest.
It's going to be awesome. I need to go.
Where's the potion person?
I think they're like in another little area, aren't they?
Oh, they're all over here. I'm thinking of Act 3.
Yeah, I got to think of a good arena team.
Because
there's going to be a lot of options.
Bye, bye, bye, bye.
Super health potions.
Okay. Yeah, this game is awesome
for solo. The reason why me and him are having trouble
right now is because this is nightmare.
This is on a higher difficulty mode.
And when there's
more than one person in a game,
it makes the game like twice
as hard.
So when three people are in the game, it's three times as hard.
When four people are in the game, it is at max difficulty.
All right.
Are you ready to try this again?
Yeah.
If we wipe again, then we're going to have to go back
and we should be
all right this time. We didn't have potions.
You got potions, right?
I got four. I'll be good.
All right. You sure? I don't know about that.
Four potions doesn't seem like very much.
I better put on the heroic ones, too.
Let's go.
Here we go again.
We're doing it again.
Let's do it. Nightmare.
You know what I'm going to put on?
I got to put on a different passive.
Where is it?
I forgot to do a better offensive move.
When we have a second here,
I'm going to put on the health globe one because we get more health globes.
Because we need them bad, bad, bad.
I'm going to hide behind your minions.
All right. Let's do it.
What am I going to replace it with?
Where is it?
Take it. Thank you very much.
So what this is going to do, guys,
is I just put on a passive ability
that makes it so much more
health globes drop and they heal for much more.
The health globes are little
health bubbles you see on the ground.
This is absolutely
worth getting.
Troy Thorn. What's up, man?
I'm not sure I'm going to be able
to make it to Pax Prime.
The only reason is because it's just a lot of money.
I don't have the money to fly out there.
I think the tickets are even sold out now,
to be honest.
So I'm probably not going to make it to Pax Prime.
We'll see, though. I'm not totally
ruling it out of the question.
All right. I'm doing much better this time. Much more controlled.
I died twice
last time. Can't blame you
for that.
Are you going to watch that poison?
My guy's like
too, like,
his back is too ush to run.
I was
at Pax East. I was at Pax East.
All right. Here we go.
Wow. We destroyed him that time.
Yeah. Well,
this is the part that matters.
And here we go.
Thank you, Geronimo.
Whatever your name is. Thank you so much.
All right. This is where we go. Super Saiyan!
Puke. All over.
All right. Leave the health globes alone.
Let them stay. Let them stick around for a little bit.
You know what I mean? Until we need them.
I'm going to grab this one now. This one right next to me.
Good. This health globe thing was something I absolutely
should have had on from the beginning.
So what you're saying, it's all your fault.
Pretty much it's all my fault.
Watch it. There we go. Oh, no. Not again.
Anything but this.
Try and stay away from each other. We're going to like bump into each other.
All right. Let's do it.
Start it up. Start smashing.
Health globe. Health globes everywhere
now. We're good.
Or are we? Maybe I spoke a little too soon.
I had to take a potion.
Take as many as you need.
You're the tank.
Oh, don't you spray that at me.
How dare you?
I'm running this way.
He's going to do that thing again. Very, very soon.
Oh, here it comes.
Yeah, it's definitely coming like right now.
Oh, you had to do that right before
you did this. Here it is.
Oh, no. Oh, don't get clubbed to the quarter.
Don't get clubbed to the quarter.
Oh, my God. Oh, no.
Oh, I got hit by one.
We're good. We're good. We're good.
Even those dogs are like upset about this.
We got it. We got it. We got it. We got it.
So
pissed about it. So funny.
Dude,
this is getting so intense. Even like the dogs
are getting intense.
Oh, no.
He's going to do it one more time. It's going to happen probably like
right now. I'm going to have
super saiyan mode one more time.
Come on. Oh, no.
Watch it. Here it is. Here it is.
Oh, this is the last one.
That's it. We got to only deal with this last one
and we'll kill him.
Yes.
All right. Burn him. I'm going super saiyan.
To death.
Burn him. Burn him.
Kill him. Oh, legendary.
Come on. Oh, it's over, baby. Legendary.
Legendary. Legendary.
Legendary. Come on.
Crap.
Kidding me.
What is that? Garbage.
Oh, man.
All that for blues.
I just got blues too.
Rage. Quit.
Oh, well.
That was pretty difficult. Not going to lie.
Where is auto?
Auto. Auto.
I don't want to move on.
Where are they?
Where is shibby stealth star? Where is everybody?
Get a four player action going.
Continue on to act three.
I would absolutely say that.
That actually was not auto.
That was Burger Boy's two dogs.
He has two big crazy dogs.
They're like 180 pounds each.
They both like
they stand six feet tall.
I got to
check on the stuff I just got.
Well, that was a bad crate.
Yeah, it was.
That was like a crate eight.
No strangers, no nothing.
The only crates I ever opened.
The real problem here is
we've got to get magic find.
I don't have like any. You don't have any.
We need like 100 percent
extra magic find.
I'm going to save those for shibby.
These
are actually not that great.
I'm selling them.
Could I sell them in the auction house?
Probably not. The stats on these are really just
dumb. I'm selling them.
Sockets are good, but not
I'm not really too concerned about it.
This is not that bad, but I got better.
This is
not that good. This is not that good.
And this is not that good.
Alright. Actually, I think I had auctions
that were going. I wonder if they sold.
I'm going to check on my auctions for a second.
Okay. So I'm going to
show you guys the auction house.
I'm doing the same. Okay.
So this is the auction house.
So what you do here is
you go to equipment, gems,
crafting, recipes, pages,
and you can search for stuff. So let's say right now I'm level
43. So let's say I want something in
40, the 40 to 45
range, right?
And I want one-handed
weapons. And it doesn't matter
what one-handed, I want it to be rare
though. I want it to be of rare quality.
So right now I just hit search. These are people
that are selling things on the
auction house in
that particular category
that I just mentioned. So right now
if you take a look at this, this guy is absolutely
not going to sell this. This thing, he's selling this for
8 million gold. Which is
I mean, I don't
know if you're like going to sell that.
But see, what you can do is
you can play the auction house, right? You can play the field.
So you go back to like the
bids and the buyouts to some of the cheaper stuff.
There's a lot of pages
as you can see. And Burger Boy
is going to like puke on
his microphone.
See this is the least expensive one in here
for the level 40 to 45 range.
$115,000. So if I bought this
right now, I have $118,000.
If I bought this
right now for $115,000
I mean it really wouldn't be that
good.
Because obviously you can
find stuff, you can make stuff. Or you could buy this
and then resell it and try and get more money
for it. But for now
let's go to my completed auctions.
See I put this up for $160,000
gold.
This should have sold though. This is $14,000
that's like chump change.
You can see your past auctions.
This is like the money that I've
made. Money that I've made.
Money that I've purchased.
See it can get really really addicting.
It can get really addicting.
Eventually
see currency.
The real currency auction house will be available
at a later date. $529.
So in a couple weeks you're going to
be able to use real money
to buy things. People are going to be able
to put like oh here's my
attack weapon thing.
It's $5.
Real money. And it's going to be totally
legal, totally encouraged. It's going to be
ridiculous.