I'm gonna say explain why you're late. He's late. I said this before and I'm gonna say it again
I think a lot of you guys stop reading after the three is three to four p.m. I think you guys just stop reading after three
Hey, what's going on? How you doing? Welcome back. We can't count past three. Yes, you can
I've seen you get to like six thousand in this chat, but how you doing guys? Good to see you again
Hope you're having a good day. I'm gonna play something interesting today. I feel like I'm gonna love this game
I've been hold on to this through a long time and
We're gonna give it a try. What happened to beautiful Joe?
Beautiful Joe is is hanging out
Out back here for a little while. I I'm not sure beautiful Joe will make a triumphant return
He's fucking exhausted
Maybe I'll play it. It's it's ready if this game's not any fun
If this game's not any good, I'm gonna play it
But I've been sitting on this one for a long time too chat killed beautiful. Yes, they did
Yes, they did
Only only like six of us like that fucking game currently
Take beautiful Joe out into the oh my god. He's the what a great cool game
You know what? It's over. We're done. We're gonna move on. He is fucking exhausted
We're gonna play casino ink tonight
Casino ink is a casino management game. You make a casino and you run it. I'm all over this
This game came out like 15 years ago
So I wish they'd make a new one. I want a new up-to-date casino like we're gonna be good
You gotta set the fucking restaurants the hotels the tables
They could be troublemakers. You have to throw out of the casino. It's gonna be a lot of fun
I like beautiful Joe to people happy me too. Thank god. It's not beautiful Joe. I okay
Well, you gotta get off
All right
if you remember when I played Kenshi and I got like three or four streams into Kenshi and it was like
Get off this game. It's like don't ever play this game again. This game's boring. It's game sucks
That was like beautiful Joe was like Kenshi too. It was wild
Kenshi is great though. Yeah, but hey, you live and die by the
By the chat hive mind, I think
And she actually sucks though see what I'm saying now imagine imagine that five thousand times
And she is good
But without further ado
We're gonna play casino Inc. I'm happy. I can't wait. This game is gonna be fun
I'm gonna fucking have all kinds of like blackjack tables are gonna be slots. You can make an arcade in this game. Yep
You don't have to make a casino. You can make an arcade with arcade machines and pinball machines
You don't have to make a casino not money doesn't have to be involved at all
Chad is like an untrained dog
You have to be the alpha male
right
but what happens when
There's 5 000 untrained dogs are all running at you at the same time. Am I gonna
Start banning people start timing out five three four five thousand different people
Maybe I will
Maybe i'll start to lock it down. Maybe maybe i'll start to lock it down
I would be careful if I were you chat
You're on thin ice
And then my chest just fucking sticks out and I lean my neck back
All right, let's go. Let's see. Does it can you see it? You should be able to see it
Can you see?
I know you can hear it
I know no. No, I know the window's tiny the time the window is tiny
That's just temporary because it's an old it's like a game from like fucking 1993 or something konami
Konami made this game. Holy shit fill up the space with your face
No, this is just temporary. This is the first little loading screen konami of europe made this game interesting
All right. I have by the way, i'm prepared for this stream
I did at least five of these like at least five or six of these
I did these so we don't have to oh here we go. He's gonna have to learn it
No, I know fuck. I know how to play the game a little loud though, isn't it?
Whoa
That's that like scared me
The rumors have got me all fucked up
That's still so loud
Okay, how is it possible that even at like 10 percent? That's okay, right?
That's good, right?
Right there. All right. That's good. Here we go new game select your casino theme. I know you can't see it
I'll read them to you. You can never
Imprison a hunk. I can never do an impression of a hunk. Is that what you're saying?
You were saying i'm sorry, what was that? All right, we got cleo's casino cutthroat's casino
This looks like a pirate themed you can kind of see it toy box casino kind of freaking me out though
Why would you the casinos are for adults?
Not for why is it like building blocks and shit the tex casino?
Centurion casino polar's casino. Oh, I like this one. It's like made of ice the lucky seven cheap
Cheetos casino cheetahs casino the astro casino. Oh astro's kind of cool
It's like a ufo themed the club club casino clams casino or the crypt casino is like an
Undead theme which one what do you think i'm leaning towards?
Uh, the toy box casino is just odd. I like the the underwater one clam
Cheetos crypt crypt casinos. Yeah, it's cool club club penguin toy box is
based
That's such an annoying building
Imagine having to live next to this building toy box is based. Is it toy box is based based on what?
Yes, I know
Uh, well, no clam is based. All right, i'm gonna flip the coin. I'm gonna flip the coin heads is clam
Hales is toy box and if it lands directly on top standing up, it's the crypt we go
I forgot everything. I just said i'm not even kidding. I don't remember. What was it heads was what I don't
I have no idea what it was. I just called it. I don't know heads was what heads was the clam
All right heads was clam heads was clam clam. Okay. All right, let's do the clam casino
Uh, we can choose where we want to go. We have a little hope springs fortune falls
chancersville cashmore heights dolla dolla ring dolla rington chip city
Okay chip city demands that you can't read this but i'll just read it to you chip city demands the best from you
It's the hardest city in casino inc little hope springs
Is the perfect challenge with which to start so this is just in difficulty. This is just difficulty
So we can do one two, three four is one through six in difficulty. I'm not doing chip city
I'm not starting at the hardest fucking difficulty. This is probably a hard game chip city is based
No, we're going to like fortune falls. I'm doing fortune falls
Fortune falls is a mid-sized city with plenty of nightlife to attract visitors bars restaurants theaters nightclubs fast food outlets and entertainment of a
Sleazier nature are all there to entice your would-be customers added to all that three casino owning companies have a head start on you
Your ultimate aim is to dominate the gambling and entertainment markets and to put two of the three major competitor casinos out of business
In addition to building an efficient business empire, you will need to use cheats troublemakers and hitmen
Exclusively extensively to harm your opponents. This is why they like command points the challenge in fortune falls shouldn't be underestimated
You'll need good advertising transport security and lots of cash. I know it's small. I know it's small. It's about to be fixed
All right, let's do this one enter your name. How about uh, yeah derma's fine. That's my fucking name. Here we go
Is this an rts?
Uh kind of what what was that?
This is a busy city with many tourist attractions just recently gambling has been legalized
Quick gambling's been legalized send in the choppers
We just became legal quick get like 10 fucking buildings up easy competition will be tough
Not only will you have to build and manage your own gambling and entertainment empire
You also have to actively win customers. Don't worry. I will that's a good face cam. Yeah
What what's going on? What's going on with the suit here?
Okay, this is a suit. What is this?
Why is there a bunch of like chewed bubblegum stuff down his shirt?
My job is head post if you settle in and show you how to experience that
Won't you take a tour of the city?
Yeah, i'd like a tour take a tour of the city
Visitors arrive the busy railroad terminal. There are several one and boston road nearby
The city has good transport links from here to the better quality hotels to the north of the city and around the central square
Okay, so they come in on rail on the railroad terminal
There are several one and two star hotels nearby
City has good transport links from here to the better quality hotels. Okay
At the heart of the city the central square houses the courthouse and the conference restaurants bars and theaters
This is where we want to go
During the tour you can scroll the views. Yeah. Yeah, I know
Who are these people?
Oh, it's a senior because he's looking for something to do. We gotta get we gotta give the seniors something to do
Holy shit. This guy's locked in
This guy this is a hell for this guy. Imagine being in this fucking position
A bus in front of you and a bus behind you
Holy shit, that's the worst possible scenario
Okay
Let's keep going
One in the central square is west street. Your casino lies at the far end of it
Competition for customers looking for cheap food and drink will be fierce here with a cafe and a bar just oh
What the fuck you go? Hold on. There's a cafe and a bar across the street and i'm the i'm the casino
I got a bar in here, too
All right. I gotta make my drinks cheaper than that
There is the clam clams casino on west street. Yep. All right, I gotta make my shit cheaper
Always north street takes visitors from the central square to the intersection with canada street
The most popular areas of the city
There are several hotels
Canada street boston street canada street tennessee street
england street
Just across the road in a great position to win customers is your first rival casino
The owner has already told us he intends to make life difficult
Really? Okay, just across the road
Oh shit. All right
Okay, this this this is this is the guy the cheetos casino
Head east from here and you'll reach. Oh, I wish that was me
Although it's conveniently placed between the railroad term. I wish that was me this area houses mainly offices and wastelands
Carrying advertising for delights found elsewhere in the city. However, we believe this quieter establishment could wasteland
This place is popular with high rollers
why
The crypt to the south of this casino. These are all the ones you were gonna pick
This is entertainment capital
Yeah, whatever so
You've got two empty floors okay, two empty floors 50 grand let's jump inside and spend some let's go you ready
We get we go. All right, let's go
inside the casino
Okay, your first judge is to achieve a market share of 15 percent in gambling
Then notice that your current objective is always displayed at the top of the screen
Get a market share of 15 in the city. All right gets zero percent. Okay
All right, let's take a look. This is what the floor looks like
Where's the entrance?
All right. This is the first floor. What do we what do what do what do you want to do?
We got a basement
Okay, is it you play chess in the basement you play chess in the basement with fucking propane tanks. That's kind of
I don't know why those are down there. That's weird. We have second floor is just the same thing. All right, first floor is the entrance
Let's do um
Well, that's the exit. Where's the entrance?
Oh that didn't know that's both. Okay
All right, let's let's say coming out here
We got you can buy attractions
We do gambling slot machines just the whole floor. What do you think?
Baccarat blackjack craps poker roulette slots slots slots
small sports betting
All slots low bet slots or what?
Should we just have a bunch of like one cent slot machines that take up the entire casino, but i'll lose money
I won't make any money
No, no, no, no, no, we're gonna we'll we'll at the entrance. We'll have a few low betting slot machines off to the side
So if you come on and you like, you know
I'll throw a nickel in there
And then the cool shit will be over here. All right, so slots low bet
We went with this right here
Wait, wait, wait konami
Here's the funny thing
Uh konami slot machines are actually the the thing that the only thing that makes them fucking money nowadays
So this is real life walk into any casino and go find this
Thousands probably have konami slot machines. So it makes sense. All right, let's say right at the door right here
How much is this 500 how much money do I have back to back you think
Yeah, we'll just do them like along the wall here. We want to have enough to really have a go
All right. That looks okay smart way to fund your game. I mean, yeah if they made any anymore
I gotta get these controls done because I can't like mouse scrolls games too old
All right. What do you think should I do same thing over here? I have just slots lined up low bet slots
I can go and configure these that's what i'm gonna do. How much money do I have 46 000? Okay
All right. It looks good. All right now
Slots medium bed. No, it can't just be fucking slot machines. I need some like decorations here. Let's start with this
How do I pause the game? It's paused, right? Okay, it's paused. All right
Uh bean bags should there be bean bag chairs for the slot machines?
That seems stupid, but your first customer just walked in what oh shit. Nobody walked in. There's a customer
How do I pause the game?
lc matthews
trailer trash
It just goes right
All right. Wait, wait, wait configure configure. This is the only person in the casino is this trailer try. Okay
Uh jackpot frequency. We're gonna do low because he's a fucking one cent machine return percentage
We'll keep it at medium keep it at medium. Okay today profit but use one. Okay today
Uh, all right, she spent 50 dollars already
We're doing just fine. Okay, low jackpot percentage. Wait a minute income profit. No, she hit a jackpot. Fuck. We need slow
She's gonna clean us out. All right. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, we got more stuff. Wait, you're out
But she oh she wants drinks fuck they have drinks across the street. I can't pause the game. Can I?
No, that's slow motion. All right. I gotta okay go go go go go go go go go. Okay. We need um
Blackjack table over here. I'm gonna have slots slots slots
And then we're gonna have blackjack table blackjack blackjack blackjack or two blackjacks blackjack one. Oops
I need to move that blackjack one blackjack two. That's all right for now. I need to move that
Move move option. I know I already know there we go. All right, that's better now. We gotta get dealers here, dude
These are working these are these vacationer. How's my slots doing? It was like the money screen
The i'm attracting socialites. I need dealers
Uh dealer dealer dealer. I need dealers. All right, we need a dealer. Who are these people? Okay. Wait, hold on
This is this is dealer, right? Yeah, these are dealers
They're all 25 bucks each and they're all like the same person. I got two dealers here
Holy shit, I gotta get more of these slots slot machine. Oh, this is every individual one. I see. Okay 50 bucks 50 bucks
40 bucks. All right. No, they're doing all right. They're doing fine. These are doing pretty well
All right. I'm gonna do uh, let's get some more slot machines in here. They need chairs
Um, can I even put chairs in here? I can't put like beanbag chairs
How much is a black sofa a staff? Wait, we need a statue
Perfect ready right when you come in the front door. Yep, trash cans need these two
Um, oh they're playing. Okay, let me get a trash can there. What about some stuff?
Cactuses, uh hanging plant hanging plant. No, those are ugly. All right, we got a
Blackjack table's full. Wait a minute. I didn't even I gotta configure these minimum bets
Okay, minimum bets for blackjack one blackjack two. We're gonna say five dollar minimum. That's five max bet of 250
No, no, no max bet of 100 max bet of 75 dollars
We don't want people to lose all that money quickly. We want them to stay here for a long time
That's a huge trash can what's wrong?
Okay, blackjack one five seventy five blackjack two
Technology high roller. All right, let's do the let's do a max bet on this one. We'll keep five dollars
75 max bet how these guys this is the employee who's doing fine. The salary's fine. The average is fine
Uh, just talking a thousand dollars of income from that guy. That guy lost a thousand dollars. Sorry
I need like staff too. All right. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait
These things just absolutely print money low jackpot low bets
Just keep them here. Look at they love this place leaving for the movie theater
Wait, I need to see the where's my stats the bribe brothers
Wait, what I don't know what that means. Hold on. What's you can rename your casino. All right
What about we'll show you name it? Uh slots slots
and
slots of
Slots of fun. It's gonna be a slot casino
Slots of fun. What? Uh, wait, what do you I have messages when asked to nominate their favorite
Establishment in town crypt casino on australia street one of the most votes from trailer trash
Okay
Anything else police authorities are reported to be concerned about the number of hookers allegedly to be operating in the crypt casino
Okay, may's general store on jamaica road has gone on the property market
Congratulations. Elsie matthews is your first visitor. Wait, i'm
Wait firefighters are going. Wait, am I following this lady?
Wait, what the fuck
She's pissed
How do I get like a thought bubble? I want to see what her thoughts are
She's looking for a drink. This place is huge
all right, I got a
Three people visited today. The day's takings are 110 dollars. The day's profit is minus
11,000 dollars you've paid zero staff
All right, give me back to the casino
Uh, okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. All right. Where's my casino? Give me back to my casino
Where is it? How do I get there? How do I get to my casino?
Okay, here it is
All right, go in get in my casino
How do I go in?
I don't need I know I can rename. How do I go in?
There we go. Okay. Uh, we need uh staff members. This is just like there's like prostitutes just walking around. Um, we need staff
Uh police security. Okay, we need
Security, this is a bouncer
The advertising audit board of fortune falls has announced that the crypt casino has been voted best advertiser. Okay
Toy box casino has bid thirty thousand dollars for the wasteland space
City tourist authorities are concerned that there's a lack of one-star hotels in the city
Okay, um, just we need a bouncer
Okay, we need a I want to have two bouncers. We also need a float. This is like a pit boss
We need like a floor man a bassiner. Okay. Yeah, that's like a pit boss
That's the floor manager. They walk around and make sure nobody's like cheating
Uh, that's because the delegate is he cheating leaving for the crypt casino. Well get him out of here
Kick him out
All right, can we get can we get her out of here
Can we can you get I I don't we don't want prostitutes in here?
Get out. You can't be in here prostitution is not legal in here. Just bought another property
Excuse me. You have to leave. There's nothing even in here
Prostitution is not legal in this casino yet. That might be I don't know. Wait, what's wrong with this? Is it broken?
This is fucking trash everybody. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait. I need um, okay. We need uh, maintenance workers
Okay. Yep. We need a couple of uh maintenance workers. Uh, we need janitorial staff. I just threw you out
What are you doing in here? Hey, how much money? I got 34 000
Wait, is it all the only people coming in here?
hookers and trailer trash I need to up my
Casino, well, okay. I guess it makes sense. All I have are low minimum blackjack tables
And penny slots. So I guess that all right. All right. All right. I got a what's on the second floor
Can I make the second floor a hotel?
Isn't that not isn't that against the law?
What is this? Okay. This is like a board. All right. All right. All right. We need some we need some more. Um,
Cheetah's casino is being raided due to a large number of hookers. Well, I don't want that to happen to me
Okay, I need to build something. Uh, okay
Advertising no, i'm not advertising. I need some more staff. I need a wait, is she back? I need a bar
Okay, we need okay. Here we go poppy machine soda machine 29 people visited today
Wages have been paid
What the fuck was that? Okay, 30 people the day. Okay, so i'm all right
Five thousand dollars in takings today's profit is in minus five thousand. That's horrible, but we need a bar
How about a small drinks bar? Uh, where should I put this about like
Right against the yeah right against here. That'd be like kind of nice, right?
Would that be nice or would that be ugly? No, that's nice because it's like right in the middle
There we go. A hooker just came out of the bar when I she she spawned in it. Okay, we need a bartender
Uh bartender, here we go. Now we can serve drinks. We figured this. All right price of drinks
Uh drink quality low quality drinks. No, I want like nice. I want like
businessmen and bankers and and
um professional athletes and
um
I like
I need expensive drinks 20 dollars a drink, but they're very high quality
18 dollars a drink, but they're incredibly high quality tons of ice. All right. Looks good ruby nolt. She's a five star
Bartender this trash just fucking everywhere seniors seniors seniors seniors. Are they playing blackjack? All right, get you
Okay, don't attack
Eject eject eject
Get go get out of here
Dude, I don't you can't just smoking in here. You guess you can you can smoke in a casino. Never mind attack
I'm not gonna he's hungry. Oh shit. Okay, they want food too. I need more. Okay, I need more money
Let's do uh, what should we do? Another row slot machines, but this time they're gonna be more expensive medium bet slot machines
These are expensive. These are expensive. Let's go right here one line one line. We'll do it in a row like this
I don't want to lose all my money. Okay, and then we'll do this here, too
Uh, and anton faster thinks he has spotted visitor oscar owens cheating at blackjack, too
This guy's cheating. Wait anton has spotted a
Eleanor oglesby is cheating at blackjack who?
um
Discipline are you cheating? I need you
Uh discipline say don't do that elevator cheat eleanor has offered her services to you. Do you accept? Um, yeah
Eleanor oglesby has transferred 600 to your account that was earned through cheating. Hold on. Wait you yeah you go
Down to the basement this guy's like honest. This guy's on vacation. The visitor you just beat up is apologized
Okay, we got the 225 back. Oh man. Okay
I just hit him in the head with a hammer
A few times. This is my cheat. Hold on. Yeah, I can cheats waiting in the basement. Okay
Go cheat somewhere go cheat at the which one which one's the worst the crypt casino
Which one's been doing well go to the crypt the crypt casino and come back when you get like two fucking thousand dollars
You're on it. All right going to the crypt casino. You have to be careful. Let me know when you get there
All right, let's go back to our
How's it looking?
I quote zero profit. Nobody of course this whole this whole place is trailer trash
No one's gonna pay $18 for a drink. I'm saying that just as a like matter of fact right here
Right, like i'm just being they keep getting raided because of hookers. No one's bought a drink. Wait, here we go
Our first customer the senior. Yeah, that's that's not strong enough. Can I make them cheaper 15 bucks
It only costs five dollars to make discipline him. He's not breaking any rules
Leaving for the crypt casino
It's watered down drinks. It's trash every
You guys need to work
Work clean
Clean this up. What are you doing? You're supposed to be
You're supposed to clean you got a bag. I didn't even configure these
Okay, get off the bouncer
Okay, these are jackpot frequency. We're gonna do let's do um medium and payout percentage low, right?
Like frequent jackpots, but not very much money. They're not janitors
Fuck they're not okay. We got two janitors now 31 000 bucks. I need more entertainment
Vacationer the looking oh, he's going to gamble
Okay profit minus 180
Minus 160 nobody wants to fucking play blackjack clean this place up a little bit
Everyone's supposed to play the shitty slot machines
All right slots bet we're gonna go through these we need the jackpot frequency return percentage jack fuck
We need everything on low
All of them on low return percentage low they cheat slots
And we're gonna the medium slots will have a medium return
That's how it works
Yes, of course, it's rigged if you if you put a cent into a slot machine
The payout percentage is way lower than if you add a one dollar denomination spin. Don't you guys know that?
That's how it works. I put the medium ones on low
Oh, well, I mean but
Not all of them. Yeah, I did it to all of them. Yeah, they're all on low. Okay. Oh
Well, okay. I'm gonna put an expensive one over here. I gotta make sure I get some seats
There's no seating. All right. I need a restaurant. All right
What's going on? What was that? You just went a bunch of money
Info, okay. Here we go profit loss settings times play your cheat. Oh, she's stealing from the bar
This place is fucking jammed
Wait, where are we going? Why are there teenagers in this casino?
Where is she? There she is
All right, which tables you're gonna go to all right the end of the day. I'm i'm losing money, but i've been paid
The richardsons toy store. I don't have any money for that
All right, she's cheating
How's it going so far? Let's get a little info on it
She's she's fucking hacking the machine
She just opened up the machine with like a screwdriver. All right. Where are we at? What's uh, what's this backer rat?
All right. Watch out. Don't get caught
And she is I can like I can play innocent
How much money does she have? Oh shit. She's got 625 bucks
All right, keep cheating
She returns with two thousand dollars if she can do it. I can't believe I beat the shit out of that guy with a fucking hammer
All right
Don't get don't get cocky
Did I bring her back?
850. All right. She has almost eleven hundred dollars in cash. Did I pull her back?
Where's security? There's okay security's coming over
Where's the where's the pit boss? That's a guard. Oh god
There's no pit boss over here
Okay, stop stop stop stop stop
That's a pit boss right there act innocent
are you really gonna go sit down and
Play right next to the guy that's
Your cheat is being ejected from the casino
Did I make did I do I get to keep the money?
I get to keep the money, right?
Wait, we're not going to the basement, right?
No, there I am. I just want to make sure that she's all right
Well, she's all right. I got a little cocky. She's a one-star cheat
If you're between one and five stars if you're a one-star cheat
That's just you elbow the slot machine until money comes out of it. Now. She's got 1100 bucks. They didn't take it from me
Yeah, we're good. All right, she'll be back
Let's head back to the casino
All right. How we doing?
Answers good
Most at 15 market share and some more stuff in here. This blackjack table is getting crushed
Let me I let me run the numbers
Let's get what's okay slots medium bet is not getting played
Blackjack tables, uh dog shit. They're not making any money. So i've made 26 dollars from that. Okay
Look, you gotta play to your strengths and i'm gonna we gotta serve cheap drinks
Blackjack one is just getting killed. All right blackjack. We need cheap drinks
Cheap fucking drink. Let's go
medium quality cheap
Like six bucks for a drink. That's a big deal and we need a restaurant too
Maybe another bar. No, I need um
Which one of these is losing money this one here? Why?
Nobody's playing it
Jackpot. All right return percentage. We're gonna do jackpot percentage low return medium. That's better, right?
Then people will be more inclined to want to play because they just get they get more return
But they don't get a bunch of big jackpots socialite. She's upset. Why?
Isn't it? I can can I see?
Is the city map? All right. Where am I? I'm right here police department
Bank, you can put you can buy property and shit. This is this is crazy
All right. Hold on. I need to see the info from my staff members
It's like the staff info dude. This place gets raided every fucking day. This place gets raided every day
Pre-recorded face cam one. I wonder why
There's a guy who just knows they're just walking around no clothes on
This place is fucked
Cam frozen. I I get it. I get it as I the big nose guy
In the corner. This guy's just resisting
They can't get rid of this guy. He just walks around his dances. There's no clothes on
I need to make like a movie theater. I need all right how much money I only I gotta wait till I have some money
Nobody, okay, they're cooking the books here
Look at this
Empty fucking empty empty empty empty. Nobody's here
This place is all prostitutes only this is this is just a front for prostitution
Nobody does anything here
There's a one chef in the back. That's just very angry
To a point where he's jumping up and down
Leaving for xxx stage show. What's that? It's that guy
It's this guy
Your cheat just got back with some loot
Really?
Nice. Okay, you hang tight for a little bit. How are these going? All right, somebody bought a drink
All right, here we go. We got we got a we got a high roller here. Oh fuck. Yeah
Keep losing 750 bucks down the drain. Let's go
Keep going good again. I got one customer. Yeah it guys this is just like an ipad game
Don't you understand?
Somebody said mobile game. Yeah. Yes. Yes whale from a mobile game
500 people will come here and lose 50 bucks
And maybe gain 30
Did he just shit his pants?
Uh, okay. Anyways, a thousand people will come in here and lose a hundred dollars and then gain like 60
And then all this guy has to happen is this guy has to drop like fifty thousand dollars in 20 minutes
I got a hundred visitors
What congratulations?
Catherine chavir chavir is your 100 visitor click camera to replay movie
Oh
Does the game save automatically?
It does right just make sure it does wait are these two gonna hit it off
Everybody's getting raided
These casinos are just there's prostitutes everywhere in this city
I'm and you guys were telling me wow. I can't believe you like kicked out the hookers. You banned the hookers from coming in
Oh, yeah
Look who hasn't been raided yet. Not me. Although my casino sucks. There's only like slot machines and two blackjack tables
Let me go back to my place. Yeah, these guys are gonna lose out. I'm gaining money. I want to see
Calculate okay. Here we go financial records
furnitures and plants
Bingo the end of the day finally we turn to profit
7200 days profit is 3100 bucks
Okay, here we go profit from blackjack
expenditure income
slot machines
Slot machines are our only thing that's making any money wages
Gambling if that's pain but putting down the slots. This is remember this is like month one. Okay total slot machines are
I mean we're talking about 1700 bucks in revenue
Brink bar is they're doing terrible
Brink bar recovered from cheats. You know, it's bad
when
Half of your income for the month is money you stole from another casino. It's been two days, right? Whatever
All right, let's go back to ours
plan
But no, no, sorry. It's called slots of fun
I think we just all right
It's time to just load this whole bottom floor up with just everybody likes the low machines
Get a right. I get a restaurant. Okay, this is a small kitchen burger kiosk. Yeah burgers
Can I put this like on another floor? Should we have like the food and restaurants be on the second floor?
No
Wait, where should I put it? This is right next to the slot so you can just keep eating hamburgers and go back to playing
Block the entrance
Uh, how about right here? We'll have burger kiosk and then an ice cream kiosk
Yeah, that looks good right here. There we go right at the elevators
Now we need some workers
uh
Level this is a level two
Burgertrition, I don't know what you call this person and then ice cream. Okay. I'm good
All right. We're good. And let's check it out. How can we change this figure?
All right price for a burger quality
high quality, uh
Quadruple cheeseburgers and we'll make them cheap too make them like seven eight seven bucks
No, medium quality seven bucks
What about the ice creams price? Uh
One dollar to make five dollars to sell it. Yeah one scoop. It's not this thing. Whatever that is
Okay, can I take a look at how much money the technician has spent?
The technician is spending all of their money
Where's like staff? Where's like my staff window? Here it is. Okay, here we go
staff
This is the salary. This is it. They're all happy technicians right here
Mr. K. Alberts
Try give mr. K. Alberts like a five dollar bonus
How about like I'll give you five dollar bonus
Here's a five dollar bonus to the technicians that are playing the machine
Okay
There's no attractions here
Do you notice that?
Can I zoom out? It was a a big muscly chest
Is what that lady was looking for?
Okay, we need entertainment entertainment entertainment. Okay
bowling alley
Movie theater a huge movie theater. It's gonna be the second floor. All right, the second was gonna be movie theater. Got it
Floor two movie theater
We'll have two movie theaters on the second floor one. Okay. That's a lot of money. That's a ton of money. Hold on
Just one big movie one movie theater. Okay. How much is a ticket you figure?
Uh prices
Wait, you can have
It's adult but you gotta fucking pay
50 adults adult showings. Why is the screen so thin? Okay. I need like a movie attendant
Uh, this is level three movie attendant
Yep, that's good
50 dollars for porn. Let's see who we attract
Coming up next adult show
We need somebody to come in here
Okay, wait
You better give janitors a raise
Okay, we're not gonna look at that
Okay. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right
We're gonna we're not gonna be on the second floor very much your avatar. Okay. Bye
It's just a porn theater on the second floor
It's just one giant porn room
Oh
Will nobody buy anything?
Quit playing slots and buy food
Okay, we need tables and shit. I need some dining
seating
um
Internal wall. Oh, all right. Hold on. We can do this
Yeah, this like separates it
Yeah, that's like more separated
So it's not you know, just like have to look at the hamburgers
Okay
Well, you know, let's do this. We gotta keep people in the same in the right spot
You can lose your money and lose it. What?
Look, this is this is gonna be a rhyme. There's gonna be like a food court entrance
All right, get out of the way like prostitute number 400
Okay
Now it's not gonna be it'll be like more concentrated
Put like a bench over here
You're blocking the porn entrance. It's not just gonna be porn upstairs. Okay
Casino maze. Yes, every casino is designed to be a maze
It's designed for you to never know where the fuck you are
There are no windows
And it's there's they they build these architects really in a way so you get turned around every 15 minutes
Well, that's fine
There we go. Ooh
These are making money now. We got like high rollers and vacationers coming. Why are you upset?
Oh, this is taking all your money, right?
Drinks doing all right. They're okay. We need some seating near the bar
We need some just like seats, right just to hang out and like talk
It's evening corner. Yeah, like how like right there like we'll do like a little
Is there like a table?
Right there right there
Yeah, like yeah, we can sit down and talk after we get our drink
I can move it around a little bit columns
Okay, how about um
Get another trash can over
Probably in the corner over here. Yeah
This is the food shit
It's the end of the day a lot. Okay. Yeah, that makes sense
Because I've I built a lot of stuff
Palm tree plants. I gotta put some like plants too
right in the corner
All right planting that corner and planting this corner as well
Fuck i'm gonna put stuff in the middle here
I'm gonna have the best bucket. You know, you could ever see
I need a yeah like maybe
ugly
I like plant too
Nice, okay
It's uneven. Yeah, what it's who cares?
There's only one old guy playing blackjack
Seriously
Why does nobody want to play this?
Lost a lot of money here. What happened three days ago? We hit a big jackpot
Nobody bet a bunch of money. That's why I put the minimums low lower the minimums again
I mean lower lower the maximum 50 max. I don't want somebody doing like 50. That's three or four
Yeah, whatever get the fuck out of here
I don't want somebody doing like oh i'm gonna put down like 250 250 bang bang hit hit hit hit hit
And you may you make out like five grand. No 50 max
Advertise the casino not yet. Not until i'm comfortable with how many slot machines i'm gonna do another row right here of low quality slots
And i'm gonna put two super slots right here
high bet slot machine
One two three right in the corner right here
Yep, there we go. Okay, these are expensive
jackpot frequency
high
return percentage
medium
No jackpot frequency low
return percentage medium
No high jack. Uh, should they hit more often but low less money?
Remember jackpot frequency does not mean how much money it pays out
That's it. That's this that's just how often they get like a big number like a big. Whoa, I did I hit something
No, that's how it works
That yeah, no, that's how it works. Trust me. That's what the tutorial said
High return low frequency
Okay, that's wrong. No, that's what the tutorial i'm telling you. That's the tutorial said this
Is that the jackpot frequency does not mean it pays out more money. That's what the return is
We'll do that. We'll let people have some some hits here
Low but big hits
All right, where's high?
I'm gonna have to rename these
I have a lot of slots
17 low high
16 low high. All right, they're good
I'm almost at okay. I have to stop moving around. I gotta i'm running out of money
Our biggest customers
Are the technicians they spend every dollar they make in the casino in the casino
There's somebody in here low the price of the porn theater
Oh
No, yep
He's the best. He was somebody was in there these two guys were in there
Ernie rag sale
Ah that porn sucked i'm gonna go get some cheap drinks
See see you next week nardo
This guy's watching two in a row
Dude, this thing's profiting
Five ten fifteen twenty twenty five. Okay, so he's watched three movies in a row and the other guy watched two
He's a delegate
Oh god, i'm gonna get i gotta look at that one
He's just sitting here in motion
Almost
Okay, can somebody play these?
All right. Now i'm gonna advertise i've got a porn theater
i've got
I've got adequate seating. I've got a cool bar. I've got slots
We've got trailer trash
Put a lava lamp in I only have 3,400 bucks man, and I'm gonna blow it all
This is huge
This is a lava lamp. What the fuck is a lava lamp?
All right, we're gonna put this is gonna be like a little chill corner
Daff unions have voted slots of fun on west street the best place to work in fortune falls you win an award
$2,000 nice
All right. I'm doing good. My market share is almost at 15. This is a little just hangout area
Just come over here and sit down for the drink. All right, it's time to advertise. I got I need I got food
No one's bought any of this. I got food and I've got ice cream
I'm gonna do an advertising campaign
We've got two blackjack tables
No one's here
Where is everybody? Why where are the customers?
Where are the customers?
The only customer is nardo
And he's about to leave
Okay, let's do an advertising campaign
Advertising you can do advertising which is available owned by you right? Okay, so we need
This one this is a high spot. This is 6,500 bucks
I don't have that kind of money
What about boston road right part of the road? Yeah right here
Ready 400 bucks right in front of the train station billboard going this way
get it
Okay, I got an advertising campaign right there
I don't want to I don't lose all my money though. All right, that's good
Good, we're gonna senior here
Where's my uh, okay time to cheat. What are you up to down here? Okay. I need you to go on a mission
If you could that'd be great
Okay, I want you to go cheat
At the toy box casino too
And we're looking for five grand
No, no, we're not your one star thief. We're looking for a thousand bucks. Go for it
There's no way a one star thief is going to take home five grand
You can buy configure view various types of transport. Okay, this is
At least the shuttle buses. All right, so I need to do I need to make some shuttles. How much money do I have?
Pick up and drop. Okay. So this is my casino right here
route one
So I need
What do I want this to start at the train station?
Okay at the train station
They're gonna see the billboard. They're gonna drop off at this two-star hotel
The man this is called city hotels inc
It's the end of the day wages have been paid and then we're gonna come back over here. All right
Here's the shuttle route. This is my casino right here
So they get out of the train station get in you can go to the fucking
Okay, this is the red light district
I don't think I want the I don't think I wanted to go to the red light district first
Uh, and then they get in there and they come all the way over they stop over here at what's lots of fun
Um, let's change this
Let's do
What's the airport? Is there an airport?
At the church. Oh, yeah, let's go. Okay, we're gonna stop at the church
four-star hotel
Over to the casino. Look at that good from the church to the four-star hotel. No get rid of this part
Okay from the church
To the red light district and then to slots of fun. That's the route. All right, she's there
We'll go check on it in a minute. That looks good to me. The competition just bought another property. Okay
Looks good
Um, that's it, right? Is that is that going? I think that's going right? Oh, I need to actually have fucking cars
Shit
Okay. Well the route can stay be careful. We need this money
We desperately need this money. Don't get caught
Cheating the craps. Oh, you're gonna get fucking you're gonna get be careful. You don't want to cheat at craps
That's the worst thing you could have done
450 bucks. All right
All right, last one. We're not gonna go for the limit. We just want you to come back with some money. All right, get out
No one more
Send selected people back to your basement last one. Come on
Come on
You're losing market share fuck. Okay night. No, no
Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Okay. I'm losing market share shit. All right, we go back to my casino
Back to my casino. All right, we got people gambling good make more payouts make more payouts payouts bigger payouts
Yeah, jack return percentage to do medium
We need people to come in and play. Okay, that's good. It's empty. Is there anybody up here watching the porn?
Yeah, there is okay
They're just sitting next to each other
Oh, here we go
Come on in fifty dollars
now, all right now
Now i'm gonna change i'm gonna change the movie on them to a musical while they're in the middle of watching ready
musical
He's pissed
It comes to music. Oh, I ended the movie early
I turned the movie on
I just ran the credits
It's all right. They're still in here. Let's make the price a little cheaper
35 bucks to the musical i'm gaining share. Okay. So here's the here's the thing. Do you now as one of these guys?
Stay here. You paid 50 dollars. It got cut off halfway, but a musical starts playing
Is this your opportunity to say?
Okay, uh
This is what I can tell everybody I did
I watched uh, I watched cats
That's what I did and this is my alibi and this is my my scapegoat here i'm gonna sit and watch this
They walk out. Oh, man. That was a great movie that I watched and I actually did watch that
So thank you for showing that movie that I had someone I paid for goodbye. It's a porn musical
But they're still here. They wait do they pay once?
and then sit and watch again
so wait theoretically if they stay in here could I
Can I charge like five thousand dollars for them right now? This is watching the same movie
Now the only people that do this are the people that are dressed in the darth vader costume. All right
Are you are you doing you watching it again right after it's over?
Okay, I still can go poke. Can somebody go poke cornelius and see if he's still alive
What cheater?
You know what to do. Take his ass
You're cheating the blackjack. Is this the same person from before?
Your cheat is being rejected. Oh fuck
Why did I thought she left?
I thought she left
I didn't tell her to leave
I told she's cheating on her own
Let's see. What what we're gonna do this guy. Why is he down here by himself? Okay. I'm ready
I'm ready for it. Wait, I can't see it. What's he doing to him? The visitor you just beat up denied it
pay attention
He denied it
I didn't do it
The visitor you just beat up denied it
All right, get out of here. Don't come back
What is he
Why did he do that
Why did he do that wait wait get back here
I can't even react
That was fucking crazy
Wait, come outside. He's gone
Made money. Thank god the day wages have been paid
All right, get out of here out get out fire far does it this place burning what
Oh, everybody come to my place
Everybody come to my place
What where?
When we came in here this guy was stomping up
Oh, you got this guy in a fucking cube
Get this guy out of this cube
Did they all come to my establishment
Oh, they all coming to my place now
No, they're not. All right. I gotta get another
Oh, that was fucking ridiculous
God damn it
Why are they just?
prostitutes this whole floor. It's all prostitutes and ten
Delegates. Oh nobody gives a shit anymore now that the porn's not on
Wait, why are you running your business up here? He just he's got three. Oh my god
This guy's just ordered like five prostitutes. He's getting them all
And this guy too. Come on. Come on. Do it. Come on. Get them all
Come on. It's a party. God damn it. Yeah
Wait, what?
There's no place for them to go sleep
Get rid of this guy
Go go go kick this guy's ass
I need a staff member right now
They're not available. Why congratulations you've achieved your first objective
Oh, they did. I got it 15 market share
I got that's what i'm talking about thirty thousand dollars. You've got some new attractions available. Ooh
You can now expand your fast food with the addition of candy soda coffee and I can get a big bowling alley and a dance floor
Market share by another 15 percent enter I need market share in entertainment
Dance floor going right here. How much is it medium dance floor?
Holy shit. Yep. Okay
uh
movie theater dance floor
Where should I put this?
Where's the elevator?
Right here right in the corner. I have found a cheat another cheater
Hold on. Wait, wait, wait. I can I can do a new floor
All right. I got my dance floor. I need a dj
All right, let's go
You figure price to get in 20 bucks. Let's do 10 bucks to get in
And we're gonna do rock and roll
Okay, you're doing fine. You're good. Here we go. Let's get a bunch of people up here
Oh wait, actually, I need I need a dj
Okay. Yeah, so we need that and staff
Here we go
This is gonna be all prostitutes, isn't it?
Why is it?
This is club penguin
What?
Will some of you guys go dance?
All right back to porn
And it's it's a 50 off night
It's only 10 bucks to get into the club
Back downstairs what we got for gambling
All right, we got 27 grand to spend
I can do a new floor
All right. We're starting to get some traction here
I need like a hmm
Wait, what's the person that was cheating?
Oh, sir. Get over here. Are you cheating?
All right. Well, i'm not gonna hit this
I'm not gonna like beat this old lady up with a fucking hammer, right?
There's a lack of one star hotels in the city. I'm gonna look as it doesn't need
I'm gonna deliver
Let's get another floor
Purchase an additional floor fuck
All right. No, we
Oh god
Do I have to watch this every time?
I bet I I guess I do, huh?
And it's a fucking bat this time. Okay
Do you know
The visitor you just beat up is apologize 750 bucks give it back. All right now go home change the second floor
But the second floor has is like my entertainment floor. I got I need a third floor. I need more money
Okay, hold on
Leaving for the crip casino because there's no restaurant. Oh yes there is
No, I need a nice restaurant
Let's put it next to the porn theater
Yeah, this all don't ever have this be anything but a porn theater ever for any reason. I thought this lady's name was edith puke
Okay, save it. Okay porn still going half off porn night
No one has is anybody even here? No, I make it cheaper
eight bucks
How about uh disco?
Yep
Seven bucks disco night
I'm gonna get raided from hookers. Well, why they're all upstairs
I'm like hiding them upstairs for some reason change the second floor to entertainment not casino
I think there's only two options. I think there's only hotel and casino
Yeah, casino floor hotel floor
So if I click this is gonna be a hotel
No, I need that third floor for hotel
Yeah, I need to what do I need for staff?
What's this?
higher
What this is kirby?
This is right to star escort right when they get out of the theater
What was that?
It's the end of the 26 000 bucks good been paid
Somebody's got like punched
Oh, no, it's it's it's okay
Are you coming into dance?
Can we get a dancer?
Yes
Here they come. Oh, I gotta get up there. I gotta get up there. All right, there's on the dance floor
Finally word got out
Pick up all the old people
Holy shit, this guy can move
This is not even i'm losing money on this
Yeah, why this is sleepy?
Let's take a look. How's how's staff doing?
All right. This floor man is making a ton of money
Who's making the least money
You're not making okay. Yeah, let's give you like six bucks an hour. Whatever right whatever this is six bucks a week
Nobody's coming to buy anything from you. We're gonna make you happier. Let's do six bucks
Who's the most skilled it's trash this place is filthy
um edith puke
has
Been in this theater
and has seen
Probably 15 pornographic movies in a row
There are no trash cans up here. Well, fuck I gotta well, I just looked out of the window
We're good. I think the game crashed
Uh, uh, uh
It's trying it wants to
I did just save it like two minutes ago though. So that's good
Yeah, we're gonna have to kill it. I did just save it. Oh fuck. I can't even that
I can't even escape
I'm stuck in here. I gotta control all delete
Uh-oh
Even the task manager can't come up
Oh shit, this is bad
Is it paused? No, it's crashed out
Shit, I can't even I can't get it off
It's hard crashed. It keeps resetting
And trying to come on get out
Get out get out get out get out get out do it. How do you force quit an application?
That's not control alt delete. I can't do what is it control what?
Alt f4. I hope I don't okay. I hope I don't close out of obs
Try windows and tab
I mean it's working but it's not working
Yeah, I I can do windows and tab and pull the window up, but I can't get rid of it
Change your desktop
New desktop
Okay
Now let's see if I can get task manager on here. Nope
Fuck got it down. Wait, hold on. Can I do it from here?
Wait, I can do always on top
This should do it
always on top
Got it. Okay
End task got it got it. Yeah. All right. We're good
Let's just open it back up and I did just save it. So that should be fine
Uh-huh. Uh-huh. All right. Let's see load game
Uh, it is this one
Wait, this one auto saved
Auto say this one's closer, right?
17 25 48 17 for yeah, that's like
Five minutes before this crashed
Let's do it too many hookers now we we just rewind about three minutes
See everything's back to normal
Remember I said he is puke has been here for like three or four straight hours
All right
Like that like that sound man. I gotta just fucking get away from it
I want a bowling alley advertise again this time. I want a really good one
This one right here on east street. It's like insanely high quality buy it
plus
The routes we were gonna do remember route one. Here it is
from
Church to the red light district over to the casino now. We just need to have a shuttle
Are you sure I want? Yes, I am sure I want a new shuttle
In fact, i'll take two of them
Done did they come?
Good now we have uh, now we have some we have some good. Um
Now we need a trash can I need another another where's janitor?
I need a janitor
Look this place starting to really
Pick up uh customers
All right. I need a janitor
Where is my janitor?
Near staff janitor
You I want you to come up. All right. You're just staring at a wall. Come up here
I want you up here to pick up trash out. Are you moving?
Now come up go in the elevator
Come up here. All right. Go good. Get up there and clean
I drop for a chance to get a kiss
I think this game is less than five dollars on steam
It's still puke on the ground right in front of the food
We're gonna change this to
like
Low quality and it's two dollars
Yeah, low quality two bucks
Low quality three two bucks
We need customers and I need a uh, I need a trash can upstairs. Thank you. Finally. All right
We got a movie theater. We got a dance floor
Cheating profit is twenty six thousand dollars. What?
how
Who's cheating you?
Oh with the 30 grand, right?
Get out of here speaking of cheating
Oh, she's a level three thief. Yep
We have a level three thief now
Okay, you level one thief you go start stealing just go to go to the crypt casino. That place is a fucking dump. Okay
Just go they get 500 bucks and come back
You you're gonna go to the high class place
And you're gonna I want you come back with more but toy box casino is a big hit
I want 50. I want 1750 from the toy box. You know, so do you think okay?
Uh, should I have a limo service? Okay
Uh limos automatically cruise the city and stop at certain preset points. You just need one or two
I'm gonna buy one limo
We want a limo service because we want to bring in the the high class customer seems good to me
No entertainment only cars. What I got what do you mean? I got plenty of entertainment
I've got a dance floor up here
And it's cheap. It's only all right. Nobody who wants disco
brah
country
It's eight bucks country time
I've got a dance floor and I have a porn theater and this thing has brought in two thousand dollars. So
Go to the attraction
Who's going to the attraction?
Country
Okay. Now I need a trash can
we uh
Janitors and hookers
Okay
trash can
Let's put some fucking slots up here, dude. Get them up here
No, no, no, let's get like let's get sports betting
Sports betting in the bowling alley right next to it
That's perfect
Yep. Oh, that's ugly
But no this works
Okay, don't don't spend any more money bowling alley and a sports betting kiosk
Okay, how much does it cost to go to the bowling alley? That's a lot of money. How about how about 10 bucks for bowling?
and then minimum bet
50 dollars
Maximum bet 250 no maximum bet
Yeah, 250 this is gonna be a high roller section up here the lack of one-star hotels in the city fuck
Any of you hookers know how to bowl?
high roller bowler
Good idea
Wait, what?
How did you get in here?
She's a kid
What the fuck get out out out? How did you get in here? I don't have I don't have a doorman
I don't have a doorman. I don't have a doorman. I don't have a doorman. I don't have a doorman. I don't have a doorman
I don't have a doorman. I don't have a doorman. I need a five-star doorman
Uh, what is that? That's a doorman, right?
This guy's 500 rolls a week
How about okay you you're 300. All right you know, I need a three-star. Okay, I need a doorman
There's no fucking doorman
doorman
All right now get out there. He's a pianist
What?
I thought he was a doorman
I thought he was like a hotel doorman
He's a pianist. He doesn't even have a piano
What is he doing?
Is it the pianos?
I need a piano. All right, we're gonna do what we're gonna put a piano down here. What's he doing?
Where is he?
Is this guy eating trash?
Oh my god
What
What is that? All right, where's the I need a doorman. Oh
Stop him attack him
Kill this guy
Punch him. Don't let him go out there. Don't let him go there with a teenager
Get him
Press this guy
Is he fucking kidding me? Get out of here. Where's the police?
Where's the police?
Stop stop get out of the way somebody grab this guy
Somebody get this guy. Okay, I got him
Somebody what do we do with them?
All right, get him get him out get him out. How do we take him out?
It's the end of the day wages. Um, your cheat has arrived
Stop puking get
Get him out
Eject him
It's twenty thousand dollars. Get rid of him
Are there no police in here?
It's because the quality of the food
Food
It's fucking bad
Bad rotten food
Oh fuck
Okay. Hold on. I gotta slow down. Wait, who's this guy? This is so wait. What did I do?
What the fuck was that? The visitor you just beat up denied it was slapping him
The camera is like a hard to control. I'm sorry. I'm freaking out right now
I need to I need a janitor
I need a janitor. I need a janitor janitor
Janitor, I need downstairs and then you just
I need a janitor
It was like kids in here this place sucks
Oh
He was thrown up everywhere. There's like teenagers that are in here. It was like, oh I need a janitor. How do I pause?
Where's the janitor? I'm gonna lose my mind
What the fuck are you two doing?
Come clean this trash can
and
How many kids should we have?
Okay, good figure medium quality food
Now high quality food and sell at a discount so people stop getting sick
I have nine thousand dollars. I can do it high quality ice creams
the six dollars
Okay. No, no, no. I'll just six dollars high quality food
Oh my god
You're gonna lose money. I what am I supposed to do? This is insane
I lost all my customers. They're all gone
No, I didn't
Okay, we're good. I'm at 13 market share entertainment
Clean this shit
Clean this up. This is ah, this is horrible
Why are you so defiant? I'm gonna give him a bonus
Here i'll pay you 12 dollars
Start cleaning up man
Thank you
Get rid of the wall should I get rid of the wall?
Oh my god
Okay, sell the wall
People are just throwing up and then going and watching porn and then coming down and eating like poisoned food poisoning food
Puking going back upstairs and watching porn again
This place is a joke
This is an absolute fucking joke of the place
Where's the pianist?
I just I hired like a five thousand dollar pianist. Where is he? Where is he? I don't have any people here
Oh, I did it. I'm gonna get some money
$10,000 reward nice. You've got some new attractions available. You've now been licensed for marriages and you can purchase a wedding chapel
You'll need a host take a look at your third objective
Ooh
Okay, wish I I need another floor
However, you're going to need some serious cash to build a gambling and entertainment empire
Increase your cash reserve by twenty five thousand dollars and keep it for 24 hours
Where is the pianist? What the hell are you doing down here? What? Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
Are you in the basement? I need a piano. How much is a piano?
Can't even buy a piano
We're forming a union
Arcade and I have to clean this shit up man
Just wait
This guy refuses to work
It's unbelievable. There's more track. I need more janitors like where's the other one upstairs get down here
We need a couple of personnel
We need uh you
Yep, we'll have you here. We'll have you over here
We gotta get some more. We're getting some income from this shit sports betting
Big money. I roll a bowling high roller you go downstairs now. Just got back with some loot nice
675 bucks good good haul
All right, get down here and help them clean
I'm gonna I gotta hire like three more temporarily three or four more janitors
Yeah
Okay, we're gonna do one
two
Three three janitors four four janitors temporarily. We'll fire them when they're done. We need this place needs to be deep cleaned right now
Medium high quality drinks eight bucks five seven six dollars a pop. These are taking in some money
I think I want to change these up a little jackpot frequency medium
return
medium
Fire the pianist
Oh shit, that's right. I should fire the pianist where to go. I'm trying to fire him buddy. I'm sorry
I really hate to do this, but I thought you were a doorman. Have a nice day. He's pissed off now
Well, what am I supposed to do?
What are these people doing over here? Why is this guy over here?
Where's the penis?
I'm gonna lap my ass off if he just goes over to one of the slots
Okay, we're nice and clean now
clean
This crash what what does this need to be clean?
What's this? Oh, okay. It's good
Okay, we're now cleaned up
Uh, we're gonna fire the weakest of all the janitors
How do I how do I get the teenagers? I need a doorman
Doorman that's a waiter
dj
post dealer
Here it is. Okay. Okay guard
doorman
This is a five-star doorman. You bet your ass. He's going right here
I mean, I want to guard wait. That's why
The bounces was just beating the shit out of that guy. That was that escort, but this is like a police officer
All right, we need you walking around control
There we go. Finally
Okay. Now I can set
Where is it?
Doorman reports that high roller ryan
mcgroy has just entered wages have been paid. Oh cool
All right. How do I with my with my how do I do this and I edit door policy? There it is
Um, no fucking teenage. No teenagers, please. No fucking
Frighten. No, should I keep trailer trash?
Royal high, okay
All right. No teenagers stay out
If I make an arcade
Maybe I can have a teenager arcade
People are actually buying the food now
Okay
We've cleaned up our act
Now let's fire half the janitor
Janitor who's the most high skilled janitor who's okay. We got a low skilled janitor
Here's the the the lowest skilled janitors are gone trip casino is being raided again
That's so good. We got rid of two
What was I doing right upstairs?
Oh people look
alvin kaufman
He's up here. Oh, yeah, he's sleeping. I threw one ball time for bed. That's why I need a I need a hotel upstairs
This is still adult. It is. Yeah, 30 bucks now, please. Thank you
I'd like to cook you breakfast. Okay
Devin has this
whoa
900 bucks in profit somebody came in here with a lot of money. I'm gonna keep the way it is then
All right, 25 grand
Change it from country, please
Well, I just people using it
Before this was country
Nobody would come in
I've made 500 bucks since changing this to country
All right, we'll do classical 10 bucks. I don't have a classical dance party. This thing is the biggest profit
3,300 bucks so far that takes in the most money
500 visitor
I want a different name
All right, I want to change my name. I don't like this name. We're gonna change it to
slot of
the fun and
slots
Slamming slots
Slamming slots and lanes. Here we go slamming slots and lanes
nice
Bouncer has spotted somebody causing a disturbance
We got an old lady fight
Wait, what?
This is an old lady fight
Hold on. Uh
where
They let they took it outside
No, they're good. They took it outside
I need more table games. That's another problem. I'm gonna have let's see. What do I want?
I want me like a roulette table
I roll high roller dutly rickets has just entered. We need a high roller table over here
Right in the back right here
This is a good spot for like a nice nice high roller roulette table
100 max bet 100 minimum bet
This is the high roller table right here
High roller hong kuang has just entered the slots. Okay good. They'll be sitting right here
Another one high roller sad fra has entered. Okay, let's go. Come on. Get them all over here high rollers
Because I got a minimum bit of a hundred bucks a minimum sit over here
Where are they garfield weller?
Oh, no, that's the floor man. Where's this high roller door, man
What the fuck are you doing? Do your job?
eject eject eject
This is supposed to be a five-star door, man
Get out
Guys sleeping on the job. What are you doing?
To take ten dollars off of your pay
All right. Where's the high rollers? Where are those high rollers? Where are my cheats?
You know you go back to toy box casino come back with two grand if you can
Good configured door policy. Yeah, I did
This shit was configured man
Look ready door policy
No teenagers are not allowed in here. He's not even he's not even paying attention
Look at this
He's done. What are you doing?
He's just standing there. No, I said no teenagers
Get out
out
Leave leave
It's for the second floor only
How much food are you gonna eat?
Wait a minute you shitting me. You're telling me that you're gonna go to the crypt casino now
to drink
You can drink at the crypt casino apparently
And what the fuck are you talking about?
If you're under you a teenager can drink at the crypt casino
Where's the crypt casino?
I want to see this
Holy shit
Teen
Are you letting teenagers in here?
And why are you letting them drink?
Wait, what what was her name?
How do you got your casino set up?
Do you got all right? Yeah, you're showing there's a convention starting soon wildlife convention. We'll start in a few days
Really?
Who cares?
What does that have to do with me?
Wages have been paid support. Yeah, there's porn right here. Okay, you got hold on you got two
All right, this place let me i'm i'm spying on this place. This place says one two
Three four this they've got like three movie theaters a couple of bars in the middle arcade
Holy shit. This place is awesome
pool tables
Super lanes dance floor
What's on the third floor?
Wow, this is where the casino is this place is cool. I would come here
Look at all these medium slots
Nice what's on floor four?
restaurants and dinner and bar and stuff
Large kitchen well, at least this one's not gonna burn
What's on five?
And more this guy's look at how much money this person has a cool bar in the middle
Way too many movie theaters though. I will say anybody getting beat up in the basement
That's not a real casino that I I run a real casino. We will get beat up in the basement
Now let's go back to mine. What is this place?
Oh, it's the train station. Okay, let's look at my place in comparison
Cheating let's get out
These tables are losing a lot of fucking money
a lot of money
up the minimums
25 dollar minimums
I'm sorry. They uh, like at least for temporarily
Oh
Dude, look at this
We got two socialites here hundred dollars a bet
Look at the money this thing's taking them. Okay, they don't give a fuck
1600 bucks eye roller coming in put the doorman outside
I mean, I don't I think he he he just stands at the door
Change the tables winning chances. Well, it's roulette. There's no such thing
How you doing? You happy?
3,500 bucks coming in. Look at this
Oh, they won
Dicks
I gotta add some more traction. Yeah
These guys just stand at the door
All right, we need some more. What do you think? Uh, another row of slots over here
Or too many commotion maybe more table games
The blackjack tables are not doing well roulette tables doing all right. See a cheat another cheater
All right, well just just beat him up
Uh, did I pick the wrong person?
No, no, no, that's the wrong person. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. She just moved tables. No, no, no, no, you're fine
Over here. Uh, the doorman is reported that another high roller is in here. Oh your cheetah's there
Cheater run. Where's she going? All right, she's going up
Looking for two grand here. What's the what's the play?
Perhaps
This is the three-star cheat
blackjack
Right in front of the fucking floor man. Are you serious?
The visitor you just beat up is apologized
Um
Why would you do that right in front? You're supposed to be a three-star cheat
Can you just run?
All right, just run
run away
being disciplined
All right, should I just fire?
I think you got I think you I think this is you got you're fired
You sat down
At the table in front of the floor, man
Is
She gonna snitch
Uh, I think he killed her your cheat has taken a beating
Well, I was gonna fire you anyways
She changed sides
Oh you piece of shit you yeah, she changed on me
She dropped just now. She's the cheater for the okay. What was her name? What was her name? What's her name?
What's her name? What was her name? You remember the name? I want the name if I see her in my casino
She's dead, you know, I mean dead
We're gonna whack her. What was her name? Okay. Keep in mind
give me an alert if you see her a lot of traffic in front of the uh,
slots and lanes or whatever the fuck this place is called
All right. I need uh some surplus
These two people have been sitting here playing
But we need drinks. I need another bar
I think it's time to i'm gonna I I got a can this blackjack table is fucking fresh
These things are doing. All right
The middle one's taking in some money this blackjack table is dog shit like this one at least
I need a new carpet
How much candy oh no, this is huge
Table finally I can make a table
This is what I wanted for so long like right here. Okay, let's get rid of this shit
Sell this crap
I can stay. All right. Let's put a nice like table right here. You know what get rid of this shit
I'm sorry. You're gonna have to stand up
We'll move that get up
Is that table? Where's table?
Where's table?
Oh
Why does it want me to have a waiter like to wait for the burger and ice cream stores?
Really put the doorman outside. I
What are you talking about?
Now, I don't think the game is is that intelligent
The doorman has been already telling me things. I'm getting i'm getting doorman puff up
Like i'm getting doorman puff up
How am I supposed to move the doorman?
There is no doorman go outside. What are you talking about?
Buy a third floor. I will in just a second hire a new one outside. I don't think that's how it works
Yeah, doorman reports that the doorman is doing his job
It's the end of the day
What she's here? What what where where?
Where is she? Where is she?
Where is she? Where where where where where where she's here?
That's not her
No, there's like five models in the game guys. It's not her
carmelia
edita
Elvira monica
She's at the bar
What the wait, who is this? Oh, it's a there's a furry convention in town
Right. Okay
Ah, you see it worked
He doesn't go outside. Look, he just said uh, uh, get out of here. He did his job. See
upstairs
alexine
joe
My god, no
Stop
How do I?
Huh? This is on my staff
No, that's alexine. Oh
Well, nobody will see your identity
I need
janitors
Is it a rhino?
That guy just puked in his mask
Oh god
Oh my god, that's so bad
Technology high roller next to trailer trash in a rhino costume and he just puked in the costume
What do you think these guys are talking about right now?
What do you think the conversation is?
Remove the trailer track
The police say your casino is full of puckers
What because the god damn good god thing you gotta you gotta fucking you had a teenager in here
And I try to
Get them all up get out out out out out
Staff not the panda not the panda out out out out out. Where's the with my other bouncers?
Near a staff bouncer
I don't have any bouncers available bouncer bouncer bouncer get out
Like i'm hiring another bouncer. This is fucking ridiculous
All right out
Get them out
Reject leave out. I don't you're gonna get me you're gonna be getting trouble
Where's the other guy?
Out puke everywhere. Why is the puke everywhere?
Do I not have any bouncers available for this?
hold on
He just insta he puked and it was instantly cleaned up by a
This guy's got to go
This guy has got to go
He's pushing employees
He's just shoving employees
All right, get him out of here kick kick his ass beat kick beat this rhino's ass, please he's shoving people
That's too much you didn't have to shoot him in the fucking head
What the fuck are you doing?
Garfield is gonna go to jail
Kill
They don't know who did it they don't know who did it
Oh, he's serious
Oh my god, my head hurts
I can't believe he shot him and killed him
It just kind of ruined everything
He's so proud of himself
Okay, he is
He is a one-star guard. So I guess
Like hey like hey
Go beat that guy up
He's he's pushing employees and he's hurting people and he's throwing up on people and he punched a person
He punched one of our janitors
I guess like
I shoot that guy in the head is the response for a one-star guard
Holy shit
Everything about that was fucking crazy
Oh
Okay, can we oh no, everything's clearing out
What about
Wait, did they arrest him? No, let's make a hotel while this cools off a little
My goodness. Okay. Look at this. This is insane
All right, tell one of your ads is finished running. Yes. Yes. Yes
Leave
Eject
Why the janitor is not coming up here. I don't know eject them all
Wait, all the hookers are gonna walk by
Uh
nothing to see here officers just
I wonder the police leave
I have more police in here than I have patrons
Here they come. This guy's trying to get the fuck out
Oh man, he's running for the exit. Where's garfield? Wait, why are they what do you mean disturbance? You're causing a disturbance at the exit
Did you flick him the finger?
Fuck out of here. He wanted to pay. Clifford wants a pay raise
It's the end of the day
Where's officer garfield
He's leaving quitting. He's quitting. He's quitting. You can't quit. You can't quit. Don't let him quit. Don't
Get rid of the hookers. What do you want me to do?
Just i'm trying get out
Out all of you
I'm not gonna shoot anybody. I'm not gonna shoot them. I'm just gonna say leave
I have a word
Doorman them
Just shut the door
Okay
This thing's seen 4100 bucks
Okay, and it's causing problems
All these the furry convention. Everyone's like
He's all right. All right. I gotta we we've had a problem. We gotta fix it
I'll put this on expenses
Are you gonna play?
If the janitor arrays
I want to try let's okay. Let's go over some staff here
Uh this the janitor everyone's pretty happy
Who's saying that?
This game is outrageous man. Oh, there's a fire
Huh?
It's another chef on fire
Why is it always the chef that's on fire?
Okay, we gotta spend some money. Here we go. We're gonna buy an additional floor
Let's go. We're gonna spend some money
Buy a new floor and this is gonna be a hotel floor
One to five star rating
They there's no one. We need a one star hotel the room rate is going to be
60 bucks a night
one star
Third floor is there
They said there was no one star
Hotels in the area there is now
But these aren't expenses
and
Seriously, this is unbelievable. The convention has now finished
I need a janitor up here now
I'm playing this
15 bucks
How's this doing? Huge money good
Bury convention i'm gonna just bowling a little bit. We need some money. I got people have to get up here
Crash can 3 is full. Yeah, no shit. All the janitors are standing around downstairs
Get over here janitor 3
Go upstairs
That's not a janitor
Get up there
Get upstairs
Clean that
Buy another janitor. All right, i'm gonna fire a janitor downstairs and hire one up here
How many janitors do we have?
um
This one's gone. And so is this one
But who is pissed off here?
This this janitor is not happy
Take a bonus of five dollars
That'll hopefully hopefully help you up. All right. I don't care about the high rolls
What is he doing up here
Get out
Do not
attack
Do not do that
Do not
Okay janitor
Who's firing a gun
What the hell is that?
janitor
Start cleaning, please god
This is still playing porn
Firefighters have another fire at the cheetos casino
At least the chef got out. Okay this time
Thank god
They're locking them in they lost all that look at this
You lost. Yeah, you lost it now. It's coming to me in my group everybody in the hotel
Nobody in this home is it because it's too expensive 45 dollars a night
that's
Very that's dog shit cheap. That is cheap as shit 45 dollars a night
Do you need staff there? You guys know you do not need staff
All right. I got some room here. Let's make some more slot machines
Those are the ones that print the money
Or don't fucking poke her over here. No, I need another room
craps
No backer rat a whole lot of room
For god damn it
You go right here
Go right here
Negative 28. Yeah. Well, I did some wages. I did some work
All right, let's get some backer rat going here minimum bet
50 bucks
75 max bet 200
You're failing at keeping a casino in the black. What? I just made a bunch. I just spent a bunch of money
Here we go hotel room who's in these rooms?
Oh first customer coming in
Okay, these are occupied
Did you leave the water running?
Rhino wants bubbles. All right, the hotel is going good so far
I'm gonna take this guy ages
All right. I need now i'm gonna start bringing in some actual income here
Empty that trash can
I'm gonna put another uh, another one up here. I need it
Add just we got they just gotta be two walking around. That's just that's too much junk. I need some seats
Put like a sofa over here
People can like hang out and watch sports betting if they want to like one two three
One two three. This is how it works
Cheating at blackjack. Uh, fuck
Uh cheetah at blackjack
Oh interesting. All right, you know what to do
What's with the puking?
honest to god
What is with the puking?
Why are they puking?
puking
I change the food quality is better
They're just hurling
Oh, so nobody works here anymore. Are you gonna are you gonna fight the bouncer? Are you stupid?
Oh my god
Get high quality drinks
I mean there are high quality drinks high quality drinks eight bucks
I need another dealer here
How many more how many two?
One on each side
I'm bleeding money. Am I?
I mean, how many fucking dealers do I need?
what
Three dealers
All right. Finally. All right. This is this better make some money
Who's the guard? Who's the guard? That staff is not happy. Hold on
salary, all right
27 bucks
35 27 bucks supply
Ah, what your level three janitor wouldn't even do it
35 fine
Level one dealer and you want more money?
Get out
Now you okay you i'll give you 10 bucks
Jay fry i'll give you your level one dealer man
No
level one dealer
Fine. Let's see how much better you do level four technician
This dealer is pissed
Which one?
This is a dealer
What do you mean? What?
Oh, okay, right. No, no, no
All right 60. How does that sound you want more than 60? I'll give you a bonus of 10 20 bucks
15 buck bonus good
Bouncer wants more than 40 city average is 35. You know
Technician is 65 bucks
She said the average is 60
60. Oh what i'm overpaying you
55 give you a bonus of 10 bucks
I'll give you a bonus of five dollars
I'll give you a bonus of five dollars and i'll give you 22 bucks
All right, that's it. This is losing money. Why is this? Oh cheating
I didn't I
what
Where's my bouncers?
Where the fuck are any bouncers?
There's a there's a visitor causing a disturbance
He's spitting on him
No, there's somebody cheating
Oh my god, where are the bouncers?
What get the fuck downstairs now?
All right. Thankfully how much are these making?
Yeah, I think the play here
Is slots look at these medium slots
They're just absolutely destroying. All right, we're doing more medium slots over here
It's gonna be some expenses, but i'm gonna go for it
a thousand bucks a piece
They they make a lot of money
All right, and well don't spend any more money. Yeah, apologize. Thank you
1.7 000
This is where we just hold on for a little bit. This is losing so much money
Max bet make it higher
All right, I fired this guy
fire anybody else
No, we need some waiters. Oh, yeah, I need a hamburger step
Level four, I just need level two
All right, it's the reason why everybody's getting so sick is because you're a level one server
Blackjack is losing money. Yeah a lot
This one why is this one losing so much money?
It's because this somebody's just burning it. It's because the cheaters is this person cheating
We don't know that
Where's the floor manager?
Get over here
Check on this guy
I'm gonna give him a look
I'm sure they're cheating
Oh, they are cheating
Interesting
It's the end of the day wages have been paid
Get him downstairs. He's this guy's got three or four grand in his pocket
Kill that guy
Oh
2,400 bucks. That's my money, but he's level five cheater. He's a level five cheater and he's ours now
There's a convention starting cowboy convention
Excuse me. One of your ads has finished running
Action that might be too much money. Maybe I'll have 30 30 bucks. They're all gonna come up
All right, let's go. I i'm gonna send this guy to take a ton of money. This is a level one cheat
I mean, we got a level five cheat at this point. I'm sorry elinor
I think it's time for you to go
now you
You are going to go take money from
He's a level five
He could go in the cheetah casino. There's another fire at the pasta italiana
Italiano
Wait, no, no, no, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop
Fire
That place needs to be redesigned
Go get five thousand fucking dollars. Can you do it at the cheetahs casino? Can you come back with five grand?
Go check on the pasta italiana
Where is it?
pasta italiano
Um, there's nobody
So
Actual firefighters this time. I think the chef may have done this
I believe the chef, uh
Is responsible for this one. This is a nice place. I'm gonna I should buy it bleeding money somehow
Fuck you. What?
You you
No, don't kill I can't get the money back if I kill her
Nice 4200 bucks. Look at the book on this thing
Come on
Minus 18 minus 24. I only have one bouncer. No, I have like three
Where's that cowboy convention you need to go back downstairs
He's got to hang out downstairs
I'll do another bouncer down here
Hang out down here. This is who you just beat up is apologize
Oh lee shit
this person
Absolutely ran me through the absolute render
7800 dollars
You've got to be kidding me
Are these things are running yet? Nobody on them what he's using them jackpot low percentage
Yeah, you know what? Let's make some let's get some let's get some turn around
Big payouts on these machines because they're new you've got to make sure they pay out
Big jackpots big payouts get them hooked
Okay, where's my uh, is my criminal? All right, he's there. He's there. Okay, we're looking for five grand
This is bad
Is he going going upstairs? Okay
Waiting for orders cheat
Cheated the slot machine
Oh my god. Nice
Wait, stop stop stop stop stop stop
A lot of bouncers just came off that elevator
Okay now
Cheat at over here cheat at this one. Wait, why you can't cheat? Oh, because somebody went to it. Okay now go. Um
Nobody got these tables. All right, you're good cheat again. There's just a bunch of waiters on here. I see a floor man
God damn it. Watch out. Did you see me? He knows
There we go. This thing's blocked by a wall
They made this cool attraction over here. Oh, it's a wedding chapel. Can I rob the wedding chapel? Come on
Come on do it cheat. Is he waiting? Is he just playing the machine?
I think he's just playing this
Steal don't just play what are you doing?
Are you gonna cheat it back or at that's dangerous. I don't there's no floorman over here. This is perfect opportunity. No floorman at all
Here we go. 1100. Let's keep on the eye out for floorman
This the security in this place really sucks
I'm gonna come here every time i'm gonna come here and take five grand every single time
every time
Keep an eye out for the floor. We're good
Good keep going
I stop at five
Um
Why stop at five this to the janitor and this old lady are getting married. Wait, who's getting married?
Oh, no. Okay, the two old people are getting married
We made 10 grand. It's the end of the day. We go back to this table over here
Oh, and that's sweet that's sweet, isn't it?
You're going upstairs. I'm gonna pull twenty thousand dollars out of this place
And then i'm gonna make another i'm gonna make another bowling alley
Are they going up?
We're done
There's a convention that's just started good
Oh, I see what he's doing here the room that has no security
Holy shit. This is a fucking george cloney
seven million iq oceans
12 whatever it was
All the way in the back
No floor manager at all cheating. Well cheat then he just had a good spot
He's gonna get shot. He's not gonna get shot
He's not he's gonna be fine. No floorman
Playing the blackjack. This is the this is the one that I got most of my money taken from
Time to return the favor
He's not gonna get shot
This guy doesn't know what's going on the floor man and the security team do it. This is dude
This guy just carries out the sentence
Should I try to get a hundred thousand dollars from this place? We're doing
I've detected cheating on the floor. What?
Oh
Okay, you stay right there for a second. Oh, we're gonna throw this guy out
We're good
3,500
Okay, watch that elevator for a floor man
No, this is a high roller
I'm walking out of here with at least ten fifteen thousand dollars
This is gonna pay for my new floor
Thanks a lot cheetahs casino made a better view
I won
What no don't do it. We're good. Everything's fine
Candor is not gonna do shit
The visitor you just beat up is apologize, but uh-oh
It's nice. Not gonna say anything is he?
You're constantly losing thousands of dollars. I'm like i've got 12 000 bucks
And i'm about to pull back another
What's the book look like?
My book looks pretty good
11 000 12 000 i'm in i'm in the full. I mean a few days ago. There was an issue, but i'm i've got 1600 bucks in cash
Honestly, why stop at 20 when you can do 50?
Blackjack is losing money. Yeah, but that keeps them in the casino
They'll win 100 bucks at blackjack and then they'll blow it all in the high limit slot machine
Why not a million? I mean, why not? You're right
Get down get down get out
Go go go go to get out get out get out get out get out
That's 6200 bucks that I took out. Look at him. He was ready
Just make sure he gets out
You know what's out? He's almost out. He's almost out. He's almost out. He's almost out. Uh
Go at 6200 bucks. They thought it was the old guy
really
Wait, what?
Imagine they were beating up the old guy down here. That'd be so sad. All right, we got 6200 bucks
But that's a very good use of our time
Okay, let's see
uh
Blackjack and baccarat are getting crushed the three slot machines. Nobody's playing them at too high
Why nobody's playing what's the most roulette one is the most profitable thing?
And all the slots on the left side. Why is nobody playing those?
I closed blackjack down. Let's go check out the casino. How's it doing?
Now that's what we're talking about
1,845 profit. That's good
Almost every room is occupied too
Yeah, i'm gonna i'll get rid of the uh
Blackjack tables just getting killed
This one's all right. This one. Yeah, we're gonna we'll get
What a fight
Where are they? It's a cowboy convention guy
He's sprinting to go to the sex show
I kind of want to see how this plays out
We voided the cop
He's not happy
I have no idea where he's even going
Your cheat just got back with some loot
Yeah, thanks for 6200 bucks
He's made it to his destination
I've detected cheating on the floor
All right. Well, fuck it. This is a cheater
Okay, 21 000. I need to hope we need more
I need 44 grand. We need some more profit
Offers to services
Sure
I'll take the 900 bucks he took from me, too. How's this doing?
You figure
Medium and bring the price down
No one's ordering this shit. I need a restaurant man
I need I need a restaurant
How's the hotel doing?
Uh almost two thousand dollars in profit so far
Pretty good
This is not doing bad. This is doing pretty well too. Still with that fifty dollar minimum bet
This is doing all right drop the price
25 bucks
All right. Okay. What is this person even doing?
Who's wait is he yelling at this person?
It's this case the cowboys the cowboys are causing trouble
How much does he pay?
There you go. Eleven thousand dollars in profit wages have been paid
Yeah, right where the sun down. Yeah. All right. I have
Uh, you guys are not doing anything at all
How do you get fired?
Wait, somebody's not happy
Thousandth visitor got it
What's what's wrong?
Why are you unhappy?
level one technician
Bar staff little four bar staff
Oh shit, you've been working here a long time
You make this doorman makes a ton of money
Fine. I'll give you 165 the bonus of five bills
I'm not even happy really
Let's go back down here
Uh
This looks like it's a pretty it was a pretty bad investment unless it's because of the wall
Are they not going ever could know there's a wall over here. No, it's not. Okay. I gotta move this. I gotta move
No somebody whoo
I jackpot medium return did he just win
Ah, he just won. I just he put 150 in and then it just gave him 150
Shit hundred it's it's fifty dollars a bet on these things. He's not gonna hit
Help he's pissed. He's not gonna hit he won his 150 back and now
He's just gonna lose it
Still win eject him before he cheats. This guy's not gonna just he's not cheating. He's losing money
Changed the settings while he plays that's fucked up
He's being watched
Well now they're coming in
There we go
All right, this thing took in 250 bucks
All right, the bar has a bar doing high quality drinks. That's good
Baccarat table is getting fucking killed pull the bets down
25 minimum hundred all the max it's getting killed
We i'm gonna get rid of blackjack while i'm gonna place a roulette. I'm gonna move
This blackjack over here. We're gonna do two roulette tables here. I'm gonna do another advertising campaign
Uh, I want a couple
right here
Do it and then I want another I want another good one
Another three or four star right here
Do it
another one
Fill this place with people
You are the one for me
Is an omega link omega low link? Um, I gotta be careful. I don't think I should click it because it might crash again
All right. Hold on. Let's hope this doesn't crash
Why do you want to use this
My nose ain't that big
There you go. Okay, so I have a huge ad campaign going
No, we've got a we've got a belligerent drunk
All right, you're up
That's enough scream. Oh, this is what happens. This is why I didn't want to alt tab
I told you this was gonna happen. Yeah, it's crashed. I told you this is gonna happen
I told you guys this is gonna happen
I think I can actually reset it though. I saved it. I can't click on any more links. I'm sorry
They're not gonna be i'm not gonna be able to do it
That's the one that's your one link you get for the night
He remains
There we go. All right. I just did an ad campaign
Oh, right, this is right before we uh, i've detected cheating on the floor thinks he has spotted an employee
Wait, the dealer is cheating
How does that make any sense?
Hold on the dealer is cheating
What?
Wait, is that this is a cowboy guy? Okay. Look
Let him cheat
That's good. It means the customer loses. Yeah, but he takes the money
All right, what what do you want the bat the axe the whip or the frying pan
The convention has now finished. I guess i'll take the uh, you don't get a chance
Oh, I feel bad these he took 15 dollars. Oh, that's not even a big deal
That's not a big deal at all. That's not very much
that's
Oh, that's I don't think that
Wait, now he wants a raise
You motherfuckers
All right fine
65 dollars
You want more than 65 fucking to 780?
All right, get out of here dealer 85 90
Door man, you just got a raise you i'm about to fire the doorman. I'm gonna fire the door
I gotta fire you just got a raise like you got two raises. He's a five-star doorman
Should I get rid of him?
All right. All right. All right fine here
180 oh my god 200 no more complaints
70 no more complaints 75 no more complaints. You know what fuck it
Just give them all give everybody a 20 increase in their pay
All right, no more complaining and do what do you work? Well?
No more cheating Fenton
Get this guy's just get make this guy leave
This is prostitute just leave
Get out
Leave fire the
80 dollars 80 dollars for
Are you one? No, she's two-star. She's two-star. There's no other dealers that are five-star
Are there any five-star dealers?
No, everyone's a one-star dealer
What was that?
Who's that?
Oh, it was a teenager
15 grand keep
Her table always has cheaters
Okay minus 37
minus
Are you gonna fight the dealer right now? Get out of here
Inside job
What the fuck
I'm doing it. I think the doorman wants another raise
By the way, the doorman was getting paid 120 130 dollars
And all of a sudden now I have to pay him more money every three every two days
What the fuck?
Minus 32. I don't know. All right wages that's
You're asking for too much here 235. Are you fucking kidding me if you're not happy with 250?
Get stopped this nonsense. You want any more money you're out
I cannot I cannot control. I cannot alt tab it
I can't alt tab it
Fire him if he wants more money. He's gone
18 grand how much do I need?
I need 44 000 to guard up to I need waiters
Just one star waiters are fine
Just one waiter, right?
Okay, if somebody wants to come sit at a table and get served
uh
Serve ice cream
Or mcdonald's hamburgers
You're not just gonna be ten dollars a week that I just throw away, right?
cheat
Right. Yeah
Where is he hanging out in the basement, right?
Let's go make some more money
Okay, you go cheat. I'll give you a small limit here
you can go
and
What else is we got?
Crip casino 2
That's one just come back with like 750
You you go there too work at the same angle. Yeah 20 grand work at the same angle
We'll check on him in a minute. Is the advertising campaign going good?
Now, what the fuck is this bribe brothels?
So I can bribe brothels to send more
prostitutes
I'm not doing this
No, thanks
Okay, let's see what the what the bus route the bus routes
I need to buy more property too. That's another thing
Should I have should I get some more buses?
I already have a limo service
Where's limo one limo one's dropping somebody off
Maybe should get some more buses
another route another bus
All right. I'm gonna do another route
This route is going to be from the bank
to the casino
Okay, we're good on the bank
To my casino and then back to the bank
And then maybe over to one of these hotels
Yeah, that's good
Yeah, because that'll like go around it'll stop with this it'll stop at like the bar and it'll stop at the bank and then yeah
That's it. That's a good route
Add a couple of shuttles
That's enough. Okay. Now I got no one more
All right. I got good cars moving around
I'm gonna spend money to make money guys
How's my hotel doing? Good profit good enough to make it go to 50 dollars a night
What is this?
Whoa, this looks like fun
Can I cheat? All right. What's the best place to where are they both going to the same?
table
um
Guys, I really don't think this is a smart idea to both cheat the same table
Because if the floor man's right here, you're gonna get caught. All right, get out you go
Go home take the money do the bait good. I just gotta watch this shit
The only floor man over here was this
uh
Are you telling on me?
Why is it standing here like this? All right, go down. Let's go to floor two
This punching bags and oh look at how much fun this stuff is
I need to make one of these this place isn't really a casino. Is it?
Is there any slots or anything?
Oh shit, this is not even a casino. This is their second property. It's an entertainment property
Fuck there's only three tables up here and this guy
Can I distract this guy? All right, go to a different casino
Go to the toy box casino
This is a bad place to steal
All right, that's fine
Back to my property
All right, this floor needs some serious redesigning
This is taking money in this is taking money in we need some stuff here
I need some I need a restaurant a good one a nice one a big one
medium kitchen
There we are. Let's put a nice restaurant over here. Okay. First of all, delete the fucking couch
Right there
So it's not even that expensive. You know what? Let's do another kitchen this way
Let's do two back to back make this bunch of fucking seats and tables and shit over here put a wall up
double kitchen
Small kitchen next to the big kitchen
This can be for appetizers and this can be for main and main entries
But why I don't know
Your cheat just got back with some loot. Good. Okay. I'm gonna move the movie theater
to
Over here. He's never gonna hit 44k. Yes, I will this restaurant's gonna be sick. I'm gonna get a five-star chef
There's only only one star chefs
Great. Um, how about?
p de shoes
All right p de shoes
Go for it
Let's get some waiters up here. I need three waiters because it's already weird downstairs
Wait, they can like deliver food downstairs, right?
one two three four
Waiters, we're ready
Open it up for business
Give me a wall and dumb ass couch get out of here minus 90. I spent money at the end of the day
Wages have been paid
Seating. Okay. How about we need uh internal wall?
Can I give one more table here?
Come on in. Okay, you can watch it through here
Configure the restaurant
But you're good kitchen. Here we go
There's a convention starting soon a wizards and witches convention will start in three days. Why did I say three?
high quality lobsters or french fries
steaks
What I mean an air filter
Is it really heat? Is it just hookers coming to have dinner?
No one's coming over to eat
How much is this costing me a week?
Nobody wants to eat at the nice restaurant
The sports betting is you should read maybe we should change the minimum too. No, I think that's good where it is actually
You're hiding it behind a wall. Well, I mean it's a bit that needs to have a little space
Nobody wants to eat at restaurants with porn grunts. This thing's almost maybe 10 grand. Okay
It's the best thing in this entire casino
So it has to stay
Yeah, get out
Well, all right. I need something here
These are still making money. They make it a lot of money actually
Just only have porn theaters
The waiters have no purposes that there's in the kitchen on the same floor
All right, so fire. Uh
fire this person
Wait, but they're
Oh, what was that?
somebody just
Ordering a drink the bar that's on the floor
Well, um, sorry. We just got you just got shown in real time
That the waiters and waitresses serve drinks
Look at that
lion chat
Acares getting killed again. Is he cheating?
None of these aren't making any money. Oh, okay
How to cheat
Casino good
Where do I want to put them? Looking for floor men?
teen teen escort
That's not that's not good. That's not good. All right. There he is. Where's the floor? Uh master
Lie leaving for xxx stage show. I need a stage show. I'm gonna put an xxx stage show next to the um
xxx movie theater. That's not even what it is. Why am I god fucking damn it at floor man?
You gotta find a spot where you can just cheat dude
right up here
What
Wait, somebody punched it
Where oh he lost at the machine. He broke it. What is he doing?
What is this?
Tom stuff in here is older than me
I can see a cheat
Cheating. Oh, no, not in baccarat. All right. Well, you just punch just like just punch him in the face already
Why are we all watching somebody quit?
What is going on?
All the staff is just sitting here sad
Somebody do something
What are you doing?
He's like, I can't do it. I can't shoot the old man
Somebody do something the police are on their way to the casino
And the elderly
Oh look at you. I wish I you would give me more money than
265 fucking dollars
Everybody in this whole casino. I make 30 times more than every fucking person here. I want more money though
So i'm stepping here is older than me
And he was like
Gyrating and like thrusting
Because he lost him. All right, which one was he on?
Which one was he on? I'm curious
This one right here. All right. So this one right here slot number four low bet. Let's see
profit today
Is that total? Where's profit today for it?
I think I'm gonna go like this, right? Yeah. I don't know what this problem was
What was the problem?
Oh, I think it was the next one. It was low bet five
Min and max bet are both 10
Uh, I can't I don't I can't change the bets
These are just 10. These are 50 and the other ones are 100
I don't think I can change it
X number four. Well, hold on. I gotta wait for the police to get out
Where's the cheater by the way?
He put he like that was so fucking ridiculous
He's just thrusting around the four bounces staring at him
This is the end of the day raises the gun puts it down race the gun puts it down like the janitors are all just watching
What's gonna happen?
Fire the doorman. Oh my god. Fuck this guy. Yeah
Staff are asking for a raise
Yeah, the guy that's about to go down
He's going downstairs
Hey bill, how are you? I'm doing pretty good. I'm doing pretty good jerry
Yeah, I know you're coming down here to kick the shit out of me with uh, probably uh tire iron
Uh, you know, let me think about giving me a little bit more money after this
You're gonna have to talk to the boss. I've got nothing to fucking do with that
Yep. Uh, well, I mean I make I make 60 times your income. Uh bill but okay
What side do you want to hit first? Oh be quick for leaving police have reopened the floor
He's not gonna come all the way down here
Shoot him right the police are on their way to the casino
Okay, so um
All right, but I mean like the guy the guy was getting paid
A hundred times everybody and he kept asking for a pay raise
It's like no you're not gonna get a pay raise and then he spit on the guy in the elevator
You didn't see that part and he pushed him and he shoved him into the wall and the bouncer hit his head
On the back of the fucking wall, is he still hanging out down here? This garf is kind of freaking me out
All right, go back upstairs
What wait? Oh, there's a wizard convention. We're gonna change some stuff
Anybody eating here?
All right
20 dollars
How much is a steak?
It's 10. Okay, so we've made we've served two people
I gotta change this to
What are you doing in here?
Uh, what do what a wizard's life?
On a disco or something
Okay, nice
How's the hotel doing?
The hotel's doing fantastic. Actually, I just want to build another one
I could put a few pinball machines over here. No, I need money. I need money
All right my cheat
Okay acting normally at the toy box casino
Oh, he's just he's just winning. He's just playing and winning
All right. It's time. Let's start cheating
There's a lot of flora men down here
Go over here and cheat on this one. All right, he's got a thousand bucks. All right. Good. You didn't get anything
You have how you have a thousand dollars. You don't have anything
Are there three scoop? What's with the four scooby-doo characters?
What are they all doing?
You know, I want to sit at this poker table
Shit is there another floor here I can go down and and and
I gotta go up
All right up here. They have so many floor men. It's so hard to cheat here. Oh pianist
It's so hard. Wait money wheel
Uh, go play this. I just want you to play it. This place is awesome
All right, put a bet on um, I don't know five. All right, did we lose him? No, he's coming back
Police have reopened the floor good. I can't cheat here. There's no opportunity. I mean I could try it
I could try it back here
No, it's just everywhere
Let's just start cheating in front of them. Should I be that ballsy? I mean, he's a five-star cheater
No, it's not worth it. It's not not worth it. All right, just go home
I'll take a thousand dollars. How much more do I need?
Fuck I need more money
Low jackpot frequency low percentage payout, uh high jackpot frequency low payouts
Like make them think that they're winning. This place is dead
I guess it happens when uh, you kill a doorman you shoot a rhino
and an old guy
also dies
That's I guess what happens to your casino you start losing money
Drunk rhino dies old man belligerently punches through one of the screens and gets shot
And then we kill the doorman in the basement
Cool
I still haven't unlocked these yet
God damn it. Come on. I need that forty four thousand
How's the hotel doing hotels? The only thing keeping me afloat right now. I'm gonna have to
55 dollars a night
Give garfield a raise. I already did
1465 bucks in profit. I mean i'm still i'm still in the green
Not by very much, but I still am
I need to get a new property. I mean, I have to buy a new property
Where do I even buy a new property?
Okay, real estate
We got how many of these places are open?
What's what's available?
cupcake bakery
snows pawn brokers, these are all 200 grand 160 160 120
75 go all the way down
All right. This is a wasteland casino
These are all 30 000
No
Don't have any money just buy a streamer house with eleven thousand dollars. I think you need to add a couple zeros
There you go. Play it
Bar is doing all right
I have some staff that I gotta got we haven't we have a staff bloat problem
We got janitors standing around in circles
Let's take a look. What's the bloat here? We got dealers that aren't doing anything good janitors standing around
You're out
Oh garfield
Keep you around
Floor this okay. This floor man's been pretty good actually been been very very very very very very good at sniffing out potential
cheaters
This bouncer I think I believe has been pretty good
There's only two there's three bouncers
This one's got to go
All the servers where are you located?
I think it's time
Yeah, we it's time to liquidate these nobody. You know, nobody cares
Look at the profit on these
These have made a i've been i've been streaming for three and a half hours these went up at least two guys some loot
These went up probably two and a half hours ago. They've made a hundred dollars. They've made less than three hundred four hundred dollars total
It's time for them to go
Let's see
Where's the food?
food kiosks
Six fucking dollars these things made four dollars
Or six. Yeah, goodbye
Make the prop the price is reasonable
I've been always buying them
This shit is five bucks
For a good quality hamburger
Fire at the cheetah casino again
I'm getting rid of them. I'm gonna put more slots in here
Foods upstairs. Oh, yeah, you just bought one good
Yeah, that's it. We gotta get rid of them. Just make a crappy one, but i'll make one this no nobody
It's ice cream. It's the ice cream. It's the problem. It's the ice cream. It's gone
Sell for a hundred bucks
How much did I put this down for this thing is sucks?
Yeah, but it's not about the profit it's about no one is buying them
This shit is incredibly reasonable
Even if I did like four dollars, I mean no one's purchasing these
And when I put the low quality everyone started throwing up everywhere
I just watched five people. Yeah, five people just bought for the burger. Do you see do you see the numbers? This is the book
Look, let's just do food only
Look the food kiosks, they don't they don't do shit
They make 20 bucks a day
We're checking the numbers right now as opposed to for instance
Like the movie theater the porn theater makes three to six hundred plus dollars a day
The back of that table loses a thousand dollars
Uh, well, there's one day somebody probably cheated and I didn't kick them off the table
Uh slot machine didn't do very well. Yes, but it's fine. Whatever
No food porn
It brings people in that's how business works
I don't try to don't try to lecture me on fucking business. Okay, I try to like to be on business
I'm the guy that decided to make the expensive drinks only three dollars more than my profit margin. That's business
The convention is now finished
Ah, she's gone
I won
You're good. All right
12 000
They're actually getting the they're actually
Ordering drinks. I should probably get another bartender
Another bar another bartender. I'm making money slowly
What about another ring? Uh another row slot machines slots slots right here. That's what i'm doing
The low ones the small ones the low bet ones
Why does this casino look like a tf2 trade server map?
I don't I don't know why
Oh wait, that's the wrong way
People love these things. God damn it. They just they they okay. I'm filling the fucking casino with these
If they go people go nuts for these
I need to put a poker table. I need poker right here. Okay. This is this brings in people
poker
Bang, I know it was five grand, but I need it
And a good dealer
Five star dealer at poker. Let's go. This is gonna bring in big money
Minimum bet 100 fucking bucks high roll of poker
I'm gonna drop the minimums on here back to 10
maximum 75
A dealer doesn't play poker
Right, whatever
It's just the man. It's a video game
Oh all the uh technicians quit. That's make sense. Okay
Here we go. Oh, you're a floor man
We're let's doing real well blackjack's picking back up again
Old lady playing poker. No blackjack
Leaving for the other casino fine
Look, they're having like fun over here
9200 negative end of the day fuck. I keep spending money. I keep spending money. I can stop spending money
Let's go. All right, I gotta stop spending money
I gotta let the casino do what it's supposed to do and make money
Are you cheating here? No, you're just playing here. Why are you playing here? Wait, you are cheating here
Are you cheating here?
ludo your
Ludo don't don't make me do this
This thing's negative 17. He's cheating here
Just check i'm not gonna point fingers yet. Where's my floor manager?
Can you check on him for just a second? Please please ludo, please
ludo
It can't be
Not ludo
No negative. Oh, no, it's not
No, no
Don't take anymore
What are you doing to me?
Stop
Oh my god. All right, kick his ass beat him up beat him. He's obviously cheating. I have to we have to stop him
I'm gonna be the negative. I'm negative. I'm negative. He has to he has to die like right now
I try to give him the benefit of the doubt
Give me that money back
Did he forget what he was supposed to be doing? He's supposed to cheese. He was he's acting innocent
In my casino, he works for me
You don't have to act innocent on my property, why would you act innocent and and you just bleed one of my machines four thousand dollars
That's unbelievable. Give me this money back now
That's bullshit
No, i'm not going to execute him
He just took like five. Look at this
Can you tell me that there's some kind of that there's not an and uh abnormality here?
4100 negative 3500
What do you got to hide? That's up. What do you mean up to? What do you just beat up denied it?
Get over get over here. Get up
Garfield the visitor you just beat up denied it police are on their way to the casino
Hey, by the way bouncer, you ever seen that movie? Oh, no
wait
He stole all the cops
No, okay. It's no more shooting people in the basement
This is not like uh, yeah why this is not like a fucking casino
I'm fucking a casino operator and I got a fucking 70s. We did all that shit in the basement
We beat people up and we shot him
That's not i'm not doing that. I stopped this
I'm bleeding money. I'm bleeding fucking money
Yeah, what we do is we take him down stairs
You know, I give him a one two pop in the head
That's what we did back in pegas
No, that's this is not like a this is not a fucking movie from the 70s. Okay, i'm not doing that anymore
I'm running my establishment
It's now this i'm i'm gonna be bleeding money again
That guy was a five-star cheater, but he's not cheating
So you're telling me that he was just getting really lucky and winning a shitload of money
Just having like playing having fun in my casino
well
What do you want me to think when you when you?
Have a five-star cheating record and you're acting innocent in quotes in my
casino
And the machine you're on is draining thousands of dollars
I need to start to put two and two together here
Negative thirty five hundred that's not even possible. Look at you no way
Look at I want to see look at look at this
seven days
Wait, oh shit. Was it just ready to go?
I mean, but I think it was the machine just ready to go
I mean, no, it hadn't been played in a while
Really lucky
Wait, I changed the settings
Yeah, I changed the settings to be payout percentage low
return percentage
Is not
6,800 bucks in a day
Yeah, high jackpot low payout. No, it's not backwards. I I look I did the tutorial
It means it wins a lot but not a lot of money
Yes, I did. Yes. I did look
What?
I'll show you
Do you want to you want to see?
Justice for ludo. No, he
uh
Just wait till the cops leave we'll be fine
Look, all right. If you have if you have a jackpot that hits
for a hundred dollars
every day
right rather than
You have a jackpot hit for a thousand dollars
Once a week
That's the difference
You understand
Get that scalp that hashtag. Okay this tutorial. Okay. First we'll look at configuring gambling tables
Okay, let's see. Let's see. Let's take a look over one of the roulette tables and click the right mouse button
This is the attract the top three. We don't need to hear this
Now click on the attractions. This displays a list of all attractions
Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep
You can now see the position. Yes, I can. Yes, I can. Yes, I can
The button on the extreme right on the screen the info about yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep
Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep
Walter the minimum or yep. Yep. The display. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep
There are two buttons. Uh-huh move the cursor
Okay slot machine, let's go
They allow you to set the jackpot frequency as low
Medium or high and the return percentage as low medium or high
A high jackpot frequency will pay smaller amounts more often
And a low jackpot frequency will pay higher prizes less often
The overall payout is not affected by jackpot frequency
But certain visitor types prefer their payouts little and often
Other types prefer them big and less frequent
The overall payout is not affected by jackpot frequency
This is a high jackpot will pay smaller amounts
More often a low jackpot will pay
Higher higher will pay higher prizes less often
The overall payout is not affected by jackpot fucking frequency, dude
That's what I was give me the clip. Give me the clip. Give me the clip. Give me the clip
Give me the clip. Give me the clip. Give me the clip. I said that exact shit
Altering the return people were telling me not to do high jackpot low return return percentage will pay out more
This is what we were this is what we were fighting about high low high jackpot low payout
Okay, can we get back to fucking life here look look this is the machines of the machines everyone was screaming about high low
Uh
What no, it's not what are you talking about the casinos on fire that was the bowling alley on fire
What?
What are you doing
How would you like the bowling alley on fire?
Somebody is anybody gonna get up here?
Fuck the chefs. They always fuck everything up
Still at work you go get out I need the firefighters right now
Um, where are the firefighters? Oh, let's go
Fucking god damn you motherfucker. Yep. God damn it vandalized
Who's vandalizing property?
Can we go back to work?
Somebody walked by
Somebody walked by and kicked the machine
Somebody just like did a full drop kick into the fucking screen
Oh my god
Curse of ludo
Can everybody get back inside please?
Jeff desues a one-star fucking chef
Unbelievable. I hope you lose all your money. Hey
Don't say that
Where's he going?
Asshole, he's gonna light on fire again. He just burnt it down again. He almost just burned it down again
He burned he almost burned it down again. Police are on their way to the casino
They're not gonna go they're not gonna arrest the chef. Are they?
No, they're not right?
There's even more
You guys want food or anything? Okay. No. All right that that I I
Keep the noise down. It's a casino
Oh my fucking head hurts
Ludo strike back ludo had nothing to do with this
Send out the cheater. I don't have any left
He's dead and the other one ran away
Okay, here we go
I want another has poker done. Okay poker's been all right
How is this place noisy?
Have carfield shoot ludo's ghost
Maximize income i'm making money if it wasn't for the uh constant
uh
removal of all patrons
Conflict
High jaguar frequency low pair
Okay, everything's we can you get our everybody leave now. We're good. We need a janitor up here. Is there one downstairs?
All right, come up here come pick up the puke
discount adult boobies
This oh, this is three star chef. Holy shit. Nice when this on fire the advertising board
Has announced that germa has been voted best advertiser by recent visitors. I won two grand
Give me more money than that
All right back up to seven
Once we reopen then at the floor will be fine and we can clean up all this junk
I'm gonna put my walls back up here
Having a good time. I don't have enough money for that. Do I?
Do I have enough money?
And this this looks much nicer when it was like this
There there we go. That looks better. It's like a restaurant
All right looking good better
Uh, this is not being used. Let's drop the price to 15 bucks. Let's do uh jazz
Third floor hotel rooms are doing so good. I should I should have just done only hotels police have reopened the floor. Thank you
Give it a 55 bucks
Imagine like a two or three star hotel above this. Oh, it'll be so much better
It looks so good
How would you like to spend with me? All right. We're good open it back up. Where are those servers?
Who's unhappy server?
Yeah, let's um
Just fire that person
We're gonna do a mass
Uh a mass pay increase before four dollars a week
Okay
Where are the servers?
server
I'm up here only one server. I need some cheaper
Get some cheap servers
It's cheap. All right, uh, mr. Kennedy
Uh, mr. Jackson
That's all right. We don't need that many. We don't need every table. It's fine
Just like four and then the chef denis kirby will take care of us
This boy's bedding is still doing well. The bowling alley is still doing well
Restaurants here porn theater is still look at the porn theater with that ten thousand dollar fucking increase
This every the whole this whole top floor is doing really well
The bottom floor is the one that's having problems
The poker socialite
Let's doing all right. These are okay over here. Let's change this up a little jackpot frequency medium
Hey percentage medium. We're gonna make it so we're gonna put these very standard. I want people to play them
I want people to win
Four grand in problem. All right, we're back on the uptake here
Remember you have like five waiters doing nothing
Shit
How many wait, how many waiters do I have?
Didn't I just check and see how many waiters I had what the heck?
Oh, it's not it's server
Server is not the same as waiter
Okay
All right. Um
There's a convention that's oh horror convention. Somebody's cheating it back around a lot of fucking sad mad people right now
um
Fuck they need to pay increases. It's been a while
Five dollars and then a bonus of ten for everybody everybody
Who's cheating?
All right, beat him up
Let's start making money again. Here comes the horror convention
We're making money again. That's all good
Poker is turning to profit blackjack is doing. Okay
Machines back here are all right. There we go. They're they're pretty much even
All right, we just want to play
Why is this closed?
Oh person quit
The visitor you just beat up is a plummet
Holy shit
It took 4,500 bucks
Nice
I think at this point. I probably no one floor man is fine here. I think i'm gonna do maybe another row of mediums
Maybe somehow. Ah, no, just get that get to 44 000. Don't do anything. Just keep the ball rolling
What
What why the police coming in here cheat while the police are in here? This is pretty dead up here. What happened?
Um, I don't think nobody even cares that this is happening
It's like you're not evacuating
This is just kind of a normal occurrence for this guy. This guy desperately is like I hope it doesn't set the alarm off
I think I can get it before it shuts off the alarm
This is the guy's our hero
Holy shit
I want to hire this guy. Can I get this guy? One of your ads is finished running
Oh
Fuck, uh, let's get a couple of cheap ones
But no more 10 grand keep it up
Because the casino needs
30 grand for no. All right, you need to do at least one doorman
Oh, I was gonna I just was about to ask
Where's the doorman?
right
I killed him
Mr. Packard
Mr. Ridgway, mr. Deacon mr. Billings
Mr. Barbertoni, mr. Downs, mr. Hawk
Uh, mr. Castle, mr. Kirby
Uh, one of them mr. Barbertoni
Welcome to the staff. Mr. Barbertoni
I hope you know the policy
You two work together
The door policy is of course, you know, no teenagers allowed
What is this? Oh, he's like a werewolf
All right. We're doing okay
Okay, I want you to go cheat
We have a new cheat go
Waiting in the basement. Okay, you just go get fucking caught and who cares? I don't care
Go into the cheetahs casino. You look I come back with 1500
you same deal
go to the
Go to the cryptocino and I want you to come back with that with a thousand
This cashier is gonna quit you're making like twice
Well, you're dealing with like, okay, how much more money do you want?
Then you're fired. All right, what do you want to do?
fucking
It looks like there's a fight
Let him fight
All right trailer trash versus
I'm not sure
Oh trailer trash wins
All right, how do I where did she go?
I didn't have access to the game
Don't do it. Just just tell her to leave
Punish her for losing she went in the elevator
Which one who was it?
Just ban all trailer trash
But why would I do that?
there
I've that's the only people that are staying here
Some random people that didn't read the yelp reviews
And then all the trash people
That's who's
Picking up all the space here
I need more drinks. This is making good money. Let's charge. It's there's a convention going on. Let's charge way more money
12,000 I need 44 then we can move on to the next level and i'll get like 20 30 grand
You need the trash to function
Kind of I I kind of do old people and
Look at these they're just loaded with people
These are so popular
There we go, you got money to spend put it in the expensive machines and it's 10 grand each
only allow trailer trashing
uh
Okay, if I had trailer trash, I would do like three bars have the drinks be a dollar
And then just do only low paying slots covering the entire floor. It's the end of the day
Wages have been paid. It's a casino for the people
Wait, what are you doing?
Yeah kicking out good. You're kicking out the team good
And while you're at it kick out the prostitute
12 grand come on
This waiter's just okay when you get you're gonna go
All of that just made everybody sad. They everybody liked her
Oh, everybody loved andrea
Oh, she was really really popular among all the staff
Is she the one holding everybody together?
Look here. Don't worry. There's money. This fool man makes too much money
So does the bouncer
Staff are asking for a raise. Oh fuck i'm firing everybody and they're all getting so scared and sad
Just wait escort get out of here
Okay, just now everybody wait, don't you know now I can go like this
Look money five dollars
everybody gets
$10
This dealer makes too much money level five dealer though
brr brr
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
The three dealers here we've got over here there's still these are the dealers that weren't asking for like five million dollars
Your cheat has been oh you took 500 1500 bucks good for you
Are you both working over here?
Wait a minute. Why the two of you?
When did I hire a second person?
Oh, I need a floor manager
Mr. Chubb fun. I'm forever stuck at ten thousand dollars. I'll never make it up
You got ejected. Well, at least somebody took money
All right, I think i'm gonna try that strategy trailer trash only
And have the bar hire another bartender make drinks cheap and make them a dollar
I need a bouncer. Yep. I'll get a bouncer. Look at my money's already increasing
Two bouncers all I need down here on the bottom floor
How's the hotel doing? Just it's so much money
Okay
Just buy more money
Money money money money. Let's go. Nobody's going here serve people serve people. We need more patrons
We need more people
Oh, who's up here?
The chef is just cooking food for nothing
for nobody
There's no one up here
This is already even working at the bowling alley
We just need one waiter up here
Almost a 13
13.5
Good second bartender
You know what?
Yeah, no. Yeah second bartender, I think
Level three bartender two of them here
Let the alcohol flow
Medium drinks
Six bucks a pop the convention has now finished
Here we go. Come on
Just get me to 44 000
No more spending no more attacking back with some loot
1500 more bucks
This is a cheater right here. That's my cheat. Okay, good
um
Oh cheated the toy box. I want 2 000 this time get on it
You have 450 in your pocket. Good. I'll take it
Okay, we got the bowling alley set up everything's good to go how cheap let's make everything cheap
12 bucks to bowl
This this i'm not going to change. This is doing really really well
Get a janitor on that second floor
What's their janitor? Where's the janitor just up here?
All right
Back to adult movies. No, no, no, we've had people are getting sick of the adult movies
It's the same adult movie over and over again
Like you can't you got to move on you gotta
You can't you can't watch the same movie more than like five times
Stop it. So let's put that up 25. How much is food here?
10 bucks. Let's make it expensive and make it if 20 dollars a plate
At least maybe one or two rich people will come up here and eat this
Come on. We need people
It's almost like um when your potential hazard for people to come here and people nobody nobody shows up
Has something to do with it. Probably
Yeah, I hear that they I hear they execute their doorman in the basement
We're going somewhere else
These did okay
Ow can hurt i I promise that hurt you more than it hurt me but still hurt
Your cheat just got back with some loot
What did you just knock somebody out?
Who is this?
You just blasted somebody
The party never stopped the party never stops
Wait, what?
Where are you going?
I attacked the waiter. No, no, that's not what I was supposed to do 4900 in profits
Wages have been paid discipline
Staff are asking for a raise
Stop stop stop stop go back to work. You're fine
Oh, I think he's stuck
There we are. All right
No witnesses
No, he's not it's a lot of what is he works here. Oh this two
What is the these gas cylinders are freaking me out?
Wait, are we
Holy shit staff are unhappy and threatening to quit. Okay. That was fucking nuts
Who wants to quit?
You can't quit
You can't quit. You can't quit
This janitor wants to quit. Oh, you mean the janitor that's staring at a literal wall. No joking like
Oh, what are you doing staring at the wall? He's staring at a wall
But where are you?
We only need one janitor. Anyways
Eye roller
Stop blowing money here. I'll blow big money. Yep
Yeah, good to check on a guy like this, right? I mean if he's if he's just checking to make sure he's not cheating
He's losing a lot of money. This is good
And the mummies really love the slot machines
he's uh
Doing really well
All right, we're climbing
We're increasing in money right here. I'm doing fine
Backer at table. I think has to go
There's too many staff and it's nobody cares
If you are you gonna sit at the background table if not, then it's gonna go
It's gotta go. No one's playing it. He's playing. He's playing. He's playing. He's playing
Okay, it's done. Okay. This guy's gonna lose money good
18 000
Getting there all the hotel rooms. Look at this hotel. Should I do 60 60 bucks a night?
Speed up time
Oh my god, that's too fast
Build another hotel. I don't have the money and I got any 30 grand
Get a carpet that doesn't look like this
I I don't I can't I don't I can't afford it
I need to level up again
I'll get there. I'm almost at 20
Okay, these are not negative, which is fine
You're still serving customers this this cattle high roller
another
wall
uh
Whatever at least pretend like you're working, you know
Pretend like you're working. I don't care like as long as you look like you're doing something
19 820 000 good
And here we go
Okay, that's good for me
Everything's nice and clean. Everything's running. Well
Damn it. Can I get a drink please? Can I get a drink, please?
This table's dead. It's out
One guy played it and lost 100 bucks. It's gone actually actually actually being sold and the dealers are gone, too
That's it like glare
Okay, we have rickets mason
And groft all of them gone
Six, okay good. It's the end of the day wages have been paid
Don't worry everybody
Everybody gets five dollars
fine
Everybody gets ten dollars
fine you two
Get a five dollar salary increase good. There we go. Now i'm not losing just bleeding money
It's too loud for me
I need walls
That's why there needs to be a wall here like here in here
Here that's the problem
Okay
Yes
Yep, we have to make walls
Fuck shit. This is bad. Okay, is that gonna mitigate some of the sound? Why does it play so ugly? I don't know
Nice wall stupid. Well, what do you want me to do? I didn't plan with walls
Separate them by floors right only slots. Yes. Yes, you're right. You're right
But I put bowling alleys upstairs
And I put a porn theater and a restaurant that no one goes to nobody eats here
I have a delicious five-star restaurant up here that nobody wants to eat at might as well make it fucking burgers and fries and
And that's it three dollars a meal
We got dennis kerby one of the most talented chefs in all
of
What's the name of this place?
Slam of slots and lanes
Would you eat in the porn restaurant? Yes, of course I would and people use this shit people like this shit stuff up here
This is actually has made some money
This whole floor is worth like let's say six
seven eight
nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen
Yeah, I mean this whole this floor has made like 25 plus thousand dollars
You put a restaurant on the hooker floor
Why am I losing money again?
All right lady. I've had enough of you saying that
so
It's time for you to leave
What this lady just beat his ass
She's just puked
Why would you puke for that? Why would you puke?
Or I don't care. I'm busy
Just wait somebody on this one and they're losing money. Wait, somebody's still fighting you
Wait, is he going in for round two?
That lady just one hit knocked him out and now he's going for round two
Oh, no, he's
Losing money. I'm actually getting fucking knocked out and coming and losing five grand at the poker table
Come on. I gotta put this in a better spot
Because it's too loud up here for us old people
Early early you need to be a squid billy's grandma
No, I don't think so
Where do I put this? I'm just gonna delete this shit. There's no reason for it to be over here
Um, maybe I could go like bang bang bang. Yeah, let's do that. Put it down here for now
Move this out of the way. It's okay. They're idiots. They'll figure it out. What the hell are you doing, man?
Oh, what is this? All right. Hey relax. I don't see you doing
Fucking you know there. Okay, they come in here and i'm gonna put some nice little things in here
I'm gonna put like a palm tree like no, we're not it's too. Yeah, look at no, that's not good
Hanging plants or something practices. I don't know a plant put a couple of plants or
Um, oh that's where these are
That's what these are
Right. Okay
It looks like there's a fight
No, don't I have 26 000 i'm getting there. They all want drinks and shit. This is actually going really well
Just do your thing
Get rid of them. Okay
Put it like a sofa back here
It's the end of the day wages have been paid
People just gonna hang out
for like a fucking plant
Flowers here. Look, this is nice
All right
There's see that look at this. This is like a little slot area. There's a convention that's just started. Oh nice
Kind of make money
Put the slots back to back
I know what you mean
I know what you mean. I know what you mean. I know what you're saying. I know what you're saying here
I know what you mean. I know what you're saying. Yeah, I know what you mean by that
I know what you mean by that one
I know what you mean
Okay, it looks like there's a fight
Stop fighting
What the fuck stop?
This guy is another fight from this guy
Second fight today
This is going right back to the machine
All right. I'll let him stay
Get rid of the shitty plants
I need them
Fine i'll give her this shitty plants they add character
Look, this old lady's already sitting down
Okay. Nice. Nice. All right. Now we need one more of these
What?
Why is the fucking casino on fire again?
What is going on?
Yep, Dennis Kirby ladies and gentlemen a freestyle one of the most pop starred chefs and all of
slamming jamming slots
Aha and you're gonna cost me you're gonna cost me a lot of money here kirby
Yeah, great
He's outside
He's doing just he's out here
We're at the fucking place to the ground just besides the guy just hanging out. That's okay
What?
How was the ground floor the floor too as where's the fire down here? What the fuck? How did this happen?
Okay, so I need a fire department in here. I i'm fucking actually i'm mad right now. Where's kirby? Look at everybody
Everybody's leaving they're going to the other casino
All because of a shitty restaurant that nobody went to I was on pace to have
$44,000
Oh my god
Where's the chef? Where is he? He's still outside
Is he running away?
This motherfucker is running away
All right. I didn't know what I didn't know what this is
He's coming down the street to with department stores. I can't attack him outside
All right, give me
$4,000
Oh back to work everybody
Where's he even gonna work?
In the basement, you know, stay here stay down there dick
26,000 i'm almost there. I need about like 10 grand
This is all right. This is looking good. This is what I wanted to be like
Oh fuck the beanbag chairs is what i'm just keeping here
That looks a little more clean
Oh looks nice and clean. I made 800 bucks
Considering my casino almost burnt down
Why did I just lose money what's going on who's somebody stealing what are you up to?
Yep
I knew it
Just throw her out. I don't even want the money
and go
Come on
Come on 30,000 30,000 30,000 30,000 30,000 30,000 30,000 30,000
I'm just stuck at 26,000
Change the decor. I I don't think I have I don't have it's not available for me to do that
I probably have to level up. I have to get I have to do this. I have to get to forty four thousand dollars
Okra's doing really well
Twenty seven thousand good
Ten thousand just look around
All right. Nothing suspicious is going on
Okay
27 grand
Get it up. That's not us
Floor man
What's with the fighting
What the milkman versus
Teen why are you in a
Wait, they all these are the the the there's like a navy convention or something, right?
This is because this cheap drinks
Oh shit, that's right
This will make them even cheaper
The convention has now finished
I gotta get to forty four thousand
Two thousand visitors do I get money for that? I don't come on. Let's go
No cheaters thirty thousand. I need to be at 44 for one day
I think another get rid of the blackjack table another poker table after this
I was upstairs looking what an absolute fucking monumental waste of time
Sell it sell it all. I'll do it again later. I can't make a small kitchen with the hamburgers or something
It's the end of the day wages have been paid
I can turn this into something else. I can't sell the hooker
Uh, one of my I gotta put something over here eventually it's not making any money. It's just losing money
It's great of it
This is still making money. This is still making money
Come on that up techniques to keep going 30
I'm gonna start charging more money for shit
I think we have to sacrifice the dance floor
I expanded too quickly
Don't ever sell don't ever sell the dance floor
I need to charge more money for this shit go back to adults adults only horn
back downstairs
i'm gonna do
Low quality food eight bucks
low quality
seven bucks
Okay
The drinks are gonna be cheap as shit. That's fine
and
Let's go come on
Grow grow grow grow grow grow growth growth growth growth growth growth growth growth
Why is somebody say trump steak?
I'm here with trump steak. They're the best steaks that you've ever had in your life
delicious
Prime country, mate. Come on. Let's go
All delivered right to the front door your beautiful friend
Fight
Oh this lady, oh get her come on come on malakowski hit her with the cane
Oh
Wait, why are you attacking the whoa?
What's up easy?
Why are you?
It's the end of the day. Holy shit. This lady is unbeatable
Why are they all fucking punching each other?
That lady was almost unbeatable
casino rumble
34 000 skip
There's a convention starting martial arts convention. Good. Maybe it'll maybe it'll put me over right at the edge here
Almost at 44 000
Where one of your ads has finished running whatever which one's damaged who damaged it?
back here
Oh somebody did damage it. No, I didn't catch him
Is that we need a casino tournament arc god this person is cheating you know what to do
Take a break it's been five hours. Yeah, we're gonna end uh very shortly here
I feel like I want to play this tomorrow
At least a little bit. I want to see the other stuff
tomorrow is supposed to be the
dumb movie night
But I think I want to see some more of what at least another couple hours of this
Maybe we'll do this and then watch the movie
That would make sense, right?
Play this for like another couple hours and then do a movie
Yeah, we'll pick the movie tomorrow
But i'm gonna play this tomorrow when we start. I thought that just said 54 people died today here
I was like, holy shit. What?
It's the end of the day wages have been paid
I need that money. Come on. I'm just like skipping time. I could be spending this
Invented it's just started
An attraction has been damaged come on. I don't care. We just need the extra money. We need the extra attractions
They'll get them
Your casino is being raided by the police. What?
Everyone's scattering
No, I don't need this right now. I was already having trouble with patrons
Watch this be like a thirty thousand dollar fine
I would shit my pants
Everybody's leaving i'm gonna be bleeding money
I was so close. You've been fined by the police. Oh my god
Floor two has been reported to the police
Oh, yeah, has it now that's isn't that just great?
Oh my fucking god
I can't believe this shit. Come on
These poor dj's just here spinning records with nobody here
uh
Sacrifices need to be made. All right, let's go
Wages have been paid
All right this I don't want let's not go too fast
What happened? I sold the dance floor
Because it was it was five or six thousand dollars that I could I could get
I need that. I need more people to come back. I need
I'm gonna have to buy an ad campaign have to otherwise there's gonna be like three people in here. One of them's a hooker
I have to buy an ad campaign
a good one
Just buy them up good. Let it now let it roll
We got plenty of staff. We got plenty of food. We're good to go. We got our slots all taken care of
Get rid of the cheat
Are you chasing our dealer around?
Wait, why is this like some weird?
What is happening?
Just chasing the dealer around stop
Are you gonna actually knock out garfield? There's no way
I can't believe you're gonna actually fucking knock out garfield. Did you
You gotta be shitting me
An attraction has been damaged. She's breaking shit
It's her
Get rid of her get rid. She's attacked janitor do something. She's smashing stuff
Garfield where's garfield? Get up. Okay. I
This has to end right now. I need a uh, uh, uh, um
just uh, uh
Mr. Dearing
Staff are asking for a raise. Mr. Dearing
Shoot this person
No
You missed
You've won star you've won star
Unbelievable one star one
You're fucking fired. Oh my god. I'm never you're fired. You're fired. Get out of here. You're fired
I'm so mad right now. I need this money
I killed that guy
No, i'm so fucking mad
How did I kill that? I didn't kill the wrong person
He did I selected that person that was breaking stuff and beating people up and he missed
Staff run half threatening to quit garfield. Don't quit. Here's fucking 50 dollars
How much money do you want garfield garfield? I know you got like beat up by some lady being raided by the police
Staff run he's unhappy. All right, everybody everybody relax. Everybody's gonna get a 30 a 20 dollar raise
That's a big fucking deal
here
Okay
God damn it. I'm not gonna get fined
I'm not gonna get fined right for having too many fights. That's not my fault. That's the fault of the
three dollar
drinks
nice job garfield you got like
street fighter comboed over here
And then I had to
Hire another guard because you got knocked the fuck out
I'm not happy with you garfield. That was bad
That was really bad. We need to get to 44 000. I'm not turning the stream off till I get there
staff are unhappy
She just
No, you can't trust me
Who's causing a disturbance?
Well, one of the police officers fucking go do something about it
The convention is now finished
Um, are we just not gonna have a police officer do anything do something about it
Staff are unhappy and threatening to quit
This guy's threatening to quit. Oh my god. You've been fined by the police
20 000 in fines
in the last 15 minutes
That's unbelievable
The visitor you just beat up was working for an opponent. What?
What the fuck you're sending people deliberately to cause problems
That's that how do I get that?
I would just hire 100 people just to go cause problems
It works. Yeah, it did. Police have reopened the floor. Thank you
Okay
Uh, good thing my ad campaign started
let's go ahead and um
Let's make this a little better
So it's not just
uh
22 000 and it's empty
We are empty
It's just staff
There ain't nobody here
Nobody's here
Your empire is crumbling. Oh, no all because you murdered ludo
That's true
What you're saying is accurate
He brought thousands of dollars into this company
I need some customers
13 people visited today. Oh my god, this is bad
It's the end of the day. This is bad have been paid
This is bad
Okay customers coming on in
Come on
Nobody wants to come to the casino anymore
It's over
They all don't like this place. Nobody likes it here
my ad campaigns
No
No, it's a disc. We're gonna have to close our doors
ferris, right the last patron
The last guy here
All right. Now just watch this
Damn it. See if we can get any more customers
I might have to just go nuts for ad campaigns
Kick out the hookers
There's too many of them
When I get rid of one another one appears
Porn theater still okay now get rid of you
I might have to just go absolute nuts. We're gonna have to let in uh, we have to let in teenagers
and just open it up and
Not serve alcohol
I need more page. I need people to come to the place
I'm gonna turn off the porn theater. We're gonna stop serving alcohol
I'm gonna add a couple of arcade machines and i'm gonna let teenagers come in
We're gonna change our image
nope
Desperate times call for deaths absolute desperate measures
This is a chuck-e-cheese
I can turn it into a chuck-e-cheese. I think that's the only way
they've been banned from the casino the whole time now, what if I removed the bar and just
They we're gonna turn it into a we're gonna turn it into chuck-e-cheese right now
Save it right here. Just in case it's a bad idea. I'm going for it
Check this out. We're gonna save this company
I'm gonna save this company right now
Keep these those are okay keep the restaurants. It's the end of the day wages have been paid
Okay, get rid of the bar. The bar is gone
The little slot machine plays though is all right for the the adult. Uh, no, it's not
I'm turning this into a fucking chuck-e-cheese right now
Oh, by the way, I have forty four thousand dollars. I win. What's the chef doing here? What is the chef doing here?
Kirby the chef there's a convention starting a cloud convention
No, don't shoot anybody there's a clown convention coming. I gotta make sure it's ready
I gotta make sure the chuck-e-cheese is ready for the clowns. Okay. He's not coming down, right?
I called off the hit right?
I called off the hit. I called off the hit. I called off the hit
I called off the hit. I called off the hit. I called off the hit. No, we have to get rid of the
Do not shoot him. Do not shoot him. Thank you. Don't shoot him. Don't do it put the gun down put down the gun
Do not fire that gun do not fire that gun go upstairs go upstairs now, please
Up here put the gun away. Thank you. Okay, I gotta get rid of the fucking clown convention
We're gonna turn this into a chuck-e-cheese immediately our hotels are ready
50 bucks a night clowns
This is the one shot I have
Okay, we need
Uh, we need um, first of all, we need to wait because it said in a couple days, right?
It's gonna stay over 44
It's still profitable
How am I more profitable with no business staff are asking for a raise?
Five hours to go
Police are going to an opponent's place, but
the rest of them all
Did it?
I did it. I just have to sell the business
All I had to do was sell the business
It's the end of the day wages have been paid the business had to be sold for me to get this
He did it. You've achieved your objective. Yes
There is no cash reward for completing this you have enough already to assist you two hitmen are waiting in your basement
Here's your fourth objective
Are they?
Two hitmen are waiting in your basement
Where are these hitmen? Do you talking about?
This is an old guy
There's a convention that's just started
What is this why can I do this this is gonna make a mess
Don't do it to my own place
Oh, no, go back go back go back
Staff are asking for a raise
Morale is low staff are leaving
Isn't this the guy that I just killed
Isn't that the chef?
Wait, who the fuck is this?
Oh, no
Okay, bye bye good to see you. Thanks for more. Thanks for having thanks for working here for as long as you have
Oh my fucking head. Staff are unhappy and threatening to kill
The fuck is this
Wait, what?
This is gonna hold on. Why can I do it again?
Okay
Red spy in the base. There's nothing even in here
He's trying to leave who is this person?
Who is this?
Somebody just came down here
Wait, where are you? They shut the door
How much is it for a new casino? Thirty thousand dollars, right?
The police are on their way to the casino
What I didn't who are these firefighters?
No, no, this is gta, man. This is not gta
The clowns where the but there was a clown college that was coming in. All right, i'll see you tomorrow
Oh my god
I'm, sorry. I so badly just wanted to kill that chef that chef was just fucked it all up for me
We were on a trajectory of growth and that guy burnt the casino down twice
So, I mean he did it back to back and he ruined everything
So the second I had the opportunity you gotta give me a hit man
And it's an old guy with a gun downstairs in the basement
You don't think i'm gonna get you don't think i'm gonna eliminate the chef down there
And then I mean the I did I plant that was not the the second part of that. It wasn't supposed to happen
Oh, we haven't saved for the clowns to come in. We're gonna continue tomorrow. Oh this game is
Hysterical
What an absolute mess of a game. It's great though
I gotta I gotta do I I gotta uh, okay, we'll continue tomorrow
lady
There ain't anything in here to do
Yeah, I think you kind of may have accidentally walked in here. Oh, man. All right. I forgot the steven image was even still here
oh
And i'll see you tomorrow. We're gonna pick up with this tomorrow
And maybe spend another hour or two in it maybe try and do some more things
Once it becomes I think i've had enough
Uh, we'll watch we'll we're gonna potentially do that prime watch a movie together thing
Just because I just want to do it for no reason
That was a lot of fun
I'll see you guys tomorrow
Take care of yourselves. We'll start probably around the same time around 3 30 probably ish four o'clock between three and four between three and four p.m
And that's gonna be it
Take care of yourselves. See you soon. Let's do the end of the stream
that was casino ink by the way if you uh
You're like what was that? I would like to play it. It's casino ink. That was traumatic. Yes, it was
Very traumatic. It was insane
Anyways, let's do the bits. Let's go back to earlier. I missed a bunch of bits
I was just so hyper into what was going on on the screen that I missed a bunch of stuff
I do apologize for that
But let's go back. Let's uh cover them all that were coming in
So if we had 250 at the beginning from sticks renegade hey germ boy
Thanks for deciding to play jackie chan stunt master on june 11th
means a lot
That's a fake date for a fake video game that i'm fake not going to play
Well, i'm not gonna play it. I mean i'm that that's what i'm saying. Thanks for the 250
Hey, thank you. Uh tell naga for the 275
Um, I don't even want to read this out loud. It's fingers. Whatever. Thanks for the 275
Thanks for the 275. Hey espada escalata. Thanks for the 250
Hey, just some quick bits in celebration of my one year sub anniversary. Thank you
Thanks for subbing this channel for any reason
If you got a community sub
And you kept it cool if you didn't that's cool, too. If you've been subbed for a year awesome 10 years. Thank you
Or if you just watch that's fucking great, too
Thanks a lot with fingers in his ass sunday. Yes, it was
Yeah, a whole of one zombie thanks for the 250
I feel like chat needs to give a piece of paper with a childlike handwriting on it
And you'd read it in the auto voice
Sorry, your joey game was burr. Here's a picture of a brick
I like and there would be a sad face in a wicked cool brick. There'd be fireman doing a kick flip, too
I feel bad for beautiful joe beautiful joe had to be sacrificed for casino inc to be played
It's sad
Good worth it. Yeah, but I mean but I was I eventually was gonna play casino inc i've had it on the list for a long time
Hey abomination zero. Thanks for the 260 put your face on the guy in the corner. I think we did that for about an hour or two
Worked out pretty well
Hey anarchy the op. Thanks for five dollars watching germa is like having blues clues on tv
Okay, el sombo. Thanks for the 500 bits back to vr. Please. I will eventually
Starting to feel a little bit better
I'll move to vr when i'm ready
Hey marvosh magali. Thanks for the 250
Germa, how do you reply to the rumor that bernie sanders decided to drop out of the presidential race?
After finding out that you decided to raid kiwo instead of him
You guys would never have behaved yourself. There's no way that you guys would have been like a hundred of you would have gotten banned
Instantly and then it would have been like who fucking sent these people
but I there are some lines that I need to draw and it's uh
Trolling the potential next president of the united states. I think I have to draw the line there somewhere
Yeah, I think that's where the line potentially needs to be drawn
coward
I didn't I said potential I didn't say next I said potential he would have raided you imagine getting raided by bernie sanders
How do you even react to that?
That'd be that'd be a trip
He's got emotes and he's got like a big what if bernie had like a pog face emote
He has like all the typical streamer emotes
Like bernie with a heart like bernie with a pog face bernie with like a oh shit face
Bernie was doing like a facepalm. I want everybody to go and raid germa 95
and please
Do bernie pog I want him to know I want to see bernie pogs. That was oh, that's obama
I was I I it's been a long night. I hadn't even it's been five hours, but it's still
Everyone needs a haircut. Yes, I do. Hey alec the bunny. Thanks for the five dollars and ten cents great stream
Jerva. Hope you're staying safe and well. Thanks for being a source of great entertainment. Thanks
For giving me five dollars
And for watching the stream really appreciate it
Uh ye of little faith. Thanks for 500 bits. There's no message
$30
3000 bits from dusk dynamite a bunch of money. They say uh
Was gonna say something but I forgot
Well, i'm sorry to hear that you forgot but I will take your insane
Bit drop anyway, so i'll take $30 3000 bits. Thank you. Thank you dusk dynamite
You also gave five community subs right after that. So thank you for those two, uh notorious thug
Thanks for the 300 bits germa my washing machine broke and sprayed poop water all over my clothes
Really cheer me up if you played theme hospital again when your washing machine broke and sprayed poop water
Are you going to the bathroom in your washing machine? Yes
How does that work bidet washing machine? Oh, man, that's disgusting
I'm sorry to hear about that, but I will not play play theme hospital again
Thank you. Got what I wanted out of it. I think and I think uh people a lot people weren't really into it
Were they I might remember it wasn't really
Uh, people weren't really that into it s kilo. Thanks for the 250. Hey jerkma. Nine eight five. Check this out
I drew the chef on fire
Yes, you did. You did
Thanks for the
Thanks for the 250 s kilo appreciate it sir k-9
Thanks for 250 local streamer and casino runner freezes face cam on stream and then admits to plot to murder casino patron live on stream
mucka s
Uh, I ate us I eat us
Thanks for the 300 bits. I tried to decipher the coordinates you read out on stream yesterday and I think i've narrowed it down to somewhere
in
someone
well
Coordinates are hard
I'll let you know if I find out more
Oh mucka s
You know, here's the thing about living in vegas. That's how you're ready. Here's the here's the here's one thing about living in las vegas
There are like three places that a lot of people live
And people are like hold on a minute. I think I know where he is
Las vegas has
Popular places. Uh, you know, have you ever been a germa? Have you ever been to henderson? Yeah henderson. Yeah, it's okay
ever been to
summerland
Yes, I have
Have you ever been to the north las vegas?
Yeah, those are the three places where anybody lives in this entire city
We got him. That's a hackinator question
He lives in vegas
Yes, I do. He's actually at the fourth secret place
There yeah, but you guys might not know about the fourth secret place
bernie pog
But anyways, yeah people have said yes, I have I have experienced time
In most of the popular places in vegas
Summerland's really popular
Henderson's very popular a lot of people live there north las vegas
It's nice
They're all nice places. I could live in a casino. You never know but one thing I will say
This doesn't matter where you live
As long as you like where you live
It doesn't matter where you live, but who cares as long as you like it
I'm a big fan of east vegas. It's where I am. It's a good place
Where I live shit thanks for the uh, thanks for 300 bits appreciate it
Time to vroom and listen. Oh you guys are fucked
I'm looking at it. I'm looking i'm at i'm looking at his house right now
That's like all right. Let me let me be real with you
Let me look we're gonna no more like jokes about like where people were like, you know living in vegas
Like if I if that if I like ever looked out my window and there was like a person there
You know the yeah, I literally i'm calling i'm calling the police immediately, you know what I mean?
Just like hello. There's somebody out there. It's good. Somebody's outside go get them
Like that's what i was having immediately and I was like all the doors are locked by the way
Why wouldn't you i'm sort of saying
What if somebody was just going for a walk?
Freak out somebody's outside walking by my house right now
Okay, we'll be there. Yep. They're walking
Wait, they're walking. Yep. Do they have a dog?
Yes
The dog on a leash. Yep. Are they dressed in
outdoor
Where yes they are. How fast are they moving? They're jogging
Hello, I love vegas everywhere in vegas is great. I love this whole fucking city, you know, you know, i've seen
I've seen people talk about the hell. Oh man vegas
Shit this sucks. It's a fucking dump
Oh, it's not
There's so many great places in vegas. I mentioned three or four areas. They're fucking beautiful. They're phenomenal places
Really really great
And you can do animal crossing. Uh
It's humid not in vegas. What are you talking about play vegas make it big
Didn't I play the one for super nintendo? All right, we're getting off track
Thanks for the 300 bits
Appreciate it. Thanks hole of one zombie for the 250
So what's your experience in catering? I'm a serial arsonist you're hired
Thanks for the 250
Last time lord gave some community subs three of them a few minutes ago 20 minutes ago or so. Thank you
Twanco, thanks for 300 bits. Hey germa. Thanks for all the laughs over the years
You helped me feel better during some of my lowest times of recent
Just wanted to ask you a quick favor of you
Today's my 19th birthday and I really appreciate it. You can sing happy birthday for me. My name is samantha by the way
Happy birthday samantha
Happy birthday
Tim hold on
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday
Happy birthday. Happy 19th birthday. Nobody else's birthday is on monday and i'm supposed to stream on monday
But if I don't happy birthday to the person that's fucking birthday is on monday and i'm happy birthday if I don't see you
Thank you. Twanco. Happy birthday
Silence serenity. Thanks for 250 people are ripping on you for the porn kitchen
But the only place I can see something like that existing is in a casino
That's yeah
Well, yeah, pretty true rock writing. Thanks for five dollars the sandy vomit soaked floors the screams of pleasure and
pain
Interimly with country music dance floor employee outrage five unprovoked killings ludo's
Slog garbowski revenge arc aside from the hookers. This is what I imagined when you mentioned something about doing a live event
In a public venue last stream
What the fuck noodle is bad at gaming thanks for 250 this casino reminds me of the hotel
They stay at in fear and loathing in las vegas
Also, please consider my group therapy stream idea. I need this in my life hire an actor instead of a therapist if you must
a
Okay, a group therapy stream
Would just be the family dinner stream again
You know, that's what it would be. The only difference would be it would just it would be
Somebody would be there
Sitting there pretending to be a therapist
I'm for part two
Let's see if I can get the gang back together again. I don't know about that
Miami hotlines. Thanks for the thousand bits king your interior decoration skills need work. Your casino is ugly
That's all right. It's okay. I said I wasn't gonna read king out loud anymore, but I just did
Let's put the credits on here. What do you say?
All these subs. Thanks a lot guys
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you
I can even run them
There they go
Thanks a lot guys
For your subscriptions. I appreciate it, but they've been subbed for a year sub for a week sub for a month or never ever
Thanks again. Hey snooze. Thanks for the 1500 bits. Hey jerma
Thanks for the great content you make and hope you and your loved ones are well during this time
Not to get into anything personal
But I was wanting to ask your opinion on how couples who don't have much in common make things work
You and kim seem like almost opposites in terms of personality
I might be wrong, but it just comes off that way. I wanted to see your thoughts on it
Thanks again for all that you do opposites attract
Isn't there isn't there like a whole thing about that? They hate each other
You guys have magnets
um
How do you hold on? Let me let me think about this
How do you
Couples don't have much in common
Well things that me and kim have in common you guys don't see
That you don't hear about
Like kim doesn't really play very many video games or doesn't really she's not really into this whole space here
She's not really into twitch or youtube or like gaming really but that's
We have a lot of other stuff in common that you guys don't even see
but
in terms of how
How would you have?
How would you make it work if you didn't have anything in common?
I don't know. I really do. I really can't answer that question. Unfortunately. I can't really give you a good answer
Because i'm trying to think of of if i've ever been in a scenario that was like that
But all the relationships that i've had there's been there's been at least a few things that were really
That we really clicked on
So I really can't give you too much advice on this or I can't give you my thoughts on it because I don't really
I don't really have an experience with it
Like what what do you have in common?
We both knit
We both sew
We both like we both love wine. We both like wine. We were very very passionate about wine
We both love food
We both love animals
A majority of our conversations are about animals are about dogs specifically auto
um
We both live in north las vegas, you know, right?
or henderson or summerlin or
Enterprise or i don't live on the strip. Yeah, nobody can live on the strip. It doesn't work that way
Nobody nobody like lives in like the belagio guys. That's not how it works. So that pretty much confirms the strip
Stop
Stop that now we got him. Nobody got me. Nobody got me
Uh, no, but we have we have plenty things in common. I don't know anything about knitting at all. I made that up
To make us seem cute
Shit, how do you have so much energy?
uh, it bottles up to a point where I can't contain it anymore and it has to come out either with a loud expletive noise
or
This has to come out has to but thank you snooze for the 15 dollars. Appreciate it. Miami hotlines again 250
Wow king you're so bad at this game. That's really epic and sexy of you. That's funny
That actually is kind of a funny comment the end of it. It's funny, too
Uh, thanks for the 250. Thanks the fax machine for the five community subs
Appreciate that
50 from goiki goiki. Thanks for the 5000 bits clown convention waiting room. I know and we didn't get to see it
We didn't get to even see it
Thanks for the 5000 bits
50 fucking dollars, dude
It was a little while ago, but sorry. I missed it. It's a lot of money
Hey geo love. Thanks with three dollars germa. Go see the clowns. I didn't I know I
Shit went off the rails there at the end
We'll come back to it tomorrow. We'll figure it out
Fix related cabbage. Thanks for 250 germa
I saw that you played super mario rpg last year and I was wondering if you would ever play paper mario
Maybe around august for the first game's 20th anniversary
Um, I mean august is long enough away where I could lie to you and say yes and then forget
But i'm not gonna do that I feel like I do that quite often
um
I'm gonna say maybe maybe for the 20th anniversary. Maybe
I know people love that game
Worth a shot. Hey skinny peter
Thanks for the thousand bits germa if we're going to get an easy bake oven stream
Could we also get a creepy crawly bug maker stream?
Part of the plan not only is it going to be an easy bake oven stream
But i'm also getting a bunch of other of those toy food item game things
And that's going to be one of them
Although I might refuse to eat them because they creepy crawler bug maker shit
Released in like 1998
And this stuff probably is not edible anymore. We'll find out if there's any new ones
Thanks for the thousand bits though
Our alecran thanks for the 250 germa. It's so nice to have found a conservative trump supporting streamer. I know I knew
As soon as you refuse to support bernie by rating him
political bernie pog
God you guys
You guys are on point tonight
Find his address
and
What political party does he follow?
Because you guys are fucking on fire tonight
He's actually northeast vegas
Northeast vegas left leaning
You guys are fucking nuts
Northeast vegas left. All right
We've had so many conversations on this stream about random shit. You could probably fucking piece together
The type of kind of political leanings that I have
Do it's not you know what I mean? Like do I really do you really what do you think?
He's a fucking liberal. He's a liberal
He must be he's got to be he's got to be and that's big that fires me up
No, he's probably he's one of those fucking right winners
God, I hate those mother fuckers
You understand how like he there's no winning here
What if what if I say one of these out loud half of you hate me for the rest of my life
You understand how this works?
Even if I do fall politically in one of these categories saying it out loud is a like
A third of you no longer want to hear me talk anymore. We don't already god damn it
At the east
Left leaning god damn it
All right. All right enough enough enough enough. We're moving on we're moving on from this
I don't like that. I don't like this joke. We're moving on from it. It's too. All right, we're too much. Let's go
No more no more of this. No more of this. No more. There's no more. No more. No more. No more. No more
here, okay, I live in a giant shoe in the middle of space and
I'm not even from your fucking planet. So how am I supposed to know where I've leaned politically on your planet?
I don't even know who what this is. I don't even know what the democrat republican left serve. I don't know if that is
I've got my own system up here
There you go. This is your answer for all your questions. Thanks. Goobery juice with the five dollars
Hey, oh, no ludo. Nine eight five. These are some memes and chat that you missed. Why don't we have like a me a chat meme?
Recap I thought I should start donating these so that the creators of these memes can get your reaction
Also last stream you implied
That something was going to happen to bugleberry in the future. No
Like no, that's not what i'm talking about
Bugleberry's gonna be fine. Don't worry
uh
But for the for the meme reactions, here's what's gonna happen. This is what's gonna happen here
I don't know how this is gonna be done, but this is how it's gonna be done
There's a lot of images that come on this stream tons of people give
Images there's links and links and hey, I want to see this. I want to see that. Hey check this out
Look at this. There's a photoshop
What's gonna happen is i'm gonna have
a window browser source that is capturing
a website that website will be
I'm not going to tell you what website this is
Because I don't fuck who cares. It's reddit. There's going to be a reddit
That's specifically going to be for image uploads
And I can capture it and over the course of the stream. I can just cap it and we can go through like three or four of them
They'll just be right there
And if there's images that come through the stream like they always is like at least five six seven of them come out of each stream
It'll already be captured and we can already just do it
And they can be you know
If we have a good enough non shit posting kind of yeah guy
I'm just gonna spam the reddit. We'll have people check them before I click so there'll be ways for me to check
That'll work out
So then it keeps image links out of the chat room so people can chat
Or yell their favorite video game at me once a day
And we can have that in a separate place that it's easy for me to get to
Crash bandicoot 2 that's your favorite game
Well, we should probably talk about that
But that's where they're gonna be and I and by the way, i'm making the reddit
So it's like well, okay. I I have two already. No, no, no, no. No, it's i'm gonna own this shit
And you will not know what it is until it is ready and it's only gonna come from my mouth
That's where it's gonna go. How'd you call me out like that?
I've won. I said we have to talk about that. Why not crash bandicoot 3?
Racing team racing. Why two?
I thought three was a better one three had more characters three had more tracks and it was graphically superior
I'm just I that's just my opinion. That's what I think
Is there a crash team racing three?
Is there one?
No, okay. Never mind. Uh in the meantime
we're
we're gonna have to
abstain from
Clicking on images and till I get that shit going i'm gonna try to get that going over the next few days
Probably like next week or in like probably two months because that's like a real time frame from my fucking
High koala brain
Uh, let's see. What do you got?
What do you got? What do you got?
And there's a bunch of videos on here
I'd save them save them save them. There's there's like eight. There's like three videos and eight like seven images on here
Those three images in four videos
And I save them for community content night. Oh, but we never see those because he never fucking does those either
Yeah, I know. I know. I know give it to me. Let me hear it. Let me hear it. I know let me hear it
At least click the last image
Hold on. Let me load some of these up. Oh my fucking god
I this is not even my
Okay, i'll show off the images and let's hold on a second. Oh, this is fucking terrifying
Why do all these have to be besides the bernie pogg one?
Let's take a look at this one pretty good. All right, that one's good
This is an ed ed and eddy picture of ed
I believe that is him eating a shoe
It is okay
and then here is
bernie pogg
Where is it?
Okay. Well, I didn't mean to stretch that what is this one? I can't make that an emo. That's not my face
Watch that if you want
Here look it's like a ton of noise and a bunch of kids like
Oh look at that you just walk in and you just go like
All right. I'll see you guys tomorrow
That's the end
That's where it ends
except
Uh squimps gave ten dollars and fifty cents ten fifty
Thanks to the bits. Thanks to the big bits. That's over ten dollars. Thank you. Hey germ
I'm a college student who got kicked out of the dorms by the whole covet situation
Those streams have really helped me get through everything
I've been in quarantine with my dad and we watch your streams together pretty much every day
Anyways, it's his birthday tomorrow
You can wish him a happy birthday. That would be pretty cool
All right, you don't have to of course I will
Hey lewis, happy birthday lewis
Take care of each other. Hope you have a great one
Not sure how old you are, but
Hey
38 never looks so good, right? Happy birthday lewis. Thanks for watching you two both of you
38 with a college. I'm not that that's that's like a
Like a hey you look 38 and if you're like 40 or 55 or something like that
Oh, if you're like in your 40s or 50s like oh what i'm 30. I look 38. That's good
That's like a good thing like hey 38 never looks so good, right? You look like you're 38. You could be like 50
That's good. That's why I said that
That's a boomer joke
Yeah, okay sweat out. What are you? I'm not no i'm not mocking anybody
So it doesn't look 38. No, i'm saying like
Let's say for instance, let's just say for instance that somebody's like 50 years old or 45 years old
Hey, dude, like hey 38 never looks so good, right? Like, oh 38. Yeah. Okay, you're fun. Stop we get it
No, you don't half of you don't half of you don't get it
And that's very clear
By the way that you are acting
See you tomorrow wait
I
Didn't want to miss
bits
from dumpus rumpus
Dumpus rumpus. Thanks for five dollars. Jeremy long time viewer first time donator. Thanks dumpus
Thanks for being my favorite entertainer for the last like eight fucking years
I can't believe you still think i'm interesting eight years later
We've talked about this before
But
um watching tv shows
After season seven or eight usually people just don't fucking care anymore. That's shocking to me
I'm like, I can't believe people still like this
Well, thanks
Appreciate it. No, we're not raiding it. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
No
I gotta get them under control. I've got to get them under control
That's gonna it's gonna take a double to get them under control
We're gonna have to take double. I think yep it is
Stop
Okay, good
Hey, juby. Thanks for the five dollars. This has been a god tier stream. You ever played evil genius
If you like this game, I think that'd make a great stream too. It's actually on the list. It is on the list
Get rid of me, please
You're gonna say my name spell it correctly
Be a lot. I see it misspelled quite frequently actually
All right. I'll see you tomorrow. Good night guys
Take care. Have a great rest of your night. Yep. We're gonna play more casino ink tomorrow afternoon and then from there
From there we will go
to potentially watch a movie
I and I i'm i'm not gonna talk about this tomorrow. I think i'm gonna talk about this tomorrow, but
Never mind. This is funny to me. I'm holding this for tomorrow
This is a funny thing that i'm gonna say that I can't wait to say tomorrow. It's gonna be great
I can't wait. We've got to pick the movie tomorrow tomorrow is pick the amazon amazon prime movie
So during casino ink we have to i'm gonna have to go on cam. We're gonna have to figure this out important
I'm not gonna forget
Say it i'll miss it
No, no, no, it's basically it's a it's a part of that stream joke that it's gonna be funny
It's gonna be very funny for me
No, it's not even a joke. It's not even a joke. It's just something funny that I think is funny. That's it
It's gonna be i'm gonna think it's funny
I don't need to write it down. I look I don't need to write it down
It's not a joke. It's something that i'm gonna do on the stream
Or not do on the stream. All right, let me okay fine
Fine
No, i'm not gonna say it because it's funny
No, it's funny. I'm not gonna do it. I'm doing it tomorrow. See you tomorrow night. Bye. See you tomorrow