Once we turn this corner, you're probably gonna kill a lot of people.
This should be fun.
Alright, you ready?
Where'd the sniper come from?
Right when you come out here.
Oh, come on!
That would've been so epic.
If you had just jumped out here and there was like a dozen people.
That was anticlimactic.
Yeah, just a little bit.
Look at this big, handsome Russian.
Ha ha!
What was he a spy?
Oh no, he changed him. Shit.
That was the stupidest thing ever.
He looks conspicuous. Oh, ready to give him a sandwich.
Oh, I got him.
Oh, I think I gave it to the sniper by accident.
Dude, you just walked up and just like, yeah, like punched that guy.
He just like, groaned. That was great.
He changed him.
That was great.
You guys could not have planned that.
That was fantastic.
I'm so glad I'm recording that right now because I'm probably gonna put it somewhere.
Yeah, definitely. That was funny.
Uh-oh. Oh, here we go.
Oh, nope.
Damn it.
They're just rolling it.
I feel like every time we get up here, it's like, just the most...
I feel like we're in like a movie and there's nothing ever happening.
We're gonna win, right?
You know what? Here, just...
Yeah, I'm done.
Oh, where did you come from?
There was a scout behind me.
A lot of stuff going on.
Oh, I can't go up there with you, man. I'm gonna get destroyed.
And there's a spy right here. Get hit with a guy with a beard.
Shit.
Oh, he actually got the point. Shit.
That's... What?
Wait a second.
Oh, he's real.
Hold on a second. He's real?
He is real.
I shot him. He walked through me.
Oh, wow.
All right, let's do the pyro behind.
Sandwiches.
I got you. Come here, brah.
Come here, brah.
Oh, okay.
Why are we all still just like standing here?
Is this not the right capture point?
I feel like this guy's a spy, man. Every time.
He's just holding the syringe gun.
Boy Who Cried Wolf. One of these times, someone's gonna come behind us and it's gonna actually be a spy.
Oh, come here.
Oh, this guy needs it more.
Yeah, I'll grab a health kit.
All right, I got crits.
Here we go.
Let's overheal the hell out of everybody.
This pyro.
And...
Let me know when you want it.
Wait till we see a bunch.
Oh, come here.
Yikes.
Is the healing beam even on you?
Why is it going the...
What's going on here?
Why is it going the other direction?
Did you get a headshot?
Yeah.
Oh, dear.
Are you a spy?
No, you're not.
I'm gonna use this crits, man.
It's holding on to this.
Yeah, it's popping on anybody.
All right, Ryan.
I hope you're ready.
They're gonna come from over there.
And we're gonna need you.
Oh, baby.
One more.
Yes.
And we're gonna...
Oh, good thing we killed that one heavy...
This is so, like...
That's a pretty awesome arrow.
This guy looks like he's literally just standing here guarding the door like a bouncer.
Hey, quote on the cop.
What's up, buddy?
Come here, Mr. Green Acid Face.
Now, let's see how many people liking beard in a row.
Here we go.
I'm gonna go for some beards.
You wanna get bearded?
You wanna get hit with a beard?
Come on.
Come on out.
This guy is afraid of me.
And I literally am holding the beard as a medic.
I'm holding the do-no-harm thing.
Let's go.
Here we go.
Going in.
Oh, you wanna go?
Going in hot.
Come on, man.
Really?
What?
You're not gonna do it?
I'm following you.
I'm gonna follow you all the way to where...
Oh, you prick.
I'm still gonna get him.
Oh!
I got crits.
I don't know who the hell...
There's only two snipers here.
Crits behind you.
Turn around, please.
Turn around.
Well, he died.
They got a sentry.
Oh, this is gonna be hard.
Yeah, that sentry's looking at me funny.
I'm just sitting here with this guy.
Get, like, a nice hefty over-heel.
Thank you.
Ah, it's a demo, man.
And he missed.
I'm just sitting here.
This guy is so ridiculous.
This guy's insane.
This guy's just getting, like, headshots over and over again.
I'm just, like, protecting him.
Pocket sniper.
I don't know.
That's not such a good idea anymore.
Come to me.
Oh, thanks.
So, this is a very unsafe door.
Oh, boy.
Yeah, this is not...
Almost hit me in the head.
It's not a good place to be.
Sentry.
Is the sentry still there?
No.
Dead with a spy, I think.
I got a charge.
Are there any, like, power classes around here?
Oh, the sentry's at the back.
Oh, no!
Get away from me!
Eat beard!
I just lagged, but please let...
What the hell is going on?
I was about to make fun of myself.
And this guy, when he makes the step over here, is dead.
Heavy, when you come out, I'm waiting for the heavy.
Specifically.
Just to make, like, a point.
Where is he?
If this is not the most obvious spy in the world, I really don't know what it is.
I'm standing here.
Fuck you, Jared.
Go back to Subway.
Please just roll us right now.
Oh, my God!
What did I just do?
Dude, I just...
Oh, my...
All right, dude.
Okay, so I just...
You know, when you use the huntsman, you just, like, come out and, like, block...
By the way, I'm so glad this is over.
We just, like, lost.
All right, so, you know, you ever just use the huntsman, and you just blind fire randomly, just, like, knock an arrow for fun?
I just did that out of the spawn door, and I headshot a guy on our own team who was a spy, and he had him in the face.
He was, like, all the way down.
That was ridiculous.
That guy's probably so pissed.