Hello. I told you it was gonna be no later than five. I said no later than 5
p.m. and it is 4 59. I tell you there's no way it's gonna be later than that. Were
you in chat? Um, for a- for maybe five minutes? Over the last hour and ten
minutes? I think the chat was open but that's just to make sure I have it
prepared for when I truly am live. Yeah. The only excuse for this is if you are
currently on a face cam and you're in a full fat suit. Yeah, sorry guys. I had to
get- I had to get in a big fat suit. No, that is unfortunately not the case. This
is gonna be an instant classic stream. We'll see. I'm just gonna watch ads. I have
some compilations of 80s and 90s commercials. These streams are comfy. I
like these too. It's fun just to kind of watch and hang up. I'm enjoying it
already. I'm gonna do- yeah, I'll do face cam for a little bit. I'll do face cam
for a little bit. Are these American or international? These are American, I
believe. At least most of them are. Oh yeah. I don't plan on streaming for that
long today. I'm not gonna give a time limit but it's probably gonna be a few
hours. Something like that. I feel like there's only so many of these I can do before I just
need to like take a bath and then I'll be live tomorrow. Why are you taking a
bath? Bath? Well guys, I don't know. It's nice to take a bath sometime. What are we
doing tomorrow? We are playing House Flipper Farm Flipper Update or whatever
the hell it is. I'm very excited for it as you know. Maybe you don't. You might be
new to the stream. House Flipper is one of my favorite games ever and I'm
probably- I'm probably the only person on Twitch that has streamed it for a hundred
hours. I can claim that fame, I think. If somebody has streamed it longer than
me then yep. I'm good. You can take that award. Have you been doing- am I gonna
read that? Alright, are you guys ready? We're gonna watch some ads. I got
compilations. I'm ready. Are you ready? Are you excited?
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. There's only like 2,000 people here
that heard that so I don't care. Yahoo. Yeah. It's 10k? What? It was- my thing
says 2. There's way more people just heard that. Whatever. I feel like if you've
decided to watch this stream you've already decided what could happen here.
Does that make sense? I feel like if you've been here, you
did you have watched more than one stream, I think you know that this stream sucks.
Let's go. Alright, I'm ready. No, this stream is sick actually. This is a
good stream. I like this stream. It's my stream so I want to say that. Come on.
This is mid shit. I like this mid shit. Alright, now let's watch commercials
together. Alright, this is this is 80s. Are we ready? I'm sure it's not too loud.
Yeah, back off. Hair dye. No hair dye actually. I'm just- I'm just gonna go
until it looks bad. You know what I mean? If I started using hair dye now, why'd you go
with 986 and not 985? I don't know. No, I'm just gonna age. However I look is
how I look. I'm just gonna age. Alright, let's go. I don't know why I sat there
for so long. Alright, are you ready? These are 80s commercials. I can't wait to
start to talk about them. Oh, it's not too loud.
Return after these messages. I think it's alright. Alright.
Okay everybody, come outside. Everybody ready for a-
I had one of these.
These were fun. I'm pausing. I know. Don't stop pausing. Don't skip. I just have to
say something about this. These things are really fun until you hit a bunch of
rocks. There was always that one- that one kid that was- the thing was laid out
and you start all the way at the back of the yard and you run as fast as you
possibly- this thing was not- this thing was not designed for you to go that fast
on it. You could just go off of it or there'd be a bump in the grass and it
would be a fucking rock and you would just start sprinting. Sprint sprint
sprint jump like layout and just fucking slide like a cartoon bowling alley. Like
you're sliding all the way down and then you sort of rock on your elbow. These
things were crazy. This thing was a hazard. It really was. But yeah, it was a
hazard. It was still fun though. Didn't they make changes to this over the years
where you kind of couldn't go that fast? I feel like that was- I feel like that's
accurate. Oh, I didn't tweet. Okay, let me tweet. And there was always that kid at
the party or whatever that they did this until they went home. It was, okay, let's
get the slip and slide out and like little Jerry just does not stop for eight
hours. It's the only thing they do. They were fun though. All right, let me tweet.
Hey, there's a tweet. Good, okay. All right, officially tweeted. They are going
fast though. I want to see how fast they're actually going. Yeah, you sprint.
Slip and slide comes with plastic slide and fasteners from Whammo. And fasteners.
Did anybody even use those?
Thank you. Where's Grimace's voice lines? Is that before that Grimace had voice lines?
What the fuck? How does this not hurt? This would be excruciating pain. What? I want to
see more of what happened there. That dude had a straight face. What was that an ad
for? What was that an ad for? They did- oh, for Turboteen. Okay. What was it trying to
show us? Excuse me. The no reaction is just- I don't know. I like it. I don't- this is
like- there needs to be a little bit of, I think, emotion here. We'll return after these
messages. That's the same guy. That's the same kid right there. This is one of the Turboteens.
He's in the same outfit. That's super accurate though. Kids just like- when kids really just
love just random made up words, it's just so fun to them. That's a very accurate commercial.
You try it. What was it? Let me see if I can go- Well, let me give me a second to do it.
The floppy- the floppy flat fruit snacks from S- Sunkist. I didn't- I couldn't do it. The floppy-
the floppy flat fruit snacks from Sunkist. The floppy flat fruit snacks from Sunkist. Fucking
easy. Yes! What simpler times? Wow. Times are so different. This was enough
to drive everybody crazy. I got a standing ovation back in the 80s. Times are so simple back then.
Oh, carrot. Otto's gonna eat one of those later. What are you fucking down that?
What is this food?
Oh, Jack. Turboteen's back.
I just want you to know so bad that this kid could turn into a car.
Is that the whole show? Is the entire show Turboteen that?
Dairy Queen Sunday free. Oh, free Sunday. We're gonna replay this because I don't give a shit
that McDonald's like serves coffee. You know what I mean? I'm gonna restart this. I don't give a
shit that McDonald's has coffee. It's like a cafe now. She's like, oh, McDonald's. It's like a cafe.
We have coffee and lunch. Where are these fucked up characters?
Where are all the McNuggets? Like the puppet show?
Packages of Froot Loops. Ronald McDonald presents us Chicken McNuggets. It makes the big story.
One day Goldilocks and the Gingerbread Man were bringing delicious sauces to Grandma.
Wait a minute. That's not in the script. You're in the wrong story. I am. Aren't you little bo-peep?
Hold it. We're doing Little Red Robin Hood and it's two pigs. Pigs?
It's a good time for the great taste. You're all in the wrong story.
But the right sauce is Ronald McDonald's. That was so funny.
A lineup of fun starting out. Oh, it's the credits of Turbo Teen. What's happening?
Then just around the bend, it's that unpredictable Gary Coleman and different strokes.
And for high flying action, it's the Dukes of Hazzard at four. It's all happening. You hate
Ronald? Why? Right here on BRC 6. How could you hate Ronald McDonald? Like I have all the things to hate.
Oh, I'm all right with this.
Schoolhouse Rock.
The curtain is rising. We're so glad to have you here. Come see a new show daily in the atmosphere.
Act one. That's fun. The sun shines down on field and town. On forest, mountain, desert, sea and snow.
Some heat's absorbed. Some bounces off. So here it's hot. This is an ad. Maybe not.
I think it's just here.
Sing with, I don't know the lyrics.
There's science here.
Look, I don't give a shit if you have coffee.
I want this. Get this back.
How do you read this trap? Laughing my ass off. I'm playing Metal Gear Solid 5,
so I won't listen for your answer. Whoa, why am I reading your comment?
What? What does that mean? You asked a question and you just dipped right after asking the question.
This actually, did I go to, no, it's the same one. It's some educational shit, right?
Cloud Japan. Remember, you're not learning. How do you know that?
Skip it if it's not an ad, but I kind of like it.
I mean, Herboteen technically wasn't an ad. I'm glad I didn't skip that.
ABC's Schoolhouse Rock is brought to you by.
Okay, now we're on Schoolhouse Rock. Okay.
Wake up, guys. We've got work to do.
We've got to get out the breakfast edition. What's it say? Snap, crackle, pop.
What else? Hey, like wake the fuck up. Like, holy smokes.
What are you, a newspaper?
Sounds good. Kellogg's Rice Krispies, the talking part of this complete breakfast.
Hold on a second. Good work, guys.
I love this because this is actually really hard. This is really difficult.
This kid doesn't, can't see these characters. They probably,
they probably told him to look in a certain direction and this is really hard to do.
So, Kellogg's Rice Krispies. I want to see the beginning again.
I want to see, oh, they're sleeping.
ABC's Schoolhouse Rock is brought to you by Kellogg.
They are, they're in REM sleep right now and this kid drops the equivalent of like
three bowling balls on the table right next to his head. Right next to his head.
Look at that reaction. Look at this. They're not happy. This is awful. This is, this is awful.
Look at the fear in these faces. This is tons of, this is uncomfortable. This is awful.
They still don't know. Look at how tired they are. And then, to do what?
What was this kid waking them up for? He's still not out of it yet.
Keep in mind, they just were ripped out of REM sleep and told they needed to do this today.
Was there a job to pour the cereal?
Oh, Schoolhouse Rock. Let's go.
I don't know why I thought that was so funny. Just, just listen. Hold on.
I don't know why that's funny to me. Is that funny?
I think it's because I could hear like the, this is ABC.
You're the power line. Your daddy and you make the house look fine.
Wait, why are they doing this?
This lightning bug doesn't raise his ass in the near power. Stay away from power. Stay away from power.
Yeah. Okay. That's good. We'll return after these messages.
You're in the big league play. You make a perfect sly. You're in the big league.
Big league house. When you keep the team alive. You're in the big league.
Big league shreds. When you block a shot or two.
You're in the big league flavor. You're in the big league chew.
Big league chew. Man-sized wads of great taste of shredded bubblegum stuffed into a giant stay-fresh
couch. You're in the big league flavor and big league bubble. You're in the big league chew.
Did it say man-sized? No, it didn't.
You're in the big league flavor. You're in the big league chew.
Big league chew. Man-sized wads of great taste of shredded bubblegum stuffed into a giant stay-fresh
couch. You're in the big league flavor and big league bubble. You're in the big league chew.
That stuff is delicious, by the way. I love that stuff.
That there's OJ Joe. I haven't had it in a long time and it's good.
Where they'll take the sweet juice and put it into new OJs. A crunchy delicious orange
juice. Wait, this is a... It's a cereal.
That's weird. I never heard of that. Orange juice cereal?
You get detention for shit like that. You get detention for shit like that.
Sometimes a man just needs to be alone with his fruit chewy Newton's cookies.
Those are still good. With fruit chewy chunks of real apple.
Hey Jimbo, where are you? And Finn Newtons too.
You're here somewhere and I got those fruit chewy Newtons.
Fruit chewy Newtons. Let you ride my bike.
Tastes too good to give up. Nabisco.
I mean, they're good. Next, who's the hippest? Who's the happy?
What big surprises come in tiny packages? If it's fun we want, then it's the little...
Can we watch? Can I see? I want to see something one more time.
I'm Captain OJ Reborn. My motto's tried and true.
Read a book today, I bet you'll say OJ. I'll read more too.
Okay.
We now continue with Rubik the OJ.
I want to... I just want to see one more time.
I just need to see this. Just one final time was Rubik the Amazing Cube.
Okay, there's so much weird shit from the 80s and 90s.
I just... It's just, this is so fucking messed up.
I have to just... I just need to see this one more time.
What is giving him this power? Watch something else?
I am. I don't want to give you any spoilers.
I... Let's come back.
You're in the big leagues.
All right, this is 90s. I had a lot of bookmarks.
I want to make sure I didn't... New novels set in the 80s.
How's the camping? Is it... Oh, is this... Oh, okay.
We should read this.
Mr. McDonald, let's talk chicken.
What?
Are you aware that the public prefers the taste of Kentucky nuggets
to your chicken muck nuggets by almost three to one?
No, sir.
And is your muck chicken sandwich made with the colonel's secret blend of 11 herbs and spices?
So how do you expect to sell chicken?
Toys. Lots of toys.
Taste our best.
A dollar and 99 for the colonel's chicken sandwich and fries or Kentucky nuggets and fries.
What am I supposed to be doing without makeup on?
There comes a time in every guy's life when, well, things begin to change.
You know what I'm talking about, fellas?
Suddenly, wheels means cars instead of skateboards.
Look, let's broaden your horizons. It's time to move on.
Instead of always reaching for that same old bag of potato chips,
why not tear into a bag of nacho cheese, Doritos tortilla chips?
Bigger taste, bigger crunch.
What is this fucking AI-generated couch that he's sitting on?
Nacho chip that bites back.
Come on.
Nacho cheese Doritos.
You're a man now. You're gonna handle it.
Oh, man-sized portions, of course.
Punch all you want.
We'll make more.
Dave. Dave.
I think these are a lot of fast food.
If you make a grilled chicken sandwich at Wendy's, they will come.
They will?
If you make it with a chicken breast, they will come.
It has to be boneless.
If you make it with lettuce and tomato.
And honey and mustard.
And put it all together on a toasted bun, they will come.
Call it Wendy's grilled chicken sandwich.
Dave, I told you they will come.
It's Wendy. I just can't figure out how she's doing it.
For fun around here, me and the boys like to do something a little bit crazy.
Put two kinds of cheese on a cheeseburger.
Oh, that's crazy.
For a new taste, head to the store for two kinds of cheese and lean ground beef.
Cheddar and mustard.
Crazy.
Uh-oh.
Fortunately, Seeley's exclusive post-traumatic sleep system is designed to support everyone differently.
Keep your night from becoming your worst nightmare.
Is that a sink in their bedroom?
For a better night's sleep, better sleep on a ceiling.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wednesday.
Marty, this isn't just a-
Where is this?
More comfortably.
Is this supposed to be the bathroom?
Keep your night from becoming your worst nightmare.
Oh, I thought it was sitting, like, where a nightstand would be.
For a better night's sleep, better sleep on a ceiling.
Wednesday.
Marty, this isn't just about sex.
No, no, I know.
There's a little about sex, though, isn't it?
It's sort of nice on the phone.
It's a portable. I'll bring it with me.
Things are really heating up.
Anything but love after Doogie Hussein.
When Reggie and I agreed to meet for breakfast,
I didn't think I needed to say where.
It could only be one place.
Where else can you get this delicious bacon, egg, and cheese biscuit?
Uh, nowhere.
So much for him.
True.
Jump that with your car?
Nice move, Jack.
The Prelude SI with four-wheel steering.
I mean, I would consider that cheating.
That's cheating.
They didn't do it.
You think you could have a party every time you come out with a new product?
This is really nice.
They don't have a party like this every night.
This is big.
This is really big.
This new light microwave popcorn.
I thought that was a cigar.
With one-third fewer calories and two-thirds less fat than our regular microwave.
And it pops up more than any other light microwave.
It's gonna keep my figure just like it is today.
Well, you're pretty good-looking, Grandpa, you know.
That's what Grandma says, too.
Yeah.
Not all of us can be as good-looking as you, Grandpa.
That's great.
That's true. That's true.
If you don't have the Orville Rennbacher in your pantry,
I don't know what the hell's going on.
Look what's new at McDonald's.
What is it, Dad?
Let's just wait and see.
It's the stars of Walt Disney's classic movie 101 Dalmatians.
Oh, they're just trying to sell toys.
They got the real chicken over here at KFC.
The Colonel with Sergeant Tibbs.
Lucky, get down.
Or Cruella Toy.
Each week when you buy your kids a $1.99 hamburger Happy Meal.
It was a $1.90.
It was only $2.
How much is Happy Meal now?
Does your man control you, McSalad?
That was just staring into the camera.
Now at Little Caesars, you can get Picnic Picnic.
Two medium pizzas, two orders of crazy bread,
and two servings of cold classic all for only $7.98.
It's Picnic Picnic.
Two pizzas, two crazy breads, two soft drinks,
all that food for only $7.98.
What?
When it rains, it pours.
Picnic Picnic only at Little Caesars.
This was $8.
What?
Are you serious?
Why are beers that go down lightly?
Watered down so heavily?
Why?
Ask?
Turn off the water.
And turn Bud Dry.
It's smooth draft-tasted dry brew.
Bud Dry?
Not watered down.
To drink light.
What are they implying about their other beer?
So why get soaked when you can drink Bud Dry?
A baby changes everything.
Safety takes on a whole new meaning when it's somebody you love in that car.
This is our family.
They're the most technically advanced and life-like dummies in the world.
Only GM uses a family like this to develop safety technology
because we know quality cars, safe cars, should help protect everyone.
I look at my family and I want us to be thinking of everything.
GM safety, it's not one thing, it's everything.
She's everything to me.
Dorothy.
Can you marry me?
Where's my ring?
A life.
I thought they had to show the car speeding.
Like going fast into what I imagine is a wall.
Like that was just like kind of came out of nowhere for me.
Ugh.
Fuck.
It's important.
This is important shit.
GM safety, it's not one thing.
I want us to be thinking of everything.
It's everything.
She's everything to me.
I, it just, it just kind of fucked up.
Dorothy, can you marry me?
Where's my ring?
That's important stuff.
A lifesaver?
I did not like to see the car flying by and I'm like, what the fuck, man?
Don't worry.
We'll live with my mother.
Lifesaver's candy.
Isn't life delicious?
Macy's preseason sale.
The shopping opportunity of the year.
You'll save on fall's newest fashions now.
Before the fall season, at our lowest prices of the year.
The best for women, men, and kids.
Why are they taking pictures?
Everything you need for fall, from the names you really want.
These aren't even the models.
These people just walked up on stage.
Macy's preseason sale.
Don't let prices go up.
This fifth.
This is just, the show's not on yet.
A bunch of people just started walking up on stage.
Our famous steak or chicken fajita combos and a delicious dessert.
All just $7.95 at El Torito.
Three bites, hey!
Three bites big, house of eight.
New snacks, snacks, and Milky Way.
Hold on, I missed that.
This one's fucking crazy, hold on.
Three bites big, house of eight.
New snacks, snacks, and Milky Way.
Introducing Milky Way and Snickers.
They're a brand new size.
Are they huge?
A new snack size.
Snack around the house side.
No, they're small.
But wait, wait, wait.
Why are they so big in the bag?
Three bites big, house of eight.
New snacks, snacks, and Milky Way.
And now, today's weather.
Cold winds out of the north-northwest.
With a 30% chance of snow tonight.
Temperatures dropping to the mid-to-low 20s.
Boy, this is going to be a hot day.
Keep it out there today.
At last, a weatherproof formula that
holds longer and stronger than the other leading pumps.
Honey, don't forget your boots.
Exclusively ours, new final and ultimate hold.
The weatherproof hold that lets you laugh at the weather.
Sandy Davis Jr.'s 60th anniversary celebration
will continue in a moment.
Tuesday's terrific in Port Lauderdale.
Hey, first, did I just feel a drop?
Or are you drooling?
It's who's the boss then?
She dumped me.
Paul, snap out of it.
She said I was suffocating her.
I thought she wanted to be suffocated.
The Wonder Years, Tuesday.
This is what American Airlines does better than anyone else.
Arrive on time, again and again.
In fact, American has had the best on-time arrival record
of the nine largest domestic airlines
for as long as records have been kept.
American Airlines, the on-time machine.
Is that still true?
It was a big day when the new equipment arrived.
It's big.
I got to make sure I carry my jacket around in two fingers.
Hold on.
Let me pinch my jacket between my thumb and my index finger.
It was a big day when the new equipment arrived.
It's big.
You're just one I've ever seen.
Of course, being a custom job, some assembly was required.
It'll be a few weeks, people.
But finally, it was ready.
One of the world's fastest check writing systems.
Some insurance companies look for ways
to get your money from you faster.
Here should be $12,000 an hour.
At Aetna, we look for ways to get your money to you faster.
Probe of misconduct by Oakland Housing Police on 7 at 11.
See, a woman's body is merely a frame
I created to release.
You won't see a leg in Paris this year.
No matter what the gentleman prefers.
The lady prefers hands.
Wake up to the nutritious delicious taste of carnation instant breakfast.
I would have loved to have been in some of these commercials.
Hey, can I just say, if all I had to do like,
okay, sir, you are the actor for this commercial.
You're going to take a sip out of chocolate milk
and you're going to do like a goofy movement with your arms
and do like a weird walk and that's it.
That's that's what you do.
I would be so good at this.
Take a sip of chocolate milk and then do like a little like,
whoa, I can feel that all the way through my bones
and then just walk out the door.
I'd be pretty good at that.
I think dog dog lovers.
This is ordinary dog food.
But feast your eyes on grand gourmet.
Twenty five percent more protein and less fat than leading brands.
Why do I feel like now it looks better?
Why do I feel like they're advertising to people?
It's like, oh, yeah.
Hey, dog lovers.
They didn't say anything about, hey, your dog is going to love this.
It was, hey, dog lovers, don't eat this shit.
Eat the chunky one that we just came up with.
But feast your hey, dog lovers.
This is ordinary dog food.
But feast your eyes on grand gourmet.
Twenty five percent more protein and less fat than leading brands.
Oh, grand gourmet.
And now it looks better.
It is better for dog lovers.
Red Lobster introduces our shrimp sensations dinner.
Just seven ninety nine with tangy shrimp vera grooves and new parmesan fried shrimp.
We can see your mouth of watering.
I'm just sitting there like, hold on.
That's so stupid.
I mean, it looks it does look pretty fucking delicious, doesn't it, though?
Very dog food.
But feast your I guess if I can get through this.
Hey, dog lovers.
This is ordinary dog food.
But feast your eyes on grand gourmet.
Twenty five percent more protein.
I can't.
It looks kind of good.
Less fat than leading brands.
OK, I'm telling you right now, I've eaten Salisbury steak that looked worse than that.
Grand gourmet.
And now it looks better.
It is better.
Red Lobster introduces our shrimp sensations dinner.
Just seven ninety nine with tangy shrimp vera grooves and new parmesan fried shrimp.
Together with popcorn shrimp.
Specially priced.
Just seven ninety nine.
Why is everything in nineteen ninety eight dollars?
It's Red Lobster's new lunch special.
Shrimp and chicken.
Just three ninety nine.
Golden fried shrimp and grilled chicken breast with salad and baked potato.
Wait.
For a limited time at Red Lobster.
Wait a second.
Together with popcorn shrimp.
Specially priced.
Just seven ninety nine.
This is way more expensive than the other one.
For a limited time.
Now at Red Lobster.
This is a huge difference.
It's Red Lobster's new lunch special.
Shrimp and chicken.
Just three ninety nine.
Golden fried shrimp and grilled chicken breast with salad and baked potato.
For a limited time at Red Lobster.
For lunch.
Oh it's a lunch special.
To our tribal breakfast cereals.
Total.
Kellogg's just right.
Both high nutrition cereals.
So what might make one better than the other?
Just right has vitamin B1.
We have vitamin B1.
Just right has vitamin B2.
B2.
Just right has iron.
We have iron.
Just right has vitamin E.
Oh plenty B.
Just right has vitamin B6.
B6 here.
Just right has almonds.
Just right has sweet dates.
Plump raisins.
Plus four different tasty grains.
Just right has two out of three people preferring our taste.
Which means just right is just better.
Kellogg's just right.
Well what if you don't want all that shit?
It makes it just better.
Something that the 80s and 90s did that kind of went away.
I don't know if you guys have picked up on this too.
Companies used to eviscerate each other by name.
It wasn't just oh oh those other brands.
No no no it was like like hey total.
Your cereal sucks.
You suck.
They would do it by name.
Nintendo.
Sega.
They used to just make fun of each other and use logos too.
They literally have the total logo.
And they have some guy being an actor.
Four different tasty almonds.
Pretending that this cereal sucks compared to this one.
It's crazy that this is they used to do this all the time.
Yeah I don't think you could even put this box on camera for like a commercial.
I don't think so right?
They do it on Twitter now.
I feel like I haven't seen it in a long time.
Just right has sweet dates.
Plump raisins plus.
Right now this representative to total is coming to a realization.
Which means just right is.
Oh no no that's way better.
My cereal is stupid.
It's the taste that makes it.
Your cereal is better.
I'm gonna eat yours now.
The Mureen earwax removal system has drops.
I don't want this one.
I don't want to wash this one.
It's probably gross.
That safely loosen hardened wax when used as directed.
Plus an ear washer to gently flush wax away.
Mureen, the complete medically approved system to safely remove earwax.
Is well below zero this morning.
That's Chevy's heartbeat.
With the electrical system fully taxed.
Chevy delivers for viable cold starting.
After thousands of tests an incredible 99.9% success record.
With 84 models redesigned and engineered.
GM is putting quality on the road.
All right I just gotta say um there's like a hundred million people in the United States.
That do what they did like a third of the whole year.
And there's not a whole team of people with walkie talkies.
It's Velveeta versus cheddar.
It's orange juice.
Our Velveeta.
That is thick.
Oh that's not I thought it was orange juice.
When the cookbook.
Oh that would be fucking awful orange juice.
Naked with Velveeta it cooks better.
That actually didn't even look good.
That looked kind of every day.
Gross didn't it?
When the cook.
Oh it's because they're saying it's gross.
It's Velveeta versus cheddar.
Our Velveeta melts much better.
When the cookbook calls for cheddar.
Naked with Velveeta it cooks better.
I mean you saw what the you saw what was on camera.
Every day 22 million people come into McDonald's.
They count on the same hot fresh food at every McDonald's all over the world.
But imagine if there were only one McDonald's you could count on.
And 22 million people came in at the same time.
The whole restaurant would fill up.
The city would fill up.
And all those people in one place would cause the earth to tilt off its axis
and go spinning into space.
Good thing we can avoid this catastrophic adventure.
By McDonald's having like 50,000 locations.
And that would make a real mess of everything.
That's why we make every McDonald's from Poughkeepsie to Pomona
just as good as every other McDonald's.
McDonald's protects us.
While the Daytona Shelby Turbo may not be quite as plush as the Aston Martin
and the power plant isn't quite like a Lamborghini.
You're never gonna catch me saying a goddamn thing bad about McDonald's.
One of the most powerful front wheels.
I'm sorry I'm never gonna I love that one.
And while it doesn't quite reach the speed of a Testerosa
at that speed you might miss something.
The all-new Dodge Daytona Shelby Turbo.
The hot new spirit of Dodge.
Now get the $2,000 back at Dodge.
Guaranteed.
Bravest men.
And no dream.
Turbo teen.
Are those with something to prove?
They gotta know that nobody's gonna fight.
Red cars.
We're just super popular.
Come daddy go and let the 54 get into us.
Matthew Broderick.
We'll be ready sir.
Denzel Washington.
Come on!
Kerry Elwes.
Ready!
Morgan Freeman.
Now playing at a theater near you.
In Vermont Washington when a kid's 18 he's old enough to drive.
Old enough.
There it is.
And old enough to worry about something most adults have.
Gingivitis.
An early reversible gum disease that left untreated could get serious.
Just ask your dentist.
Fortunately many know enough to use Listerine.
The only non-prescription mouthwash accepted by the American Dental Association
for helping to prevent and reduce plaque and gingivitis.
Yep.
If you're old enough to worry about-
Hold on.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
To reduce plaque and gingivitis.
They're not ready for this ball.
Yep.
If you're old-
Oh, was somebody there?
I couldn't tell.
Enough to worry about gum disease.
You ought to be smart enough to use Listerine.
I want to try something different.
Um, hold on.
I gotta process this one.
Oh, rewatch Andy.
Rewatch Andy.
I don't.
I need to see it.
Now playing at a theater near you.
Let me process-
They're saying-
What were they saying?
They're saying, when you turn 18, you worry about driving a car.
What was it?
In Vermont, Washington, when a kid's 18, he's old enough to drive.
Why only there?
Is it?
Old enough to vote.
And old enough to worry about something most adult.
Old enough to drive?
Old enough to vote.
And old enough to be terribly concerned about your gums.
Gingivitis.
An early reversible gum disease that left untreated could get serious.
Just ask your dentist.
Vote?
What?
I thought this was like some, like, boomer shit.
Like, oh, you're old enough to drive?
You're old enough to go vote?
Vermont, Washington, when a kid's 18, he's old enough to drive.
Old enough to vote.
And old enough to worry about something most adults have.
Gingivitis.
An early reversible gum disease that left untreated could get serious.
Most adults have Gingivitis back in 1980?
Just ask your dentist.
Fortunately, many know enough to use Listerine.
What?
The only non-prescription mouthwash accepted by the American Dental Association
for helping to prevent and reduce plaque and Gingivitis.
Yep.
If you're old enough to worry about gum disease,
you ought to be smart enough to use Listerine.
Okay.
I want to try something different.
Can you make me look like that?
Tuesday, it's a brand new job.
100% of those residents have Gingivitis.
Oh, I'm sure you can, Iris.
I'll go get the wand.
But she's the same old person.
100% of those residents.
I'm not going to spend the rest of my life slicing wire.
We all got chances, Elvis.
Some of them we just can't take.
In 1954, Vernon Presley wanted his son to have a steady job with a secure future.
His dream came true.
A special preview of Elvis, Tuesday.
Sammy Davis Jr.'s 60th anniversary celebration will continue in a moment.
You don't want, you don't get.
That's arithmetic.
Joe Kennedy.
He became the father of two senators and a president.
You're a very successful and wealthy man.
Isn't that winning?
No, not yet.
He had an appetite for power.
For the first Irish Catholic ambassador to England.
Wealth and women.
I've never made history with anyone I've made love with.
How soon will you be home?
If there's any dirty work to be done, I'll be the one to do it.
The Kennedys of Massachusetts.
Two weeks from tonight.
Lexus LS400 looks like an elegantly contoured luxury sedan.
It doesn't look LS400.
Nothing fucking funny even happens.
It's just a car just like slowly was zoomed in on and it's like enough to make me laugh.
Why do I think cars are so funny?
I don't know why.
I think it's because a lot of car companies treat cars like they're alive.
Like an animal or like it's a person or something.
To me, this is like a living being.
It's like, oh, look, there's like nobody in there in my brain for some reason.
It's like an elegantly.
It just makes me laugh every time.
Because there's nobody in this car.
And it's just like moving around and look at how luxurious I am.
I'm a fucking car.
Much.
What about Herbotein?
That's what I'm saying.
You like seeing living beings getting hurt that the car crash is to you?
No.
The cookie and cracker sunshine makes has absolutely no cholesterol.
Now, what could be better than sunshine?
Have a little sunshine.
Pentagon Waste reaches the billions on 7 at 11.
No cholesterol in the cookie.
But, all right.
Producers of the show, the producers of the show was hoping you'd have a little more feeling of.
Wedding dress.
You know, a little more Mike Tyson.
You know, more Mike Tyson.
Hello, ladies and gentlemen, Sammy and I would like.
We keep seeing the beginning in the middle of all these things that the programming was.
Oh, yeah.
Rock music.
Hey, Rizuchi.
Look a little pale.
Maybe he needs a doctor or something.
Maybe I do.
Hey, don't look at me.
That was very confusing.
The car.
I'm laughing at that last one.
Bad timing that a car came on screen.
I'm laughing at that last commercial.
This is delicious, Danny.
What do you call it?
It's new ragu fresh Italian pasta sauce.
So delicate.
What's it called?
Fresh Italian pasta sauce.
Yeah, it's really fresh, but what's the name?
Ragu uses less heavy tomato paste.
And twice the crushed tomatoes.
But what's the name?
Then total.
More crushed tomatoes, more fresh tomato taste.
Here's a jar.
Look, it has the name on it.
Forget it.
They instantly turn on.
You put that show lead on, and that spark is right there.
That's the difference between a good dog and a great dog.
These are champions.
They deserve the best.
And I recommend Pedigree and Pedigree Meal Time.
Pedigree.
Recommended by top breeders.
And now there's a new kind of pedigree.
Pedigree Choice Cuts.
The sauce dogs can't resist.
One look shows you its choice.
One feeding shows you it's irresistible.
Pedigree Choice Cuts.
Recommended by top breeders.
My poor brother Tom.
Every time he tried to see what he was missing,
he would miss what he was seeing.
The dog did it too.
Then Tom got this amazing Magnavox
TV that lets him watch one show
while he checks out all the others on this
remarkable little window.
Hey, that's a smart window, Dick.
They call it Tom?
No, no. They call it smart window Tom.
This was a big deal.
I kind of like Tom.
Magnavox. Smart choice.
Very smart.
The technology to do that was actually kind of crazy back in the day.
I am now officially a teenager.
It's DJ's first kiss.
13 candles.
An all new full house.
I'm 13!
Followed by a new Family Matters Friday.
All episodes.
Driving pretty.
Driving smart.
Chrysler New Yorker Fifth Avenue
is saying something all new.
And it's all about comfort,
style, and technology.
And Chrysler's exclusive crystal key
owner program completes the package.
This is so stupid.
I'm like pissed off at myself.
I'm laughing.
It wasn't even funny.
It was funny.
It wasn't even what I was laughing at.
I actually wasn't even laughing at that.
I think I'm in love.
I was laughing at the guy
just absolutely sucking.
Just throwing that.
Just flipping it over there.
Like he just throws that shit.
And that's all I could focus on.
And it's all about comfort, style, and technology.
And Chrysler's exclusive
crystal key owner program
completes the package.
All new Chrysler New Yorker Fifth Avenue.
If the rebate goes up,
Chrysler will pay you the difference.
The difference.
I think I'm in love.
They've got us unwrapped.
Out of your league.
Yeah.
Watch.
May I have a towel?
Recharge?
Never underestimate the doctor.
No. No.
Hi, excuse me. Are you French?
You look French. I love French food.
No, that's not what would have happened.
It would have gone like this.
This morning, I was following
a Sears service truck when it dawned on me.
I see Sears trucks all the time.
It also dawned on me that I hardly
ever see a service truck from those so-called
super stores.
So before you make that next big buying decision,
ask yourself what kind of service
you'll get five years from now.
Or if they'll even be around to answer the phone.
That's one of the big reasons
I feel better when I buy a major appliance
or electronics from Sears.
And that's what they mean by your money's worth.
And a whole lot more.
Yeah. Yeah.
Know what a lot of today's teens are doing?
They're thinking.
About their futures and the future of Black America.
That's why once again,
McDonald's celebrates Black History Month
by looking to the future.
Join us now as we salute our 1990
McDonald's Black History Makers of tomorrow.
These ten teens have been
selected because of their visions,
their dreams, and the roles they want to play
as leaders in America's future.
And someday they may truly have a place
in Black History.
Sears is gone.
This commercial
was awesome. I love every second of this commercial.
I remember this one.
Cake-sized Ritz Bitz
Peanut Butter Sandwiches.
The taste of Ritz Bitz and real peanut butter
in tiny sandwiches with no assembly
required.
That part where it spins.
Hey, what's your name?
Monday.
MacGyver goes out on a limb
to save the trees.
I can handle it.
MacGyver, then, based on a true story.
Daddy, you're alive!
The father who refused to let his family die.
I don't think he can. Are you sure?
Robert Conrad, anything to survive.
Monday.
I'm using this other long-distance company.
Try to call Phoenix. I miss dial feature.
I call the operator.
She says she can't give me instant credit.
I say AT&T always did.
She says you're not dealing with AT&T.
If you miss dealing with AT&T,
it's easier than ever to come back.
Just call 1-800-582-1700 right now,
and we'll switch you back for free.
Come back?
They kept saying how much money I'd save.
Then I get the first bill?
I'm not kidding. I thought it was a title.
Give us a call anytime.
People who thought they could do better than AT&T
are coming back for the real value.
You can too. It's simple.
Call now and come back for free.
Come back for free?
You have to pay?
What do you mean come back for free?
I couldn't believe it.
You're not dealing with AT&T.
1-800-582-1700
for dependable, crystal-clear
AT&T long-distance service.
Call now and we'll switch you for free.
You couldn't pick a better time to come back.
I wonder if there was another promotion on top of that.
If you want an anti-lock braking system
like Mercedes,
a driver airbag like BMW,
a rear load-leveling suspension feature
similar to Rolls,
and a more advanced transmission
than Jaguar,
this is a simple way
to get it all.
Introducing the all-new Chrysler
Imperial.
There is no luxury without engineering.
Thank god it didn't move.
The guaranteed rebate has been extended until February 28.
There's only one thing I used to hate worse
than having to wash out my pantyhose every night.
Trying not to laugh.
And that was having to throw them out.
Pantyhose that lasts are no nonsense.
I would lose.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Dennis Miller.
I just knew they'd call.
I wish I wasn't so easily amused by cars.
It's almost as if someone once said,
just in case people like sunshine and water,
we'd better make Florida.
And we'd better make miles of beautiful beaches
and places like St. Augustine
and Key West,
just in case people want to go.
There are over 4 million miles of roads
in Alamo territory,
all across America.
And nationwide, only Alamo
gives you all those miles for free.
Including the ones that run through a state
that's named after sunshine.
Knowing how to read and write
can really make you feel wanted.
Trying so hard.
Help someone learn to read.
Volunteer as a tutor in your community.
Tuesday.
Hi.
I've missed you.
You're married.
It's a second chance for love.
What are we doing? We can't do this.
I wish that you didn't have to go.
I'm in love with you.
30-something, Tuesday.
The day may come when every free-standing range
will have a smooth, sealed-in surface
that's easy to clean
and heats up this fast.
But Whirlpool has it.
Today.
Hey, Mike, I really like this white Sinfandel.
Well, good, good. Now put it down.
I'm going to try another one.
He loves to do this.
This one's great. Yeah, I like it better.
Why?
Can't it just taste better, isn't that allowed?
Did you know Gallimano White Sinfandel?
No, it's terrific, isn't it?
Am I going to get any credit for this?
I didn't even make the wine.
This is synonymous.
Last year, I shopped at Alpha Beta,
and now that it's switched over to Lucky's,
I find a significant reduction
in my weekly grocery bill.
It's important that I have quality
and affordable prices,
and I find that I get both of that
when I shop at Lucky's.
Alpha Beta is now Lucky.
We think you'll like the change.
All right.
Open 24 hours a day.
I want a 10-minute breakfast,
but you don't need a clock to time it.
You don't need a clock. The waitress has a stopwatch.
If her watch is stopped, how will I know when 10 minutes are up?
Because if breakfast takes longer than 10 minutes,
it's free.
I get a broken watch for free.
I'm talking about breakfast.
And you've rambled on long enough, it's time to go eat at Lenny's.
What?
10 minutes?
Now you can have your breakfast or lunch
served in 10 minutes, or it's free.
Did they lose like $100 million in revenue
for the two quarters they did this promotion?
10 minutes?
What the fuck?
That's so fast.
It's
where individuals become
a family. It's where they share
memories. 10 minutes? I can't
believe that.
It's where parents get to know their children
and their children's children.
This will always be an important part of people's
lives. That's why home loans
are such a secure investment.
And that's where Home Savings of America
has put its depositors' money for more than
100 years.
Juice!
Quiet, please.
Hold on.
When allergies come on
this strong, Benadryl
comes on stronger.
Time!
Sorry, sorry. My nose won't
stop running. When allergies
come on this strong, Benadryl
comes on stronger.
A change is coming.
It's understood.
Happening all over my neighborhood.
Only it's got the taste
for me. Gonna change the
Pizza Hut delivery.
Call Pizza Hut delivery now for the
double cheeseburger pizza. Get one
medium for $8.99 a second for just
four bucks more. Or make it deluxe
with bacon and onions for just one more
buck. Gonna change the Pizza Hut
delivery. Yeah, hold on.
Pizza Hut delivery, making it great.
What is?
I'm still on the Denny's thing.
What if you
after the big baseball game,
like a little league baseball game
you go into
Denny's with like 40 people.
Is that every single person?
How would
it just gonna be free?
Hey guys, we're gonna take the entire
baseball team and the other team
and we're gonna go to Denny's and it's probably
just gonna be free. That's kinda crazy.
How would they do that?
It's here. Trying is believing week.
And here's how people who are trying breakfast
with Grape Nuts feel. You've gotta try
it. I did and I feel great.
It's a great
natural energy source and it's fat
free. You won't believe how good you
feel. I do.
I feel great. Grape Nuts
cereal is full of complex carbohydrates.
You won't believe how it helps keep you going
all morning. Look for this display in your
store. Post Grape Nuts trying is
Be careful you don't knock the fucking thing over
because it's literally a house of hearts.
I haven't had Grape Nuts in a long time.
I remember them being really good
but I feel like the fake memory.
I think we saw.
Did we see that one?
Where they were like fucking flies
all over the place.
I think we saw. Did we see that one?
Where they were like fucking flies
all over the place.
What was it?
I don't know. I feel like I've seen that one.
That would be so fucked up.
Does he think that they're bugs?
It's a bunch of flies.
That's so ridiculous.
That's classic comedy right there.
So they're the same.
Don't you get it?
Ritz or Ritz Bits. Two sizes fits all.
They're all laughing.
No car.
Oh, it's actually for a...
Oh, this is a long one.
This is a long one.
This is a good one though.
Stop having fun.
Call this number.
And we'll give you an incentive to find out.
A certificate worth $10
toward a consultation visit with your doctor.
Call 1-800-556-4800.
I gotta pee. Let me pause it.
I've been drinking water. I'll be right back.
We'll pick this back up in a sec.
Actually, I just got sent a link
saying that you should watch this one
which is kind of interesting.
I haven't seen this one yet.
Interestingly enough.
Okay, well, let's watch it.
Oh, no way.
Then I summon...
Meowty!
The two-player starter kit contains
everything you need and more
to get right into the action.
Master the arts of grottos, beasts, and wishes.
With 200 different cards,
you must choose your challenger wisely.
Hey, mister.
Will you stop doing that?
Uh, oh.
You can even call upon my power.
So craft the strongest deck you can.
Grotto beasts, available now.
Starter kit and booster pack sold separately.
Order while supplies last.
Well, that was a weird one.
That was an interesting one.
You have no idea
how hard it was to shut the fuck up about this.
It was so hard to not talk about this.
Weird. I...
This would show up today, of all times.
Should we watch it again?
I think we watch it again.
Let's watch it again.
The two-player starter kit contains
everything you need and more
to get right into the action.
Master the arts of grottos,
beasts, and wishes.
With 200 different cards,
you must choose your challenger wisely.
Hey, mister.
Will you stop doing that?
Uh, oh.
The two-player starter kit contains
everything you need and more
to get right into the action.
Master the arts of grottos, beasts, and wishes.
You can even call upon my power.
So craft the strongest deck you can.
Grotto beasts, available now.
Starter kit and booster pack sold separately.
Order while supplies last.
Alright.
Let's talk about it for a second.
A lot of people worked on this.
We have credits
that I want to put up.
That was Studio
Yada that did the animation work.
And they did an unbelievably
phenomenal job.
Absolutely beautiful.
And then the live action
portion was
produced by Indie Film Factory,
which is a local group of Vegas
filmmakers. So it was
a long process
to get this out here, but this was
part of the reason to do the project anyways.
They're going to have this
90s parody
kind of world. And hopefully
this commercial
took a lot of work.
Hope you enjoyed it. Long process.
But yeah, let me show this
real quick. I want to make sure that the people
that did spend a bunch of time on this
get some recognition for it because
it was phenomenal. Let me put it on screen.
Let me just get it.
Hopefully it fits. There's a lot of names on this list.
All very important.
The video will be public
on the Grotto Beasts YouTube channel.
I'm so happy. I'm so glad
to actually show that. And yeah, Grotto Beasts
is out.
It's available. I want to make
sure I give a meaningful update to
that. We had a couple
of small shipping issues.
But they're actively being investigated.
And a lot of people have gotten their orders.
We've seen a ton of people that have opened cards.
And we're
so happy that people actually like it.
That was a huge
amount of stress over the last
six plus months is making sure like
fuck, I hope people like it. I really do.
But a lot of people have been getting their orders.
Seems like people think it's fun.
And interesting. Which
that is a huge weight off of everybody's
shoulders. Because it was like, fuck, hopefully people actually like
this. And no, the cards are not
edible. Oh, let me see.
Alright, let me get this shown. Here
are the credits. Lots
of work went into it.
Here you go. Huge thank you to every
single person on this list. From the people at
Indie Film Factory to obviously
Holly to Studio Yotta. All the
people that came together to make what you just
watched actually watchable.
We're thinking of maybe
putting up a clean version
that doesn't have kind of the crust on it.
There it is.
There will be a no crust clean version
uploaded. Obviously for this stream
I wanted to, you know, we wanted to
make sure it was like 90s and
80s kind of aesthetic.
Bugleberry as himself.
Crust is great. Oh yeah.
Tomar, oh yeah. They were awesome
to work with too. It's a swell group
over there. Yeah, both versions will be
uploaded. The Grotto Beast YouTube will upload
both of them. But now,
now I actually am going to take a
BRB. Because I want to get some water
and we'll put the other ads back up.
BRB, I'll see you guys in a minute.
I keep forgetting to play the BRB music.
I have it. I just keep forgetting to press the button.
Oh, sorry I scared you. But um,
yeah, let's go back to watch
more 80s and 90s ads.
You just saw one.
Remember next time.
Yeah, it's, we could probably get a like
grottobeasts.net if you have
no idea what we're even talking about.
Sort of a parody 90s
card game that is
essentially being treated as streamer merch.
It's got a game built on top of it.
It's available now. Why didn't you
turn into a car during the commercial?
Alright.
Let's, this
compilation was pretty good. We'll stay on this one
for a little bit. Asking the real questions.
Yeah. Okay. You ready?
Does old Old Spice
smell the same as new Old Spice?
By the way.
I feel like it probably does.
What?
I would get out of that
car. I would get out.
I would get out.
Hold on.
This lady is facing this way?
How?
What seat is this lady
sitting in over here on the left, on the right?
Wait. I'm so confused.
Aren't you glad you used dials?
To the airport. Let's go.
Don't you wish everybody did?
She's standing?
I'm confused.
There's not enough room to do that.
Look at this thing. It's a magazine.
TDC magazine.
I open it up and there's this
grid, which is great because I can see the whole
week at a glance. So I just circle
the shows I want to see. Alright.
And look at this. It's a complete description
of every single show. And check this
out. These photographs.
Gorgeous. There's even articles
by famous authors. Amazing.
All I expected was a program
guide and I get all this? What a bargain.
I wonder if there will ever be a
swimsuit issue.
This is the kind of thing that
dad leaves a voicemail
for you about. I've got this
magazine. I'm telling you. You're going to love it.
It's got all this educational stuff. You can circle your
television shows. Call me back
when you get a chance.
TDC magazine and receive 12 monthly
issues for only $14.95.
That's more than 50% off the cover
price. Or tell the operator to bill you
later. Visa and MasterCard accepted.
Is it Peter Griffin?
Get all this?
My famous authors.
Amazing. All I expected was a program
guide and I get all this? What a
bargain.
I wonder if there will ever be a
swimsuit issue. Call now.
That's a stretch.
12 monthly issues for only $14.95.
That's more than 50%
off the cover price. Or tell the operator
to bill you later. Visa and MasterCard
accepted.
There's never one food that gives you
what you need. It's the combination
and the balance. And how you balance the
combinations. So at McDonald's, there's
lots to choose from. Lean burgers
to low fat shakes and frozen yogurt.
Salads. No fat, no cholesterol.
Apple brand muffins. I got
muffins at McDonald's? When? Chicken, potatoes,
and fish. We've got a long list of good
foods to choose from. All
you've got to do is just choose the food.
When were they muffins? That sounds amazing.
Always good food. Always good value.
At McDonald's.
It can be downright frustrating
and difficult to get
perfect orange juice. One with
that pure fresh squeeze taste.
They did this on that Guy Fieri
game show. But if you remember
juice comes closer to this.
This. Tropicana
Pure Premium. We think you'll
find everything will just fall
into place.
Tropicana Pure
Premium. He missed almost all of them so he's not going to
get the $10,000 or whatever it was.
Responsible.
Just because the other guy is
on the road doesn't mean his mind
is. So the superb traction
of the Subaru Legacy with four
wheel drive and anti-lock brakes
can be quite a comfort. Since
the next guy is capable of almost
anything. Shouldn't the same be true
of your next car?
So the superb
traction of the Subaru Legacy with four wheel drive
and anti-lock brakes
can be quite a comfort.
My god dude.
He's wearing these like
blackout shades and
no audio. He just got
to know what he's doing.
And by the way
what a scary stunt
person. This stuntman.
I would be shitting my pants.
Look at how close the car comes.
It doesn't even flinch.
The four wheel drive and anti-lock brakes can be
quite a comfort. Since the next guy
is capable of almost anything.
Shouldn't the same be true of your next car?
Factory to dealer cash could mean
great savings to you during the Subaru
Spring Value Days.
Three hours, nine minutes. May I ask
what you're doing? Timing tiny time
pills. Excuse me? Well this morning when I woke up I
talked like this and that. So I took
a contact. So well contact
has 600 tiny time pills that last 12 hours.
Up to three times longer than ordinary cold
medicine. There's a whole day's
work in every contact.
Eight hours and 30 seconds.
Look if you're going to time the tiny time
pills all day when are you going to do the work?
Right. You time.
There's a whole day's
work in every contact. What did he close?
You're going to time the
tiny time pills all day when are you going to do the work?
Right.
You time.
There's a whole day's work in every contact.
Coming to ABC. I saw his hand up in the, both hands
in the air. No way. Two years
tops. Three. Two and a half. Three or no deal.
Done. He put both his hands up and then
he closed the drawer. Was that his stomach?
You said you took on the cases
nobody else wanted.
Witnesses. Fail
tonight. Oh your honor. Got a big problem here.
Treat Williams. You mean you
are a real lawyer? Surprise.
Eddie Dodd. Premiering this week on ABC
TV. Oh that'll fix the case.
Down here. We got a problem
here.
Yeah.
The sentence is final by the way.
Lifetime. No wonder many of us seem
to always. Pacific Bell calling card.
You can easily charge
calls. Wherever you are.
Just down the street.
Or somewhere up the coast.
But unlike most calling cards
Pacific Bell
is based on your own familiar phone
number. And since it's welcome
at most every phone
it's really the only calling card you need
to hang on to. Pacific
Bell. We're making things easier.
Everywhere.
Fifty years.
McDonald's explodes another myth.
If it's low fat it can't be delicious.
Not so.
Introducing McLean Deluxe. Made with a
91% fat free beef patty.
Low fat and delicious. There's no way that tastes good.
Can't be done. Can't be done. Can too.
You wanted great burger taste with a lot less
fat. Only McDonald's responded.
New McLean Deluxe will blow you away.
It's terrific. It can't
be low fat. It can't be. It's both.
New McLean Deluxe after billions
and billions. Another first at McDonald's
today. That went on the
menu and off the menu in three weeks.
Make me touch me.
Touch me of you. Wait what's
happening? Wait.
What? Oh.
For skin salt is the day you were
born.
Now it's gonna be
Are you gonna give
your love to me?
They turned her into
oil.
Meet the Kodak Colorkin toys.
Get them free by mail when you buy these
Kodak products. See this displayed
for colors you can love.
I love the real not fade away.
Big
odors lurk in small places.
Big odors linger in small places.
A huge door.
Wait why is the toilet so big?
A new decorative design and a great new scent.
The toilet was huge.
My friend Carol is so
different from me. She does lunchables
all at once.
But I do it one by one. Wait what the
fuck? What are you doing?
Oh hold on.
What are you doing?
My friend Carol
is so different from me.
She's just like
I'm confused what's happening here.
She does lunchables all at once.
But I do it one by one.
We're total opposites.
But we've been best friends forever.
Oscar Meyer lunchables lunch combinations.
Lunchables?
Did they start to market them to adults?
I don't remember that.
It can't be delicious.
Not so. Introducing McLean Deluxe.
Made with a 91%
fat free beef patty.
Low fat and delicious? Can't be done.
And two. You wanted great burger
taste with a lot less fat.
Only McDonald's responded. New McLean
Deluxe will blow you away.
It's terrific. It can't be low fat.
It's both. New McLean
Deluxe after billions and billions.
Another first at McDonald's today.
Oh. Wait they're gonna
I thought they were gonna
snap this lady back.
Alright we're getting repeats.
We're getting repeats.
I thought they were gonna snap
her back.
Oh. Repeats.
Mother Goose?
Playful pictures too.
Eleven designs in every package.
Now Sam and Samantha are
full of glee in new story time.
Lotus lately absent for your tea.
Here it comes.
No.
I skipped right into a sneeze.
Here it comes.
Allergies come on this strong.
Were they gonna kick her out? Stronger.
This. Okay.
Okay.
Cheezer, cheezer, cheezer. Not one
but two pizzas loaded with cheese and
up to five toppings for $8.98.
Cheezer, cheezer. Okay.
Bravely Fred has faced one too many healthy
but boring breakfast. Enough.
I want taste indulgence.
Kellogg's Frosted Mini Wheats.
Oh Fred.
Naughty Frosted.
Ready. Kellogg's Frosted Mini Wheats
are good for you. There's fiber.
No. And no salt.
But they taste so good.
And they're fat free. See? Fat free?
Kellogg's Frosted Mini Wheats. Sinner.
Surprise. They're good for you.
You see it your way. Sinner.
I see it mine.
We're all going to Italy. Tuesday when Tony
inherits a vineyard. Greetings fellow
villagers. He's welcomed with
fresh fruit. Who's the boss?
And at a special time. What?
That's a chemistry set. Every
boy should have one. No you shouldn't
have done that Ed. We could just turn on the gas
and blow ourselves up. An hour of
Rosanne. Ed. I flew here this morning
from Colombia. A dope smuggler
swallows his stage. If somebody dies
it's not your fault is it? No. Not totally.
What percentage would you say?
Stand. Tuesday.
What?
What? What?
No. I don't
want to see this person get snapped out of existence
again. Wait. It's a different
person?
It's a different person.
I just like choked on my spit.
That was rude.
That was sick. I'm telling you
I see somebody do
this. I'm going to be like
nice job.
Nice job. I was just waiting
for that guy to do the stomach thing.
Lucky. Your mother will make a
ride of golden twirls to go with them.
True. Golden twirls are very
delicious and so much fun.
I wonder how they grow these.
True.
The average driver puts 12 to 13,000 miles
a year on a car. At Saturn
we knew this.
Where and how though is anyone's guess.
For sure we knew people
would be taking the new Saturn places.
And using it in ways
you'd never figure.
Or even imagine.
So we tested it.
We ran it six million miles.
Six million?
Like a hundred thousand miles
on a car considered to be
getting kind of up there.
Six million?
Unpleasant as it might be
it was time to break a heart.
Would you go with me?
Depends on the car.
It's a growing pains European holiday
and Mike's getting a head start.
Party! Party!
It's a tale of two vacations.
Happy anniversary.
I'm stranded in Spain with a crazy woman.
Catch all the fun Wednesday.
What?
Critics are saying McDonald's
new McLean Deluxe is revolutionary.
That's because it's made with the leanest
beef patty in the business.
91% fat free.
They're calling it phenomenal.
That's because it tastes fantastic.
The public demanded McDonald's responded
with less fat. But don't fill up on the press.
Taste for yourself.
One bite and you'll be talking about it too.
The swallow first. New McLean Deluxe
after billions and billions.
Another first at McDonald's today.
What did that taste like?
Bradley decided to express his artistic
talent on the living room wall.
Glitten will cover it in one coat.
They're so cute at that age.
That's so much of one brand of paint.
Of one color of paint.
Are you sure you have everything?
Hmm. I got the
Fujifilm while you were in cosmetics.
I didn't forget. Oh.
You forgot you married the perfect husband.
You were right, Dad. Kmart's pretty cool.
You should listen to me more often.
Wait. Hold on.
Oh, it's not for the paint.
It's individual candid conversations
caught on camera.
Bradley decided to express his
artistic talent on the living room wall.
This kind of looks like
mac and cheese containers.
That's a real brand?
Glitten will cover it in one coat. Boom Mike?
Hold on. No, no, no. Where?
Oh, shit. Where were we?
Turn on the gas and blow ourselves up.
Where was it?
Artistic talent
on the living room wall.
There it is. Boom Mike?
New McLean Deluxe
after billions and billions.
Another first at McDonald's today.
Bradley decided to express his
artistic talent on the living room wall.
Glitten will cover it in one coat.
They're so cute at that age.
You can't get mad at them. What a bet.
Are you sure you have everything?
Yeah, it's right there.
Turn around.
It's right there.
I didn't forget. Oh.
You forgot you married the perfect husband.
You were right, Dad. Kmart's pretty cool.
You should listen to me more often.
Now, it would be so much
if another group came by and were like
Oh, so cereal tonight?
Of course, son.
Yeah, sure.
Oh, you're filming? Oh, they're filming us.
I feel like that felt
I don't know.
I just think it's funny.
Kmart's pretty cool. You should listen to me more often.
Of all pine cleaners,
more people choose Pinesaw.
Pinesaw's got more active ingredients
than the next leading brand. Does that mean it's better though?
There's more stuff in here.
It even kills staph germs.
It's not really clean until
it's pine solved.
Friday on Full House, Joey and Jesse
get close to nature.
If they get sprayed, I'll laugh.
Are they going to get sprayed?
It's time for our boy to become a man.
Your mother sent out 150 invitations
and we got 10 tons of potato salad
downstairs. Rejoice!
Robbie comes of age on his howling
day and all new dinosaurs
come to Full House Friday.
...to the Indianapolis 500.
Thrilled of living some of the biggest names in auto racing today.
Feel the rush of driving at speeds
of over 200 miles an hour.
Tribulations of top contenders careening toward their
place in racing history. Many attempts,
only 33 will qualify.
Be there as Channel 7's Dan Lovett gives you
a driver's eye view of the Indy 500
from the local racers who make it great.
The Indy 500, the Bay Area Connection
tonight, tonight, tonight on Channel 7 News at 11.
My goodness.
Royal Caribbean's three and four night
buses from Los Angeles to Mexico.
The grand resorts that offer so much
for so little. So why wait?
This session has the same energy as watching TV
with your boomer uncle.
Welcome. Is this your kid?
And is he drinking the only juice drink
with a full day's vitamin C?
Four other vitamins and all natural flavors?
Well, maybe this isn't your kid.
But this should be his juice drink.
Tang Fruit Box Nutrition
in disguise.
Don't care about movie stars who live
in Hollywood.
Don't like their attitude. What they could taste
I know I taste good.
The best things always seem misunderstood.
Just give me what the doctor wants.
Dr. Pepper has been
pretty consistent flavor-wise.
They could have
probably pivoted if they wanted to.
I would consider Dr.
Pepper's flavor to be extreme.
You can't just say you're the best.
It's kind of extreme. You have to prove it.
And they probably could have pivoted.
That's why century 21
professionals are trained to know
their business better.
Skilled at making everything work together.
Committed to giving you the highest
level of professional service.
The standard of
performance by which all others will
be judged.
Oh, it's like a...
I like wearing white, but not under
my arm. This solid leaves a white
flaky mess. But now, there's
new arid sports scent. Solid protection
that never turns white or messy.
New arid sports scent.
Solid protection without
the white mess.
For fun around here, me and the boys
liked it.
It might be time to change compilations.
We've watched this one for an hour.
This one had some pretty good ones.
We'll get a new compilation.
Let's give it like
a few more.
Damn.
Lost again.
Kiss me once
and kiss me twice
and kiss me once again.
It's been a long
long...
Unlock the magic.
Alright. Okay.
A cool new star.
Snickers ice cream bar.
Rich milk
chocolate, buttery caramel,
and fresh roasted peanuts.
Only a few of these came in a box.
And
my brother used to be so fucking
angry with me. I would eat
three of them at least. I think only three or four of them
came in a box. And I would
eat three of them in a row.
And he would open the box and he would scream
at me. He'd be like
STOP EATING ALL
THE SNICKERS ICE CREAM BARS!
And I would just be like, I didn't.
I didn't. It's like, what are you talking about?
Like, there's literally four in the box.
We know who's eating them.
You've told this story before? Oh yeah.
It would happen every time. And that was a treat.
If there were Snickers ice cream bars
in that freezer, I would just eat
I would eat them until they were gone.
And I would only think about
how bad I was being after.
You know what I mean? I would eat
two or three in a row.
And I'd be like, that was bad.
And then my brother would just be pissed.
Does he still do this, Holly?
Um, yeah.
I don't mean to. I just like
love food.
I love orange juice. And
we'll get orange juice. It's like
alright, orange juice. Just to make
sure this is completely clear.
This is only going to be in the fridge
for like maybe two days. It's all
going to be gone. All of it. I'll drink
the whole thing in like a few days.
It's bad.
Orange juice is like one of my favorite things
in the world. And if it's available
to me, it will be gone. The apple juice
incident? Oh, okay.
So...
So, okay.
I like kefir.
It's kind of a yogurt. It's like a yogurt
champagne. And
I keep telling her,
oh, you should really drink kefir. It's got like
probiotics. It's really kind of good for you.
She didn't have an opportunity. I drink the whole thing
before she gets a sip. And I keep saying,
why don't you drink some more kefir? Why don't you have some kefir? It's good.
And then she'd be like, hey, where's the kefir?
And I'll go, oh, it's all gone. I drank all of it.
So,
I just, if there's
orange juice, kefir,
or Snickers ice cream bars
in that fridge,
why is my voice doing that?
Yeah, I got a special apple juice
specifically because
it's the, what's the brand?
It's that brand that's super,
everybody loves it. It's super delicious.
It's an apple juice brand.
What is it? What is it? What is it? Yes,
it's Martinelli's. So, Martinelli's
makes this delicious apple juice.
And I bought one specifically
for her. It was a surprise.
I was like, hey, look what I got
for you. It's Martinelli's
apple juice. We love this stuff.
But I want to make sure the record is correct.
Yes, so
I bought this for her because
I wanted to surprise her with lunch.
And I drank it before
I want to make sure I get the record straight.
I drank it before she could drink it.
Even though I specifically was like a surprise
for her.
I remember looking at the bottle
and I was like,
oh, shit, because I drank it.
And I was like, no, no, I have to
replace this. I have to replace this.
She found the empty bottle in like the recycling
or something, right? And I
was like, I'm so sorry.
It was supposed to be a surprise, but I just was too
delicious. It was truly,
truly a moment. But I replaced it.
And I make sure now that I get
double. This is, alright,
this has only happened like
twice ever.
Okay? She said it was so
funny. No, twice
as in, you don't put Snickers
ice cream bars in the freezer because
I'll eat them all. And orange
juice. You were so
sad. I really was. I was just like,
I can't, I gotta be better
than this. I gotta, you're better than this.
Just the way you like it. So have it
your way with the coolest
new star, Snickers
ice cream bar at Burger King.
Get one of those bear
fruit boxes that they put on
camping trip. Yeah. And then
set, then set a camera up
at like 3 a.m. pointing
at the fridge. And you'll just get me coming
down with like a bathrobe on, just like
and it's like,
door opening it
like sleepy,
And
it's, don't get it.
What if I smash it?
You're hungry. That's
the grizzly bear. That's the classic grizzly bear
noise. Beat Otto his carrot
treat. Oh yeah we will.
Mini fringe fridge with a
combination lock. Yeah
she'll do, she'll do that. And all the sudden
All of a sudden, a day or two later, she will hear, in the other room, this is the lock
picking lawyer, and here I have a combination lock that is, uh, a little outdated in my
opinion.
I mean, like, how do I get into that thing?
Taste the cold of Diet 7 Up.
It's a few degrees away from the everyday.
Diet 7 Up with NutraSweet.
Break the ice.
That was intense.
50 years of magic will continue in a moment.
Customs officials harassed for reporting possible corruption in the war on drugs.
ABC News investigation on world news tonight with Peter Jennings tomorrow.
When is Disney's 100 year anniversary?
Literally right now.
Tomorrow.
Wait, really?
It's literally today.
It's literally right now.
2037, okay.
I thought he was carrying a television.
I thought he had a CRTV in his hand.
I was like, why is this guy carrying a fucking TV?
We already saw this one.
I want you to close your eyes.
And I want you to imagine this as somebody just sipping coffee.
This is a nice, smooth coffee that they're drinking with the same lighting.
Okay?
Across the USA.
As long as we've been around.
Our passengers are our neighbors.
This country's our hometown.
Oh, the bold flavoring.
You know how hard blood has flowed.
And like hitting, you know, ding.
And they're going, ah.
Serious burger lover.
He's doing a blind taste test of McDonald's new McLean Deluxe Sandwich.
Oh, wait.
And the taste is going boom.
McDonald's is the only one with this 91% fat free lean beef fat.
Wait, hold up.
91% fat free?
No, man.
Straight up.
The taste is kicking.
And there's a serious volume.
The new McLean Deluxe.
100% down.
On taste.
Word up.
If your socks are announcing unexpected new breakthroughs.
That was a weird, that was a weird, what was that explosion?
New breakthroughs.
Introduce your feet to ours.
Burlington socks.
For quality at a price you love.
Why is it such an explosion?
The green C means more sock for the money.
They're the first inhabitants of the moon.
If you want some bon-bons, have some yummy bon-bons.
If you like bon-bons, they're so yummy bon-bons.
Not going to leave them out there.
Wait, hold on.
If your socks are announcing unexpected new breakthroughs.
Like.
It's the first inhabitants of the moon with the dream of a new life.
There's a solar flare heading for them.
But it becomes a fight for survival.
My father's out there.
I'm not going to leave them out there to die.
Incoming flare alert.
Do you copy?
A world premiere movie.
Plymouth.
Sunday.
Next, John Stossel discovers some of the best kept secrets in child care.
Mastering the terrible twos.
Getting your children to sleep.
How to raise a happy child.
Whether you're a parent or not.
It just shows me chugging apple juice.
Special edition of 2020.
Next.
And looking into the camera, concerned.
Once you've tried something like this, you just don't go back.
After Johnson & Johnson created AccuView disposable contact lenses, there was one thing left to do.
If they would give away.
So we did.
It's comfortable.
Just put them in.
Boom, they feel great.
You don't clean them.
Visit your eye care professional for an exam, and if AccuView is right for you, you'll get a free trial pair.
That's all it took for me.
Just to put them on one time.
See your truth shining through.
Truth shining through.
Because the world gets more colorful every day, Kodak introduces a more colorful film.
New Kodak Gold 400 film.
It now has the richest, most saturated color available in high speed film.
Isn't it worth this to get a bag that can take this?
Isn't it worth this for a bag that can take this?
Announcing the new Hefty Steel Sack.
The toughest, most puncture resistant bag Hefty makes.
And only two cents more per bag than the average.
Hefty Hefty Steel Sack.
Two cents more?
Go wild.
Go crazy.
Go Disney.
Go wild.
Go for the Jungle Book.
I'm very much money.
That's not very much money.
Buy it today and get five dollars back with our Nabisco rebate offer.
The Jungle Book.
What was that Cheers collection that was like ten grand to get the whole thing over like
forty years?
Yeah, I know.
What?
It was cheaper.
I saved a few cents.
Mom.
It's not the cheesiest.
What's the difference?
No.
Sam.
Come on pal.
Dinner.
Mom, you never serve anything but Kraft cheese and macaroni.
Right?
I wouldn't dream of it.
Oh.
That's not for dinner tonight.
It's broccoli.
Kraft macaroni and cheese.
And asparagus.
You're going to hate L.A.
I will?
Melissa's got a job on a sitcom.
Do you have a real feel for the show?
Loves the star.
It's a pressure cooker.
It really is.
Loves the writer.
There's something about you.
Hates the business.
Who do you want us to contact?
Excuse me?
Who represents you?
I do.
Thirty-something.
Tuesday.
All across America.
One out of two homes is a Kenmore home.
Here's can be two.
With our large capacity washer and matching Kenmore dryer.
Just $399.87.
$309.87.
Exclusively at Sears and Sears brand central.
I'm trying to think of like a washer and dryer combo now.
It's hot.
And it's only linked to Pizza Hut.
That'll get one new Sausage Lovers pizza for $8.99.
Or a second for just four hours more.
Yeah, that's like at least $8.99.
It's hot.
And it's only linked to Pizza Hut.
Or a second for just four hours more.
Yeah, that's like at least $500, $600, $700 now at least.
It's a deal you can sink your teeth into.
A thousand bucks now?
Yeah.
You're not leaving until you eat breakfast so you might as well do it.
If we've told you once, we've told you a thousand times.
Have you forgotten everything we taught you?
A suggestion for all you grown-ups who think there's no time for a hot breakfast.
Kellogg's Pop-Tarts.
Zero fruit.
You like fruit, don't you?
And open wide.
Kellogg's Pop-Tarts.
The hot breakfast everyone has time for.
You know you like them.
Is this back before there was frosting all over?
I'm Kate Kelly in New Orleans.
Coming up tonight on Nightcast.
The power of voodoo.
There was no frosting on there.
Could it determine the outcome of Sunday Super Bowl?
What is going on?
What was that?
And are the 49ers superstitious?
What was the audio?
What was that?
I went through before the game to try to get myself as nervous as possible.
I'm just going to stay out of the small towns and stay away from the people working the voodoo.
Voodoo at the Super Bowl.
What?
Live coverage from New Orleans continues tonight on Nightcast.
Wait, what?
I'm so confused.
We've been telling you how the four-wheel drive Subaru helps the U.S. ski team get to their events early.
Yet at the 1989 World Championships, the U.S. team was not the first to arrive.
The Norwegians beat us.
The French beat us.
As did the Italians and the Swedes.
How'd they do it?
Dude, everybody in this car is screaming.
Do you understand?
This is not like a fun trip.
If this is me in this car, I am screaming.
At the 1989 World Championships, the U.S. team was not the first to arrive.
Where's the road?
There's no road.
We don't know where we are.
This is, I'm screaming.
The Norwegians beat us.
The French beat us.
As did the Italians and the Swedes.
How'd they do it?
The U.S. team was not the first to arrive.
It wasn't road.
I don't know.
That was kind of scary.
Imagine a Disneyland as big as the city of San Francisco.
A Disney World with a surprise around every corner.
43 square miles of tropical paradise.
The spectacular new Disney MGM Studios theme park.
And the incredible Epcot Center.
Imagine yourself here.
Walt Disney World in Florida.
As big as imagination gets.
Holy shit, Mickey.
Be careful up there, dude.
That was...
Whoa.
You never know where history will unfold.
But you always know where to turn.
Epcot?
I actually...
Epcot is...
That's cool.
But it's CBS News.
Gary's being pushed too far.
If you love me, you must leave me alone.
His worst nightmare is taking shape.
My children are gonna be living under the same roof as a rapist.
His last resort, an act of desperation.
Speak now, or else forever hold your peace.
I'm gonna yell, rapist, rapist.
On Nuts Landing, Thursday.
This is CBS.
It's the biggest party in the history of Disneyland.
It's Disney!
Birthday separation.
What the fuck?
The biggest parade we've ever staged.
Towering four stories over Main Street.
Our biggest giveaway ever.
A new GEO every day.
And over 400,000 other prizes.
What is going on?
What is going on right now?
This is a huge party.
Wait.
I thought they were celebrating 50.
35th anniversary.
Instead of sitting there, you could be sitting here.
In a Mazda MX-6 GT.
Get one now and you'll also get $750 cash back.
It's a better value than Toyota Celica.
The features Celica doesn't have.
And a price that's already less.
So for your MX-6, an additional $750 cash.
This looks kind of nice though, doesn't it?
This seems actually kind of better.
Instead of sitting there, you could be sitting...
What an unbelievably wonderful afternoon.
Oh, I can sit here with my cat.
And enjoy the sun.
Rather than going really fast around tight turns in a car.
In a Mazda MX-6 GT.
Get one now and you'll also get $750 cash back.
It's a better value than Toyota Celica.
The features Celica doesn't have.
And a price that's already less.
So for your MX-6 and an additional $750 cash back.
You know where it's at.
At your Northern California Mazda dealer now.
There are very few guarantees in medicine.
But if you have arthritis pain like I do,
you should know about Mediprin and the Mediprin Guarantee.
If two Mediprin don't relieve...
Oh yes, you can open your eyes now.
...better than two regular aspirin, you get your money back.
Strong promise? Strong medicine.
The medicine that concentrates the power of ibuprofen into these potent little caplets.
The medicine that guarantees better relief than regular aspirin.
Better arthritis pain relief.
That's the Mediprin Guarantee.
They know they want to win.
You know, there's a certain medicine.
It's actually kind of remarkable just how well stuff like Tylenol, acetaminophen, ibuprofen...
It's crazy that you can just take this thing.
And it's very, very safe.
Right?
Like if you...
Obviously if you take this as directed.
We came up with a way to make it so you just tell your brain that this doesn't hurt anymore.
That's kind of unbelievable.
Oh no, no, yeah. Just take this.
You've got like a really bad headache.
Oh, just take this thing and it'll be better.
Soon.
That's kind of remarkable.
Ibuprofen Andy.
What?
Ibuprofen Andy?
Alright.
...begins with what you feed it.
I mix the pedigree with the pedigree mealtime because the dogs enjoy it.
It's the perfect combination.
These are champions. They deserve the best.
Pedigree.
Recommended by top breeders.
Right now, you're just 90 seconds away from Chef Boyardee with Microwave Meals.
Chef Boyardee pasta, hot and tasty.
And with no messy cleanup.
Chef Boyardee Microwave Meals.
You look like enough.
Thank goodness. In just 90 seconds.
This morning, I was following this year's service...
I could probably eat four or five of those.
...and it dawned on me.
I think so.
...Messy Sears trucks all the time.
It also dawned on me that I hardly ever see a service truck from those so-called super stores.
So before you make that next big buying decision, ask yourself what kind of service you'll get five years from now.
Or if they'll even be around to answer the phone.
That's one of the big reasons I feel better when I buy a major appliance or electronics from Sears.
And that's what they mean by your money's worth...
We have the same hair?
...of a whole lot more.
No, we don't. Not even close.
It's not even close.
Not even close.
This looks like something my mom would eat.
It's kind of quiet, conservative.
I don't think I can get into this.
I mean, it's just a bunch of flakes.
Hmm. Doesn't taste the way it looks.
Doubter.
I like the way it crunches.
Maybe it's good because it's simple.
Wait, wait. Don't tell me. I'm just like my mother.
Kellogg's cornflakes.
Why would you do that when you can follow your nose...
...to the delicious sugary Fruit Loot?
I hope you'll be with us tonight. Dan Miller will be live from New Orleans Decisive Super Bowl, bringing you updates on goodness knows what, along with actress Karen Black and much more. See you later tonight.
...a special edition of 48 Hours Thursday.
Sammy Davis Jr.'s 60th Anniversary Celebration.
Brought to you by...
Dr. Pepper and your local Dr. Pepper Company.
Dr. Pepper is just what the doctor ordered.
The good-time, great taste of McDonald's.
AT&T. The right choice.
And...
The Chrysler Corporation and the Chrysler Motors Black Dealers Association.
Bump the start button.
What do you like about your Eagle Premier?
Everything.
You mean the leather interior and the roominess?
I said everything.
So what's Premier got that other cars in his class don't have?
Turbo Teen.
Me.
I will never see a standard red car the same ever again.
You got it.
The Taurus and the Cressida?
Then you tried the Eagle Premier?
You got it.
What'd you think?
I got it.
Business back.
Now AT&T can set you free.
With the first cordless phone specifically designed for business.
The Multi-Line Merlin Cordless.
This guy's on fucking rugs.
So you don't have to lose any quality to gain your freedom.
Set your business free.
Call 1-800-MERLIN-AT&T.
I don't think it's fair to give only one of your workers the Super Mario Mushroom.
You understand?
Oh, it was Dr. Pepper.
This is who bad strolls.
Austrian downhill racer and Olympic gold medalist.
He's not afraid of extreme vertical drops.
He's not afraid of speeds over 90 miles an hour.
He's not afraid of anything except going slow.
But if you think he's tough...
Yeah, he is afraid, isn't he?
Isn't that scary?
Wait, hold on.
Isn't that like scary?
It's like he's not afraid.
This is who bad strolls.
Austrian racer and Olympic gold medalist.
He's not afraid of extreme vertical drops.
No, no, no.
That was a battle cry.
That was a war.
Okay.
I'm just...
Yeah.
All right.
We're good.
Except going slow.
But if you think he's tough, wait until you see the guys at the ticket window at the Olympics
if you don't have your Visa card because the Olympics don't take American Express.
It's everywhere you want to be.
Yeah, that was a battle cry.
Really?
You will laugh all night long.
It was your kind of thing.
You made me laugh.
It was so embarrassing.
I haven't seen him in years.
It was great.
He still cracks me up.
I'll tell you one more time because I think I like that.
I just did that.
We just did that.
Yeah.
No one helps you share the feelings like AT&T long distance.
I wish I could have been here too.
Who's that calling?
Who's this on the phone?
To reach out.
All right.
That was cute.
That was nice.
I guess.
I don't know.
But when you've got the style of Hanes socks, who wants to run around and...
Boo!
I hope he blows the socks.
Like to try total?
Mom says grape nuts.
Hope you're hungry.
He takes four bowls of grape nuts to get the vitamins in one bowl of total.
Total has 100% of a day's supply of 12 vitamins and minerals.
What the fuck?
You tell her.
Total, one bowl, 100%.
So total hates grape nuts.
Total is then the enemy of...
What was the other one?
They all hate each other.
They're all in the circle of just hating each other.
What was the first one?
They don't talk shit to each other.
Okay, so Jess Wright hates total.
Total hates grape nuts.
Who does grape nuts hate?
Are we going to get a grape nuts versus like frosted flakes?
And are there any, you know...
I'm addressing you now, the person that talked shit.
They all hate each other.
Red Lobster announces great new trios.
Six delicious trios you're going to love.
Terrific.
Like our large lobster alfredo and scallops.
Love it.
Or our crab legs, juicy scallops, and shrimp.
Let's go.
But hurry.
Try the trio with the unbeatable price.
Oh, 6.99.
6.99.
That's incredible.
On one life to live, the start of a love affair.
This is going to be a good trip.
Or the beginning of the end.
Oh.
It's an attraction that could be fatal.
You'll be perfectly safe in the boat.
Trust me.
You'll never forget the incident at Loom Lake on one life to live.
What?
Ford trucks.
A lot of what going on.
The first vehicle Henry Ford sold was not a car.
It was a truck.
Our full size pickups were first with rear anti-lock brakes.
First with electronic overdrive transmission.
First with push button four wheel drive.
Now what does all this get you?
It gets you number one.
And if you keep doing it, you stay number one.
More people are driving the best built, best selling American trucks than ever before.
One.
One just ain't no fun.
A trip is better than a one.
Sex.
It's two bits in one.
Freshens breath and tastes great.
Oh, I remember these things.
I actually remember these things.
These things were so intense.
They were kind of grainy and they were super powerful.
I remember those things.
Those things are crazy.
New Caledrill Clear not only works better to stop the itch, it dries this clear.
So nobody will ever spot you.
New Caledrill Clear.
One man unwilling to forgive.
You break the law, don't come running back to me.
The other unable to forget.
I swore an oath to my country.
Not to what was going on over there.
Charlton Heston.
Peter Strauss.
Proud Men.
Saturday.
I said I was going to do a different one after this.
I mean, we're almost at, we're literally at the end.
We've got to, we've got to.
Can life come from lava tomorrow on Good Morning America?
How a lava field blossoms into one of nature's miracles.
Then meet B.I. Warshawski. Kathleen Turner turns private eye in her new role.
Plus Irma Baum back here on Good Morning America tomorrow.
Lava.
You know, the Channel 7 newsroom is not unlike the community.
Was Richard Lewis in this much of the spotlight back in the late 80s?
Oh yeah.
Everyone comes from different backgrounds.
Richard Lewis was a superstar.
He was everywhere.
Everyone has their own ideas in the newsroom about how they think the day should go.
We tend to have loud laughs and loud debates.
I think the newsroom is a microcosm of the community.
We're really a cross section of the Bay Area.
In a form of life, Sandy can be seen walking in the park,
wearing sterile pants and stretched denim.
A deep purple waterproof parka,
with an arctic fleece liner.
A-line.
And climb.
Climb what?
The dog in a past life war.
The woman who lives on Mission Hill is talking to her brother Peter.
What was that?
Remarkably, this call costs 25% less than last month.
Because Peter is in Jody's bonus zone.
And Jody just got call bonus from Pacific Bay.
Bonus zone?
Wherever you live in California, call us.
We'll check and see if call bonus can save you money too.
Call 1-800-PACK-BELL.
We're making things easier.
So it was less money if you called somebody close to your house.
Another wimpy sandwich.
Not me.
I've got vintage farm's deli loaf.
It's got real sliced meat chunks.
Still going.
Nothing outlasts the energizer.
They keep going and going and go.
A better way to catch your Zs...
I like this one.
This is a good one. I like this one a lot.
...designed to conform to your shape.
Distribute your weight evenly.
Feels like this a lot sometimes.
Really posthopedic, has it?
So for a better night's sleep, better sleep on a ceiling.
That's a good one.
Someone finally made oatmeal the way I like it.
He doesn't like oatmeal.
Oatmeal crisp is big, crispy flakes with oatmeal.
And it's not grapefruit.
Lots of crunchy almonds.
That shit's gross.
Don't you lie to your mother.
Look, ma, I'm eating my oatmeal.
Look, ma!
Crisp oatmeal raisin crisp.
Look, ma, I found something for nothing.
Pop secret popcorn.
Free and specially marked boxes of oatmeal crisp
and oatmeal raisin crisp.
Be sure and write them a nice thank you note.
Oatmeal flakes with oatmeal.
Where is mom?
Someone finally made oatmeal the way I like it.
He doesn't like oatmeal.
Where is she?
And why is it so scary and dark and terrifying where she is?
Why is mom a detective?
Oatmeal crisp is big, crispy flakes with oatmeal.
Little brown sugar, lots of crunchy almonds.
Don't you lie to your mother.
Look, ma, I'm eating my oatmeal.
It kind of sounded like Pee Wee Herman.
I'm imagining like a ha!
Like right after that.
Crunchy almonds.
Don't you lie to your mother.
Look, ma, I'm eating my oatmeal.
Look, ma!
Crisp oatmeal raisin crisp.
Look, ma, I found something for nothing.
Pop secret popcorn.
Free and specially marked boxes of oatmeal crisp
and oatmeal raisin crisp.
They all keep going.
Be sure and write them a nice thank you note.
Now there's a new reason to put down those fizzy diet colas.
It's crystal light in a new shade.
Pink grapefruit.
Crystal light.
Light and luscious with no carbonation.
Okay, sit down.
Bring side seats.
250 bucks.
This is gonna be great.
These days a good value is hard to come by.
Unless you come by KFC for the amazing
double bucket deal.
That was a good one.
And the second's just four bucks.
Repeat, four bucks.
The double bucket deal.
Only from KFC.
That's sad.
He was Rock's first and only king.
He had the fame, the cash, the women.
And he had the pills, the pain.
One woman saw it all.
Lived it all.
This is her remarkable story.
Priscilla Presley's devastating account
of life and death in the eye of the storm.
Elvis and me.
Sunday.
Here is a group of people who were going along
doing what they do better than they'd ever done it before
and someone came along and pulled the rug out.
It was a struggle for survival.
Peter Jennings reporting from the heart of Harlem, Thursday.
Let's say buenos dias.
To breakfast and tortillas.
Come on, Ramos.
Let's go.
See it's so close.
McDonald's introduces the breakfast burrito.
Scrambled waffles.
Desserts and aprons.
Sausage, onions, and tomatoes.
Don't forget the cheese.
Why did they do this?
$0.99 each.
McDonald's today.
McDonald's did breakfast burritos.
I feel like those probably were really good.
They still actually make them.
They still make them?
Breakfast burrito.
Only $0.99 each.
They still do.
They are really good.
Oh.
All right.
I know what I'm getting next.
My chill out gives us permission to let our hair down.
What is it, chiller?
I don't know.
But what else am I going to do this summer?
It's games, promotions, fun, and free costs.
It's like Woodstock, man.
It's people in tight pants moving fast.
For my family, Tartar Control Aquafresh fights tartar.
What makes you feel this fresh?
Tartar Control Aquafresh helps remove plaque.
Tartar Control Aquafresh fights cavities.
What makes you feel this fresh?
Only Tartar Control Aquafresh is the...
Why are you bringing a toothpaste to a water park?
I'm sorry.
If you have a full tube of toothpaste in the box and you bring that to the water park,
I feel like you're kind of strange.
That's strange.
You never know.
Aquafresh...
What does Aquafresh Riz mean?
Aquafresh Riz?
Tartar Control in tight pants moving fast.
For my family, Tartar Control Aquafresh fights tartar.
What makes you feel this fresh?
Tartar Control Aquafresh helps remove plaque.
Tartar Control Aquafresh fights cavities.
What makes you feel this fresh?
Don't drop it! Don't drop it!
Tartar Control Aquafresh is the fresh way to fight cavities, fight plaque, and fight tartar,
all with one great Aquafresh taste.
Tartar Control Aquafresh!
It fights tartar...
And makes you feel this fresh!
I've got great news for everyone who uses bleach to clean up the kitchen and bath.
New Clorox Cleanup is a bleach specially designed for cleaning.
You see, Clorox added a special cleaner to bleach, so it cleans even better.
Now you can clean up stains, clean up germs, and clean up greasy dirt bleach alone leaves behind.
So, when you reach for a bleach to clean up, reach for the one with the special cleaner inside.
New Clorox Cleanup.
When you want to reach for bleach, just get bleach, right?
What would they add?
Come to AC this fall.
The war is over.
A celebration has begun.
It's better. It's different.
Boys have returned as men.
Bleach is not a good cleaner. It's kind of toxic.
To open arms, to laughter, and to love.
Yeah, but I mean, just in general though, bleach is...
The whole time I was over there, all I thought about was you.
I thought it was like the ultimate in like removal of everything.
These are their stories of triumph.
This is an oppressive record, soldier.
And despair.
They can't pay you less than other men on the line.
They can if I'm a janitor.
Their hope for the future.
Hank has been fighting a war, not dating.
Their dreams left behind.
Americans are wonderful people.
Linda, if you'd made an effort to pretty yourself up,
you wouldn't have lost Mike to some Italian.
They became wartime heroes.
Now they've returned to the home front.
Bro, I can't believe you're an adult.
What? Why?
But America is watching ABC.
Hey, you can't know everything about everything.
China Beach will continue.
I know very little, and I'm telling you that.
You can't know everything. You can't know everything about everything.
Should government require business to guarantee parental leave?
They tried it in Rhode Island on ABC's World News Tonight this week.
This is a Channel 7 News Brief.
San Francisco police tonight are investigating why it happened.
A tour bus careened down a street and slammed into a child care center in San Francisco.
He's so right for that.
The force was so tremendous, the bus smashed through the walls.
No one was in the child care center.
Holy shit.
The driver of the bus was killed.
One county in the Bay Area is looking at a new source of water
What?
Rock stars are telling rock fans about the growing problem of hearing loss.
And what's hot in fashion?
Clothes that change colors all by temperature.
See it on 7 at 11.
What?
Hey, listen to this.
Wait, they showed them.
Wait, what?
A green conditioner as much as a salon brand.
Oh my, oh my god.
I didn't see that.
Holy shit.
Would you switch?
Agree.
It's that good.
Oh, oh fuck.
I was more wondering about sex.
No reason not to have sex.
Sex is definitely in the mind.
Sex.
Call it what you will.
It's still sex.
That's awful.
30 something returns Tuesday.
Get ready to feel softer.
Caress with its silky touch of bath oil.
Leave skin softer than soap can.
Get ready to feel your softest.
It looks so right in the shine tonight.
Before you dress, caress.
All right, we're almost through.
We're almost through this one.
I won't wear anything without cross your heart.
Because great looks start with cross your heart.
With crisscross shaping, I always look better.
The cross your heart bra.
Great looks start with cross your heart.
From Playtex.
The fit that makes the fashion.
Oh, I forgot about the little 7-Up guy.
What happened to the little 7-Up guy?
Hey, thanks, man.
Stay cool.
7-Up.
The cool spot.
I liked that one.
That was cool.
Let me show you how the educated consumer
can tell the difference between my deli meat
and Oscar Mayer deli thin slices.
Now, you can't go by looks or taste.
On the conner, they're both sliced fresh.
Real thin.
But my deli meat comes in this beautiful white paper.
See how nice you can write?
But Oscar Mayer comes in this resealable bag.
Who cares?
This one comes in plastic.
Mine comes in paper.
What a disgusting difference.
Can you believe it when some margarine say buttery taste
and there's no butter in them?
Kraft touch of butter spread has rich, creamy butter in it.
Just a touch.
Kraft touch of butter.
A touch of real butter makes a real difference.
Hi, this is Suzanne Summers.
All this week, I'm hosting the new...
All right, we went, we got through it.
I'm having John Snyder...
That was an hour and 24 minutes we stayed on this one.
...in my old friend Norman Falcon 3's company.
Check out Into the Night.
Huh?
All right, that's it.
My pit rate's probably awful.
Am I a little blurry right now?
I...
Margarine versus butter.
I don't...
I feel like I know what margarine tastes like,
but it's kind of...
It's lost to how butter tastes.
There's a whole day's work in every...
All right, let's do another one.
I should have another one here.
I have a few, actually.
This one...
Oh, this one's old Nickelodeon ads.
I'm curious about this one.
1993.
Let's try this one.
Rugrats!
Glass Geek Supo.
This is unlocking so many memories.
Saturday night has arrived.
And Saturday night belongs to Snick.
That...
Blah, blah, blah.
Here's Benjamin Hall on the Jaguar system to place Cybermorph.
Let's see how those beastly graphics and intricate moves
have only come from 64 bits of mega-power field.
Cybermorph only on Jaguar...
Why?
Why did he puke?
Why did he puke into the lens of the camera?
He just hurled directly into the camera lens.
This one's crusty.
The Muppets is so great.
Go watch all the movies back-to-back.
Ooh, what's this thing?
Super Van City!
Whoa, that thing's way cooler.
And I don't know, something that's cool.
Real power tools.
Is that Dad back there?
Whoa.
Are you supervising back there, Dad?
Dude, you know what I want to watch so bad on-screen if I could?
I wonder if I can.
Do you guys remember Crash Box?
On HBO.
Crash Box was fucking unbelievable.
That's one of the best shows for, like, a young audience.
I'm thinking the same thing.
Yeah, that's exactly the first thing I thought of when I saw that.
Crash Box was so good, man.
I actually took a lot of inspiration from Crash Box.
I was watching that show during my formative years.
Strange and powerful forces are attracting people to Pizza Hut.
It's the Marvel Comics X-Men video.
With a mini comic book, pull-out poster, and trading card.
All for only $4.99 with any pizza purchase.
You're gonna do it.
Yes!
Wrap that up.
Exclusive at Pizza Hut.
Strongest power.
Tamed by success, the turtles lost their savage edge.
Greed is dead.
The new breed carved from the streets.
Concrete fist, batter, alien flesh.
One-on-one.
Wait, is this a...
There was a game.
With rage, ripping through fear.
It's a tear.
I remember this game.
Soft shells, hosts of reality.
It was the fighting game.
This game was awesome.
I gotta play this.
By the Super NES Super Set.
And get five complete Mario games.
Standard.
You'll find the Super Set is like no other...
This is like the equivalent of the Orange Box.
Performance, handling, and mode seven control.
You'll get Super Mario World.
And for $3.50 in postage, Super Mario All-Stars free.
With four Mario games in one.
Mario.
So stop by your Nintendo dealer today.
Your Nintendo.
It's not like a car company.
They're presenting it like a car, too, weirdly enough.
Hey, that's me.
The kid with the cool clothes.
That's my little name.
Cool, too.
That's the joke.
Oh.
Right.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's what I meant.
That was the whole bit.
Yeah.
That was, yeah.
I know.
Cool clothes for cool kids.
At prizes even your mom will like.
Shop and save at Happy Days.
The Disney Channel presents new episodes of one of our most popular series, Avonlea.
These will be very exciting moments.
What is it called?
The Cable Ace award winning series continues to attract a variety of exciting guest stars.
In December, watch for Diana Rigg and Robbie Benson in an episode full of mystery.
I don't remember this.
And suspense.
All will be revealed in two course.
It's a special Avonlea only on the Disney Channel.
It's the most popular show on the network, apparently.
Watching.
Nick!
And back to Clarissa explains it all.
Oh.
I was going to say, I hope you hear the names.
Are you afraid of the dark is up next.
Extra early this week.
Followed by Ren and Stimpy's.
Are you afraid of the dark?
It's such a wild show.
Son of Stimpy.
So sneak right where you are.
Are you afraid of the dark?
They kind of sat around and they made up the stories and then they threw this like weird dust.
Clarissa explains it all.
They used to throw the dust into the fire, right?
At Universal Studios.
Orlando.
And then all of them would sit around and they would just hallucinate.
Whatever the person was talking about.
It was in that dust.
Stay with the program.
Sneaking.
Kellogg's frosted mini wheats?
No, Sid and I.
So grown up.
Oh, he's eating so sensibly.
Well, he knows just how cool this stuff is.
Just check out all that whole grain wheat.
Whole grain wheat.
Very nutritious.
He's definitely.
Can't see this frosted.
I'm going to talk like this when I'm a dad.
Genius.
Should eat.
Kellogg's frosted mini wheats taste so good, who cares about anything else?
Besides, it's part of this complete breakfast.
We know what's absolutely nutritious.
Writing his dissertation on world peace.
Oh, there you go.
All right.
That cinnamon toast crunch.
I see that.
Mrs. Crotty.
She sees everything.
So can you see what gives cinnamon toast crunch its intense taste?
It must be something sneaky.
What?
It's obvious to any kid.
The cinnamon and sugar squelch all over every bite.
It's covered in cinnamon.
For a totally intense taste, you can see.
Cinnamon toast crunch is part of this complete breakfast.
Cinnamon and sugar, huh?
Looks pretty wild.
No wonder kids love it.
Connects.
The these things are off.
I love the way that it sounded when you snapped them together.
They made it.
It was such a great sound.
That was half the fun.
Connects.
The new snap together color coded construction set.
These ones aren't even funny.
They're just cool.
Racing aerodynamics, sleek stabilizer rods and the exclusive two speed power shifter.
You're on more than this bike around.
You're on the fastest.
Bikes were so huge.
Afterburner.
Only from Murray.
Bike brands were actually car companies.
Some play games that go away.
And some play BMW.
Oh, you drive a BMW.
Nintendo's new Honda.
Pinball video game called Kirby's Pinball Land.
And Kirby's the place.
All you do is keep Kirby.
I was so bad at this game.
I hated it as long as you can.
Get Nintendo's new Kirby Spinball Land for Game Boy.
And we'll bet you won't go.
Joy to the world.
I was so bad at it.
I just didn't like it because I was bad at it.
Holidays from the Rugrats and Nickelodeon.
Afraid of the dark?
Stay in the glow of the couch and stay tuned.
The orange couch.
I remember the orange couch.
Tonight's Ren and Stimpy.
A new episode.
Did it ever land on old?
Tonight on stick.
Did I ever tell you guys the idea that I wanted to do?
I wanted to get a shitload of these.
These old weird fucked up 80s and 90s games.
These weird like board games.
And I wanted to get a bunch of streamers.
And do like a competition with them.
Just play them all.
Play like 20 of them.
Over the course of like a couple days.
I think they'd be kind of fun.
Put some weird stakes on it too.
I think it could be kind of fun.
Maybe.
And when I say a bunch of streamers.
I mean like two.
Or like three.
About like 20.
What is this?
This is wearing these weird plague doctor masks.
That's kind of creepy.
Is this the crazy?
You put it together dolls and fashion souls
separately.
I'm, I'm just going to say it.
Barbie stuff.
That was crazy.
That was super super cool.
working electricity and shit in there.
Mario games standard.
You'll find the superset is like no other system of shit
performance, handling, and mode seven control.
You'll get super Mario world.
Yeah, oh no, my Barbie mansion has a working jacuzzi.
Four Mario games in one.
Excuse me?
So stop by your Nintendo.
Oh yeah, wait, wait, wait, wait, you don't have that?
You don't forget to super contend those supersets.
Oh, and the lights can change freedom colors.
It's Batman at his best.
Super charged with power.
The turbo fat plane soars at breakneck speed.
It's Catwoman.
Fearing the killer claw, she leaps to safety.
Look out!
This feline's got her own set of claws.
But Megwing Batman can rise above this cat fight.
He fires.
The evil and figures hold separately.
Batman, the best just got better.
Look for America's favorite hero at this Christmas
in the animated movie, Batman.
See where the inspiration of the Grotto Beast commercial
came from.
Now the sneaking begins again with
Are You Afraid of the Dog?
We watched a lot of these.
Now get ready for Ren and Stimpy's long awaited
snow-filled saga.
Son of Stimpy, the heartwarming, heart-burning,
dead-of-winter tale of Ren and Stimpy and Stinky.
Next on Snick.
That's another job that I think would be so much fun.
Being the voiceover, the narrator in between
television shows, especially for a kid's network,
I feel like it would be so much fun.
Stay tuned for the wild, wacky world of Ren and Stimpy.
Coming up next on Nickelodeon.
I would have loved that job.
That sounds like a lot of fun.
Keep basking in the glow of the big Snick
will continue after these messages.
All right, we'll do like 10 more.
You've got to make a stand.
That's what the X-Men are all about.
Man or mutant, it's all the same.
Heights against evil.
Marvel Comics X-Men.
Jiggleberry's narrations, so.
This thing went so hard.
The old X-Men show.
It's so good.
You're a little quiet.
I think this is a good job.
We already saw this one.
It's a repeat.
I think it's because this thing,
I turned it up loud so you could hear that.
Peaceful land, paradise is threatened
by an unspeakable evil.
And only one person has found the power
to restore perfect order.
In a new action adventure game for your super NES
comes an exciting tale, the secret of mana.
Wow.
Oh, Bat Chest, I know, whatever.
Whatever, go ahead and do it.
Did you eat too much?
Oh yeah.
Oh no.
But it's so much fun to eat and love.
Oh yeah.
You see what I'm saying?
This is just pure content.
First defeat Ralph, all their food wins,
but be careful, cause you never know.
Eat it, Ralph.
Oh yeah.
You know it's so much fun to eat it, Ralph.
Watch out, here he comes.
Eat it, Ralph.
Oh yeah.
What was I gonna say about this?
I was gonna say something, hold on.
What was the last commercial?
Oh, right, so I'm telling you I'm like,
oh what, a Bat Chest, right, the secret of mana.
The secret of mana.
Oh, legendary video game.
One of the best, one of the greatest.
I like kind of pretend that I,
so my experience with the mana series,
especially secret of mana,
was renting this game from the store rental place,
the video game rental,
and opening up somebody else's save file,
I believe is what it was.
Walking around, not understanding what was going on,
and then returning it and never playing it again.
I just had no idea it was happening.
I did that a lot though.
I did that with tons of games,
and it's kind of sad that I met,
I probably was just a little too,
I don't know, like ADHD and young,
kind of at the same time,
where it was just like,
oh, somebody already has a save file.
I don't wanna play that.
I just wanna see, they already did it.
I wanna do it.
And just don't understand what's going on.
I really wish I actually played through some of these,
because I feel like these are like
some of the most incredible old experiences,
and I just skipped all of it,
and just played on somebody else's save file for an hour,
and then it went back to the stores.
Hey Ralph, want my burger and fries?
You still do that.
Dredging up on his bat cycle,
Batman races to the scene, surprising Ridman.
True.
Time's up, turbo jet Batman.
These old Nickelodeon,
what are they called?
Bumps or whatever they're called?
They were so good.
Stimpy and Snick will be back after these messages.
Nice, the Roundhouse takes on the Hulk.
I'm in the-
All right, we're going down to the final three.
Sorry.
What?
Meet Lisa, I invited her for breakfast.
I just heard the shark music.
Be central on Snick.
Hey squirt, meet Lisa, I invited her for breakfast.
Nice.
Can I have another bowl, Billy?
Sure.
She's got my Kellogg's Corn Pops.
Stay calm.
Sorry.
Sorry, you ate all my pops.
Oh, with that taste like sweet popcorn,
and all you can say, Ms. Space Cadet,
with my loser brother for her boyfriend is sorry?
What am I gonna do?
Billy, didn't you have Megan over for her corn pops last week?
Megan Keller, I'm not hungry.
Aw.
Kellogg's Corn Pops is part of this complete breakfast.
I gotta have my pops.
What?
That was an aggressive commercial there.
All right, we already saw the sponsor.
We got two more.
I went to look for the guys on foot that Saturday.
My old bike just didn't cut it anymore.
Nobody anywhere.
I kept hearing this sound.
Moto Blaster?
Brother, the world was shut down.
Sorry, I don't know where they went.
Where was everybody?
Dad pulled in, then I saw him.
This thing's awesome.
I don't remember that.
Here's one time, it doesn't matter who your neighbor is.
Holy shit.
Here's the other.
Life's too short.
Stop the hate.
Announcing the Room Plus Triple Header Holiday Bonus.
First, get special holiday rebates on everything we make.
Instinct pass rebates on our already low factory direct prices.
Then, put only 10% down with no payments,
no interest until next March.
Finally, you can get delivery by Christmas
on everything you buy now.
But this special holiday offer is for a limited time only.
So hurry to Room Plus.
Look at all these things.
Just round the corner.
Watch.
To the glow of the Red Stimpy Show.
All right, last one.
One more.
Now, stretch your vocal cords for the kind of caroling
that could only occur at the Roundhouse,
as Snick takes you to the Roundhouse Holiday Bash.
Next.
Belongs to Snick.
All right, last one.
When Snick brings you a special Doug Christmas.
I'll go to prison.
All right, last one.
Only on Nickelodeon.
Triplets.
Cute.
I love my buss and giggle triplets.
What the fuck?
That was so scary.
That was terrifying.
All right, that one didn't count.
We're gonna cut off.
All right, this one doesn't count.
All right, no, we stopped.
I thought we stopped this one.
All right, here's the last one.
Flexor can do.
The spring-loaded fork handles the tough stuff.
No problem.
And the oversized tubing is made for rugged riding.
Yeah, he knew what my Murray Flexor could do.
But he does now.
Hey, hey, hey, Flexor by Murray.
All right, that was, that was, I like, that was fun.
How do you get the girls to come in?
We're gonna have tons of refreshments.
Basically, this is trying to catch someone's eye, you know.
If you like a girl, you know, you invite her to a party.
Yeah, we're ready.
This could be a lot of fun.
All the popular people are gonna be there.
PJ and Vogue.
Some people just wear, you know, regular clothes,
but since we've talked to them.
Have an awesome birthday party?
Who's Kirby?
What?
Behind the flabby facade, a physical powerhouse.
A street fighter.
A weapons expert.
Kirby was so cute.
Is whatever the situation demands.
Everybody loves Kirby.
In Kirby's adventure,
evil King Diddy stole in Dreamland's dreams.
Now Kirby's fighting to get him back.
Leveled by nightmarish level.
That's Kirby.
He's cute, till you cross him.
Then he's one tough cream puff.
Kirby's Adventure on NES.
All right, I think that's a good one going on.
Flameless, I was only gonna stream
for like three hours or so.
And there's only so many ads I can take in a row.
You walk like Kirby?
Oh, the carrot, that's right.
I forgot about the carrot.
It's time to give Otto a carrot before I leave.
All right, I'll be right back.
If you want to see Otto get a carrot,
you'll have to stay tuned for only another minute.
Okay, he's ready for his carrot.
You want a carrot?
Wait, you're gonna be able to see it.
All right, you want a carrot?
You want this?
Go eat a carrot.
Ready?
Good dog.
Crunchy carrot.
I don't think you can hear the crunching, but he is.
It's pretty loud.
There it is.
Good job, Otto.
He's kind of like, where are you going?
I want another one.
All right, let me let him out.
He's like, he's looking for more.
He's like, where are they?
He's like, there has to be more than one.
All right, I'll be right back.
All righty, this is the only Otto moment of the year.
Well, so far.
All right, everybody, I will see you guys tomorrow.
We're gonna continue and play House Flipper.
There's a big update for it.
Thanks for watching.
Short stream today, but I kind of just wanted to do this.
Wanted to show the Grotto Beast ad
and watch these commercials.
Tomorrow, I'm gonna start probably the normal time,
probably six o'clock Pacific.
That sounds like a plan to me.
Take care of yourselves.
Thanks for watching.
If you are there tomorrow, we'll see you tomorrow.
And then I think mid-week, next week,
I think Ster and I are gonna play some games.
So I probably am only gonna stream,
I wanna say maybe once or twice next week.
I think Holly and I are gonna take a break.
I feel like we've been kind of running around like crazy.
So I think we wanna take a break,
but I'll be live next week.
I'll be live once or twice.
I wasn't streaming for the last four or five straight days,
but we were kind of making sure a lot of things went smoothly,
especially for the Grotto Beast stuff.
And we are still actively working on it.
So that is still actively a project
that is being worked on every day.
But it's gonna be literally,
I'll be live probably Wednesday and maybe on the weekend.
We'll see.
The music, why am I so bad at this?
You know what, it's because I moved it.
I moved the audio.
Hold on, where did I move it to?
Where did I move it to?
It's in a folder here somewhere.
No, where is it?
No.
I'll find it for tomorrow.
I put it in some folder.
But yeah, take care of yourselves.
Have a good night, see you tomorrow.
Thanks for watching.
Call your mother, you know what to do.
That was the fourth auto moment this year, was it really?
Well, maybe one or two, I don't remember.
Ow, my finger.
I just like crunched it.
Sorry about that.
I just thought of the guy's toe coming through the sock
with that sound effect.
All right, see you guys later, take care.
See you tomorrow.