Hello, how are you? Good afternoon. Stream will be idling soon. Maybe, possibly. We do have a few
options. I just saw this come out on Steam and needed to play it. I just want to see what's in
it. I have a pretty addictive personality and if something's fun, sometimes I want to do it more
than once, more than twice. The game we're going to play today is called NGU Idle. It's called
Numbers Go Up. And the whole point of the game is for numbers to increase in value. That's it.
There's nothing else in this game. So I have a backup in case this is not fun. All right,
there's two things that will happen. The stream's been live for a minute and a half. Here we go.
We will either play this for 30 minutes or 16 straight hours. We may also play this for
30 minutes and then move on to the floor is lava game. I don't know. I have no plan today. Don't
do it. I just made that up. I pretended like somebody said don't do it. What's the... No,
no. It's actually the floor is lava. The name of the game is called like Lava Floor. Right? What's
it called? What's the name of the game? What is the name of that game? A Hot Lava is the name of
the game actually. It's a parkour game where you can't touch the floor because of course the floor
is made out of lava. But we aren't going to do that yet. I've got a number game to get addicted
to first. Is this pre-recorded? Why would this be a pre-recorded stream? I would pick the numbers
go upstream to be pre-recorded. I mean, I guess that would make some sense now that I think about
it. It is just going to be us watching a screen with numbers going up in succession. But there's
RPG elements in this game. I guess. I've tried it. I opened it to just so I... I didn't want to be
the idiot that has no idea what he's doing. And yes, whoa, it's easy. You just watch numbers go
up. This is way more involved, I believe. I'll show it to you right now just so you can see.
Just so you completely understand. But there apparently there's like a jackass disclaimer.
I'm gonna assume this says like take a break every seven hours or something, right?
It has to be. It's gonna be like a Wiimote take a break thing. Somebody just give $50.
That's 5,000 bits from Phylactery Lich. Phylactery is back with another 5,000 bits. Can't wait to
watch my favorite streamers numbers go up. Now give me some box steps. The two completely different
streams the last... Yesterday we did a bunch of crazy shit in Hitman. Today, if you got a book
report to do, you know, just just to have it in the background. If you've got some work to do,
we can all just pretend we're playing this together because you could like go to sleep
if you want to. I know that like business management 101, I would get grabbed and like
an earpiece would be in my ear or something that says don't fucking tell your audience just to like
leave or sleep on stream. Well, I didn't tell you to leave. I told you to stay and study
because you have a book report due tomorrow. I saw somebody in the pre-stream chat.
They need it. They were like, I got this paper that's almost done. Do it now. Look what right now
with us. Well, I'm not going to do your paper for you, but do it now. It's a babysitting stream.
All right. If you've got... No, that's not right. Nevermind. Stop reminding me. All right. Let's
read this. It says whoomph. As you come to the first thing you notice the taste of copper in
your mouth. Why is it always that? Even a game like Portal had that. Remember when you walk through
the first thing, it's like, oh, the taste of iron and copper in your mouth is normal. It's always
like some metal that's in your mouth. The second being the stench of raw sewage all around you.
You get up nursing your busted lip and rubbing your head, which feels like it was lovingly caressed
by a concrete block. You try to remember how you got to, well, whatever this place is. You realize
with a surprising lack of panic that you've forgotten who you are. Based on the state you're
in right now, you're thinking they must have been an asshole. I love the writing in this.
That's such a great sentence. Tossed in a gross pit of sewage. At least for the short term,
you have an objective. Finding a way out of here. It kind of feels like the right thing to do. You
try to stand up, but your knees are weak. They shake, they buckle, and you fall back down.
It's only now that you feel the weakness in your body. Not any normal sort of weakness,
like when you stand up too quickly and get lightheaded or have your arm ripped off in
an industrial accident. No, you feel like something has sapped away the majority of your strength.
Well, there's nothing to do but to try to regain some of that strength and to get out of here.
Maybe hitting a big white button named play will let you do something fun.
All right, here we go. Fun is relative, I believe. But this is, uh, wait, has this been,
have this, this has just been on for an hour and 23 minutes because I was sitting at that screen.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. This is, this is not right. This is incorrect. This is incorrect.
I have to restart it. We should do a new game. That new game. It was sitting at that press play
screen for an hour and 23 minutes, apparently. All right, whatever. We're good. I'll start a new game.
So I was ready for a total time played one hour and 23 minutes. No, this is, I was like eating
food and like getting the stream ready and like taking a shit. This is how long it takes for me
to start a stream, guys. That's an hour and 23 minutes. So I got everything ready and I was like,
all right, I've got to take shit. All right, that's 25 minutes. I got to take a shower. That's like
15, 20 minutes. I got to eat food. That's like 30 foot. Yeah. That's how long this is exactly how
long it takes for me to start a live stream after like getting up in the morning. 25 minutes. Shit.
Yeah. What are you talking about? I don't buy this for a second that some of you guys take.
I'm not 20 minutes, 15 minutes. I don't know. 10 minutes, 15 minutes. It depends on what I'm
reading on my iPhone. Look, if there's like a big thing on Twitter that I'm looking at,
I'm going to be there. It takes two minutes to take a shit. Holy fuck. What are you talking about?
How long does it take you to wipe your ass? It takes five minutes to wipe your ass.
Two minutes? You are a liar if you think that you can tell me right now that you wipe your
ass in less than five minutes. Nope. I don't believe you. And if you do that and that's
actually true, I don't know if that's totally, I don't know if it's totally clean or not.
Like a three minute ass wiping. All right. So first of all, that's all I need to say.
That's funny though. That actually is funny. That's how long it takes. Okay. Start a new game.
Oh, you come too. This guy has swamp ass. No, I want a clean body. Completely void of all filth.
All right. We're done. It took me two minutes to say that. Did it take me two minutes to do that?
No, it didn't. How long has Stream been live for? 10 minutes. What? We've been live for like three.
Oh God. All right. Hey there, whoever you are. Glad you decided to check out NGU. I'm something
of a game developer myself. The guy who made this game. People call me 4G for short. That's all
right. That's cool. I see the something. And then we had a ton more money just came in. What's
going on? Why are you guys giving so much money right now? Uh, La Crona gave 5,000 bits twice.
They gave, uh, 10,000 bits. Derma step up your shitting game, spread your ass cheeks. I don't
think I can read this. Your asshole. No, no, everybody has their own way to do that.
Everyone. If you talk to anybody and I am going to get a little gross. Okay.
No, I'm not. This is going to be, we're going to be PG for this one. They write books for kids
on this shit guys. Don't worry when you, but two different, two different people don't go to the
bathroom. Same way. Everybody has their own bathroom ritual. All of us. It's like built into
the DNA of humans. Some people, you know, they, they prep, they prep for like five minutes. They
just sit there. They prep. They did the prep work. Some people need to drink a coffee in the morning
to get themselves or water to get themselves going. That's prep work. That's included in the
ship time. There's also post work too. I stretch after I go to the second one because I want to
make sure everything's all, you know, the urine testings need to be kind of nice and moved around
jog in place for a minute, shake around. I stretch after I, what are you talking about?
What do you mean stop? What are you talking about? I'm talking about like I get up and like do like
touch my toes. I'm not doing these exercises in the bathroom. What is, what are you just talking
about? Somebody's gave another $5,000, but they say pee pee poo poo. That was bala koala for
5,000 bits. Wait, I hold on. Let me, I want to make this really, really, really completely
totally clear. I can't talk about my post shit activity, but I can get messages spammed here in
this chat room that says pee pee poo poo like he pooped his pants. There's a, I think there's a,
that's an issue. I think a bit. We put an image on screen yesterday of everybody laughing their
asses off it. A fake of me pissing my pants, but this is weird for me to talk about how I stretch
after I go to the bathroom. I gotta, I gotta restart. Do I have to restart? Debunk. No. All
right. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. This, this, I have like a, I'm flying like an airplane right
now. Like, hold on. What the fuck do I do? I love how that's like a message. All right. Well,
I'm just going to go. I got five, this is energy. Okay. You need energy. Fuck the tutorial gives
a shit. I know what to do. So we've got 500 energy with this. This increases each moment.
You can fight people. We have to, we have a thousand HP, a hundred attack, a hundred defense.
And we, uh, current rebirth time is six minutes and 26 seconds.
Auto save in seven seconds to make sure just in case something happens, you know, in case
you sit in there for too long and you got to get up and do some prep work before you use the bathroom
and then obviously do some stretching afterwards, get out of here. So basic training, we have idle
attack and idle block. We can't do these ones yet. And I mean, what do you say we turn on a little
bit of an OST here? My favorite OST in the world. We're talking about the turtles and time soundtrack.
Let's get it going. I have 250 energy. Let's just spam attack. Look at my attack going out.
That's a number rising increasingly. That's the whole thing. There's no other songs.
Numbers go up. This is going to get much more interesting. Maybe, maybe I have not figured that
out yet. I was going to play it, but what do I, I can't just go all attack. I gotta go defense too.
This is HP. There we go. Look at that 1200, 1300, 1415. Let's just put all 500 in here.
So I have a 500 cap of energy. By the way, for every resident sleeper that I see in the chat,
it adds one minute to how long we're going to play this. I'm tracking them too. That's at least 280
minutes. The shit, this is the best song. This is the best song in the whole, the best song
of the whole soundtrack. Levels gained to this defense skill will decrease the amount of energy
needed to cap leveling speed upon rebirth. So rebirth is you, you prestige like Call of Duty.
Call of Duty stole everything they know from NGU. All right, I almost have a million HP. All right,
I have 626 block points. Look at the millions of HP. All right, we're going to do 250, 250.
Fight the boss. Here we go. Why am I hurt? Why am I already injured? How much HP do I have?
How did I get hurt? Why am I getting hurt? What's hurting me? Wait, I need to read this. You
shakily get to your feet, leaning against the wall for support. You have to build up your strength
somehow. From the corner of your eye, you spot a small piece of fluff. This will be your first and
most intense battle of your life. 50,000 attack. I got a million. I got a million. Get out of here.
Oh, you squished the fluff. In more important news, that's a fantastic sandwich.
Smoked ham and turkey with swiss cheese and honey dijon. That's a pretty good sandwich.
Oh, hey, cool. You squished the fluff. In more important news, this is a fantastic sandwich.
Smoked ham and turkey with swiss cheese and honey dijon sauce on a ciabatta bun.
That's really fucking good. I'm actually kind of jealous about that. All right.
Uh, cool. Killing bosses brings a few important rewards. First off, you gain...
I'm getting vroomed by the LST. First of all, you gain experience. Experience points.
Turn that down for just a second. Just turn it down a little. Okay, you gain experience points
for downing bosses. EXP is used to buy permanent powers in the spend EXP menu,
which also you just unlocked. You should see a fancy yellow button in the bottom left.
Right there. Okay. Uh, all right. Uh, there's a lot of stuff you can buy with the EXP,
but don't get overwhelmed. My pro tip to you would be to buy the special offers to increase
the energy... I'm gonna burp. My pro tip to you would be to buy the special offers to increase
the speed the energy bar fills. I did specifically code them for newbies like you to buy, but no
pressure. Defeat the next couple bosses and I'll bug you again. 4G over and up. You got it.
Oh lord. All right. Total energy speed. Buying this will make the energy bar fill up faster,
which is this. Max speed is one bar fill per tick or 50 fills a second. Note, the bar fills
at a rate of 50 divided by energy speed. Ticks per fill rounded up. Later on, you'll want to
buy this upgrade in chunks such as 25 equals is greater than 50 speed in order to gain any effect.
All right. Newbie offers. That's what I'm looking for. What I got? Two experience
plus 0.3 for two experience points. Let's do it. Look at that. Max energy on... Max energy
on this rebirth is capped at 500. On rebirth, you will have 529 energy. All righty. Look
at how much fucking HP I have. Okay. I'm going to breeze through the newbie zones. All right.
Your current energy speed is 1.3, meaning the bar fills every 39 ticks. Next speed increases at
1.3 energy speed. Tap R to reclaim energy for a moment. Okay. Let's go. Oh yeah. Look at this.
I'm just completely allocating. Let's go kick some ass. Boss fight. Floating piece of shit.
You're sure that it's a fluff could... If the fluff could it... If the fluff could, comma,
it would give a dramatic death speech, but alas, you kick it off to the side.
More confident in your strength. What other inanimate objects are there to murder? A piece
of sewage as if my cube begins floating down the water right in front of you. Get fucking
instakilled. Boss fight. A stick. The sewage retreats from your onslaught of attacks. Either
that or it kept floating by. Probably your attacks though. You feel like you can manage
to make your way out of here now, but a weapon would be handy. Oh hey, is that a stick coming
down the water? Instakill it please. Oh, wait a minute. All right. A small mouse. As you turn
to head, as you turn to head to this room's exit, you notice a brown little mouse. In a
shrill voice, it squeaks. Welcome to NGU Idol. I'm Tippy. If you're all right, Ed. Eddie. If
you're all right, Ed. Oh, I don't think we can do that, Eddie. Turning out this annoying mouse's
intro, you're hit with a jolt of memory. I need to defeat every foe in your path. No matter what.
You can start with this mouse right here. What's he got? 11 million HP. I got 25 million. You got
nothing on me. Attack 1.1 million. Defense 3.1. Let's go. See you later. Oh, hi. Hello. It's 4G
again. So you killed the mouse. I guess that means it's time to add some rockin' new gameplay your
way. First off, you unlocked Adventure. Think crappy RPG within the game. You'll fight stuff
and loot other stuff. The training skills you unlock become moves you can use in Adventure to
defeat enemies. Oh, shit. What do you know about that? Enemies will spawn randomly every few
seconds when you move out of the safe zone. Fighting enemies in Adventure will drop gear,
which you can equip in the snazzy new... By the way, this game's free. I need to make that very
clear. You can just go get it right now on Steam. Or play it on a congregate, I believe. You just
play it. Fucking free. Who knows if they make you buy stuff. I don't know. Somebody just said
It Better Be. What? Come on. This is fucking... This is a classic. This is a classic game,
and I am offended that you just said that. This game's been around for like five years.
It's back before you even... That's back before you even were born. You were in diapers when this
guy 4G was making this shit. Like 15 years ago when he rode it on the back of a napkin.
This is vintage. All hand-drawn. All right. Enemies... They drop gear. There's gear in this
game. There's hats in this game. That just made everybody like it. All right. You have a new...
It's an inventory slot now. You don't have shit we're gonna have to take care of. Equipment can
boost your stats in Adventure and your main attack defense stats and later provide special
awesome bonuses. You only have the training zone unlocked. Defeating higher numbered bosses will
eventually unlock new Adventure zones to play in and get better gear to slap on. Also, boss enemies
in Adventure have a chance to drop experience. Experience is good. You've also unlocked rebirths,
which needs some explanation. I already know what this does because I sat there for an hour and a
half. Streamer in chat. Eventually you're going to hit a point... By the way, I'm sorry. I want to
count how many resident sleepers there were. There were exactly 1412. So that's 1412 minutes
added to the stream. Divided by 40. So it was like 30 minutes. Eventually you're going to hit a point
where it takes forever to grow stronger. If you rebirth, you'll reset most of your progress in
each menu and the bosses will reset. However, in return your number will grow. Number is, well,
it's a number. Your attack and defense get multiplied by number and your number can get
ridiculously big. Like stupid big. Like past your mama jokes big. So anytime progress feels slow,
it's probably time to rebirth and reset some progress to get your number up. You can try
rebirthing now if you want, but if you wait longer, your number will even grow even bigger.
Rebirth time is a big factor to decide the size of your number up until 60 minutes. I should have
just rebirthed at the very beginning. You can check how long your rebirth has been going on in the
stats menu. Cool. When you rebirth, bosses also respond with a higher number. With a high enough
number, you can defeat the high numbered bosses, which will reward experience every time they
defeat. Get to boss 17 and you'll unlock another thing. See you. All right. 65 million HP, 4 million.
What do you got for defense? Let's, uh oh. Wiping the mouse guts from between your fingers,
you head off down the sewers and make your escape. Barely rounding the second corner,
you face your next major foe, a slightly bigger mouse. You know what to do. What do I got for attack?
Uh, I think, I think I'm going to win. I should still win. I'm not going to run.
Nuke. No, I don't nuke. Click this button to blast through all those scrub bosses that you can
annihilate with a flick of your fingers. Your wrist will thank me later. I don't want to do that.
What do you mean I can't win? I just, I just destroyed it. How much experience do I have?
No, my defense is going up by the million. Uh oh. You start feeling lost in the identical looking
passageways, dripping with all sorts of goopy brown waste. This is just a shit stream. This
is a poo stream, I guess. You're worrying that you'll never escape these sewers and that every
bossy face is just going to be some variation of a rat. Cutting off your nose is starting to
seem like a good idea too. The stink. 325 million HP, 32 million attack. Okay, don't die. That was
close. Uh, what do I have to inventory? Oh god. Item list. This has like the same amount of items
as Binding of Isaac does. All right, basic training. I only have 500. Okay, I have to go back. I think
I have to rebirth. I have 20 experience points to spend. No, I can't do it. Adventure. Okay,
safe zone. Awakening. I only have, all I can do is block. Blocks 50% of incoming damage for the next
three seconds. I don't even have an attack. All right, let's go. Tutorial zone. Idle mode. Click
to toggle idle mode on and off. When on, a stick has attacked. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Automatically attacks every one second while on health regen. All right, let's turn it on.
Where's my actual, I can't attack? All right, I'm gonna beat the stick. HP rag up. One eight, one,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. When on, automatically attacks every one second. You get
20% health regen. Cannot use any other moves. Damage multiplier of 1.2. Fighting a stick again.
I don't have any manual attacks yet. Oh, okay. What happens if I get to zero HP? Does the game end?
Uh oh. Uh, I don't think I'm gonna do this. I think I'm gonna lose. I'm gonna die. He's doing
too much damage. I need like a health potion. I'm dead. A small mouse has defeated you. I lost.
Well, all right, I got, hold on. This is a different game mode entirely. What do I have? 65
million? Requires 5,000 levels in attack to level this up. Equipment, okay. Use the boost you find
to improve. This is 4G's merge and boost tutorial cube. Level 4 accessory. Use the boost you find
to improve this item's stats. Find additional cubes and drag onto this item to merge and
increase stat caps by 1% per level rounded down. One. Oh, shit. There it is. I hope to God it really
is just a stick. A level 10 weapon. Merge extra copies of the stick onto this item to raise its
level. Each level increases an equipment's max stats by 1% rounded down, up to double the original
stats at level 100. You can do this a fucking hundred times? Oh, shit. So what does this do?
Power boost? Drag this item onto any equipment. Wait. To raise its stat by 1. Raising equipment's
current stat to its cap to really toughness boost. Oh, shit. I can put this on a stick.
Don't waste it. Don't waste it. Should I not waste it? Oh, it's on max power. All right, yeah.
Fuck it. I'm not gonna waste these. All right, cool. Let's go back to adventure and see what
happens. Let's see if we can fight that motherfucker again. Now I got a stick. 13 power. Let's go.
There it is. Yeah, you ain't gonna win. I got it. I got this one. This is the train level,
if you didn't ever play this. Drop 952 gold. Drop the cloth hat. Oh, yes. Wait, what? Hold on.
I'm gonna lose. Hold on a second. Regular cloth hat worn out and tattered, but at least it feels
soft. Merge extra copies so I get one toughness and some health regen. Stats breakdown. Oh,
look at all this shit. To satify all the stats nerds. I have so much. I gotta wait. Hold on.
Should I um, all right. Adventure. Wait, is this at three to three? One on one. Fight boss. Can I
do anything about this yet? No. This is the wall right now. Click on the special prize. Special
prize. Special prize. Hold on. I got a lot of experience. Should I? Is this gonna reset if I
rebirth? You're playing an accounting game. Yeah. Oh, fuck. This is going to fire. All right. Wait,
wait, wait. 16. Total energy power. Let's do that one. Bang. 1.1. Energy power. It means
things do better. I have numbers to go up. That's all I need to know. Wait, wait. There's adventure
stats. Oh, shit. Adventure special. More inventory spaces. Fuck. Levels gained in... Wait a minute.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Levels gained in this attack skill would decrease the
amount of energy needed to cap leveling speed upon rebirth. Base attack received per level is a
thousand. Oh, let's get this fucking thing leveled up then. You're going to get this game? Yeah,
dude. If you like numbers going up, then you might as well get it. Look, this is very clear
what this stream is. Title even says it. Let's split this. I need some more. Hold on. Let's
do like increments of a hundred. Let's do like a hundred, a hundred, like three hundred.
Because I need more defense and HP. Is this a clicker? This is not really. It's more of a
management game. No, I can't fight this thing. I think I should rebirth. I'm going to do it.
Let's go back to adventure. All right, so now I should have... Let me try this one more time.
Idle mode. Floating sewage. I feel like I've given up on you. What, because I'm playing an idle game?
What the fuck does that mean? There was just a carnival last weekend.
Huh? What the fuck? You just increased the amount of time I'm going to play this game by 30 minutes.
You or yourself? We're stuck here forever. Quick, quick call the game boring so he adds time. That's
the fucking 500 IQ play. All right, what do we got? Boss battle. Boss battle. I can't do it.
I'm going to rebirth here in a second. All right, hold on. I got some stuff. Oh, fuck. There's like
four sausages now. Wait a minute. Wait, wait, wait. If I drag these on top of each other,
this has been merged. Does that do anything? Oh, he's playing a clicker game. Does he even
care anymore? Yeah, he does. Oh, shit. Okay. Three out of four power. Guys, I think he hates us all
on a personal level. I'm personally offending all 3,700 of you. We just did a carnival stream
like a week and a half ago. I think I'm entitled to one cookie clicker stream.
Uh, thank you Hurricane Turtle for the 10 community subs. Appreciate it. Put on the stick.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Hold on. Level 65 weapon. Wait, wait, wait. I didn't even look at
this shit. All right, you just add in another hour. Uh, there's no bottom zone. These are all worn
out. Kind of ruins the purpose of these boots, doesn't it? Toughness one. Toughness one. I'm just
the dirty guy that fell in the sewer. Holy shit, I'm doing great. I'm going to move 69. Uh, can I go
to- I want to go to a different zone. How do I open up a new zone? Cloth shirt. Oh, fuck,
I can merge these. I think I have to- I have to beat this. I'm not going to be able to do this.
All right, it's time to rebirth. Here we go. I'm doing it. It's been 30 minutes.
We're at the- all right, we're at the time. We're at the time here where I have to decide
if I'm going to play this for a while. And the answer is yes. Anything to do before rebirth.
Let's go. All right, we're back to zero. It's been 25 minutes. It's time to get off the toilet.
Give me a break. You just added an hour to the game. All right, 48,000 attack.
I only have a thousand HP. 500,000 HP? What? I need more. How much HP do I have?
All right, so I've rebirthed, which means I get way more per- I get more stats per point now,
and I have a higher energy cap. What if this was my first 24-hour stream? What if I did that?
Big mistake. What do you mean? What am I talking about? Look at this. Look at how fast that's going
up because- wait, I want to see the info. Where's the actual stats? That's going up so much faster.
Do it. Do it. Coward. Coward. Coward. Coward. All right, I got- uh, let's do it. Let's split it
evenly. 100, 100. I want more HP. All right, now let's just- let's just murder this guy.
Bring on the next one. Floating piece of shit. What you guys don't know is I have been on the
toilet this whole time. I'm in the bathroom. My whole setup is here. All right, 275. Let's do more
attack. I want this over like 5 million. Did you guys ever make magic potions? I think we already
talked about magic potions, right? No, I'm saying like in the sink. Did you guys have five- what,
65 million HP? I need some more. We're gonna- what do I got? Pretty dirty. I need more- uh,
I need more help. You guys ever did magic potions in the sink? You take like a- like a small squeeze
of shampoo, a little bit of toothpaste, some conditioner, a little bit of like spray deodorant
and- and mix it up and maybe made magic potions. If you say you didn't do that, I don't- I don't
believe you and you know what? You've just added 40 minutes to the spring. You see the goddamn
carnival I did two weeks ago? Add a timer. I don't have a timer. All right, I think I can do this.
Not yet. Can we get a BRB? How long has it been? We've been going for 43 minutes. By the way,
Turtles in Time has a long ass soundtrack. I didn't think it was this long. I thought it was like eight
minutes. It's been 28 minutes of this. 65 million. All right, I gotta get more. What do I got? What's
my new cap? You will hit your energy cap in one minute and 52 seconds. I need more HP or something.
What the fuck do I need? Attack. No, I want- I want like- I want 50 million HP and then we're
gonna go for an attack. What do I have for experience? Three experience points. I want to-
you know what? Let's make it better for adventure mode. I want more base power. Bingo. 14. That
should make it very easy. All right, 34 million. What's he got for defense? 3.5. I got a lot of
attack though. What do you think? Think I'm gonna do it? I think I'm gonna do it. All right, here we go.
This was the wall last time. Drain it of its lifeblood. That's what the plan is. Back to basic
training. Uh, get it all in attack actually. All of it. 615 cap. I went up by five. I went by 115.
Look at that. What's this guy got for defense? 17 million. Let's get to like 20 million attack
and I'm gonna put HP up. Experience? I don't have any EXP. I need to make the cap higher.
Once you have 100,000 max energy, you can- you'll find you can't gain anymore just by
generating energy. Why? Because I made it that way. All right, let's do adventure mode. Uh,
tutorial zone. How do we get out of the tutorial? Do you get experience every time you kill
something? I think so. All right, small mouse boss. So how do I get to the out of the zone?
He's still in the tutorial. Laugh out loud, MonkaS. Um, I need to tell you guys something very
important. This, uh, this game, some people have been continuously playing this game for three years.
So, uh, whoa. All right, any, uh, inventory? What do I got? Wait, I get to keep my stuff?
Oh shit, I'm getting like all these- hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait. I'm gonna get overwhelmed
here. Sausage. Three out of five. All right, drag this onto any equipment to boost its special by
one. Should I boost this by one? Wait, is this by two? What'd I just do? I just boosted the one to a
one. What have I done? Uh, equip the cube. Oh fuck, I didn't know I could put this on. Wait,
so can I- should I put this all in the cube? I'm still picking up dirty socks.
All right, uh, hurricane turtle gave 20 community subs. I'm almost there. Level 87. I need to boost
this. Oh, I ran out of music. We might as well move on to Super Mario World OST from Super Nintendo.
We're in a Super Nintendo mood today. All right, uh, I got a level 100 weapon now. Three to six.
I can boost it if I wanted to. 100. All right, now- wait, I have 48 million attack. It's time to do
some, uh, I gotta get out. I gotta get over this. Basic training, get this out. Cap it. Let's go.
Spam that. Put every single point in this. I just want- I need like 300 million HP. How do I get more-
wait, I need to kill stuff. Adventure. Let's go. No, we're still in the tutorial. I get- I'm
getting out of the tutorial zone. At least he's dropping stuff. Where's my money? Cloth boots.
All right, you need to defeat boss seven in- wait, what? You need to defeat boss seven in the fight
boss menu. Oh, shit. I have to kill this. Holy fuck, I didn't realize how much attack I had.
I think it's gonna happen. He makes all the rooms. Well, he's dead. Brown slime. Boss seven. 162
million attack. That's- that's not good. Finally, you begin to feel a cool breeze from one path
and heading down it, you see a light at the end. Just before the exit, a large menacing brown blob
seeps out of the nearby walls, ready to fight. Well, it's as menacing as a blob of poo can get it.
That's poo. Okay, so what do you have for defense? I'm not gonna be able to kill this. I need to get
what I have to. Uh, more socks. I feel like I should- no. I'm stuck in this- I'm stuck here forever.
I'm just gonna grind gold. This- that- this is 1.6 billion HP. What do I have for defense? 37 million.
This is gonna kill me instantly. Yeah, like, this is impossible. This is not possible. Where's my-
do I have to rebirth again? Wait, experience. 3 exp. I- I'm gonna rebirth. All right, we're gonna
start over. What do I get for- I have 11 minutes of- of rebirth here. It's not possible, guys.
162 million attack. I only have- he'll- he kills me in two seconds. Or like three seconds. Is that
locked? Give the cube food. 9 out of 18 max health. This is for white boss. German the cube. German
the cube. The cube. The cube. Use the boosts you find to improve this item's stats and find additional
cubes and drag onto this item to merge and increase stack caps by 1% per level. Uh, how many times can
you- it's level 100. So how do I just throw stuff in the trash? Right here. Use numbers on cube.
Is that- should I do that? Everyone's gonna scream at me now. Special. Energy speed. 6 out of 15.
7%. 8%. Is this waste? 9% extra speed and 1 power. Toughness. Can this thing be merged with another
cube? Pants. Everyone screams. Pants. So I can do cube and another cube. All right, well I used it
all. So, let's see. I- I still have to beat this boss though. 500 million HP. Why is this not going
up? Oh, because I have- I'm only doing attack right now. Wait, what? Why am I capped out at HP?
Why am I capped out at HP? Wait, what the hell is this? Now it's going up. Why is it going up?
Attack is HP. What? All right, what do I have? 56 million. I can't even come close. Block scales up
regen. Is that all it does? Well, fuck. I didn't know that. How am I gonna ever hit through this?
Three experience. Let's do energy power. I need 15. Adventure stats. Adventure special. No,
this don't matter until I get- I have to beat the seven blocks. What's the cube got? 6 out of 21
max health. 5k per block. Why do I say power like that? Power? Power? Play adventure. I can't. You
need to defeat boss seven and the fight boss to move on. I can't leave the tutorial until I beat
this guy. I'm gonna have to rebirth. Power. What's wrong with saying power? How do you say it? Auto
merge, auto boost. Well, not yet. I want to see. Combined stick. It's not gonna do anything though.
Little 65 chest. Hurry the fuck up! Hurry the fuck up! Hurry the fuck up! All right, I'm good. 86
million. I need to get to defense. 87 million. Now I can- at least now I can hurt it. Kind of.
I'm gonna stay for the Mario music. Thanks for watching the stream. Appreciate it. You just added
15 more minutes. No, I can't. I don't have enough attack. Play a second idle game by playing this
one. No, I don't have the kind of brain power for that. I think I have to rebirth. After killing this
thing is the last thing I'm gonna do. And then I'm gonna rebirth and we're gonna do it again.
You just have to AFK. You don't need brain power. Says you. I need all the brain power I can get.
Regular attack. Oh, nice. Hold on.
What's base attack on this one? Base attack received per levels 150. Oh, well, uh, yeah.
I need to get- oh, defense. Right. I have to get to 5,000 defense. You're right. What do I got?
113 million. Ah, it's not there yet. It's almost there. Hurry up. You're invincible. I'm not
invincible. I'm very killable. Auto merge. Auto boost. Need to unlock auto boost. I can't even
toggle these. Need to buy auto merge in the EXP menu. I can't do this. I'm not allowed to auto
merge. I have to do it by hand. 115 million attack. Come on. Let's go. Damn it. I just need to kill
this guy. Stick can't go over a hundred. Yeah. What does the nuke button do? I believe the nuke
button- now somebody correct me if this is incorrect. I believe the nuke button means you
can skip whatever you're capable of killing. Right? Wrong. This is just wrong. Wrong. Incorrect. Nuke
just autocompletes easy bosses. That's exactly what I said. You're impatient in an idle game.
It skips to the next game. If I put on the face cam will you guys relax? I just want you guys to
relax. That's what this is. We're just relaxing. You guys just- you guys need to relax with me.
We're gonna get to 1.6 billion. Show auto. The numbers are getting too big.
A hundred million is not that big when it comes to space. There's space levels of numbers in this
game. All right. Here's what we're gonna do. Here's what we're gonna do. We're gonna keep playing this,
but I'm gonna play the lava game too. I'm gonna play them both at the same time. In between
levels I'm gonna switch because I want to do this. How much defense do I have? Unfortunately,
the music has to stop though. Uh-oh. Defensive buff. Base defense received isn't- ooh.
Shit. I want that- I want to spam that. Thousand per- thousand base defense. How much do I have
right now? Let me just kill this fucking thing. 162 million. All right. Let's go. It's gonna be
close. I'm gonna lose. Fuck. I need a little bit more. Almost- just a little bit more. I need more
attack. Defense is all right. I need more attack. Just only attack. Just get it up there. Come on.
Hurry up. Attack in HP. Is it? 107 defense. All right. Now let's only do defense. I'm just going
all in. You just- sometimes you have to go all in completely. You lied about face cam. No, I- I'm
moving to, um, hot lava. You regen faster. Oh shit. Holy shit, you're right. So you lied about face cam.
You really want me to put on face cam? Is that what you want? Let me kill this. Come on. Who's
going down faster? Who's counting down faster? Is it me or them? Oh, it's even. Completely.
Hurry up. How much is he regenning? All right. If I- I gotta regen over what you're regenning
and then go again. Put your face as the boss. Hold on. I'm- I'll- I'm- it's- I'm getting addicted.
Uh-oh. Uh-oh. Uh-oh. Here it is. I did it. He's dead. We don't need to play another game.
I did it. You defeated brown slime. You've unlocked a new adventure zone, the sewers. Go to adventure
feature and check it out. I'm addicted. We don't need to play any other game. You finally escape,
gasping your first breaths of fresh air. And who knows how long. You shield your eyes for a moment
in the bright sun. Once your eyes adapt to the light, you see a gorgeous green field stretched out
before you, leading up to a forest. You can feel the gloom seeping into every branch. As you approach
the path leading to the forest, a spooky skeleton emerges from the ground, armed with a trumpet.
You try not to get distracted by its jazzy tunes while you smash it to dust. This thing is not
going to be killable now. But I did unlock an adventure zone. Oh my god. My inventory is a
mess. This is the same inventory that I have when I play Minecraft. I keep so much useless shit and
I have to merge all this. I don't even want these sticks anymore. I have to- no, I'm gonna- that's
the first thing I'm gonna buy. I'm gonna buy- oh. I'm gonna buy auto-merge immediately upon rebirth.
Are we almost maxed out? Four. All right, hold on. Adventure. Let's just- let's go to the sewers.
Let's check it out. I'm just sweeping. I'm absolutely stomping right now. 1800 gold. All
right. Hold on. I'll put on the face game in like a couple hours. I don't even know how to turn it on.
I'm using a new streamlabs. I have no idea.
Uh-oh, brown slime. We're gonna get some good gear from this one. All right, you guys get to pick.
We either play hot lava or you get a face cam. Which one do you want? 2900 gold. Nice. Big rat.
Both. Well, I'll end up doing both eventually here. This is- we're just doing the pre-stream.
Yeah, I think we're just doing the pre- stream. Guys, I just got off the plane from TwitchCon like
four days ago. I need- like I need- I need some time. I'm dead. Ooh, a new dirty shirt. Put it on.
Guys, I just got off the plane from San Diego like five days ago. Like, I'm fucking- I just need some
time. We just- we need to play an idle game for a little bit. All right, I lost. It's time to rebirth.
I think so. I'm doing it. Fuck it. I'm doing it. Uh, boss power bonus is going from two to the
seventh power, 128. Boss power bonus, last rebirth, two to the fifth power, 35. Current number number
on rebirth, 120. Time factor, training level factor. Nothing to need to do. Go ahead and rebirth.
Okay, I'm gonna have 121 times. Let's go. Difficulty normal. I ain't doing that. Rebirth. Bang. Did it.
Good. Nice. Nice. All right, I'll get you- do you deserve a face cam for that?
You do. It's gonna be real.
No. You deserve it. I'll give it to you. For like- for- all right, for every resident sleeper that
I see in the chat, I remove a minute from the face cam. What are you gonna do now? All right,
get this out of here. Let's just change categories into just chatting now and just
do an ask me anything. Right? Like, how big- okay, I can be like this big. Oh shit, I could be- I
could be- I could be this big right now on stream. That's a good track. All right, what's next? I
rebirthed. So we're gonna do basic training. I got my- let's go back to the live view.
Star Wars! All right, the cap. I'll have to redo this again. No, don't. I'll knock something off.
I'll break something. Do I fucking love Star Wars? This is not gonna go the way that you think.
This is like the best song in the whole entire fucking Mario catalog of songs.
All right, 10 million attack. Need gold. Get loads of gold to unlock this. More unlockables!
Let's just, uh, fight boss. Should I just nuke? I mean, I'm at 18 million attack. Should we just
snap all these guys out of here? Oh shit, I can't be this big. I can't be this big. You
can't see the health bar. Gotta have to shrink it. I can't be here either. I can't know, because
the- look at what- look what happens if I do that. That fucks this whole thing up.
That fucks up the whole thing. God damn it. I can't. I can't do it. This- I- it's too much-
Nope, I can't do it. I was gonna get hurt and have that song play right now.
This thing. I was trying- I was like, what is over here that I could get hurt with?
I don't even know where it is. Here it is. This guy- I was gonna have like something fall and
like drop and hit me in the head, like lean on and be like, oh no. What happened? Oh shit!
Oh, he- he got hurt! And he died! He took a hurt. Yeah, it was made out of fucking Play-Doh.
All right, let's go back to the song. All right, what was I doing? Good idea, poor execution.
You sometimes you think of something that you want to do, and then like,
I think 15 seconds go by and you're like, wait a minute. I want to do that. And then you don't.
That's not right. Nuke everybody. I only have 20,000 HP. Oh, fuck. Wait, why is this so low?
But it's- it's really low for me. What did I do? Oh, that's why. Because my headphones got like
unplugged. Okay, now that's better. All right, I need to go- I need to exp- oh wait, back to
training. What's 570's cap? Let's get it at 317. There we go. Now you can't hear it. Yeah, you can.
That's fine. You can hear that. What does sour please mean? It means dance. It's like a I'm dancing
thing. I don't know. I just learned about that like two or three months ago, so. You can't lie,
this idle game has a really good soundtrack. I mean, it does. It does. It's a pretty good soundtrack.
Nuke this guy. All right, that's pretty cool that you can do that. Uh, I have to fight the mouse,
though. Six- we're over the cap right now. That's good. Put this over. Fix the face cam location.
Isn't that- isn't this way- you wanted it? I thought it was supposed to be right here.
Is it- it's not fine there? It should be. I mean, you can't see how much energy is being
allocated. Put it over here. What about- there's nowhere for it to go. Come on, let me show you.
What if it was down here? That's not a bad place for it. Yeah, that's fine. That's fine. You- I
want to see the artwork. Did you guys want to see- it's not gonna be my face for every single boss.
I'm sorry. Come on. Okay, I have- let's get rid of- okay, that was instant. I don't want to hurt my
eyes. Gone. All right, this is why you rebirth. How much experience do I have? 10. I want energy
power. This upgrade improves the effectiveness of your allocated energy. This means faster progress
on features while using less energy. I don't- I have enough. I love this game. I'm playing it right
now. Thanks. Why'd I say thanks? Like, oh, thanks. Yeah, I like this too. Thanks. I don't know. I
have no idea. I'm gonna do that. Should I do more base energy speed? I don't think that's- that's
not doing- hmm. You know what? We're going all in on attack for now. Pull this all out. Cap the whole
thing. 778 points. Fight the boss. Boom. Just- you know how long this took last time? This was such
a fucking pain in the ass last time, and now we're at the skeleton trumpet. Although I have to wait
for this one. Time for adventure mode. What do I have for inventory? Okay, this is unchanged.
Adventure. Sewers. Let's go. Put on the Doom Eternal OST. The actual dev is here.
Actual dev in chat. This game's fucking fun. I'm already addicted. I- I didn't know if I- you know,
I- I crossed a path where I didn't think I was gonna get addicted. I wasn't sure.
And everyone here is addicted too. So that's what- this is what we're doing. Let's get some
Skyrim OST on here. I think that fits. Uh, do I have any inventory? Ooh, what's this? Crappy
helmet level four. One out of five. And better health regen. Oh, get this out of here. That's
much better. Throw it away. Wait, should I throw this away? I'm gonna hold on to it. Throw it away.
All right, we got 2.5- uh, 800 million attack. Basic training. Let's go back here. Oh, I'm just
stomping in here. That's fine. Level every item to 100. I'll- I'll give it a try. I do want more- I
need more defense. I'm gonna get- let me get this to 5,000 first. And then I'm gonna put 100 points.
Wait, listen. 100 points are gonna go here. And then 670 are gonna go down here. I think that's
a good idea. Once an item gets to level 100, you need to start putting the boosts into them.
Fuck, okay. German. Okay, um, why is the block not going up? Because I don't have any energy in it.
I'm just trying to spam this until I get to a point where I'm gonna bring it down. Because one
level of idle attack is worth 150. One level of regular attack is worth a thousand.
So that's how you play the math there. Let's spam this one now.
678. Spam it. Wait, cap. So that's the high- that's as fast as it can possibly go.
So 549 is as fast as I can do it. I think I broke it. Did I break it? Because when I do- all right,
for instance, ready? Like, cap. Like, cap seems to be different. Like, why is it different?
Cap just puts all your idle energy into it. All right, well let's do this for a little bit. I got
1.2 billion attack. Fight the boss. He's got 8.1 billion HP. He's got 4.37.500 million.
He's dead. I think I can ride it out. I think I can ride it out. Skeleton's about to go down.
Boys and girls, Skeleton's about to go down. Can I get you some hype in the chat, please?
I need to fucking think about it. Goblin. Seek out the wizard further on. You hear sighing from the
pulverized bone dust. Now swept away by the wind you venture past. Thankful for the advice. Though
unsure where to go other than deeper into this rather sinister looking forest. Before long you
sense something above you and dart out of the way just before a tiny hawk marked figure falls
onto the ground where you were. Uh-oh. Droop's in trouble. The goblin shrieks in a gross nasally
voice. The face game needs to be moved back. I can read that to you. It's okay. So he's got 4.- 4
billion. 2- 40 billion HP. 40 billion HP. Okay. I love how that's just a what the fuck do I do
button. I need to get more shit in the adventure mode. Back to the sewers. Let's go. Idle mode.
Activate it. Small mouse. Face game would be better in the bottom right. This is the bottom
right. All right. Bronze slime. He's got poison. Two poison damage. No, bottom left. I need- I want
some more coffee. Should I go get some more coffee? Ooh, I got a cracked amulet. Wait. Cracked
amulet. I need to see what that does. This one isn't covered in poo. This is a bunch of poo,
but it's brown anyways. Feels like the useful in combat. That's pretty good. That's actually
really good. What am I doing in my training here? Yeah, that's good. Just keep that. You know what?
Do this. Just to keep this kind of even here. I ignored subs. I didn't see them. Where are they?
What is this game actually called? It's called N-G-U-Idle. It's on Steam. It's free to play.
Did I miss subs? Did I? I- I don't see them. How many? How many were there? Because they're not
here. The dev gifted subs. It was 10? Why is this not here? Parag- Paraguay just gave 10 community
subs. That was 10 from- that was 10 from before too. That's 20. So that's the dev of this game.
I need that confirmed by- by somebody. I need that to be confirmed. Yes. What's going on?
That's all I have to say. Hey, what's up? Cool game. But thank you for the 20 community subs.
That means a lot. It's an interesting concept. It's a fun game. I'm liking it. Let's keep this
down here now. And then right after that, DemonsB gave 5,500 bits and they said,
I have chronic pain and watching your streams helps take my mind off of it.
I was enjoying part two of your recetteer VOD when about now I was in you leaned into the mic
and loudly said, wake up if you're sleeping, wake up and turn off the stream. You then loudly yelled
over some silly little bullshit in the anime game. Why? What the heck dude? Love you anyways.
I think you're really talented. But I'm really sorry to hear about the first part here. This-
the chronic pain. I can't imagine how much that must suck.
As somebody that also deals with chronic illness, it's not fun. So I know what that's like. Thank
you for the 5,500 fucking bits. And sorry for waking you up, but sometimes you gotta wake people
up. Like for instance, right now, we've been streaming for an hour and 25 minutes. And I know
for a fact that there's, let's say there's 40, almost 4,500 people there. I know at least a
thousand people fell asleep. So I have to wake them up and in probably the best possible way,
I think. Dude, what the fuck? No fucking way. No fucking way. It's free money coming through
right now. The screen. You just have to click the screen. It says it's free money there. No way.
No fucking way. I just got a hundred dollars. I just got $200. You gotta be kidding me. Welcome
back. What's this? What's this message today? Hey, Jeremiah, I just had a weird dream that like you
screaming in the mic about free money and stuff. That's weird. Welcome back though. If you were
sleeping. That's weird. Free? Like free? What do you mean free money? That's odd. I hope you had a
good nap, I guess. So what do we got? Let's go fight boss. 40 billion, 13 billion. What do you
got for attack? 1.3 billion. Defense, 2 billion. This ain't gonna work out. We're gonna go to
adventure mode. What do I got for my inventory? Not gonna work out. I need more gold. How much
gold do I have? That's not gonna work out either. Time to rebirth. I need something. There's nothing
in this. There is nothing in this container. Hello? Nobody in there. I need to refill that.
Wait. Also drop 4G's merge and boost tutorial cube. All right. So if I put these together,
what happens? Uh oh. That was a mistake. All right. Let's go. Sewers. More loot. More idle
equipment. You've ruined it. Reset. I can rebirth in like 15 minutes. Increases the cap of all the
skills. That's, that's all right. That's cool. Got 1800 gold. How much gold do I need? Do I need
change the fucking music? Hold on. Hey, we'll put on, how about like peaceful piano music?
I just had a fucking craze. Colonel Sanders was just chasing me in a fucking pool with a chainsaw.
I was trying to swim the fuck away. He was behind me with a fucking chainsaw.
It like stuck it through my chest. Well, did I make it? It's been seven, seven and a half hours.
Did I do it? I did it. No, not quite. Not quite there yet. Not there. Another 45 minutes. He's
wearing lipstick. Why did this happen? This is fucking scary. He's got, he's got white walker eyes.
Hold on a second. It's trying to correct it, is what it's doing. It's on auto and it's correcting
it. It's like patient zero. This is like the part of the movie where they like, I was an actor in
the movie, right? And over the course of maybe like 30, 40 minutes, I'm like, I'm like the funny guy
and the funny character that's in the zombie apocalypse movie. And I start getting sick.
And after, you know, I go, I go get quarantined in like the fucking shop behind us.
And this, I'm the first person to turn. And it's like, oh no, not the funny guy. Not the guy that
was making all those funny jokes during the whole movie. And I'm not funny anymore. Oh no, no, no,
no. Now I'm out for fucking blood. I fucked this whole camera, but I don't even know what to do now.
This fucking music's been playing the whole time in the background.
I don't know. I can't fix it. No, I'm not doing the sleep thing again. I need to fix the webcam.
Hey, there we go. Hi. I look better than I did before. Don't have a wink. How much XP did I get?
Funny. The funny guy. I got my eye on you. I'm noticing how triangular his face is.
I got my eye on you. All right, let's go back to what we were doing.
Uh, have I just been, oh shit, wait, put on Kirby? Sure. What do you want? Kirby's,
we got Kirby's Adventure, Kirby's Epic Yarn, Kirby's Dream Land, Kirby's Epic Yarn,
OST, Kirby's Dream Course, Kirby's Adventure, OST, Kirby's Dream Land 3, Kirby's Dream Land 3, OST,
Kirby's Dream Superstar, Air Ride. There's a lot here. Kirby's Air Ride, OST. Cool. All right.
All right. Cool. Nice. Is this what you want? This is what you wanted, right? All right. Okay.
Uh, gross ring level four. Wait, what is this one? Combine them. Zero out of one, zero to three,
toughness zero to one, health regen. One, three, one. That's good. What about this one? This is
one out of five. That just kind of scared me. One out of five, three, 15, level four,
it's now level nine. Get it up there again. I've got the new cube still on. That's good.
So in this, have I really capped out here? What am I putting my points into?
Really? Only three and a half billion? That's kind of bullshit. Oh, that's a baseline I can
get behind. All right. Okay. What is this? Let's see. No. I think I have to rebirth.
That's, that's meaty. Yeah, that's a meaty base. 20, 18. Let's shoot this one down easily.
Poison. That's all right. No enemies. All right. You got the tutorial cube. Sewers. Big rat.
Kill it. You can't see it. I have to make it smaller. I know you can't see it. I know.
I'm trying. I know. Am I gonna? Bronze lion boss. Die. Got it. 2900 gold. Cracked amulet.
Small mouse. Kill it. How much more gold do I need? Slightly bigger mouse. Move my camera
into the bottom left and flip it. I see what you're saying. Try it. See what it looks.
That like seems strange though. I'm like flipped the wrong way. I'm wearing a rat's t-shirt now.
All right. I'm low money. Need gold. Get loads of gold. I don't know how much I have.
How much gold do I even own? I don't know. I don't fucking know.
Rat wars. Rats wars. Ben Folds. People could be giving a lot of money today.
Every start of the Kirby's soundtrack startles me. I don't know if I want to listen to it anymore.
But Ben Folds gave 10,000 bits. They say Jerma's holding my bits hostage until I give him more
money. Not true. But thank you for the $100. It's 10,000 bits. Jerma, I think you didn't
see my last bits but just want to say that you're my favorite streamer and you've got me through a
lot of rough patches. I can always count on you right in my day. Jerma Heart. Jerma Heart right
back at you. Thank you for the 10,000 bits. That's a shitload of money. Thank you. I'm just kicking
ass in here. I got to beat boss 17 to advance to the next level. Are you kidding me? How am I going
to do that? But thank you. Seriously. Also Lunch Meat just gave five community subs. Thanks a lot
Lunch Meat. Welcome to the stream. Anybody that's just joining us. 2700 gold. All right it's time.
We're rebirthing here. We are rebirthing. Too bald to work. Money Pit. Is this Kingdom Hearts
or what is this? Money Pit. Bottomless pit. Just throw all your heart and gold into it. What?
The pit is hungry. Click it to feed it all your gold. This is a daily spin. So it doesn't actually
spin but it's random. Tier 0 daily spin reward table. 500 arbitrary points. Let's spin the wheel.
100? What? That's it? All right that's it. Wait time until next spin. Check the timer. Your daily
spin is not active yet. Feed me. Do you want to toss all of your hard-earned gold into the pit?
Yeah. You feel slightly more powerful. Plus one to power to be exact. How much money do I have?
Oh. All right. Fight the boss. What have I got? 16 billion. 40 billion. 1.6 billion. 4 billion.
I have. My defense is not terrible but his defense is higher than mine. We have to do something else
here. We gotta. Oh excuse me. No thank you. Put all of the points into here. We need to build this up
a little bit. Oh this is a good OST. Nice choice. Not a bad OST. I have more than twice as much
defense. Well he's got four billion attack so realistically he's got like 695 million wiggle
room there to hurt me and I believe this is you know this you know you know I'm saying like if
this is higher than this then it's gonna hurt you but if the same it leaves itself up. I don't know
how it works. I'm not a mathematician. I just fucking watch the numbers. Is this fighting right
now? I can't tell if we're fighting. That's exactly what I was telling you. See? We're almost perfect.
Nobody can get hurt. I have 1.8 attack. I can't even hurt him. Okay. He has four billion attack
so he can kind of hurt me a little bit. Oh shit. I have lots. Wait a minute. Okay. Um. I got one
of these cubes again and this necklace. Level 9 accessory. 14. So that's one. Uh. Crappy chest
plate. Three toughness. That's better than this. I'm gonna hold on to that though. What about these
crappy leggings? Three out of three. One out of one. All right. Um. Maybe I should keep these?
What can I my cube hold? More power. I'm at max power now and max health. What about toughness?
All right. I'm at four to seven. What about special? I can do this three more times. I want
the noob cube to be completely upgraded. Merge the cube. Last time I did that everybody laughed
at me. I got laughed completely out of town here. Is that worth it? Okay. Level 9 chest. I think
that's good for now. 20 billion health. 40 billion. I still need more attack. Attack tube. I'm never
gonna get there. Energy power. Let's do this one. 0.1. That was not even worth it I don't think.
Wait did I? It instantly went up. That was a mistake. Okay. Inventory is four out of four
power. It's already better. And it's level four. So I am now able to move on but I can't because I
have to beat the 17th boss here. I'm only boss nine. This is boss number nine. Why does you
already have a bathroom cam? Just in case. I don't know. I don't want to get up. Fight. Wait a minute.
I can kill it. That means I can nuke it right? See you later. No. I can't. Nope. I have to fight it.
We have to watch this go down. Nuke is only when you can instantly win. I see. What are you guys
what are you guys linking images for? What's on these images? So I think it's something that's
gonna embarrass me. No it's just you traced my face. I know exactly what you did here. Actually
how did you how did you do this? Did you just take a screenshot and then trace it? I don't even know
what the fuck it is. Where did it just go? Save it. Save the desktop. It's there. What the fuck?
I have so much dog shit on my desktop. It's unbelievable. I didn't mean to do that. Bring
it back. You're not leaving yet. There it is. Looks pretty good. I look very I look very sad
and tired. Whoa. I won? I didn't even get a chance to see my victory. That was like an hour and a
half in the making. God damn it. What did I get for that? Holy shit. Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
Money. Experience. This guy's got 200 billion HP. 10 versus three. No we have to revert this one.
No way I'm doing this shit. Uh-uh. Wait whoa whoa whoa whoa. Money pit. Throw it in there. Whatever.
Oh I can't. I have to wait an hour and a half. I have to wait two hours to do this.
Buy energy speed. You're killing me. I already have been. I got two points for energy speed.
What song is this? I feel like I'm going crazy not remembering this. This is from curvy's air ride
uh ost and I don't know what the name of the song is but it's the full soundtrack
just in the background while we just hang out and fucking play the game that everybody was
very happy and excited to play. I was. All right let's do uh I got three. I'll do it again. Fine.
Energy speed. Cool. All right back to the uh this is a 40 minute rebirth time. What do you think?
2,500. This is how the number that we have just exponentially increased.
Let's do it. Boom. Inventory. Let's let's make this. This is a mess.
Toughness. I can still do a few more toughness in here. What's my what are my stats out here?
Plus 15 plus 12. Special energy bonus. Cracked amulet is at 14. I'm gonna have to start putting
points into these too aren't I? 4 to 20. 4 to 21. This stick is just kind of taking up space.
The mouse is broken. What do you mean? I can still see it. What's my uh energy cap now?
Already at five million. Fight boss. It took one second. Every time you rebirth the longer
you do it and the more you just you get exponentially more. I can just click it. Oh he killed me.
Right. Oops. All right that's fine. I'm in the millions now. Dubai. Four million. Nothing. 11
million. Nothing. 65 million HP. Mouse. You're out. Large rat. 325 million HP. Let's keep let's
keep that going up. 28 million. Now I know why that person said get the speed man. That's what
I'm going for it. I'll try to get a couple. I should do just one. Two. Four. Six. Eight. Ten.
Twelve. Four. Six. Eight. Twenty. I guess it is the same. Drugs are bad. What are you implying
that I'm on drugs? Why are you implying I'm on drugs? All right. How much attack? Oh you keep.
See you later. What do you got for defense? 87 million. You're dead. 437 million defense.
He killed me. All right. I'm dead. Don't matter. I'll just restart. Cap that out. I want more
defense. I want one billion defense and it's all going into idle attack. The adventure zone. I will
in just a second. All right. Almost there. Let's see what we got now. One billion. Your attack. I
need your. I need to have a little bit higher defense than this. We are. We're already at the
wall. Fuck. We are already at the wall already. Adventure. All right. Let's go back to the sewers
and just farm. Farm money. Has it been 30? 40? I'm sucked in. Pretty good Beetlejuice song. Not bad.
Play the Beetlejuice OST. I don't think anybody wants to hear that. There it is. All right. He's
out. What was the last thing that I got to? Wasn't the goblin. This is 40 billion. I need some time
here. Need HP and need attack. What's my cap right now? Probably 800. 1,045 energy is what I can have.
Sounds pretty good to me. What I got to experience. 2 EXP. Energy speed. Keep going. Money pit. 47
minutes. Don't say it again. All right. I already made that joke. I think I've done that joke twice.
All right. Kirby's Air Ride was pretty cool, but let's do another one. How about do WarioWare?
That's pretty good. I like that one. Wario Wario WarioWare OST. Smooth moves. Yeah. That's the one.
That's track one. Here comes track two. I'm not sure why there's a track specifically for him
doing the voice line. All right. What do we got? 12 billion? 5 billion. I think I can do it now.
Yeah. This is the intro. This is a classic game. All right. Here comes the wall. 20 billion. 10
billion. I can get over that, but I need this to be higher. Holy shit. I need more. This is hurting
my eyes looking at this. I can't look at this for more than five seconds. It actually hurts my head.
Oh shit. More of this. Helmet. Just drag the helmets together and then on top. Level 19 head.
Ring. I'm going to keep just combining the rings until they're better. I think I'm going to start
boosting up. Okay. Here we go. I'm going to do power on sword. Is there a special on the sword?
There's not. Energy speed. Oh, there's special up here. 2% more energy speed. I'm all right with that.
All right. 11 billion attack. I can now hurt him, but he's doing way more to me. I think I'm just
going to dump every point into one thing. Yeah. To do auto merge, I have to do the unlock. There's an
unlock I have to actually do. It's just something for me to do at this point. Money pit. 44 minutes.
That's counting slower. That's counting slower now. All right. 11 idle. Let's just put it up here.
16 billion. Look, that's going up quick though. You know what? No. All of it goes in here. Put
every single thing in here. I want that. I want to see this number jump. There we go. All right.
I'm almost going to be doing double what you have in defense. You lied about hot lava.
Not necessarily. I got addicted to this game. He just put on this OST. Give it some time.
Yeah. I just put it on. The WarioWare for the Wii had a great soundtrack. So yeah, this will be on
for a little while. That's fine. All right. Almost going to be two times, three times what he has.
I haven't had a single clue what's going on this whole time. Let me fill you in.
Up here, you have a bar that is constantly producing energy. When you get energy,
you can use your energy. It's one point. See over here. One point will generate.
I don't know how it works either. It generates a level. One point of energy makes a level,
which increases this bar to increase your HP and your attack. And so now I'm using, I have 1045
energy. I'm using all of it right now to do like to supercharge this. And now that I've done 5,000
of these, I can do this now, which is just a better idea because this gives you more points
per energy level. And then once you get to a certain, I have a thousand points in here.
This is the defense section. So right now I don't have any, I don't have any,
the mouse is out of sync. That is weird. Why is that happening?
Okay. Right now my mouse is down in the lower lower right hand side of the screen.
That's weird. I don't know why it's doing that. Jeremy, help my dog. It'll be all right. All
right. So I'm just in the time that we've been talking, just in the time that we've been hanging
out here, I've gotten 37 billion. This is the one. So then you take what you have done. You
take the upgrades that you've done to your counting mechanism and you go over to the
fighting screen. And then you, I've built up enough attack and HP where I now I'm stronger
than this orc. And then you hit the fight button. And as you see, I call, I need to explain it better.
I have 40 billion. Let's just say, I'm going to say round numbers. I have 40 attack. He has 10
defense. Therefore I'm doing 30 attack to this orc per quadra second. Okay. That's how it works.
I have seven defense and he has 20 offense. I am taking 14 worth of points per quadra second
of damage. That's what you, that's how it works. So I'm trying to kill him faster than he can kill
me. He can still kill me faster. I'm going to hold on to my points. My inventory is getting,
okay. I can, it's the music's fucking me up because I feel like I want to press start.
Like I feel like I'm just press start already. Get, move on to the next menu.
Toughness is okay. I, by the way, if you choose, I, I, if you combine items, for instance, these
chest plates, they, do you see the number here? Um, when you, when you combine these, for instance,
when I drag this over here, the smelly chest, whatever it's called, it's splattered with some
smelly. Yes. So you can combine them. I just did. And now this makes it a little bit better.
Yeah. Why is this doing that? I'm so confused. I need power. Toughness. Yeah. I can do one more
because I just upgraded the cube. That's it. This is maxed out. Time to move on to other products.
Let's put it in here. Put the hat in. Power up the sword. All right. That's, that's all adventure.
That's all I can do. I need to get this boss 17. Go. Got it. Got it. All right. Now I need to do
this. I need way, I need to cap this out. We need more of this beat boss 10. This is pushing
your way through. You encounter a small clearing in the forest to try to dash through, but barely
make it halfway before rotting corpses begin clawing their way out of the earth. One week
shuffling zombie inches towards you might as well have some fun. Okay. He's got a hundred billion
attack. This one ain't going to go so well. Money pit 38 minutes. This is counting slow.
I'm going to adventure. I need to get to 17. That ain't going to happen. It's been a week.
It's wake up. It's been a week. I got to refill that. I wanted a coffee. Trying to Google this
game. Trying to Google this name. Uh, it's on steam. It's N G U space idle. Get it on steam
six out of 22 more special weight. No, that's it. No, I can do it. Ooh, I finally got boots.
Now I'm in, I'm in full leather Minecraft gear. Still have a wooden sword though. That's not good.
This has to be trashed. So do these get these things out of here. Should I? Yeah. What am I?
I don't need these 34 accessory. Let's see power zero. It's all zero. All right. 50 billion attack
almost there. I can almost hurt this guy. My defense needs to be much better. I have six
points. All right. Why have I not been saving for this plus 10,000, 10,000. I thought it was 10.
Oh my goodness. That opens up everything that makes it. Oh my God. All right. But it's too hard.
Okay. Six. I need to get that higher 50 billion attack. Almost. What do you get for defense?
It needs to be higher. It needs to be much higher. All right. Pull this back. We're going to do 50,
50 split here. I got a thousand. We're going to do a thousand, 500, 500, 45. Let it work.
Well, I do a Fortnite dance to Mario. Where's OST? Just kidding. What happened to the lava game?
It's still available. What did the dev say? You can't buy the energy cap upgrades until
you max out energy from rebirthing. Oh shit. I like that. I have to fill this before I lose
my mind. You know, the tooth prick, that whole joke with the convention. The reason why that
existed guys is because if I don't have something in my hands or in my mouth or something to hold,
I go nuts. It's like, it like pacifies me. Otherwise I'd be like, I need it. You're having
a fidget helps me too. I fidget a lot. That's why I'm like, I'm, you know what it is? I have,
I have like NPC coded random actions that I just pull out for no reason. You know,
when you go up to an NPC and like GTA and they're drinking out of a cup and it's empty and you're
like, oh my God, what the fuck is that guy doing? You are watching somebody do that right now.
This has been empty for an hour. I've got like GTA pedestrian wired brain up here.
Go get a refill. I can't right now. I'm too busy. All right. Let's do some power. No, in the sword.
I'm getting powerful this way. Toughness. You got it. What do we got? All right. Uh, money pit.
33 minutes. I think it's ready. What do I got? 60 to 54, 42 to 100. Not quite max HP too much.
No, I can't, I can't do it. Eight experience. I'm going to do energy power. I need 15 because
that just makes everything better. I can do another rebirth coming up. What do I need? I need defense.
I have enough attack to kill it. Training. Pull out of this. Put it all in defense. I just need
more defense. Way more. 745, 300. Sounds good. What's the name of the game? I keep winning in
Wario Kart and it's freaking me out. What color should I do? Just put it in the title. The title
of the stream. His numbers go up. He's fuming. What does stream name stand for? I don't know.
Fight boss. All right. Here we go. All right. Why are you where it's sick?
This OST has a lot of tracks that are sort of just you completed a mini game and we're going
to load a whole new soundtrack for it. Unreal tournament OST. Now that's too intense for me
right now. All right. 60, 60 billion defense. We're almost ready. Katamari. Everybody loves
Katamari. It always pops up during one of these streams. How are you guys doing today? You guys
doing good? How are things? Things going good? No? Yeah? Yeah? Katamari OST. This is Katamari
forever OST. I mean they're all good. You can kind of just pick whatever one you want. A little
louder. This is the wrong one. It's the wrong one. All right. I need to do training here. We've got
defenses. Good. It's time to only put it in the super strength one and I'm looking for enough
attack. I'm looking for about a hundred. Because if I get a hundred billion attack that I can kill
it and then we can rebirth. I might just rebirth now. Ten experience. Let's do, oh what a mess.
Okay this orange is power. That's very important to know. I can do this in here. Special is still
one more that can go in the cube and that is energy speed. Good. Special is, hold on, sword.
Let's just combine them all. This is level 19 now. Cube. Into the cube. Right? Yeah. Cube into
the cube. Special into the cube. Cube into the cube. Cube into the cube. Necklace onto the necklace.
Boots onto the boots. I can do power in there again. All right. I'm looking pretty good.
Shit. Cube into the cube. Cube into the cube. Yeah. This is a new thing. We unlock it.
Break in the lake. I need more. What's rebirth gonna look like here? That's another huge increase.
I love that there's a time factor as well to make sure you don't just spam it over and over again.
I'm gonna wait till this gets to like 25,000. I think that's a good idea. If I were to say.
Exponential increasing. I should rebirth. That number is huge. Oh yeah. I want to kill this guy
first. I'm so close to being able to take this guy out. In fact I might be able to do it now.
850. 60 to 100. It's gonna be close. He's winning. Stop. Stop. Stop. Not playing unsadistic.
What a great game. I should play this. I already did. I should play all of them.
Didn't I play two of them? I did. I should play the other ones. I'll do that next week.
I'll play the other one. I'm gonna play like two or three or something. I'll do it next week.
These games are phenomenal. Played reroll. Yeah, I did rerolled a few months ago actually, right?
All right. This is it. Here we go. Come on. This is why we were sitting here for so long.
Bring him down. Six. Six. Five. Five. Come on. Do it. Four. Bring him down to four.
And then I rebirth. It's gonna do it. It's gonna do it. It's gonna do it. I'm almost ahead of him.
Stick with it. Yes. Got it. Oh, and look at that rebirth. I wanted 25,000. We beat that boss.
Sword. Sword up to 40k. Look at that. This guy's at five trillion health. Wait, I can do
toughness and... Yeah, I can do it all in the cube. Just make that cube insane.
This is boss 12. I'm... But look at all these points. Am I streaming tomorrow? Yeah,
I'm streaming tomorrow. I was thinking about doing the community event tomorrow. Thinking
about it. I was gonna... After the stream today, I was gonna go in and pull stuff out and see if
there's enough there. If there's not enough for the community night tomorrow, then we're gonna play
just... We'll play something else. What's the gold for? For right now, it's to throw into a hole.
Maybe eventually I unlock something that's not just a money pit. I don't know. No, I'm not
playing this tomorrow. I just wanted to check this out because I like watching numbers go up.
I'm not gonna play this tomorrow. I'm not gonna... This is not gonna be the thing that I do for the
next, like, six days. Just leave it on overnight. I still wanna play Hot Lava. After I rebirth,
like, two or three more times, we're gonna play Hot Lava, and I'm gonna leave this on in the
background. 42,000. It's going up so fast. You're the number one idol gamer on Twitch.
I don't really want to be that person. I don't want to... I don't want to be that.
It's like, one day, I'm just playing this idol game. It's just chatting with some extra steps
and music. Wait for 30 minutes. All right. All right. All right. All right. I'm gonna go refill.
I'm gonna go refill. I'm just leaving it on, like, but there's no reason...
Why do I need to go to the BRB screen? I'm gonna fill this up. I'm not gonna pause this. Now,
you guys are idling. Yeah. He's never gonna play. I'm going to play Hot Lava before the stream ends
tonight. I've only been streaming for, like, two and a half hours. You got plenty of time. Don't
worry. All right. I'll be right back. I'm gonna refill. Just enjoy the music and enjoy the, uh,
number going up for a little while. Wait. Hold on. Before I leave. I need to do this first.
Rebirth. 44,000. 30 minutes. Let's see what happens as we get that time increase.
1,283 energy. How much experience? 13. I'm gonna wait for this. Basic, uh, basic training.
Let's just get... cap that out. Attack. Let's see. Holy shit. Look at each... each point. Each level
is... is, like, 50 million? 40 million? Attack? Wow. Wow. All right. See you in, like, fucking five
minutes. No. I'll be back in, like, two minutes. I'm just gonna get a refill. And then we're gonna
play Hot Lava. I don't wanna... I don't wanna check games out, man. I'm just checking it out.
We're just... I'm just checking it out. I'll be... Let me do one more thing, though. Hold on. One
more thing. Before I leave. I gotta split this up. I gotta wait till it's, like, 150, 150. All right.
What did I miss? What happened? What happened? What did I miss? Did I go up? Did I go up or
down? How much? How many points do I have? 71 billion? Did I miss anything? Perfect. 75. 75.
This is perfect. Money came out of the screen. I missed the fucking money? I hate that. I hate
when you miss, like, the click on the screen for the free money. They used to do that shit. You
guys remember that? How many of you guys remember the old 19, like, 99, 2000 year pop-up windows
that tried to get you to claim checks that didn't exist? Click here. You have unclaimed money.
Unclaimed money? Really? And you'd click it. And they would just fucking steal all your identity.
You could... Do you remember the pop-ups would just launch at the screen? There was no pop-up
blockers. There was no ad block. You got bombarded. You would have a window open here,
right in front of you. And then behind that window, after one session of browsing,
there would be 40 to 50 other windows that you didn't know were open. And yes, somebody just said
it. A bunch of them were porn ads. They just, just, no shame at all. Just porn. They would
just have open. Can you imagine browsing fucking the internet? It'd be, uh, mail and rebate, mail
and rebate, mail and rebate. Claim your check. Claim your money. You have free money. Money,
money, money. Porn, porn, porn, porn. That naked person on the screen. Two naked people on the
screen. Holy shit. Okay. How did anybody even browse back then? I don't even remember. I don't have a
memory of... I think it was just like normal. And you sat there going like this at the end of your
browsing session. X, X, X, X, X, X, X, X, X, X, X, X, X, X. And they'd play sound too. So it would be
like, yip, up, zip, yip, kip, hup, kip, hup, kip, hup, hup, hup, hup, hup, hup. They were
fucking horrible. What do I got? 145 billion. Let's do it. Should I just nuke? No, I don't want to.
I don't like nuke. I like being able to see my progress. Goblin. Instantly. Orc. Done. Slow zombie.
Remember how long and painful this was? Oh fuck, I have a ton of idle energy.
There we go. Computers were just RuneScape machines. RuneScape machines. Faster. I'm
trying to go faster. No, here's the wall. Okay. Experience. 19. We're going to do energy power
here. Take a look up here. We got 237 billion. Approves the effectiveness of your allocated
energy. This means faster progress on features while using less energy. Energy cap. I don't have...
I think I have to hit... Once you have 100,000 max energy. I can't do it yet.
Yeah, I can't do it yet. I need 100,000. Yeah, I can't do it. Play the deadly premonition OST.
Didn't I play deadly premonition for like an hour? There's something in there now.
It freaks me out for a second. Base energy cap. So, should I just wait? I'm just gonna wait.
Can I kill you yet? Almost. What have I got? Basic training. More. In fact, no, no, no, no.
Get it all in here. All 1200. Just until this gets to 5k. You didn't think this was gonna be the most
fucking upbeat stream you've seen in a week. We're just bopping. What a cool streamer. I know the
joke that if this is your first stream of mine, then you're gonna be like every stream. We just...
I don't know. And you'll be fine. Hi, this is my first stream. What's up? Welcome to the channel.
I was voted fourth most energetic Twitch streamer with under 500,000 followers.
Why did you win that? Because I did. It's a pity award. It's not a pity award.
It's an award. Weird flex, but okay. No, the weird part about that weird flex is it's a fake
weird flex. Yeah, I was voted like 16th most energetic streamer on Twitch with
followers between 200 and 51,000 and 251,000 and 14. I was voted number 14 on that list.
Pretty good if you ask me. What? Why am I lying? I have a very important question for everybody
watching right now. Important. When does a lie become a lie? Because if you say something that's
not true and immediately it's corrected, is that a lie? I think a lie has to sit as if it were fact
for at least one day. I think that's not a lie because I'm not trying to push it off as real.
What is it 15 minutes? If I tell you that hey I won an award at TwitchCon for top 40
funny faces and I didn't correct it and like four days went by, that's a lie. But if I told you,
I bet you, no that's a bet. If I told you that I won that award and then 10 seconds later I said
that's not real it's a fucking joke. When is a lie a joke and when is a joke a lie?
No, a lie has to sit for 24 hours before it's a lie. I will stand by that. Untruth. Wait,
hold on. I'm facing an ent. You haul ass and make it past the clearing managing to shake off most
of those fast charging type zombies. After putting some more distance between you and them,
you take a breather against a tree until it starts moving under you. God damn it.
Yeah, I only lie for 23 hours at a time. I'm trying to think, have I ever told you guys like
a true lie? Like a real one? One that sat for 24 hours that was me lying to you about something.
You lied about Sam and Max. I didn't lie about Sam and Max. I played season three and didn't like
it. I played something and didn't like it. That's a lie. You lied about Ace Attorney. Now I told you
that I played Ace Attorney for a little bit off stream and I didn't think it was going to be a
stream I wanted to stream. A game I wanted to stream. That's not a lie. That's me coming to
a conclusion and I told you that. You lied about Wailord. What'd you say? What did you say? I heard
you. What are you saying? I still haven't watched that by the way. You took more than 24 hours to
correct it. Wait, I gotta do stuff. Oh, fuck. I didn't take more than 24 hours to correct that.
Wait, this is power. Max power. I'm gonna go over my inventory here and see what's better. Okay,
three. This is good. Three. This accessory's not going anywhere. It's the noob cube. I'm not
taking it off. Money. Eight minutes. Where's my gold? Oh, fuck. It's because I reset. All right,
hold on. Training here. I need to do this. Hold this out. We gotta get this 5,000 as fast as
possible. You lied about Monster Rancher 4. Did I though? Did I lie about Monster Rancher 4?
Somebody just gave five community subs thanks to whoever did that. That was anonymous. Thanks to
the five community subs. Just anonymous. Thanks a lot whoever you are. You lied about the definition
of lying. What are you guys on about? What an incredible soundtrack to this video game.
I wanted to stop playing this game an hour ago and move on to hot lava, but I can't because I
have to see. I need to know. We'll do a long one tonight. How is that a lie? No, a lie is not a
lie until it is something that you specifically are trying to push forward as a truth that sits
in everybody's bellies for 24 hours. What's this game called? It's called. Look it up. It's on
Steam. It's a lie. It's only a lie if you believe it. What? No, a lie. A lie is something that,
a statement that you are making to try to push forward as a real thing or a truth that you want
people to think is real that sits in their bellies for 24 hours and you continue to try to push the
fact that it is real when it never was in the first place. Now I make mistakes, okay? Ace Attorney,
me saying I was going to play Ace Attorney was a mistake. That's not a lie. It's a mistake.
I make mistakes. I don't lie. All right, I'm almost there. I just want to play hot lava,
but I fucking can't. I cannot. I can't do it. That means I have to hit the X here, but like I can't.
My body won't do it. 25 trillion defense. All right, getting there. What do I got for rebirth here?
150,000. I need 15 more minutes and that doubles. Switch monitors. I can't do that.
No, I can't do that. No, I cannot. I can't. Watch the video of lies compiled. Nobody's made it.
I said to make that a long time ago and nobody made it. I was like, if you want to call me out,
I want a Jerma has lied video and a compilation of everything I've ever said that was a lie.
I made that challenge and what do you know? I haven't seen it yet. There are too many.
It's still uploading. It's very long. Okay. What even is this game?
It's an ever-growing video. Did you ever do that Stardew co-op stream? No, because Stardew...
All right, I have to play. I have to focus and get busy.
22 experience. Almost getting close to 40. Go to my inventory. I'm not even on an adventure.
Hurry them up. Wait, I'm going to say two. Two versus 1.3. Two versus... I need more defense.
Let's get it up. Boys and girls, I need defense. Get it up. Come on. I need 10,000 in this to this.
Never going to happen. Changing the subject. What do you mean? Make sure to unlock popping gamer.
I already was gotten by that one, so you're not going to get me again. What track is this?
I don't know. It's just the whole two and a half hour long OST.
You lied about peeking your mic. I peeked my mic yesterday by screaming about a flashbang.
Is it actually sick music? Yes, it is. Two minutes until I can throw money in there.
All right, I'm going for it. Not going to be fast enough, but I need it. No, it's not going to happen.
Stop. I need a little more attack. All right, enough. A little more attack. Cap it. Let's go.
Just enough to give myself the edge here. You said two or three more rebirths before the
lava game. I did one. Upcoming here is two, and then after that will be three. Bingo. What do we
got? 179,000. Oh, and in 10 minutes, that's doubles. Double. What's it going to be at? 181.
Boom. See you later. Giant. Entering this forest is feeling more and more like a bad idea. Even
the air is starting to taste sort of odd, like copper and iron. You strained to keep an eye on
the forest path with the haze thickening around you. You managed to keep on the path, but somehow
also managed to bump right into a giant in front of you. Enjoy the fight. Who's Bob? He's got 12
trillion attacks. That ain't going to work out. 375,000. We're just going to last another 10
minutes. You lied about Flora's Lava. You haven't waited 24 hours yet. You haven't waited, because
in like an hour, that's not going to be a lie. Oh, this is hot. I like this one. This is a hot
track. Little did you guys think that fucking idle number counting stream is going to be the most
lit stream you've been at all day. It's not a lie. It hasn't been 24 hours yet. You can go to like
a music stream in about 45 minutes and it's not a lie. Please don't say lit. Say whatever I want.
Lit is as bad as epic. I know epic is a whole nother tier. I think you can still say lit
ironically as a joke and it's okay. Epic is like completely out of completely out of bounds now.
Epic is in a category on its own. All right, one more rebirth and I'm going to play hot lava
and I'm going to keep this running in the background and we're going to check in on it
every now and then. Seven and a half minutes countdown until floor is lava. Chat complaining
about youth culture. You guys are the real boomers, but you guys are youth culture.
I can see in my my analytics. You guys are youth culture. This is you.
Not me anymore. I bet you still have cookie clicker running. I'm out of that category now
as of my 34th birthday. Everyone here is in their 30s. What are you talking about?
I, you know, I would assume there's probably a few 30 year olds here. How many people are here? Like
4,400, 4,400 people. Maybe 2,500 30 year olds. All right, six minutes until I could rebirth and
this is getting minimized and opening hot lava and I can stop getting just the outpour of fucking
hate mail that's coming in through my PO box over here. The stack this high of letters telling me to
change game. They just keep coming in using letters. Do not stop playing this game. I'm
not going to stop playing this game. Just because I'm moving on to another game doesn't mean that
this game stops because I've got news for you. Once I'm done playing, you don't speak during
this track, by the way. I forget what I was going to say. I don't remember what it was. It was
something important. Oh yeah, the game's going to be playing in the background while we play hot lava
and then everyone that wants to see a different game today will do that and then we're coming
back to this. This game might get closed. Still can't even fight this guy. What we got? Rebirth. We
have four minutes. We're going to hit a million. One million. One million. One million. Money pit.
Not yet. After I killed the giant. No. This is a bitcoin mining scam. This is a
idle game that has a very passionate developer who has made tons of content in here. How dare you
say something that much of a lie in 23 hours and 59 minutes? I demand an apology.
Here comes a call out post. I'm never going to be able to do this. Hold on. Here it comes.
And then after this, I just want to see what a million number points looks like. Why am I
holding this? Have I showed you the book of our lord? Sir, if you have just one moment.
Two minutes. Two minutes until we can play another game. Read the fucking book. This
webcam is mirrored. Yeah, because if I wasn't mirrored I'd be looking over this way. No,
I have to point the wrong way. So I have to point this way because it's mirrored. I'd be looking
this way and I'd be looking at the video game screen with my board game. Look at all these
things to unlock. All right. I'm going to take a look. Power. One, two, three. Money pit. Not yet.
Here we go. This is going to be it. One minute. He's stalling. There's a countdown on the screen.
It's not a stall. There's a 30, I have to burn 30 seconds here. The game is a stall.
All right. Okay. Now I see what you're doing with this one. All right.
Oh, one million coming up. One fucking million. Biggest number you've ever seen. I've ever seen
my whole life. Okay. Now I just want to, I just want to know what it looks like. Somebody right
now is in their chair just going like, get out of this fucking game. And I'm just sitting there
going, hey, I like this one. So you're like strapped to the chair. Get me out of this chair.
I got this like tape and God, why do you look like Leon from Resident Evil? Cause I was the
fucking face map for that game. All right. But we, I don't want to turn the music. This music is,
I don't want to, I don't want to turn the music off. We can't wait, wait until the whole OST
is done. In two hours. Wait till the OST is done in two hours and we'll play hot lava. That's a good
enough, that's a good compromise. I think it's all about compromise. Kidding. But we do have to turn
the music off. But I, hold on. Important. Let me get, let me clean this up first and then I'm
going to let it run in the background while I jump from device to device and try to not land on the
ground. Toughness. Special. Special. Toughness. Special. Toughness. Look, 27 points. Here comes
the rebirth at 1.1 million. Do it. Go. I just want to see what it looks like. I forgot about the money.
You have been immensely distracting me. It's okay. So I just need to know. Where's the cap now?
1500 energy points. Nice. All right. I just want to see. How much is one point is worth? Two billion,
three billion, four billion. We're already at billions? Holy shit. My head hurts. Take a couple
aspirin. Or like acetaminophen. If you're sensitive to aspirin, take acetaminophen.
Sensitive to that. Maybe grab like an aspirin or something. And take a break off the computer.
You know, just take a break from the computer. If you're on the computer for too long,
it irritates your skin. You know what I mean? You have to put on sunscreen. See what the problem I
think is, is your screen brightness is so high, you're not wearing sunscreen. Like, come on.
All right. Let's just go. I want to just clip through these. One, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, ten. Without even doing anything. I just want to see. Trillion. Bring
it down. This guy was a pain in the ass. What about if my nose hurts? Should I take a break
from breathing? You should breathe. Why am I not doing well? I just want to see. Uh oh. Right now.
Like, right now. Right now. When I just didn't go immediately to hot lava. The person that was
mad that I was still here. Like, the alarm sounded in their room. Hold on. It's like, wait, he's
still, he's still in the game. What's he still doing in the game? Why is he still in here?
What are you doing in here? Okay. So what happened there? Um, I went a little too hard.
I went, I went a little too hard. I kind of like made myself a little dizzy. I went too hard. I
was like bracing and pushing blood into my head. And what the fuck was that? He pooped his pants.
That would be a real alarm that I would have to leave if that happened. Hold on. I'm good.
Only 295 rebirth points? What? Oh, I'm supposed to leave. Right. I'm supposed to leave. All right.
Let me just get, I need to get to my cap. Okay. That's important. Let me get to the cap. Let me,
I just, let me get to the cap. I just need to get to the cap. Calm down. Turn it off. Don't worry.
You're gonna get your lava video game. Oh fuck. Adventure. Right. Idle it. I'm, I'm going, I'm good.
In the sewers. I want lava. I want lava. I want lava. You'll get it. Why do I have an artifacting
on my webcam? Why does my webcam look, it's like underwater. That's weird. Lava video game now.
Lava video game now. Lava video game now. Just wait. I need to get my cap so I can be running
in the background. You know how many rebirth is the continuation multipliers are going to exist
after like playing the lava game for 20 minutes? We want numbers. Shit. Hold on. All right. I got
to, let me, I need to get to 12 or 1500. I am very close to doing a 10k. Let me slow you down a
little. Let me just like even you up. Let's see. We're gonna melt faster than the lava. What can
he say? The guy likes numbers going up. Thank you. To that person. You get it. You get it. I just,
I like it. You get it. Tree dead. Giant. Let me just be the giant and we'll go and I'm actually
going to minimize it. You can, you watch me. I'm going to click the minimize and I'm going to open
hot lava. I'm going to laugh my ass off if hot lava is a bad game. At least it's a game. What's
this then? You can make a game out of anything. Guys, I could make a game out of sit like 10 or
do you go to like preschool? You can make, who can count to 10 the fastest?
That's a game. I'm going to throw this cup in the air and catch it. I'm going to make up a game
called throw the cup in the air and catch the cup. I just played a game. I mean, you can make a game
than anything. How about leak all photos? That's a game. Leak all photos, personal photos to my
Twitter. I mean, that's a game. Wait. All right. We're almost there. I got it. I'm eating spit.
There we go. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, more of this. I just got to get to a point where I can
beat it. All right. Cap that up. All right. We are going. What? I have to beat the giant. The giant
is boss 14. Thank you. Quack. Thank you. Quack up for the five community subs. Thank you. Quack.
We're good. But thank you. Quack. I have to beat this guy. Just give me a minute. Rebirth 20,000.
Not bad. Not good. Not great. Pull this down. More into here. Just dump every point. I'm at
almost the cap. 15, 15. What does he have for? Oh, my inventory. Fuck. Cubes. How many cubes
are there? How many times can I merge the cube? 69 accessory. LOL. Oh, huh. What's this at? 64,
69. Yeah. This is special. I mean, energy speed is important. 35. I have 16. His defense is
not good. I just need to have some more. Um, I have to have more defense. That'll help. Equip
the poop. If I hear the word poop one more time, I am going to be very, very, very angry. Here it
comes. Now we're all going to write it. Right? That's, that's the joke, right? Streamer says the
thing. Don't do this. Oh, if I hear that again. You guys do this one more time and then everybody
does it. You won't be hearing anything because the chat is audio. Is it not audio? Here we go. Uh,
I should be able to do it now. Come on. Drain, drain, drain, drain, drain, drain, drain, drain.
10, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5. Almost there. Get this up. All right. I'm at the cap. We're almost going to
minimize this game. We're going to minimize this and right behind it is going to be Doki Doki Literature
Club. Look at this shit eating grid. Done. Okay. I got it. Now all we have to do is allocate our
points correctly. I have 1550. I want like, fuck, 700, 800 here. I want like 800, 750 here. Good.
We're going to let this run in the background. I'm going to kill this guy. He's now going to be dead.
The giant has been vanquished. Rat of unusual size is the next boss. Okay. How many rebirth
points did that get me? Not very many, but enough. Now we wait. We sit. I clean up my inventory
and then we upgrade everything. This is at full toughness. Not anymore. Now I can do another one.
Go into here. All right. Let it run in the background. See, I'm a man of my word. We're
going to play hot lava. All right. Hold on. Just give me one sec. I need to like not capture this.
Okay. It might be loud. I'm just going to warn you because I can't turn it off right now.
And this music is also going to be turned off as well because there's music in hot lava.
I have to change the name of the title of the game to hot lava. Wait, this is on steam. Can I
not, can I run two games on steam at the same time? Wait, you can. I thought, wait, can you,
I thought maybe back. Let's try. See what happens. It's going to be loud. It's going to be loud. It's
going to be loud. Hold on. I'll turn it off. Right. Okay. Oh fuck. I'm sorry. There. Should I even move
the camera? Whatever. I'm already in that same spot. All right. Let's go. This is hot lava. It's
a game about parkouring. This just looks like I'm like a stock trader and I'm so obsessed with
keeping up to date on like the tickers and the, and the ups and downs that I have to have it on
the screen. I can't miss anything. I am a forex trader. What if it goes down by 0.2 cents and I
don't fucking sell it. All right. Let's do it. You have no friends. Gym class. I don't know how any
of this works. I can't hear. All right. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I got to hold on. I got to turn
the, uh, that, uh, okay. That's all right. That's not terrible. No, no, no, no, no. Don't discard.
Okay. Uh, how do I, okay. So WASD. Am I crouching? How many milliseconds? Milliseconds?
Somebody just got killed. What do you mean somebody got killed? There's no lava yet.
Is there a sprint? No. Uh, what do I need to do? Is this teaching me how to play? I think this is
a, all right. Trampoline trouble. Oh, it's like Mario. It's like Super Mario when you
go through the painting. All right. What's this one? Gym Jam. Make your way to the gym and we'll
run through some basics of the game. All right. Let's go. All right. Monka S. How do I play?
Don't touch the lava. Who are you? Wait, this is a multiplayer game.
Press action to skip. I went into the lava. There are people in this game.
Swing like Indy. I know you wanna. Jump to grab ropes and pipes. All right. That's cool.
What's next? That person, that person's hacking. Oh, there's a pipe. Crouch or jump to get off of
a pipe. Hold forward when jumping to launch forward. Easy. I still have, wait what? Swing
on the bars. Swing with forward and back. So I can go like this. Jump at the correct time
on the trampolines to go hot. When you jump on the, jump on the trampoline at the correct time.
What do you mean the correct time? Oh, I see. Like you just have to jump on it like that and like
that. Moss. Putty is sticky. Use it to jump off walls. Oh, keep looking straight ahead to keep
your momentum so it's like a surf. Oh, all right. That's cool. You can slide a short distance when
stuck to a wall. Sick. How are these people in my game? Oh, is this a checkpoint or something?
They're just ghosts. What do you mean ghosts? Should I go this way? Whoa, the hell? I got the
golden pin. I got the golden pin. I found a golden pin. So this is a slider. Oh shit. Okay. Is that
speed? What's on the bottom? Oh, this way. Okay. Got it. I'm going too far. Oh shit. Got it. This
is actually pretty fun. Rank two. New character available. New world available. Playground.
Playful Nya Nya. Watermelon. Nature's candy. Slow clap. Bravo. A martial artist. Must have
one for taking down the bad guys. I did it. He's trying so hard. Me?
Okay. I unlocked trampoline trouble. That's 3.2 million coming up. All right. For a second,
I thought it was still on the screen. Okay. So let's go to the next one over here. He's addicted
to the idle game for today. I'll never play it ever again after today. All right. Trampoline
trouble. This is the first real test. And that was pathetic. That was just pathetic. You can throw it
further than that. Seriously. All right. Does it, does it count if it's not a basketball?
I don't need the achievement. I don't care. Oh, this is count. Time is counting right now.
Up. Up. Well, no, there's no players in here anymore. Turn off the piano. You want to turn
the music off. I don't know where the fuck it is. Where'd it go? That way? Uh, what was that? Oops.
Trampolines. One. Two. Switch the screens. One? Are we talking about switch? One?
What do you mean switch? What are you saying? What are you going to switch my screen?
How is this worse than the number game? I told you. I told you that this was going to happen.
I told you. I can play this game in the corner. I, just give me like 20 minutes.
Just split screen it. Do a, like an old co-op game. Who's playing the piano? I don't know.
Complete it in under a minute. I'll try it. Go. One minute. Gah! What the fuck? Oh, right.
Cross. Second trampoline. Watch this. It's a tricky jump. There it is. Turn it across. Bingo.
Last one. Did it. What? What are you showing me here? It keeps doing the face. This is a new
emotion. My fucking God. I did not look like that. Do I look like this? Holy shit. I'm being like,
sucked into a tube. I'm being sucked into a fucking, like, tunnel. Oh, all you need is to
have like, air sounds. Like, look at this photo and listen to this shit. What the fuck, man?
This is why I don't have face cam turned on. Ever. Ever, ever, ever, ever, ever. And I mean,
ever. Because I just look like a fucking sicko. All right, what was I doing? Right, over here.
I don't know. I looked over at my OBS and I saw that huge yellow and orange explosion. I thought
that was a huge bit thing. I thought that was like 10,000 bits. I was about to thank somebody.
All right. Let me add this. This is the noise that I hear when I see this image.
No! No, please no! I don't want to get sucked up! Thanks for that image. I won. Over here. What
I got for rebirth? 8.6 fucking million. Holy shit, my neck. I, I know, man. I know.
Wait, let me just make sure this is all good. Okay, not good yet. This gives more training.
Okay, spend experience. 44, 10k. Guys, I need to make this bigger so you can see,
because it's important to me. This is important to me. Important to me. Why is it still taking
over my computer? What the fuck are you talking about? I'm about to do 10,000 energy. Just kidding.
What do I do? I have 44 experience. What do I do? Put both games in the corner. No,
I'm going to do base energy. Energy speed. Good. All right, back to what I was doing.
Keep it like that. No, I'm not going to keep it like that. Let's go. I got the sculpted
plastic construction means no mustache wax required item. All right, so that was good.
Missing, where's the music? Okay, save those changes. All right, I want to, I want to,
want to, want to, want to, what do I want to do? Open gym, do whatever you want. Run, jump, swing.
Completed in under two minutes and 10 seconds. Don't die. Let's five star this shit.
No dying. Off the ladder. That's going to happen again. I need to like, I need to control my face.
I know it's going to happen again. Got to be slow. This one. Two minutes, right? I can do that.
That's easy. What the fuck I was grabbing onto it. Last try. What's this game called?
That person just fucked me up. That person just screwed me up. I can do this. Just do it simple.
Two minutes is a long time. This is like the mousepads coming off of the goddamn thing.
I know, get off the screen. My momentum is gone. Skip. I was right here too. God, come on. New
unlock. What are these? What do they do? These unlocks? I'm using a default avatar.
Yeah, I'm not, I don't, I'm not paying for it. Just don't die. I don't just beat it at any time.
Just don't die. Do it slow. Hair is getting in my face. How am I making it worse? Who the fuck is
this? Wait, is that me? I got to beat this motherfucker. Got it. Oh, he got confused over
there. No deaths. No deaths and beat the time. How are we doing on the idle game? That was me.
I got a thumbtack. 120. Now start strafing and bhopping. I think you're asking a little much.
Wait, 43 million. Another 10 minutes here. All right, that's good. Fight the boss. Fight it.
I can't fight it yet. Keep it going. Keep it going. What about inventory? Oh, not good. Hold on. Just
combine everything really quickly. Hat. Hat. Into here. Here. Here. Sword. Boots. Cube.
Toughness. Cube. Ring. Ring. 64. Combine. I got to combine the swords up here. One. Toughness.
No, that's special. I can do this once more. Special is already, is there any more specials
I can do? Yep. The hat. Speed bonus. Looking good. Pants. Cube. Keep it going. We're done. I'm ready.
Prank caller. Is somebody prank calling me? What do you mean? Do a third game in another window.
I can't. No, I'm not going to be able to do that. All right. I got to go over here and
get five stars on this one. I'm pretty good at this game, I think. I don't even know. I don't
know what the... What are the... Don't perform any swings. Don't die and grab the golden pin.
No swinging. What the fuck am I supposed to do that? No swinging? And don't die. My profile picture.
Yeah, my profile picture is an awesome way to hide online. Golden pin is probably the home line.
Because that... That's a default Team Fortress 2 avatar. Oh, I can't land on that. I have to do
like that. Oh, wrong. Just don't swing. Don't swing. Okay. I didn't swing. I'm just trying
to get one of them. No swings. Didn't say anything about bouncing, right? New world school.
Okay, I'm gonna go to my avatar and do some stuff. It's the same image. You just stretch
the sides of my mouth. I have to rebirth this in... When this gets to 60 minutes, I'm doing rebirth.
And then I'm changing over here. We're gonna do the same thing. We just... Now this one will be
in the corner. This one will be bigger. Not now yet. Not yet. Not now. You've got so many emotes.
I don't even know what I would call that. What would you... What would that emote even be called?
Dermatube? Dermassuction? Dermassour? I can't like... I like... Dermassour is the best one.
All right. I'm gonna... It's gonna be there tomorrow. I have 24 hours to do that. All right.
Back to the boss. Okay. I don't... You guys don't even... You don't need to see this shit.
It's taken away. You can see... I want you to go... This was the time. All right. New zone. Wait. I
want to go to the... Menu? Yeah. Toy shelf. Lex Flora. All right. We're doing the seagull head.
Moustache pin. Thumbs down. Blue laser. I don't have it. Watermelon in the background. Sounds good.
Let's go! Playground. Gym class. There's a lot of fucking stuff in this game, huh?
Damn. That's been debunked. Why is the camera mirrored? Because we were playing a different
game before and it had to be mirrored as I was looking in the right spot. All right. New place
unlocked. Where is it? I got five in there. Not gonna get five up there. This way? Which is the
level? Didn't I unlock it down here? There we go. What's the yellow bar at the bottom? I don't know.
I don't know. Balance? Maybe it's balance. Jump timing? Wait. You mean like...
You actually do bunny hop. Well, that's advanced techniques you're not gonna get on this screen.
Sorry. Almost. I think you gotta do that though. From here to here? And then twice?
No. All the way across. Yeah. Okay. I guess that is advanced technique. Wait. Is there something
over here? Did I skip the whole thing? I think I skipped the whole level. Just win. I'm trying.
I'm trying to just win. This used to be a numbers going upstream. Feels bad, man.
Yeah. Fist bump. It's still going on in the background. We'll be checking in on it soon.
God. I missed that game. Grab the golden pin. I can't do that. So a new session over here.
What do I do to get this? Requirement beads. Surfing surfaces. Oh, this one's gonna be held.
Pogo? Pogo stick? So it's not just jumping. There's items too. Wait. Shit. This is weird.
Whoa. That was fun. Easy mode. Celebrate your minor victory. So I'm assuming I need to use that
somewhere else. So this is a sliding level. Use the sliding surfaces. I keep seeing that picture
over here and it's freaking me the fuck out. Oh, fuck. Landing on surf objects from higher
makes you go faster. Right? What? Oh, I'm bunny hopping now. He figured it out, folks.
Damn. That was crazy. Flick away from objects to disconnect and keep your speed.
Flick away from objects. Flick away. Flick it in your hand. There we go.
People are going to get really good at something like this. Wholesale.
Clown shoes. Better put those on immediately. Hole bulb. What else is over here? This opened up.
Oh, what's this? Tiny toy trial. Get to the finish line. Tiny toy. If you're good at something,
they would do it for free. I agree. We're in third person? That was a battery. Oh, I get speed.
Do I have to do this in a certain amount of time? No. The music is playing based on my speed. That
is cool. I need to go faster though. No. I got to start back here. Got it. Was this the don't
starve devs? Really? That's kind of interesting. That's cool. Whoa. Did you see? He went so fast.
Do that again. Do that again every day. Five times a day. All right. Pole ball.
So here are the poles. And how do I? Oh, shit. What? How do I just stand on top?
And he's been drinking. I haven't. I've been drinking coffee. This is why I can't have a
face cam on. I'm too strange. I can feel how strange I'm being. But before I wouldn't care
because I wouldn't be on camera. Becoming odd. I'm unlocking worlds. I'm doing a whole lot of good
here. Cowboy hat. Knapsack. Dragon horns. Chase your sister. I can do that in a minute and 10
seconds. Break through. No deaths either. What the fuck is in my way? Did I do it? I didn't lose to
the ghost. I didn't get it. Minute and 10 seconds. Get the fuck in there. Restart. Trying to go too
fast. Get it! Okay. God damn it. I fucking hit my face. I got a minute and 10. Three seconds to spare.
All right. I got three out of that one. What's chasing my sister down here? All right. This
one's called chase your sister. This is called intermediate difficulty. Okay. Try to catch me.
This one's hard. Go for the hard one. When do we start? I had it too. I was doing pretty well.
Come on. Up. Over. I gotta land these bunny hops better too.
Fucking idiot. I'm so mad. Did he have a meltdown already? No. No meltdowns tonight.
All right. All right. Stop paying attention to the fucking bunny hop. You're never gonna get it.
Fuck it. Just go. She was waiting for me to taunt me. Cry. Cry. Cry. Cry. Cry. Oh, I think he's gonna
fucking cry. What the fuck am I doing? You're like half the bunny hop otherwise you can't make that
jump. Go back to the numbers game. Fuck. It's counting in the background. It's gotta focus
completely. No talking. No streaming. Just do it. Damn it. All right. If I try to bunny hop one more
time I am just just go. Just do it. I'm not going. No. Just do it. It probably on camera looks like
I'm trying to get a piece of popcorn out of my fucking teeth at the movie theater. Like I'm making
fucking jokes. This is the one right here. Flashy. Itchy nose. Inside of my nose is itching like
crazy. I just snorted itching powder. Somebody said who the fuck are you? Oh no. Now I can't lose
because this person's gonna show me up. Look at that. Great head. They fell. They fell. They fell.
Okay. Now I don't feel bad. It was that easy. That was not even that hard. I made that way harder
on myself. He was literally pretending. Did you see the other guy fall? Pretending. The guy in
front of me too. Guy went like this. Okay. What's in here? No. All right. There it is. New session.
New little mini game here. All course marathon. No. I know what this is and I don't want to do it.
Difficulty impossible. This is impossible. How is this impossible? That's why I'm not doing it.
All right. What's up Adidas? What's over here? I see a door hit this way. What's in the what's
in the computer lab? I don't know. I've been down here, right? What's left in here? I think I've
seen everything. Play the numbers. No, no, no. We're just going to keep that one counting.
Maybe one, maybe one little peek. Maybe just a little peek, you know? How are we doing? All
right. I got two quadrillion. Ooh, hold on. Rebirth. 145 fucking million for rebirth. Okay.
Experience. 10 exp. We're going to do energy speed and we're going to do it again. We're going to do
a few times. I'm going to go back over here to fight boss. What do we need? 317 versus 148.
273. I need a little, I mean, I need more defense. This is going to be close, but I need defense.
So I'm going to go into here. Basic training. Pull this out. Put it in here. Just we got to
get a little bit more defense. Money pit. A million bucks is going in the money pit. Dump.
You gain plus a zero one health regen. Okay. I can have two hours from now. I have to come back
and do this again. That looks all right. Fight boss. 15. Let's see what happens.
No, stop, stop, stop. That's not worth it. I have a hundred more than he does. And then my defense
is 160 less. So we need to wait till I get this a little higher, but I got a strong attack now.
What does this one do? Base attack received is 2000 instead of a thousand.
Holy shit. Yeah. Yeah. Let's dump it into that. We can't see. Re. Yes, you can. Look. All right.
Uh, that's all right. I think that's fine. Fight boss. I'll have enough here. 300. I'll have enough.
I might have enough now. No, I'm going down faster. Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop. We'll,
we'll come back to it. Oh, you better believe we're going to be doing it again,
but never again after today. I mean, like actually never again after today. All right.
Oh, to the next world, wherever that is. Can I just put the menu? Okay.
Play the playground. Ooh, this one looks cool. Really? I get to slide on the slide.
You ready to play with the big kids? Don't embarrass me. Okay. Let's go. Ooh, chess.
That one. This one's called recess. It does take like a backpack. Fuck. Okay. You got to
jump around across the person. Got my way. I'm going to wait because me and this guy are on the
exact same. We're doing it at the same time. I'm going to go around the card. Did I not get it?
What the fuck did I not get that? I don't, where was, where was the thing to grab? Oh, I missed it.
It was right here. Whoa. I used to get the cards. How the fuck does this work? Climb it. Climb it.
Down the slide or riot. Down the slide or riot. I can hear you. Holy shit actually is down the slide.
Where's the, over there. I don't even have to go this way. I have to go to the tires. I'm dead.
Fall damage. I died. There we go. I just broke. My neck just like broke. Ah, it's so painful.
Learn to bunny hop or get the fuck out. Right? Card. Learn to scrape or get the fuck out.
What's the purpose of bunny hopping? I think it just keeps your momentum and you just keep
going faster and faster and faster and faster and faster. I think you unlock the big kids slide.
That sounds like fun one. Wait, let me do this. I can get at least one cool thing.
Oh, which one did I unlock? Where'd it go? Big kids slide. I think it's the big kids slide.
Apple. Forget about books. Give me the apple. What the hell is this place over here?
Always pick up an apple. Always. So if I just run on the ground. I'm getting momentum just
by running. Wait a second. Okay. So you have to be running a certain amount of speed first.
Admin, he's doing it sideways. Am I not supposed to be doing that? I always thought bunny hopping
was you have to like move your camera around. Like you have to flick your face around to like
get momentum to like throw yourself. Is that correct? You do. You do. You do. Okay.
I could see how people would get obsessed with this game.
Just trying to get every single damn thing. Where are we even going?
It's like you've become so obsessed with trying to. Oh man. There are probably people that are
going to be just bunny hopping with like times 10 speed and just drape up this thing. It ain't
going to be me. I will never do that. Not down. Slide down slide. Slide down. This really is
just kind of an open playing field. All right. Did you hear that? Somebody had to have heard
that. That was like a snapped neck. Back this way. Sorry. I did the same thing. These levels,
this one was weird. It's like Tony Hawk level. You kind of can just go anywhere you want.
But there's one goal. Checkpoint 15 of 19. Enough momentum. That's fucking hard to do.
Get on the trash can. I can't grab that pole. What? I thought it was a grabble pole. Just play
Tony Hawk instead. I could play Tony Hawk, but I don't think I can right now. I'm currently
playing hot lava. How the fuck do you get up there? Wait a minute. Just start from there.
Bounce bounce bounce. I guess this way. No. What? I gotta see that. I'm getting the Mario music.
The Mario like hurry up music. That's what I just landed on. Numbers go up waiting room. Yeah. Cool
stream. Can I have your Xbox? Like you mean you actually physically want my Xbox? Why would I
give you my Xbox? He's another pogo level. You don't want this thing. All right. This is a
checkpoint with pogo stick. Let's do it. Just trying to keep up speed. This is like an exact
route you take too with this shit. I gotta go. We're all nauseating. My head. What's going on?
Why is this doing this? He's like a dog's asshole. Where did it open?
Anybody see it? Can you guys, can you tell me what the next step thing is?
They can't hear me right? Is it over here? Chase the big kid. All right. This is freaking me out.
Quit the menu. Toy shop. Let's put on some new stuff. I'll stick with the bandana guy. Horns.
Hat. I like the hat. Staff. Backpack. Keyboard. This is rare. Keyboard. What's this? Sneakers.
Yeah. Cool. Sneakers. Fist pump. And I want the easy button behind me. Nice.
Let's go to school. Sounds like a fun time to me. I also have to piss again.
You look like Woody from Toy Story. ABC's one two threes. All right. Let's do it. I'm
starting to get like a dungeon. By the way, this is the first song you learn on any guitar.
It's the first like four chords. Chords. Chords. Chords. It's the first four chords you learn.
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. Oh, come on. Thank God. It just helps you.
You gotta get up top. Oh, I'm getting, I'm getting actually upset right now.
This used to be a fucking counting screen. Bounce from where do you want to bounce to?
No, we bolted the same exact thing at the same exact fucking time. Okay. He's waiting for me.
I went the wrong way. Fuck you. Chair. Is that lava there? I'm so confused. So I understand the
whole like the floor is lava gimmick. Does the floor actually have to be lava in this game?
Why can't it just be don't touch the floor? Hey. Throw shit. Why can't it just be don't touch the
red floor? I know it fucks up the whole thing. Otherwise, it would just be a Counter-Strike map.
It would just be a Garry's Mod custom game. I need momentum to get up there. Wait, guys. Wait for
me. Don't leave without me. Wait for me. Wait. Don't leave. Wait for me. I got it. I didn't
touch it. What? How did I not touch this? I need to put on my own music. This music is just like,
I feel like this is like a car commercial on the radio. Hold on. I got to get my own
fucking music in here. What do I want? What do I want from music? The piano. The piano is better
than music. No, not Minecraft. It's something that's going to pump me up. How about, no,
not Tony Hawk. That's how you get the whole stream turned off. Sonic? What's that song? Who's the
band that does all the Sonic songs? There's one band that's been doing every single theme song
for like 10 years. What's that band called? Anybody know the name of that band? What's that
band's name? By Crush 40. All right. Is this going to make the whole stream going to turn off?
Will it? Whatever. It's hot lava. I'm not like composing Mozart on this stream today.
Why does it feel like it's playing twice? I think I'm losing my mind.
Why will you truly follow your peace and pain
when you can't help but swallow?
If it's right that way, you can.
It's. Sing it. I need to go up that way. Something, something, whatever it is.
Do Twitch sings. I don't, I don't, I don't, I have no idea how to do that.
Plus that's an embarrassment strings. And this is not. Has it done how to bunny hop? Is that,
is that the jab there? And you see how many millions I have here? Hey, is this embarrassing?
378 trillion attack power. Is that an embarrassment? Speaking of.
Done. 443 million. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It's coming up. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Oh no, it's a long. Yeah. All right. Let's keep going. Money pit. I got an hour and 30
before I can do the money put again. What about this? No, I can't even attempt
10 experience. Let's go with I'm going to wait for 15.
I should rebirth now. Look at that. So fucking huge. That's it. Exponentially increased. My
inventory is fucking messed up. And what about special? I can do one more of these.
No special in any of the other ones. Any power in the sword,
toughness in the pants, combined boots, combined chest, pants, pants, pants, put it on
toughness, three out of seven, combine the cube, special, get in there, boots, helmet, sword.
Now let's take a little bit of an inventory here. We need toughness, toughness, special,
sword, special. We're going to put this. I don't think I can put this anywhere.
No, I can. We're good. This is now impossible. I've done my points. I wait. Not yet.
That was it. Somebody tell me. I thought I was wrong.
Yeah, there it is right there. All right. Let's get going. I'll come back in another 20 minutes.
And then I want to play this. I want to play. I want to play this game.
Wasn't it? Oh yeah. Escape from the city. That's the one, right? What's it called?
Escape the city. And this is the one that goes rolling around at the speed of sound, right?
Something like that. Let's go.
Do I do there?
Mobile viewers posting lyrics too late. I'm going to watch you. How are you doing this?
I see. I'm trying to follow them. Something going to autoplay.
Stop throwing shit at me. I've got it. It's tough enough as it is for me.
I bounced backwards. I need more Sonic the Hedgehog theme music for me to be able to do this.
This one has seven million views. What is this one? Seven fucking million. Oh, I know.
Louder vessel. It's not helping. The beat's wrong on this one for me.
It's not helping. The other one was. My turn. Get off of that. How do I do that? All right. Up on top.
I fell off. I'm just like slippery shit. It's a slippery fucking thing.
What the fuck are you in the way for? Worst Sonic song by far. Like if there's a top five,
this is five. What's this? What's this? Fist bump. Fist bump. Sonic Forces. There was a Sonic Forces
fist bump. One second. Sorry. I have a VPN. It takes me 10 seconds to load anything. Same song.
We'll listen to the real one. I listen to this way too much. I'm not even like that. I'm not
even that big of an Undertale fan, but I listened to... Didn't help. I don't even know where the
fuck I'm supposed to go. I have to go down? I have to go over there. From here. God. What the hell?
Here this way. Let's go. So let's jump this way. Down here. Across over there. Onto the loo.
Nice. Got it. Onto the wood. Oh, I fell down. Oh, that's unfortunate. Oh well. Try it again.
Oh, so wing it. Oh, nice try. Nice try. Excellent work. Oh, almost made three points.
I just have to go over there. Bounce. I jumped over the fucking thing. How many of these did I
jump over? Why is this playing again? Why is this playing again? Boom. Look at that pace.
Don't look at that pace. Oh, it's megalovania for one hour. Now I know why. Oops. Oh, got a new
session. Middle school. Was that middle school mischief? That one was difficult. Do it, coward.
Coward. What do you mean coward? Tape your face into a neutral position. Tape your face
into a neutral position. I get what? And my eyes? Do it and I'll sub. Really? Really? You'll sub
if I do the tape on the face thing. Or I'm gonna get acne. No. What if I just stay neutral? Like
the tape residue is gonna get in my pores and I'm gonna get zits. Go get it. Get tape or no sub.
Tape. What do you mean? Why? Why do I need to tape my face into it? It clears your pores. Tape
blocks your pores because it's tape. Do it. Don't sell out. All right. So one guy just said don't
sell out. Okay. Yeah. I will not make a reaction. I will put, I put artificial tape here. No reaction.
If I do any reaction. No, I tried this before and it was fucking bad. Do you guys remember
the don't make and don't laugh at all for like 10 straight minutes? That was horrible.
All right. No. All right. I'll try it. No emotions for 10 straight minutes or I do a hundred gifted
subs. When does it start? I already fucking can't do it. Every funny thing I've ever heard in my
whole life. Every fucking awful thing that's ever happened to me. They're all flowing to the front
of my cerebral cortex right now. And they're just like, I'm ready. I'm ready. Remember the time when
you did this? Remember that funny thing? Remember the movie you watched when you really laughed?
They're all getting in here. They're all getting to the front row. That was funny, but it's not.
Okay. No music's going to make me fucking laugh too. 10 minutes straight. I need, I need to look
over. Where's my timer? Four hours and 41 minutes in the stream. I got to pee first too. This is,
I'm going all in. I'll be right back. Hey, it's Jeremy again. I'm back. I have an idea for the
only reason why I would ever do media share. A stream where I have to stay completely,
completely emotionless while you guys do media share. And you have to try to break me. Interesting
scenario. Think about that. I'll sleep on that one. I'll be right back. Okay. I'm back. Let's
give this a try. Uh, I get three strikes by the way. 10 minutes, three strikes. Yes, I do. Yes,
I do. I make the rules. Okay. I make the rules. Three strikes, 10 minutes. Cause I know it's
going to happen. Three strikes. Uh, I make the rules. You guys get to pick the music,
come to a consensus on something. How the fuck are you going to do that in five seconds? Uh,
no, not okay. What, what, what is, people keep writing this shit. What is this? Pumpkin Hill?
Pumpkin Hill, Sonic Adventure 2 music.
Okay. Pumpkin Hill. Why do I remember this song?
Cause I have no fear. This probably seems crazy, crazy. Graveyard theory.
Why is Chad's thinking the worst song? It's not me picking it.
Let's go. We're not starting yet. I'll give you a big face cam just so you guys can really,
really take a look.
I'm not allowed to. Okay. Okay. Emotionless doesn't mean I can't move my entire facial muscles.
This is going to be hard. No, emotionless means like no laughing, no getting angry, no what the
fuck? No. Oh, that was funny. Nothing. Just blank. But I can like go like this. Like I can like touch
my face and stuff. You can't smile. I won't smile. I'm a fucking four year old. You can't do that.
Now I want to do that. This thing is this, this guy sucks. This guy sucks. That's an emotion,
but it's not time. I'm waiting till the end of the song because this is cheating for you guys.
Cause it needs to be at the beginning of a new song.
It hasn't started yet. It hasn't started yet.
Fuck. No, that's not one. Let me beat this level first. Oh, I need momentum. I have to stay
completely. I gotta stay completely fucking still too. Well, that's not going to happen
because I'm a fidgeter.
I ain't going to let it get to me. I'm just going to creep down the park.
I got it. Holy shit, there's more.
I know that it's here. Rocking, sensing it in my feet.
The gray emeralds be the fear. See a thing, but it's around somewhere.
I'm gonna hold my head and fear. This prophecy turns gray. A gray dark theory.
I coast trying, but he ain't got a theory. Now that it's still a second, I'm walking to the
fuck. They look like emerald shards. Oh, I'm going to hang on to that one now.
Fuck. I need you to start it because you guys have thrown shit out there that is
it's going to, it's going to fuck with me.
Okay. I get three strikes starting. Okay. No emotion, no anger,
no frustration, no laughing like this. This, I can't fucking do this.
I can't do it. I might as well just give everybody a hundred subs right now.
It's impossible for me. There's no way I, there is confetti that's getting stuffed down here
and somebody is just going to pull the string down here and just boom.
It just builds and builds and builds and builds until like it has to come out.
Brick by brick Lego Island. OST. Is this a funny song? Okay. Starting off three strikes.
Here we go. I'm going to watch the timer here. We're 450.
I almost laughed because I had this on the screen. Just sitting here huge in front of me right now.
Here we go. In 10 seconds at 451 and then at four at 501 stream time.
I got it right here. Here we go. Starting now.
You can paint a jet ski yellow like that.
That's still part of one. That's still part of one. That's still part of one.
Alright. Why did I do this to myself?
Lego seed. When you're behind the tent. If you do it brick by brick.
Fuck. I just picture like a big fucking southern family on stage. They're like a
bang. They're like a huge cello. It's like a hunt. There's like 12 of them. They're all in the same family.
There's something you should know. When you block the road. You're going to get towed.
Brick by brick. I told Nick. You can build a brick by brick.
Machine ready yellow SD by slacks. All around the island right here. No matter. You can move a man. You can move a mountain. If you do it brick by brick.
There's somebody in fucking chat. Somebody in chat said this streamer doesn't talk. Why? Like what the fuck?
The music and just the part that I like. He's just sitting there playing like fucking shit.
I don't know why the fuck I looked at chat. I needed two and two and a half more minutes.
Hold on a second. Just keep the music playing. Double or nothing? No. I ain't playing that game anymore.
It's this music too. Like what the fuck even is this music? I'll have to do it from here. How the
fuck do I? I don't know how to do this every time. How do I even give community subs? Here we go.
I don't know why I play these fucking dangerous games with myself. I continue to play play dumb
games. You play stupid games. Gift us. Here it is. Okay. Here we go. Congratulations.
Dodged it. You dodged it. That's a free shit. I didn't get one. Do it again.
That was not a lie. No. All right. Let's keep going. I'm already subscribed. What happened to
the Lego Island music? That's a vacuum cleaner. What time is it? Five hours? How many? We got two
hours in. I gotta rebirth this. Who even gives a shit about hot lava anymore? It's good. It's a
good game. It's good. But my mind is only on numbers going up in a sequence at the moment.
Let me get to the end of this. Thanks. You got one? Thanks for the sub. Yeah. There it is.
Listen to one. Listen to one hour of vacuum without laughing. I'll do. Okay. Why is that on
screen? All right. No, not double enough. And I just did it. I'll do, I'll do two straight minutes
of vacuum cleaner sound without flinching. And if I don't do it, I'll dab on stream.
That's much better than a hundred community subs. Oh, who even gives a shit about hot? All right.
It's a great game. It's fun. It was fun for a while. It was cool. I don't care anymore. Oh,
I care about listening to vacuum cleaners. Ready? Two minutes. I need to change this to something
else. Because if you're looking for hot lava gameplay and you come in here and it's a guy
listening to a vacuum cleaner, you're going to probably sort of annoyed by that. And I don't
blame you. I don't. Let's change the title. Where's my shit? There it is. All right. I can keep the
title at numbers go up. It's been like that the whole time, even with the lava one. Okay. All right.
Let's do it. Are you ready? So people, just so people can know, I need to put a text on the
screen just so people know. Cause if you come in here, you need to be curious, right? All right.
No, what the fuck is, get back here. Okay. I'm ready. I'm going to try. It's going to be loud.
Just to make sure everyone's aware of that. Both earphones. I'm not going to cheat. Two minutes.
I see it on the clock. I'm ready. Three, two, one.
There's two things going on here. Somebody said, dude, use push to talk. You fucking asshole.
And the second thing is you can, you're going to hear the vacuum cleaner going over a rug.
It goes like, going back and forth. There you go. I can do it. I've done that so many times now.
Three, two, one. God damn it. One, two, three, go.
Fix your mic. I have the gain turned up all the fucking way.
Hey guys, what's going on? Yeah. Hi guys. Just my microphone can't pick me up. So I
got to turn the gain all the way up. He's weak to mic. No, it's just like,
I just imagine somebody fucking needing to turn their mic all the way to,
how many minutes was that? It was less than two. I don't want to. I never told you they were going
to be any good. How the hell am I going to do this? Okay. I need something that's,
I need something else that's on a vacuum cleaner. Cause you guys,
I need something that you guys can't make jokes about. You know what I mean?
You guys, you guys are too quick. Microwave sound. I'll try it.
This just sounds like an airplane. It's, that's the same sound. Fix your fucking mic.
Ah, that's the best one so far. All right. How about, um, saxophone? Let's see. Okay. Three,
two, one.
It's the fucking people in the background. Oh, it's the people that were talking. There was a
crowd. It was just like street noise. A minute. I don't care if this takes me all night. I'll do
it. I don't care if it takes me all five. You know what? Fuck it. Three minutes. One, two, three,
go. That's different. What? Right. Hold on. Three, two, one, go. Three, two, three, two, one,
three. Three, two, one, go.
Nothing was funny. It just, this one went on for a long time. This one went on for like a full,
like 45 seconds. Usually the first three minutes of this video was one, two, here's another saxophone.
Here's another saxophone. And this guy just keep playing. This guy's just going. I think my brain
is, there you go. Hey, there you are. I think my brain is too fucked up to do this.
Every second, there's like something else in here. Give me something else. Something easy. You gotta,
something easy. The beach. That's actually would work pretty well, I think. I can't see myself
laughing at the beach. It's the beach. It's just a beach. What's the fun? There's nothing there.
Just imagine. Can I close my eyes? Is that, can I close my eyes? I can't, right? Like you're not
going to take that from me. Actually that'll make it worse because then I'll just see images.
Okay. We're going to go with, you just laughed at a vacuum. I know, but it was a lot more going on.
There were like four or 500 different onion layers as to why the vacuum was funny.
Okay. Let's do the beach ambience. Blinking is also emotion. No, it's a necessary
mechanism to survive. Ocean sounds for sleep. How would you think this was funny? This is not
at all. Here we go. Beach ambience on tropical paradise. Impossible to think this is funny.
Three minutes. I'm prepared. It's all out of my system at this point. Three minutes. That's not,
I've been streaming for fucking five, almost five and a half hours. Three minutes is not a big deal.
I can do three goddamn minutes, but hold on a second. Okay. I, how are we doing? Fight the boss.
No, rebirth. Almost there. And in four minutes I get rewarded with, with a hundred million,
a billion. I'll figure this out later. Okay. That sounds good. Four more minutes and I can
rebirth again. Just focus on the rebirth and that's it. Okay. This isn't funny. So don't laugh. I know.
That's what I'm saying. It's, this is just water sounds. Three, two, one, action.
Started over, started over. So is it bath time? Started over three minutes. Starting now. Go. Now.
Wait, my mind's allowed to wander. I need like some, I need sound. I need noise. I need something
talking. I can't fucking do it. I can't do it. I don't think I can. There's your one, your two,
your three, whatever it is. I don't think I can do it. Do math. I keep thinking of fucking bath now.
Somebody said bath time with Jeremy. Fuck. Just listen to a Ted talk. Is that like a loud, is that
loud? Can I listen to a Ted talk? Ted talk like science. I don't know. This is quantum physics,
quantum physics. When it starts in three, two, a lot about. Have you ever had, so have you ever
had this experience? Starting now. Having a chat with someone and they're telling you something
about a subject they're very interested in or they know a lot about and you're following along
and then at some stage you realize you kind of lost the thread of what they're saying
and then you're standing there and you realize you've got absolutely no idea what they're talking
about. I had this recently with a friend who knows a lot about investing. No. And something.
Because I just saw me in the fucking reflector watching TV this way. Like I'm watching TV on
stream and the TV's off camera over here. No, it can't be somebody talking. I got it. I know
it'll, I know what to do. Um, how long is it? Okay. The national anthem is five minutes long.
Here we go. United States of America national anthem. Um, no, uh, how about, um,
zoo, uh, I don't know what TV static. No, why would beach? Why would I not be able to do
beach for fuck's sake? Seagull sounds that actually would be okay. This, this has to be the one.
If I don't do it here, then I'm turning the stream off. I'm out of here. This is like,
I've got to go like dunk my head in water. It's plugged in just to make sure everyone sees it.
It's plugged in. Okay. Starting now. This is the last time I'm ever going to play this game.
No, I am so Zen. I'm completely Zen. So we need to have a Zen background.
This is six hours of Zen. No, no, no. Katamari. There we go. It feels pretty good. All right. So
I need now I have 25 experience points. We're going to do plus one energy speed. There we go.
Get a couple more of these too. Why not? That's for going very fast. I don't think it's possible
to fight the boss. Not yet. At least maybe in a few, in a few moments. It's possible.
Money pit is 26 minutes. We will see that again at least one more time. This guy no longer laughs.
Let's test it. Let's see if I've actually achieved true focus. Here we go.
I've achieved it. That would have the, the unascended me would have laughed at that last
one because it was so abrupt. And now I need screaming. Okay. Let's try. It's not going to do
anything. That was close. That was very close, but I've ascended. Yeah. That would have, that's what
it's. All right. Let's just play the game. There's only somebody. Oh, it's still going too fast.
It was the three. It was the, it was the third, just the same person. All right. That's it. I'm
ready. I need music though. What the fuck am I doing? Okay. So yeah, let's go back here. I'm
going to, I'm going to, let's just do it now. I'm not waiting 15 moments for this shit.
Toughness. What do we got? I can do a bunch into the cube and now that puts it at 13,
maxed out, combine all this shit. Looking good. Cube, all the cubes just put them together.
Special, right? Wait a minute. You, what did that say? That said something.
Dragon. What did that say? It said, that said a new cube. Infinity cube. You should probably
boost your equipment first before boosting the cube. What should I eat? You guys have any ideas
what I should have for food? I need some good food ideas. Chicken sandwich. Maybe. All right.
Let's, let's ascend. This is going to be a big, big fucking deal. 450 million. Get a poke bowl.
I'm actually not a big fan of raw tuna. Not really. It's, it's all right. I'd rather have it
as a spicy tuna roll. A poke bowl. But I like spicy tuna, but I don't like it. I don't, you
don't get the big red fatty tuna like sushi. Try to just wait the, no. Rebirth. Let's do it.
This is now going to be ridiculous. Like absolutely ridiculous. Microism cereal.
You're trying to gross me out. Okay. Rebirth. 450 million. Now we can, I, I could nuke.
I don't have any, I don't have any points. Let's do just, why is that taking so long?
All right. Okay. We're already at eight trillion attack. Just in case anyone was curious. Boom,
boom, boom, boom, boom. I don't want to nuke. I like to see how far we go. So we're at 20 trillion
attack. He's got 120. We've got plenty. Just drain them down. I've got an image to look at.
I'll never look at that one again. Thank you though. Uh, adventure. I'm, I'm going to get
very close to being able to do this shit. What else has special? This does. I got the money
pitback fight boss. Uh, cap is going up. Oh yeah. You got, you guys got full of, this is what this,
you guys are full of photos. So tomorrow, we're not done yet, but tomorrow I am going to,
what the fuck? It's just the idol face. German idol. Uh, tomorrow is possible that it'll be
the community night. You'll find out very soon. Uh, tomorrow I'll be here tomorrow morning,
early kind of afternoonish, early morningish, uh, to tell you what, if there's enough,
if there's enough, we're going to do the community night. And what is the community night? The
community night is the new monthly or bi-monthly stream where we hang out for a few hours and we
go over a bunch of community artwork, a bunch of community videos, a bunch of anything. That's
just original community content. It doesn't just have to be art. It's not necessarily an artwork
showcase. It's an everything showcase and we just chill. And maybe I'll do a coloring book.
Maybe I'll do a coloring book on stream. What is cracked? Oh, movie night. Yeah, kind of is.
It's kind of a movie night. If there was a police officer that wanted to guaranteed write like
50 tickets a day, guarantee, and we're talking absolute guarantee.
Hang out over there. Oh, I need music. What else we got? I'm just going to go next, next,
next on Lego Island until there's something else. Next, next, next, next, next, next, next.
Okay. This is, I guess another, this is also Lego related, which is called the catchy song.
No, no, no. Excuse me. I'm sorry. I call bullshit on that one because here's the original.
And yes, it goes on and on my friend. Some people started singing it, not knowing why
did you sing that instantly? Don't wait. Don't you come over here and she's like, oh, stop this
nonsense. That's enough. I got off with that song, please. No more. No more of this song.
Nothing in here. Let's prove it. There ain't fucking anything in here.
Turn off that song. Some people started singing it, not knowing what it was,
but we'll continue singing it forever. Just because the song that doesn't end the fuck out
of here with I'm done with that. This is a great cup though. I will say, you know, people do like,
oh, I'm going to watch this video for an hour or the 10 hour version or whatever. You've never
seen anybody watch that one. Maybe you have. Is that like a subset of YouTube or Twitch or
something that I don't know about? All right. I got a lot of, let's do this. Gorgonzola. Wait a
minute. This is 18. I just, I did it. I got to, I cut to 18. Augmentation feature unlock. Go check
it out on the features. A new adventure zone has also been unlocked. The forest, exhausted, bruised,
and slightly deaf from explosion. You hobble into this mysterious hut. And indeed this seems
to be the home of the wizard, whoever he is. You see the stereotypical bubbling cauldron,
various gross magical ingredients, and oddly enough, dozens of empty cans of compressed air
laying on the floor. Like, wait, why? Uh, okay. However, the bug-eyed wizard has caught your
attention as he whoops maniacally, greeting you like an old friend. With your memory lost,
you just take him at his word that you knew each other. Okay. He claims he can help you if you had,
if you'd head through what he calls the hazy cave just behind his home and gather some of
that good stuff. Whatever that is. Feeling unusually merciful, you agree to help and set off
into the cave. Be prepared for anything that in the cave there, fella. The weird gases in there
make you go a little loopy. And if you need a little something something to get stronger,
see Mr. Jensen. Just a couple of houses down, he'll hook you up with some of what he calls
augmentations. It's weird sci-fi mumbo jumbo, but I can't deny that it works.
Augmentation. Unlock by defeating Gorgon. Next augment, so this is a gold sink. Base stat multiplier
one. Wait, energy alo- energy allocated? What? Really? Let's get that up. Well, that's only
halfway there. You use energy to build it up and it adds a multiplier. That's cool. This is a fun
game. Let's pull this down now. Okay, I gotta do increments of like 200 now or 100 at least.
Alright, we're at 3000. What's my actual cap now? 3757. That's pretty good. That doubles attack and
defense. I have, speaking of attack and defense, quadrillion. Almost nine- eight quadrillion.
So I can do damage. I'm about to kill Gorgonzola right now and I'm going to get the artifact.
You're having more fun with this this clicking game than with the lava game. I feel like we're
kind of past the point of no return with this one. And I mean, I'm only going to be streaming
I don't know. I did it. Yes, you're fighting sentient cheeses now. Yes, it's probably the gas.
No, you should not let this cheese or anything else in this cave live. This one is armed with
a massive crossbow. How is it even able to fire the damn thing? I don't know. But I just got
safety scissors. Time left to complete the augment. Oh, I get it. 11 minutes.
Shit. Okay. Um, I have to build them. Let's go into the sewers though, because I-
Uh, I don't want to listen to that, but that's fine. I need gold. I need gold. I need gold.
Why am I not getting gold? Because I'm not doing adventuring. That's why.
That's what's going on here. This is an ad or is this the actual- no, this is the actual thing.
Okay. So let's go to adventure. I'm in the forest. These things are way too powerful. I don't think
I can do the forest. This is going to be tricky. I might get something good for this though. Let's
see. 3900 gold. You've defeated a goblin. 3344. I mean, I'm- I need more max HP. Bad.
Fairy has defeated you. Right. How am I doing on this fight? 11 and 13. Not really enough.
Let's go all the way. Cap that shit up. All right. 10k levels in previous attack,
which is not going to happen anytime soon. I'm just going to put it into here.
What's the point? All right. Looks good. So 11. I need 10,000 gold, which I almost have.
Adventure. Let's try it again. Forest. Good. This should be easy. A lot of HP though. Orc.
Is that a Mario Yahtzee in the background? Orc dropped a toughness boost 2 and 4300 gold.
Toughness boost- wait. Is it working? Didn't I have money? I thought- Z. Bonus 2 bonus.
Oh shit. Okay. Axel. Toughness. None of these needed. Toughness 2. Here we go. In the boots.
Advancing back to the adventure. Did I die? No, I'm good. I need 10 grand.
10 grand. Here we go. Augmentation. 10,000 gold. Time left to complete. 10 minutes.
Let's get some- no. Let's make that easier. I don't want to wait around 10 minutes. Are you
kidding me? 3 minutes. All right. 39 quadrillion. Uh oh. I don't really have enough.
What do I get for rebirth? This is going up like crazy. All right. At 15 minutes this is
going to be insane. Get milk infusion. Base stat multiplier 25. Marinating your bones in
milk for 6 hours should toughen them up. 200,000 gold. Is that 22 hours or 22 minutes? 22 minutes.
Good. Okay. Experience. I'm going to wait for- I want to do this at- I'll do it right now.
No money pit. Not worth it. 22 minutes if you use all of your energy. Okay.
Jerma, stop- you need to stop playing this game. Only tonight? And maybe leave my computer on
overnight and just play this and just not stream it but try to get to the vacation.
Jerma, please. Please, Jerma, please. We'll- you'll fine. We're fine. Inventory. All right.
Can I combine this? No. That's 20 attack power. So this thing is junk now. Get rid of it.
It's a wooden sword. This is junk too. Get rid of this too. I'm never going to put this on. All
right. Now I can do adventure. Let's see. Forest. I should be doing much more damage
now. It's funny because Link doesn't talk. RIP 100 set bonus. What do you mean 100 set bonus?
3800 gold. What about my augmentation? Almost there. 41 seconds. This stream is the longest
worst joke of 2019. This is- this is not a joke to me. This is- this is a game I'm playing.
This is my- I want to play this game. Not everything's gotta be a joke. You understand?
Here. Just take that last bit. Just take that last little bit. Sip it. Come on. Get it. Nice.
Wow, you got it. Nice work. Why am I doing that? I didn't spill it. There's no- I don't got anything.
I got a safety scissor. Sick. So my stats- 43 go- oh, at least shit. Hold on. Well, all right.
Well, now you die. You put creamer in your coffee. It depends on what kind of coffee it is. Ice coffee
I do usually do almond milk. All right, I got the brie. This cheese is named after a city in the
Netherlands. Knowing that, this is going to be a tough fight. 1.9 quintillion. Quintillion.
It's- yeah, it's absolutely double the stats. That's fucking pretty good. How am I doing in
adventure mode? What do we got? Anything else? Just a one? Put it in here. 51 power now.
Sextillion incoming. Yeah. I got 2.6 billion. I have to rebirth again right now. I have to.
Like, why would I not? And then when we- when we- then- and then the stream ends.
I think so. That sounds like a plan to me. Sextillion. Yeah, sextillion. It's- you don't
know what sextillion? Here comes the end of the stream voice. Uh oh. What is my issue? Do I have
one? Do I have an issue? I don't think I do. Do I have one? Tell me if I do. So I can get- I'm
getting more of these. 20,000 gold. Holy- that's insane. I can do this again? Milk infusion. That's
20 minutes. I'm gonna rebirth. I don't know if I keep that though. Do I- I don't think I keep this.
No, this ain't gonna happen. 100 quadrillion? No. No way. Would I tell you guys if I shit myself
on stream? Yeah, because I would have to leave. I would be like, guys, I have to leave. I have- I
have had a small accident, is what I would say. I'd say I had a little accident. And then I would
leave. I would just leave. I'm not gonna sit here. But that's never gonna happen. But yes, I would.
I would tell you guys that there was an accident on- like, I had a small accident and I have to go.
That's all there is to it. So, um, I have to leave very soon here. What am I gonna eat for food?
You guys have to help me decide this. Let's go back to the forest. We have to break it down first.
There is- let's go over some genres. I want genre first. Buffalo chicken wings. That- you know what?
I think you just nailed it. You nailed it. You did. Yeah, you nailed it. Thanks a lot. Appreciate the
help. Oh, I know exactly where I'm gonna get them from too. Hash house or go-go? From the Link. I
wonder if they even have them. Special boost 1. Stylish. Ooh. Skeleton. 51. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Rebirth. 3 billion. All right, it's time. It's time. It's time. It's time. I have to do it.
Doing this one more time and then I'm gonna go get food. And then I'll see you guys tomorrow.
Yeah, I will. He'll see me tomorrow. He shit himself. We're not gonna see you again. I'm
gonna stream tomorrow. I'm gonna stream tomorrow at like 1 o'clock Pacific.
All right, experience. Let's do- no. Here comes a rebirth. I got it. 6.5 billion.
Do it. Bang. This is where it gets wild. They're- hold on a minute. Max energy on this rebirth is
capped at 3900. On re- okay. All right, nice. Hold on. Trillion already? Already 7- 100 trillion.
Let's see. I haven't done a nuke all day. Nuke. Down at the fast zombie. Nuke. I can't. He killed
me. You motherfucker. You killed me. Yeah, it's time to eat food soon. Food isn't coming. I'm
gonna be- no. He killed me again. All right, so we're doing all right. You know, I'll tell you
something. I had a blast on today's stream. I had a fucking great time. This was a lot of fun.
Sometimes it don't matter what the game is. We make our own damn fun. I'm glad somebody did.
Easy. Easy. Easy. I'm admitting this is a bad stream. What? What are you talking about? This
is like the- I had- I've had like the- I had- I played Hitman yesterday and had a different kind
of fun. I had a lot of fun today. What are you talking about? It's got a pants blast.
It is a fucking mess, so I've gotta go. I've never heard that term before. It's a pants blast.
You guys are sick. Look at that. It's like lightning. Oh, already a quadrillion. Skip it.
Skip it. Skip it. No, not this one. All right, augmentation. I lost my augmentation though.
Yeah, this does hurt my eyes. I need full HP. Yeah, I also need to do this too. I need this
to get this. I need defense. Uh, adventuring is also important right now too. What do I- inventory?
Nothing? What is- 10, 10. No, there's no reason for me to- just get rid of this. I don't need to-
why do I need to hold on to this? There's a dark mode? Holy shit. You need to buy the ascended
newbie pack in the sellout shop to turn this on. Oh, that's great. I said that four hours ago. It
wasn't- it wasn't nighttime four hours ago. It was three o'clock pacific time. The sun is still
shining. I don't need dark mode then. It's later now. All right, now I can do this. It's 20,000
gold. I need more gold. How's adventuring doing? But we're gone, boss. Kill it. Kill it. Kill it.
Kill it. Kill it. Kill it. Kill it. Kill it. Kill it. Nice. Did it. They beat level 37. Oh my god,
that ain't gonna happen. Almost there, almost at 10,000. And then I'm just gonna spam- I'm gonna
take all the points away from the training. Let's- let's actually start doing this now. I'm gonna
dump every single point into the augmentation. Every single one. It's 20,000 gold, right?
one minute 57 seconds you got it there is no I cannot fight this okay that's
fine venture how's it going inventory a couple of Z's nice special energy bonus
let's do it set numbers to engineering I'm not an engineer I don't think I
could figure it out you can actually fight enemies if you do the yeah if you
do if I do this I can actually fight but I can't because I don't have the thing
unlocked like all I have is block unlocked right now an augmentation let's
go one minute I need 10,000 gold though kill it please rebirth is still doing
fine I mained Engie in TF2 yeah I did I did 39 okay I got enough augmentation
here it comes 26 seconds excuse me kind sir could you please finish playing
fist bump from Sonic Forces yeah there you go give me another one how much money do I need 20,000
gold give me another one too loud not anymore all right this would be it's
gonna be a big hit here 11 million Bree is going down go and what's after that
cheddar one guy said it was too loud I was the one guy I thought it was too
long Gouda fight it no no I'm gonna lose instantly augmentation here it comes
another thing is safety scissors two minutes I'm gonna hold on to my points
now did I die no in Missouri whoo what's this mossy ring eight twenty four
eight two two I mean I'll have to combine them and add points to them it's
not a 10 30 13 no none of this is this is probably gonna be better eventually
but not right now energy speed bonus yeah but this is region and region and
speed okay I can't wait for those fucking buffalo wings hey thanks for
fucking hanging out tonight let's tell you this song is bacon be positive I
need more more more I want no knees did I get killed giant has defeated you I
need 20 grand Morgan boss there's gonna be a lot paralyzed skillet hey yeah guys
come on I'm saying this bump too bad this Sonic game sucked that Sonic game
sucked there hasn't been a good Sonic the Hedgehog game in probably about 12
years but uh hold on people saying Sonic mania but Sonic mania is just a
compilation of all the other good ones Sonic mania Sonic mania they just like
did they said hey this is I have Sonic the Hedgehog one two and three are great
let's like kind of make that again and redo them all I mean no it's not is my
gut that do I have that wrong what's the one where they just remade the first
like three games and call it something else they never did that just wait
generations there it is there okay I was wrong Sonic mania it's just this is just
Sonic the Hedgehog they just remade it how's it what is the same game is this a
remake of like the first one generations is that game it is this has new levels
so it's a new game with the old palette okay all right okay all right I was
wrong that's fine I was wrong I was thinking of generations okay when they
come out 2016 all right okay all right okay yep okay I'm corrected that's fine
okay I got two of these now good that's all I want all right boss time basic
training let's get it in there tap it wait is it they get you don't even
flashing anymore they should make another classic Sonic game I don't know
what they should do with Sonic cuz it Sonic soda has like an unfair unfair
weight put on them I think for some reason and I'll give you an example well
now it's it's so Mario when they make a Mario game it's still like Super Mario
it's still you know like a plug most of them almost all of my platforms right so
if you make a Mario game you make six seven eight nine ten Mario games I'm
talking the last ten years that are essentially jump from spot to spot right
Sonic the Hedgehog is just I go very fast but I go very fast has not stood
the test of time that jump from spot to spot has so what the what that's kind of
how do you go really fast in 2020 you kind of can and let's just racing game
they could have taken Sonic and made it is its own it's like Mario Kart type
game I know they did they did Sonic races but I'm talking like completely
transitioned the whole entire character into this is a racing game not like oh
let's go back and do Sonic unleashed Sonic colors Sonic we go fast this way
no just have it be your race it's a race have to be like that don't touch the
floor lava game except it's it's Sonic the Hedgehog and you got to move fast
and bunny hop and put it on PC and stuff I don't know I do I remember colors
wasn't really not that bad though because Mario has a bunch of these
gimmicks right but they work gravity big gimmick right Mario Galaxy this you jump
from the planets you run around a circle is like a gravity okay that's cool that
worked because you jump around and gravity works when you jump you land
back on the ground in Sonic unleashed their Mario Galaxy type scenario was
turn into a werewolf that doesn't make doesn't that does not add anything to
going fast in fact werewolf a werewolf is slow they're not that fast if you've
seen Twilight the vampires run much faster than the werewolves because they
have like the super duper lightning like super speed so and then didn't they
they did a they did like he did it but they gave him like a sword and a shield
in one of them he had like a fucking he was like a knight right that that does
not make going fast more interesting Mario um Mario Galaxy right Mario
Odyssey Mario Odyssey they gave him this hat the gimmick you could throw the hat
on stuff and control it and it was interesting and it added way more
dynamic to jumping up and down on stuff they should have just given Sonic a
fucking car just give him a car and just make a taxi game or something I don't
know they did but I mean I mean in every game like you know once when Mario gets
a picks up the the fire plant and you can shoot fire out of his hands and
that's the gimmick have to be a thing that you pick up and it's Sonic goes in
the car and it's a super cool like Batmobile type car and it goes like 500
miles per hour and you bet you do the level in the car anything that goes
really fast like train have him like turn to a train or have him get in the
train and go really fast and train have him getting like you know he can fly
turns into a helicopter I don't know what things go really fucking fast you don't
slow him down you make him go faster that sounds awful but still Mario has
gimmicks that quantum that they they add to him jumping up and down Sonic
keeps taking things away from how fast he goes have a time travel have a Sonic
the fucking hedgehog time travel game where he goes too fast in the beginning
the opening cutscene he goes way too fast and he goes like 200 years in the
future or something they did that oh well I'm gonna go so fast it goes back
in time if they had to go back in time oh they've done all options then you
time travel going fast or that's pretty much the only gimmick you can do okay
they did it with how it was again hum what was it rated
Sonic CD generations and CD or I got a better idea Sega make another super
monkey ball game and add Sonic as a fucking collectible character he moves
fast in that thing they are okay they're doing that too they're on the right
track they're on the right track good here's Sonic and the Black Knight exactly
we were just talking about this is called Night of the Wind not bad all
right blue cheese did you know that this stuff has mold in it gross I love blue
cheese and I'm gonna have a shitload of it in like 20 minutes all right what I
need to whatever got capped out here 39 9 augmentation what do I need for milk
let's make some milk I need 200,000 gold back to adventure mode
buffalo wings and blue cheese oh yeah you have no idea I'm gonna eat too many
of those tonight I'm gonna have so many it's gonna be ridiculous texting me
whoo energy yeah I'm gonna have the whole outfit on forest helmet power so
this is all right these are not trash toughness 47 let's take a look adventure
you make me hungry I'm making myself hungry what if Sonic went to the
Olympics yes that would be interesting wouldn't it or what if they just took
away the whole Sonic goes really fast because that you always have to worry
about the fact that at some point during the game when you're walking around
you're gonna just start going 500 miles per hour what if he gets cursed at the
beginning of one of the games by dr. Robotnik throws like a curse at him and
he's oh I can't run fast anymore and now you just have to play a different game
they that's what they did that's they did that already why is Sonic the
Simpsons have they done everything they tried everything those games they've
already made well give him a fucking TV show in a CG movie that's the final step
there no way getting more games just turn it into a cartoon network show I
know about them yes the movie yes I know the movie I know about the movie that's
why I said the movie and no the TV show yes the tip that I know that shit yes I
know that's the end that's the end game that's how you ended and then that's
gonna run for like fucking 35 seasons and then Sega is gonna they went from
making hardware consoles to we don't make consoles anymore to now we make
games only but now we don't make games anymore now we just make TV shows and
they're gonna just bake cartoons in 20 years Sonic Souls born might be
interesting you've moved really fast that might be their plan
but Sega does have a lot of great properties though what Sega's number
besides Sonic Sega has House of the Dead Sonic Yakuza okay what what else but I'm
talking like relevant series that have like they've had of something to come
out in the last few years Monkey Ball but Monkey Ball well technically is
then they're making one right Parmesan you're seriously debating taking this
cheese as future corpse with you to grate over some pasta that sounds good
too I blame the game because of all the food shit and important to note here
very very quickly Sega has been getting into the slot machine business because
there is a House of the Dead slot machine now they're they're gonna be
making cartoons and slot machines like Konami just wait until just wait until
Nintendo caves somehow they cave to the mobile market when is the first Super
Mario slot machine gonna be in Las Vegas oh boy people you won't be able to get
anybody off that machine oh yeah what's wrong with the mobile market nothing
except it's seven dollars for ten gems in the Mario Kart mobile game of course I
checked because I played it for like an hour you know a Mario Kart releases on
the iPad guys I'm on my iPad every night how long is this song I'm done
with it actual boomer you guys all have to I ain't gonna take I ain't gonna take
this type of I'm not gonna take this type of abuse about our boomer with an
iPad in bed when I guarantee you at least 60 to 70% of everybody in this
chat room has like a 10 inch like galaxy note 10 they're like this all day how
many of you guys have an iPhone and how often are you like German you get nerd
neck thank you for reminding me no for real thanks but that's what that's a
great reminder careful when you're sitting down don't give yourself a nerd
neck all right ah two four six eight augmentation ten I got a hundred thousand
gold oh shit a hundred thousand gold wait a minute take this ball down I use
my iPad in bed that's what they're for why is iPad mean boomer because I use a
electronic device in bed I just have a bigger screen I would be doing it on my
phone this is this is literally in the recommended right here this is like that
on the playlist is this cuz I've listened to this bond stream and it's
cuz I've listened to this on stream I just sound like shit crossword puzzles
of the new hotness yeah they probably are I can see that all right augmentation
I want this milk thing how long is it gonna take 16 minutes and 200,000 gold oh
shit I gotta be I gotta be like the 16 moments this is not ace combat but I
wish it was have any video games released in the last like week or two
that have been worth playing I have code vain people but people keep telling me
that that's not very good we have to figure that out on our own code vain is
so bad really planet Zoo yeah planets isn't beta though it's that that I want
to play when it's actually out and release completely oh this is good this
is a new eight oh yeah put it on oh I'm sorry I've been quiet this is the best
part play Uno I don't even know how now that's it that's all the only thing I'm
really wanted to hear in this song the song is seven minutes long but only
that's like that that's like the 12 seconds that I like if I've heard this
I've played this song off straight before and sat and watched you know if
you go into YouTube analytics you can see there's a line that shows you when
people watched in rewind and it'll show you that the time that what that had the
most retention I alone have probably made that bar like 60% higher on this
video because I've rewound this probably I did this spot right there like
probably two to three thousand times okay I need 200k two to three thousand
probably because I think about it if I do it what you didn't you know if you
guys don't realize when you listen to a song and not just with this song but any
song that you actually like you would be surprised if you were being tracked
without you knowing like you just bugged yourself essentially right you'd be
surprised at how many times you actually go back and listen to the same thing over
and over again oh yeah I heard that I listened to that for a little while you
look over it's been 27 minutes and you've been on like the same song or
did I just admit to you that I'm a psychopath I'm not sure which one of
those things is it is I don't know both just kidding all right augmentation I
almost have it 16 minutes I need 200,000 gold almost there and then I'm gonna do
something for 16 minutes before the stream ends that's the final thing I'm
doing 48 billion pretty good this is gonna double here in a second no good
games until the Outer Worlds comes out yeah I mean I what there are no there
like what games have released what about greed fall no I thought about green fault
from with green fall is just it's gonna be one of those scenarios it's gonna
bore the hell out of me I know it is I was thinking about it but I just see
myself sitting there for a couple hours and then I just don't want to pick all
the dialogue options it kind of looks like it's a Mass Effect II where you got
like five minutes of combat and exploration and gameplay and then like
30 minutes of story and go talk to all the people in town is that accurate yes
okay yeah it's just not I know a lot of people like that stuff and that's fine
that's that's cool I'm not gonna tell you that that's not a good game it's just
not usually what I find to be very interesting I don't do well not I'm not
even talking on stream like oh no let's do it off stream but do you even off
stream right it doesn't click with me really at all you should play dicey
dungeons I've heard that was very good you would not like earthbound well
earthbound is different because earthbound is that's a that's like an
RPG it's like a turn-based RPG and there's a lot of stuff going on in
earthbound it's not really the same genre even bookworm adventures deluxe
how many there's a lot I haven't heard that in a long time maybe I'll do that
tomorrow that's a lie by the way that's a
confirmed 23 and a half hours from now lie all right 15 minutes and I get this
insane multiplier still can't do it although I might just yeah okay all
right it's been six and a half hours okay all right all right yeah I'll see
you tomorrow that's the only thing I want to hear all right I'll see you
tomorrow this has been ngu idle and I forgot that I played hot lava for like
an hour and a half two hours the stream kind of just melted for me like it's
six and a half hours that's hope you guys had fun because I did and it just
about having fun you know maybe you didn't like ngu ultimate whatever it's
called was it called a new game ultimate numbers go ultimate numbers go ultra
numbers go up I like the part where you did nothing all right I'll see you
tomorrow we are it's kind of up in the air at this point what I'm gonna do
tomorrow because as of as of today I'm not sure if there's enough to do a
community stream if there is you will know if there isn't then I have a couple
of things that I'd like to do tomorrow no it's not gonna be an idle game but
sometimes I just want to sit here and talk to you and hang out with you like I
said not every not every streams got to be about fucking filling up your water
but I'll see you tomorrow that's not on here why it worked it worked I did it I
figured it out what an egoist he has to be though I forgot I fucking did that I
looked at that right now I'm just like wait a minute I did that when did that
happen holy shit I did a hundred gifted subs okay well thanks everybody for
watching I'll see you guys tomorrow I always just lose my bets don't have I'm
never making a bet ever again unless I'm certain that it's winnable you're drunk
drunk on water and coffee apparently okay well let's do the bits thanks
everybody I see tomorrow regardless of what we do much love do you see some
let's go back and do the bits from earlier ow scroll scroll scroll here we
are so this is we had there was a lot of $50 5,000 bit drops today 5,000 bits
from phylactery Lich the Kronda Benfold ball of koala ball of koala gave 5,000
bits to thank you it was right off the bat right at the very beginning thank
you Jerma stinky feet for the 250 bits Jerma just admitted that he poops so
hard it displaces his intestines I said that shit this long ago oh we talk about
stretching I got a lot of heat for that by the way which I don't think I
deserved it for the story I don't think I deserve that heat I don't think so
let's get some tunes on here when we stretches everybody's got a prep that is
really funny though that's one hour and 23 minutes from computer turning on to
like okay the stream is I it's open now I've got to go get ready is like it was
an hour and 23 minutes but thank you for the to 250 appreciate it
sticks renegade thanks for the 250 hey Jeremy here's another car update I'm
officially degenerate what are you you're putting stuff all over the place
you keep like you keep putting stickers on your car thank you though I
appreciate it I'm gonna go ahead and say that I'm not gonna I don't want to show
your that part of your car on stream so thank you though appreciate it
speaking of cars there goes one imagine the person gifting 25 subs to get
overshadowed by the streamer it was hurricane turtle for 20 but yeah I know
what you mean enjoy those buffalo wings you're welcome I will I've been in such
a great mood lately have anybody else noticed that nothing I've ever in a bad
mood I think it was I was ever since like a week or two ago I've just been in
a great fucking mood buffalo wings tonight oh just being elevated twitch
calm was great too it was awesome I'm okay you know I'm coming off of like the
twitch con high it was just a really really fun wonderful time but thank you
for the 250 sticks renegade you that by the way they say also in reference to
the ass wiping convo I can wipe my ass in one minute no you can't I can wipe my
ass in one minute 100% clean then I shower to clean even further yes every
time well that means that you weren't a hundred percent clean you wouldn't need
to take a shower after you go to the bathroom if you were out a percent clean
oh god but thanks a lot appreciate it boneless bacon thanks for the thousand
bits German you smell go take a shower not really I don't think so just wear
brown underwear forehead I've I have a poo poo community huh yeah I have a good
I have like a shit let's let's talk about like poop and shit and stuff
community now do not do I we have to get rid of this is that this has to get
wiped out and I'm talking about we're talking from the top starting with me I
think when I talk about like diarrhea and stuff anymore how am I ever gonna
get those brand deals hey thank you bake me home for the 620 bits cheering from
my new chat badge nice also my Andy mark goat arrived with bits of carnival dirt
on it pretty authentic really that's awesome are they still available you
should be might be I'll still get it with real carnival dirt because it
probably hit the floor so that's how you know it's real but when last night
nice we got a link was a link to the Andy mark goat site all these goats are
authentic part of the carnival there's real dirt on them but yeah thanks for
the 620 bits stay tuned there's much more to see sooner than you think oh
yeah thank you to Das night for the thousand bits hey German start my first
day of uni tomorrow and I'm writing to thank you for the years of entertainment
took a lot of hard work but I managed to get into my dream University hell yeah
and your streams are the perfect thing to relax to and have fun within these
last years of school you shouldn't be surprised to hear that whenever I've
mentioned you to someone else the first reaction is always oh yeah that guy's
great or yeah I love those videos so keep up the good work old chap that
makes me happy I know what you like we fuck around a lot but I'm glad that
people think this is fun I don't want you to not think it's fun I don't want
me to think this was I would much rather prefer that people take something
good from this not like oh positive only positive positive positive positive
positive that's not really what I mean I just mean that no matter what happens
on these streams what you can take something from it I'm upcoming negative
stream coming up soon no but anytime I hear something like that I did that
makes me want to do better to be honest saying like oh that guy's great I love
those videos that's like I say that's awesome I should try harder now I
should do better I really appreciate it thank you for the thousand bits and good
luck at University getting into your dream University it's awesome glad to
hear it that was a das night 20 community subs from Paraguay who was the
dev of this game that we played the game's free if you want to do it
yourself this is now is this video this the stream had nothing to I this is not
an ad stream or a sponsor stream it's yeah I mean it's free if you want to try
it go for it if not then whatever who cares around it is now no it's just a
fun little game and I saw that I was like let's try it best part about this
is I'm getting rebirth time counting up I'm not even playing sitting here in the
outro good stuff you saw somebody with a glue man shirt on at your school you
should immediately befriend that person but thank you to the mocks for the
thousand bits hey look it's that guy saw at the carnival that's me smiley face
thank you for the thousand bits appreciate it thank you
gibbler for the 500 bits when will streamer close the menu and start the
game hopefully I did it sooner than you thought you've been playing it
throughout the stream cool the prestige ing is fun Paraguay came through with
another six community subs right here well not here but you know a few hours
ago thanks a lot also lunch meat gave five community subs I think we caught it
but it's still sad Vega thanks to the 250 you bully listen to Kirby superstar
it's much more soothing than this bully I love Kirby we're talking about sticks
renegade thanks to the 250 you lied about drawing me you didn't draw me it's
been over a year I don't know how to draw every you don't want that drawing
thank you sloppy sloth thanks with five community subs thank you sad Vega for
the 250 it's an image they say I have been doing what are you saying I've
been sort of a cookie clicker of this you said I've been doing a two grandma
only non world destroying cookie clicker run for two years now I survived on two
grandmas and auto clicks alone until I got to spaceships so I could send my
cookies out into the universe then I added some luck fractals and Java
cookies and yeah you how long you how long you've been doing this for for two
years that's so that means you haven't cleared your browser cache in two years
you've not cleared your actual cookies in two years well you have a hundred and
twenty two quintillion cookies in this image I wonder how many trackers you have
on your browser and maybe more over two years only quintillions omega lol that
takes a long time though congratulations quack gave five community subs skater
kid gave five hundred bits German this is literally the first time I've ever
spent money on a twitch on twitch in four years I've been on here I heard you
on the official podcast today at work and I really have a lot of respect for
you as a content creator not everyone is as passionate as you are and I hope this
helps you keep up the amazing content whatever that may be as long as it makes
you happy because I think that's what separates you from a lot of the other a
lot of other people cheers thank you I'm happy to happy to be here official put
yeah the critical official podcast I was on it a while ago a couple years ago
right a year ago a year and a half ago but thank you um I've said this a bunch
of times before but I have to stay interested I have to stay passionate
about the things that I do because the second that I'm not interested in not
trying to give it as much as I can at least every so often I will turn to dust
what is this boss fight hold on what is this boss fight streamer boy versus
twitch chat hold on a second the same style here too and by the way can we
just say like that this track from blow it out is fucking perfect it's great
gonna get some more of these why can I not put this image on here my stream
my stream labs OBS has crashed I can't add I can't do anything oh there you go
just needed a minute streamer boy versus twitch chat oh I get it those are the
views going those are the viewers going down I understand there was still a lot
of people here I think that was a pretty good turnout and about all the views
that's the dev official art from the dev that's awesome half those people are
gone yeah well we ended the stream we ended the stream like 40 minutes ago 30
minutes ago if you are new to the stream though hopefully you stick around if you
don't if you're just checking out the stream for like a week or two just seeing
what the hell is this guy all about what's this community all about and then
you're out of here well maybe we'll see you again some other time but if you
stick around I can promise you that there's way way more to see thanks for
checking the stream up as I play an idle game I got so much stuff that I'm doing
please watch me stare at a bar they can't all be fucking carnivals you guys
know that what are we doing tomorrow tomorrow is probably gonna be the
community night unless there's not enough stuff back to the bits though but
thank you that was skater kid that gave the 500 bits I'm glad that you have
found this stream and that it clicks with you it's all I care about yeah this
is also C Zekson C Zekson's s Zekson they say feetsie wheat seas feetsie
wheat seas thank you for the 300 bits appreciate hey German on a five thanks
for the hundred community subs now happy to do it thanks a lot appreciate that
hundred subs thank you dr. mcninja for the fourteen hundred bits fourteen
dollars thank you they just do a bunch of laughing faces hopefully something
was funny funny enough at least let's get the credits on here these are all
the subs and the community subs from today it's gonna go very fast cuz
there's at least 100 of them at least let's see it there it goes still not in
the right spot Jeremy what do you think hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on
ah there it is I got it exactly where it belongs it's going very fast but thank
you everybody and what do you say to start cleaning this up to places a mess
people throwing popcorn all over the place it will dump their drinks on the
ground this is a movie theater don't treat it like trash can guys spooky spit
fire thanks for the 250 bits I know chat didn't like Hollow Knight for some
reason Chad is nuts but if you play and beat silks on on stream I will give you
all the money in my bank account do not do that do not give me all the money in
your bank account that would be it would be silly that would not be smart I would
know I would extremely advise against that it's like 20 bucks you can't stop
him yes I can stop him because I'm not gonna play Hollow Knight on stream that's
the easiest solution there you go the new one is coming out though oh no see
me again at some time hmm when is it coming out next year or something I'll
take a look at it thank you mr. spoop for the thousand bits thank you thousand
bits ten bucks again thank you everybody for your subs appreciate it in fact
let's switch it over here sorry I bumped you but mr. spoop says hi
Jeremiah had a long drive today and listening to don't worry not watching
your stream helped it go fast talked about that in the beginning for those
that are curious just want to say thanks side note this is the first time I'm
giving bits and I saw that twitch had an option to pay with cash huh when you pay
okay I decided to try it out and drove to my local CVS needless to say the old
lady behind the counter was very confused when I told her I was paying
for an online service very strange experience anyways just thought I'd
share thanks again what hope your drive went very well this is like this two
different stories on this there's I had a long drive and I tried to pay for this
in CVS but thank you for the thousand bits ten bucks and hope you had a good
drive frilly d frilly d thanks for the five thousand bits from earlier why is
this guy so serious about vacuuming why the CVS proceeds so long yes why even
prints why even print receipts anymore what's the point all a receipt does in
2020 is get crumpled up into an annoying bulky thing in your pocket that you then
have to avoid when you're trying to get other shit out of your pocket that you
are actually looking for I can understand taxes for business expenses
right for tax purposes but why do I need a fucking ten foot long receipt when I
vitamin water not just for me it's for the coupons coupons it's an alibi you're
being accused of murder you killed two people you're a serial killer well I
have the CVS receipt that said I bought a vitamin water at fucking 2 52 p.m.
exonerated no you can just deep-fake that and just print out your own fake
receipt no that doesn't work anymore nothing works anymore nothing is real
anymore you can fake everything now you can print out your own receipt with your
own with the same receipt paper you buy it on fucking Amazon go to amazon.com
and type in receipt paper and then go to amazon.com and type in receipt printer
and then go to the web browser in your web browser and type in receipt maker
software and go make yourself a fake fucking receipt nothing is real anymore
seriously that sounds hard I'll just go to jail for 20 years oh fuck oh I'm
getting an ultrasound on my abdomen by the way now when I laugh really hard or
cough or like make any sudden movements inside of my right side it hurts yeah
congratulations the baby in here at least I'll get Disney World but thank
you for letting thank you Vilemi for the 5,000 bits is to back-to-back 5,000 bit
drops here derma say 0 W 0 I just did thank you both of you for the 50 bucks
5,000 bits thank you excellent excellent excellent excellent smelly
boy thanks for the 250 bits as Sonic as a character has lost a lot of his appeal
because his personality itself is dated Mario is basically a blank slate
character while Sonic has all the baggage of the mid to late 90s holy shit
you just figured it out quick quick quick quick quick smelly boy tweet that
tweet that so it's yours someone's gonna do that someone's gonna tweet that right
now and get like 5,000 likes on it don't let him steal your original content
tweet that right now that's a great tweet don't let that get stolen from you
guys get open Twitter real quick like we're all doing it thief thief thief
thief now that's yeah that's true it's true that doesn't make a lot of sense
hey Keith King Crimson thanks for the 250 the ultimate evolution of Sonic
going faster is making an idle clicker game where you keep increasing Sonic's
speed not a bad idea tweet that tweet that and make it yours except take away
Sonic have it be a different character speedo quick tweet it so it's yours
don't let anybody take that you wrote it here first I got it I have I have
documentation that you said that writer Keith King Crimson at 1943 p.m. on October
3rd 2019 said those words done it's now it's here forever not a bad idea though
hey gnarly thanks for the 250 I think this stream has solidified the fact that
I have the worst taste in German streams what I really like the Clocktower 3
Hearthstone and now the NGU stream good lord that doesn't mean you can take my
recommendations any less seriously Clocktower 3 was one of the top five
streams I've ever done what do you mean bad taste that was like one of my
favorite streams ever like top 10 really top 15 when did I do Clocktower 3 that
was a while ago was it like that was in Vegas though right that was post Vegas
move six months ago seven months ago something like that earlier earlier this
last year something like that you don't have bad taste we time Hearthstone all
right I'm gonna have to disagree with you because I think that streams bad hey
doesn't matter how bad that stream was I opened 50 packs automatic good content
I had to go during the clicker RPG thing what happened I slayed some demons the
numbers went up they did yeah thank you bone jackal for the 500 bits germ I've
been stuck in this car going past your house for hours trying to get your
attention if I slow down below 70 miles per hour you're doing a speed joke okay
please get out of here help me this is a speed thing all right well what's my
favorite stream all of them except for Mario tennis that's actually the stream
that I don't I like the least like if I could delete a stream from everybody's
memory would be that one if I had like a genie that came up with three wishes one
of them would be to delete the Mario tennis stream like I never happened not
even the bird the birdhouse stream was fucking awesome we talking about that
was that was great I made a birdhouse on stream you I still own it I still have
it it's out there birds are in it 23 hours from now you know I should do like
a German lie emote but it's German 23 HR German 23 HRS interesting but thank you
bone jackal hopefully you figure it out hey white Fox thanks for the thousand
bits hey man because you're basically my therapist here we go I started a PhD in
genetics this month holy shit but it's four hours from my fiance and we miss
each other long-distance wedding planning is ass considering just
dropping the program and moving to be closer to her have some connections with
entomology closer to her but it pays less what's your advice also more
importantly it hits her ass I'd read that okay I'm a whole I'm a whole picture
kind of guy there you go it's your answer that one why did I answer it I
don't know but to answer the other question you need to do what you fuck
you need to do what you think you need to do what you think is best if you
think that making more money is more important to you then do it if you think
that being closer to somebody that you really care about is more important to
do it you are right now you are getting telltale to right now unfortunately it
happens at least a few times in everybody's life you get telltale
no no you have like a choice that affects your life that is really one or
the other it depends how much less money right it is if are you talking like a
million versus like 50 grand you know I'm saying is it like ridiculously less
then that weighs a little more right weddings are really pricey they are I
would say if it's as large monetary gain yes but you also want to stay happy you
want to keep yourself happy if work is not going to make you happy then do the
thing that's going to make you happy if being closer to somebody that you really
care about is going to make you feel better and your job that you could do
there better I would say do that because you don't want to run into a scenario
where you're very far away and you're making a little bit more money but you
wish you weren't doing that you need to be completely comfortable with that
decision and I think the comfortable decision is the second one but it also
depends as a lot of factors here it appeared how much do you want that PhD
how long is it gonna take if you can put up with doing that for a little while to
get your PhD and do that then it might be worth it you know I'm saying why are
you asking this motherfucker for advice
easy I'm trying to help no but for real it's given advice like this is tough
because I don't know where your priorities lie everybody has different
priorities everybody has a pre shit prep everybody's a post shit prep some
people stretch that's what I've heard but your plan has to be what you want not
what I would want because I don't know if what I want is what you would want to
to me it sounds like you are putting a lot of weight on being closer to the
person that you love sometimes that on the scale tips way more and depending on
how loud like I said how long it takes for you to get that PhD it might be
worth doing it and then moving depends on how badly you want I'm avoiding the
question I just I just said I just said the second one's probably a better idea
I just said it I just did it I just said it I just said it I just said that okay
I already said it he asked for advice not a self-help novel well I would how
do you give advice but advice that is advice I am given advice that that's
what I'm doing white Fox don't listen to these
jokers in here but I the most important question there was you know I answered
it for you jokers you're doing your best but all jokes
decided it's hard to give advice when I don't know the kind of gravity of the
situation I don't know what you really want it's gonna take a lot of thinking
but hopefully you figure it out I really do wish you the best but if you're good
at something never do it for free that's exactly yes hey Aqua Reaper thanks for
the thousand and five bits Jerma how do you feel that I live in your house and
always remain out of sight waiting to strangle you well that was fucking
strange when you finally catch a shiny Pokemon Jerma how do you feel that I live
in your house and always remain out of sight waiting to strangle you to death
when you finally catch a shiny Pokemon what the fuck is this message listen to
me I don't play Pokemon and I'm quick that quick yet I don't play Pokemon I
poke it I don't play Pokemon that's just fucking this is fucking me up so much
thank you to thank you to scooch for the 300 bits I can't believe I've been
here so long I remember watching during the old TF2 days been loving everything
you put out I've been so busy hold on oh my goodness okay anyways I'm here
watching during the old TF2 days been loving everything you put up been so
busy and I've been missing some lately but I at least was able to catch the
carnival I'm glad you did anyways I've been trying to introduce some friends
to you but I've had some trouble choosing a good intro video to your
channel any suggestions video I would say Jerma Rumble live is pretty good one
I think Mario tennis get the fuck out of here with that one I the German the
German Rumble series I think is pretty good start I think that's some of my
proudest work I still do have proud work too that's not that but that was the
culmination of my entire life on YouTube so that requires so much
knowledge that's why you started one you started one Castle Griffiths did it as
well I think it's just standalone really really really like that video there's
there's a lot or just start them with the Dark Souls 3 streams then they so
you can they can know that I did it on stream that I'm very good at video games
sometimes that's where you should start thank you KXE 501 what's going on welcome
back KXE thanks for the thousand bits thanks for another great stream hope
you're doing well these days I'm doing great I am doing great better than ever
I feel great except for my abdomen this is a problem in there we'll figure it
out a see-through gold play I wouldn't start there you know I would start them
on this stream yeah because if you can't handle this stream how the hell can you
imagine handling anything else if you can't handle me at my worst obey your
If you can't handle me at my best take a fucking rest sleep all right guys
theaters now closed get out of here yeah get out here see you guys tomorrow for
something something something something something something wait a good night
goodbye have a wonderful rest of your night see tomorrow much love to y'all
check out the game the game the game the game the game and GU idol and hot lava
was fun I'm just not very good it was still fun and I've got an hour and 17
minutes here and rebirth this it's gonna be great I'm gonna eat like a huge I'm
gonna meet a huge just bucket of wings watch numbers go up for the rest of the
night I think and then fall asleep good night everybody see you tomorrow