What are you guys doing? What is this? Stop writing that. Don't write that. What's wrong with you?
What is this? I don't get it. It's a it's a penis curse. I don't know what that means.
He doesn't know. No, I don't at all. I have no idea what you're doing. There's a lot of- wait,
is this a chant? Are you chanting? Yeah, twitch added copy to clipboard. You're chanting. You know
for the time that shit goes by too fast, you can't copy it and spam it fast enough. In comes
chanting. Making your life as a twitch viewer that much more simple. Uh, let me tweet this. I'll be
right back. Okay. Hello. How are you? Today we're gonna play Fable 2, or at least start it and
play it for a little while. I think Fable 2 is like 12 to 16 hours. We'll see how far we get in two
days. I don't know. I don't know. We might go halfway Andy and I might just get to like 60%
of the way through the game and be like, nah, that was fun. You forgot the gif. You guys have
to understand, I've said this a bunch of times, but it's very very accurate. I need to make it
very clear. From the beginning of last stream to the end of last stream, I remembered that stuff
like an hour after that stream finished. Today, from the beginning of this stream, I don't have
any memory of almost anything that happened on the last stream. We're in a new period here.
I'll remember this shit for like the next probably few hours after the stream's over,
maybe tomorrow morning. I don't, there's too much for me to remember. What stream? The one
from last week. I know I played Resident Evil 8. I know I did like a Wile E. Coyote routine with
one of the werewolves. I remember the big lady. I remember like screaming a bunch of times. That's
it. That's pretty much it. I don't know anything else. I remember none of that happened. None of
us are real. There is something I do have to tell you, which I'm not necessarily happy with, but
next weekend on Sunday, I have somebody that has been blowing my phone up and
I have a contractual obligation kind of to let them stream. Let me just give it to you long and
short. They were pissed off that they weren't involved in a stream from last year and I get
texts from this person every like six days. Hey, is it cool? Can I do like my routine? I'm like,
no. I don't fucking want you. Look, you weren't there and the stream didn't happen, so I can't.
This person just fucking won't leave me alone, so I'm going to give them the opportunity to do a
routine for you, okay? That's next weekend. I don't have any idea what the fuck they're going
to do, but that's Sunday. I don't know if I wouldn't miss it if I were you. Maybe I would.
Depends on who you are. Depends on how you like anybody. Depends on how much you like somebody.
I don't know. They're going to have control and that's it. That's all you need to know. Sunday.
Either on Sunday. Next Sunday. Stream is on Sunday. Next Sunday. Be there. Or don't.
Ugh. Zero viewers. I don't, I have no idea. I don't want to tell you who it is.
Rather you just get surprised or not. But now we're going to play Fable 2. Probably play Fable
tomorrow. I'm going to do a two-day in a row of streams. You should stream at the same time.
I can't because they were supposed to be on my stream, so I can't do that. What if Fable sucks?
You know, if Fable sucks. I know. I played this game before. I played Fable 2.
I know what I'm getting into. Fable 2. Let me just make sure everything works.
I think this should be fine. This game was a lot of fun from what I remember.
I can't hear anything. Oh, there we go. Okay. I got to turn the volume up on my monitor.
It is far too low. There we go. Do we have any potions or food? That's good. So I'm going to try.
I know that you look like the streamer thing to do in these games is to get a hundred percent evil
points. I'm going to try to be a very good boy. I'm not going to like kill anybody. I'm not going
to hurt anybody. I'm not going to like kick any chickens and stuff and get yelled at. I'm going
to be a very extra good boy. I'm already seeing Resident Sleepers, but everybody does. Everybody
is evil. Everybody is like, oh, look at me. I'm evil. I have horns. I'm so bad. I'm evil.
I don't want to be evil. I want to be a good person. Don't Resident Sleeper that.
But who is the hero of our tale? I want to be a good boy. You're not going to be able to resist.
I'm going to try to be a good boy. I didn't say I was. Then let his destiny unfold.
Oh shit. I remember this part. You remember when I was like a kid, didn't they do the thing?
This is like Link grows up into like big Link, right? So many people tried to copy that shit
after they did that. Remember that? Remember Ocarina of Time? It was like, look, you play as
Link and then like your adult Link. Everybody desperately tried to do that too. All miserable
failures, by the way. This dude is ugly. Fucking 10 year old. What are you talking about? What?
He was talking about you. I'm not even on camera. This is Hogwarts. This is Harry Potter. This is
Hogwarts. The same intro happens. Wait, what? It is, right? The exact same thing happens.
Nice graphics. This game is on Xbox 360. Oh, I have to test to make sure there's no delay.
This bird poop is going to land on my head, right? Someone's going to lean in and go,
here's a chicken chisel. Bird pooped on chicken chisel's head.
I hear that's lucky, like finding a four leaf clover.
Why is there snow floating around? Is this snow or is this like fucking ash? Use LT to focus on
important events. It's a volcanic winter. I bet Lord Lucian's having roast duck this time of year,
but he must be really lonely since his wife and his little girl died
in that big castle all by himself. I don't even live in there. Oh, the town party. Follow the
glowing trail. Oh yeah, I forgot they did. Oh my God, this is ugly. This is really ugly. I forgot
like 360 looks like shit. That's rude. Follow the glowing trail to your next objective.
I don't remember it looking like this. Do I just?
I remember this. I say this on stream all the time.
I say this all the time. Yes, I do.
I've never said it. Yes, I have.
Unassuming box is actually a device created by the ancients.
Why would I even know that I said that if I didn't say it?
There's no such thing as magic. I feel like these
look like electrified. We live in grim times indeed. If the young are too world weary to
believe in magic, most children your age believe eagerly. I can see your eyes too much
fucking lit up snow. That's what the seller thinks. He has no idea what he stumbled upon,
but you have an inkling, don't you? Some part of you wants to believe it.
Why does the snowflakes have bloom on them? That seems so bizarre.
You really think it could be this looks like fucking radioactive.
You could have your answer. Listen to me, Rose. At the end of that week,
you and your little sparrow would be no closer to your dream, no closer to the inside of that
beautiful castle. We need five gold pieces.
I bet we could get five gold pieces, and maybe this could be a way out of here after all.
How does it look for you guys? It looks terrible for me. It looks awful. I'm looking at the OBS
monitor. It looks better through the OBS monitor than it does on my screen. It actually looks
better on the preview monitor. Okay, I need five gold pieces. This is to teach you the morality,
right? Okay. It doesn't look too bad. All right, earn gold by finding the arrest
warrants for Albion's most ruthless criminals. This is reminding me how much I hate this game.
Okay. Nobody hates this game. They hate the guy that made this game. This game is actually fun,
kind of. All right, let's go get them. All right, let's go. So we're looking for warrants. No,
it's because of the snow. This is fine. I'll get used to this. Oh, thank God there's an imbecile
trail. All right, let's go. How about Barnum by posing for a picture for one gold piece?
Blur is disgusting.
How come this is not PC? That's kind of weird. Beer goggles? How do I pose? I just farted. I
didn't want to do that. I was supposed to be a good boy. Okay, well, I'm already a bad boy.
Already evil? No, not yet. Farting isn't evil. It's a natural part of your body's ecosystem.
Imagine thinking farting is evil. All right, we gotta find warrants.
This guy might have a warrant. Oh, what? Why is he glowing? Oh, friendly villager. Okay. Can I go
out here? I'm gonna turn the game on. No, okay. Once the snow is gone, everyone will be like,
this is fine. All right, what about this way? That guy who did that. Oh, thank God for the
imbecile leader. What happened? Hey, don't do that. All right, let's kick his ass. Hey,
my God, she just dropped. She's like unconscious. I don't remember this part of the game.
All right, so where's the money? Oh, wait, that was for free. All right,
we're good people. We're just a good boy for free. What about the dog? Is the dog okay?
How do we help the dog? Oh, yeah. You get a dog, don't you?
We don't have enough food for ourselves. I remember this part of the game. This is like
the best part of the whole game was that they're very realistic dog. I remember,
didn't Peter Molyneux make a huge deal about this? It was like the dog who spent 6,000 days
animating the dog. Oh, I got good boy points there. I don't want bad boy points. Oh, here we go.
The dog. All right, what does this do? Clear Balthazar's warehouse of beetles or smashers
stock. What do you mean smash? I can smash his stuff?
All right, so don't break anything. Sir, you are going to have to go through the proper authorities.
I am not going to do that. Certified good boy Jeremy Albertson. All right, where are the bugs?
Why does this kid have a... That's boring. Holy shit. Smash. No. How am I supposed to be certified
good boy Jeremy Albertson if I'm... No, I'm not going to break anything. Don't you understand?
We have to have something event happen in our life to create us our origin story to be the villain.
The Joker wasn't the fucking Joker when he was like 8. He was a good boy.
That was a massacre. No mercy for the filthy buggers. That's what I like to see.
You weren't supposed to kill them. Now I think about it. I wonder how those beetles got in there.
Yes, he was. I watched the cartoon. What did you say? Did you say the cartoon?
I didn't know you were so good at fighting. We're really doing it.
Here we go. More decision making. I need two drinks.
Cover the stolen bottle. Where are the warrants? So you'll bring me back my bottle? Yes.
You'll find it and bring it to me, won't you children? Oh, okay. So we have to bring the
bottle and bring it to this lady because we're a good boy. Oh, hi dog. What'd you find? A warrant.
Nice. Nice find. Thank you. Thank you. Oh, I know. You're sweet. No, I'm the good boy.
But I told you before. We can't keep you. Come on, little sparrow. What did we find?
The warrant! Any Carmen Sandiego fans here? I guess not.
All right, more warrants. That's why. No, put the gun down. No, put the sword down and put the gun
down. Put the gun away. Oh my God, my face. Put it down. No, how do I just put it away?
Don't wake him up. How do I sneak? How do I sneak? There is no sneak.
Run. All right, return the wine to Pete. All right, we're going to return it to Betty.
We're a good boy. Hard on them. Fine. I'm a good boy, but I do bad things.
Is that possible?
Wait, what?
So we both we get a gold piece no matter what. So let's just do the good thing.
Yeah, I'm good. Take it. I think you guys are misunderstanding this.
We need to build up a hundred good boy points. Do good things. So then when I lose a hundred
points for drop kicking somebody through a window, I'm fine. I'm still normal. Did you get it?
All right, we got three gold pieces. Three gold pieces. All right, I think there's more warrants
up here. Wait, what does it say? Read? Brookridge. You know what's really important, too? We have to
decide. I'm gonna have to do a poll. Because we have to pick, right? Like melee, ranged,
or magic. Melee, ranged, or magic. It's a big decision. Magic, magic, magic, magic.
Range, range, range, ranged. Let's go back to the guard. Melee, melee, melee, melee, melee. Hey,
kids. Oh, cool. A fart party. Why can I do it? How come I can't do it? I could show all these
kids like who's the best, the biggest farts. All right, I'm leaving. How come I can't do it?
Uh-oh. Stop right there. Shut it, girl. This isn't about that. Those warrants you're collecting.
Oh, really? So does our friend the guard. Yeah, but you're gonna give them to me. See?
I'm just gonna pop this guy. Otherwise, there'll be trouble. There'll be trouble, all right?
You take these, and I'll tell our friend what you really want.
All right, you little hard case. What's he paying you? A gold piece?
Well, yeah, a nice premium you're paying me. One gold piece? You pay me a three gold piece premium
to even consider this shit. Get the fuck out of here. Did you not understand crime? Like,
you don't understand how this works? I would have considered it for three or four gold pieces.
You're gonna give me the same that I would get for bringing it to the guard?
Do you even understand fucking crime? My empire begins now.
Thanks. I've savored. Now, normally, justice is its own reward. But as these aren't normal
circumstances, there's your gold piece. Okay, I need one more. Let's pick my nose.
That just sold out this town. You just need one more.
What is this? What are we doing here? I think mother heard us.
He's an evil good boy. I- unlike the- unlike the spectrum of good, bad, like, evil, does evil
things, does good things. I just want us to be just orbiting around in a circle,
around that whole spectrum. Magic? 71% magic. What the fuck? Speak to Monty.
Are you an anti-hero or an anti-villain? Yes.
Why'd you ask me then? Maybe we could help you.
Hyperactive good boy with villainous tendencies. Where's that one?
You can take my proposal letter to the fair maiden. Oh, there is hope.
My heart soars in my chest like- Oh, you know who it would be?
I would be Loki from Marvel. That's who I want to be.
We'll do it for a gold piece. Oh, I'm a bit strapped right at the moment.
But Belinda's good for it. I'm sure she'll pay you when she receives my letter.
All right, deliver the letter to Monty's beloved. Let's do it.
Give us the money. Don't let her mom get it.
Oh, wait. Okay, so let's just give it right to the mom?
What's the good thing to do here? Deliver it to mom.
Just say, hey, there's this guy outside. Is that James Corden?
I don't know. I didn't know who that was until I had to think about it for a second.
And thinking about it for more than two seconds, I just saw in my brain
a profile shot of him in a car bouncing around singing a song with his hands on the wheel.
And then, oh, okay, now I know who the fuck that is.
What do you want? We've got a letter. We need one gold for the postage.
Kath, there's more than one British person.
There is more than one British person on Earth. Yes.
Don't you touch anything.
Okay, I'm a good person that does bad things sometimes, right?
Monty told us not to give it to the mother. But she'll pay us if we just wait here.
But then if we give it to Belinda upstairs, maybe they can run away together.
What's the good thing? I don't know what's good. What's easiest?
I don't know. You put these things somewhere so no one can find them and then you can't find them.
Letting the mother have it would be easiest.
Look, I have a letter for you, but it's going to require one specific thing.
I'm going to need one gold coin and two of your finest pieces of jewelry you have in the house.
This is how crime works, okay?
Do I need to explain it to you?
Shouldn't I be in school?
I don't know. Was there school back in like...
In like the 1500s? Did kids go to school in like the 1400s?
I don't think so.
No. When did... Okay, when was the first school?
Oh, I'm missing like the important stuff. Hold on. Watch out.
Oh wait, I can...
Rude. Point and laugh.
Social. Okay. Thumbs up.
Oh, look at me.
Maybe you should marry her instead.
What am I doing?
What was that? What is scary? Bloodlust?
Where did this kid come from? Why is there a kid in here?
No, I'm good. I just do bad things.
I'm scaring this kid.
That really is awful.
All right, get out, get out, get out, get out. Time to leave, leave, leave.
I was just trying to scare a kid. Art on the kid. No.
All right, let's buy the music box.
Okay.
24th and 23rd century BC established the first school. Okay.
Why when getting an item in the description?
Oh, a chicken. I didn't want to do that.
I wanted to like pet... I just pressed A.
I did not know it was going to kick the chicken.
I already ruined it. All right, let's use it.
Oh, make a portal to another dimension.
Or whatever this does.
Right now, the production company's splash screen comes up.
The black screen.
What?
Oh, the dog.
Well, I'm glad the box didn't take us because...
Dr. Ruff.
R-U-F-F. That's Dr. Ruff PhD.
We're gonna have like a dream or something.
Quiet, boy. What do you want?
I work for Lord Lucian, miss.
And he would very much like to see you in his castle.
I've been sent to collect you.
Who's this kid?
Wait, did I like teach this kid how to do weird things?
Why is this kid in the house?
Who is this kid here?
Is this a party member?
All right. Well, cool.
Thanks, kid.
Does dog shit on him?
Wait, what's that?
I can't...
Oh, here we go.
Oh, he hates me.
Well, what are you gonna do about it?
Get out of here. Get out of my house.
It took a while for his AI to figure out what I wanted to do there.
All right, let's go.
Oh, wait a minute.
They're coming to get us.
Go to Castle Fairfax.
Hold on to the emote.
You see, why did anyone like this game?
I mean, this game 15 years ago was pretty...
It was pretty good.
Okay.
Yeah, we're very like special children, right?
Okay, I can't fart.
Sorry.
This is the best fable?
I think that's accurate.
Why is this still...
Bro, you're playing on an Xbox.
Yeah, Xbox 360.
Oh, I know the whole story.
I forgot.
You don't care if I spoil the whole game?
Okay. All right.
I won't.
All right, all right.
Yeah, we won't.
This story is so funny.
This is just a Minecraft sword.
From like the 1200s.
All right, well, let's go.
Let me in.
Hello.
Oh, he's evil, right?
What was your wish?
Exactly.
Yes, my lord.
You sold it to us.
Said it was magic.
The boxes have no interest to me.
What's remarkable is that you...
Yeah, the sideburns are like Pinocchio for evil people.
The bigger your sideburns, the more evil you really are.
If they're like an inch down, like I write, you're kind of a dick.
This far, this guy is a fucking horrible person.
Like this guy is an awful tyrant that has probably killed thousands of people.
Perhaps that could be arranged.
I am working to rebuild something wonderful.
For which I need individuals with particular talents.
Let us find out if...
If you're bald, you're good.
Would you kindly stand in the circle, please?
Oh, would you kindly?
I'll do it.
He said it.
He said the thing.
I promise.
All right, well, yeah, right.
This is like a...
You want me to get on there, too?
Stand at the center.
Like this guy's eyeing me from across the bar.
You know what I mean?
Like what did I do?
Why does this guy fucking hate me?
What's going on?
What did I do?
Now, we're junior heroes.
Oh, come on.
Come on.
That's Donald Duck from fucking Kingdom Hearts.
Get out of here.
That's...
I give myself a plus two.
I don't care.
Run.
Get down, sis.
I couldn't stand in front of her.
We just shot like a little kid.
I'm sure there was some other way to do...
To handle this.
Thanks for like letting us go get a fucking music box.
And like...
My like sister gets shot and I get thrown out of a window.
Thanks, lady.
A thousand foot drop.
Yeah, I like hit my head on the side of a building, too.
There's no way I survived, though.
Lucian disappeared from Castle Fairfax that night.
Certain that those who might stand in his way were dead.
But some grief is so great, even death may keep its distance.
And so the boy survived.
Days later, far from the dark alleys of Bowerstone,
life slowly returned to his small broken body.
The boy awoke to a familiar face watching over a strange bed.
He reached out for the comfort of the dog's warm fur.
Yeah, that was an interesting thing to get right after that cutscene.
Oh, like a little girl gets shot and you get thrown out of the window and like die.
Be careful not to hold the fart button down or you'll shit your pants.
Not really appropriate place for that tip, I don't think.
Ah, there you are.
And your faithful friend, too.
Right.
Many years ago, I promised I would help you avenge your sister's death.
That day has come.
Today, you leave the safety of this camp and seek out Lucian.
The journey will not be easy.
There's a chest near your caravan.
Oh, nice.
Meet me by the gates when you're ready to leave.
Is this where I get to learn magic?
I can't wait.
I'm going to start to learn the fire spell, the ice spell, the wind spell, the lightning spell.
Oh, can't you buy stuff?
You can buy this house.
Once you own it, you can choose to live there and receive special bonuses or rent it out to any.
Oh, wow.
How much do I have now?
Make sure you put your house up for rent before you leave.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
I don't have any weapons.
Where's my house?
Buy and move in, buy and rent out.
How much money do I have?
I have zero dollars.
I don't have any money.
That's yeah, I get his name right.
That's Dr. Ruff PhD.
Turn safety off?
What?
Do I have a gun?
What does that mean?
Turn safety off.
Is that a secondary fart?
Your actions have affected your purity.
What?
What do you mean my purity?
I'm no longer pure?
Someone has just tried flirting with you.
Why not try flirting back?
Who?
What is flirt?
You got the attention of somebody.
Everyone wants to have my attention.
All right.
How about who likes me?
You like that?
Do I just keep doing this?
Everybody loves me.
All right.
I don't want to do this yet.
The villagers attracted to you.
You can use flirty, fun, and social expressions to make them like you.
Maybe even marry you.
Okay.
Don't you think that's a little quick?
I just woke up in the town and I'm going to have like a wife immediately.
You and I are now we're in love.
Oh, by the way, get you a man that can do this.
I mean, we're going to get married?
It's too...
It's so early.
It's so early for this.
I don't even know what this person is.
Are we married?
Okay.
So what is it?
Time?
Now what happens?
Okay.
I think somebody's in love with me.
Um, flirty, a row of pickup line.
Here we go.
Okay.
Now what?
Turn safety off and start swinging at everybody.
No.
Nobody hates me here.
Hey, why does everybody hate me?
Everybody's supposed to love me.
Okay.
So let's get, get me out of here.
Now what do I do?
Give gift.
You have no items.
A birthday?
Oh God, that's disgusting.
What am I doing in public?
What am I doing?
Yeah.
All right.
I have to leave.
I need to like do a mission or something.
What the fuck am I doing?
You are loved by enough people to be Albion's dumpling?
What?
Oh, plus 34 hate.
Albion's dump truck.
All right.
I have to get out of here.
Somebody say, somebody just say I'm going to puke.
I'm going to puke.
All right.
I'm going to leave.
Goodbye.
It was really fun.
Now I press down to use the follow expression to lead villages to places they like.
Oh shit.
All right.
Follow me.
Okay.
All right.
Let's go.
But where are we going?
I don't have any items into a bed.
Oh shit.
Okay.
Where's my bed?
Do I have a bed?
This is my house.
Oh, okay.
Let's go.
Wait, why do I have what are we doing?
Okay.
You ready to let's go to bed.
Wait, I can't.
I don't think I can do this.
This villager wants to marry you.
I thought that said rest for 20, rest for seven days.
Oh my god.
That's too much.
Hold on.
Wait, wait.
I need to get my items.
There we go.
I need a ring.
It's like 10 million dollars for a ring.
Okay.
Rusty long sword.
I'll use it.
Take it.
Dog elixir.
Caller of holding.
Spade.
Okay.
STD speed run.
Don't.
No.
Wait, that can happen.
That doesn't happen, right?
Someone just tried flirting with you.
Is this the same person?
No, this is different.
This is a different person.
Rent your house.
Hold on.
Okay.
Rent out.
Base value 800.
Final price.
All right, let's rent out.
A delightful caravan that has traveled far across Albion.
Okay.
Make sure you want to rent out this property.
Yes.
Cool.
All right.
Whoa, you got a gift?
Give someone a gift.
I'm not gonna give her a caller.
Gotta get out of here.
I gotta get out of here.
I'm getting out of here.
I'm gonna do the mission.
No, everyone get away from me.
No, I'm not giving anybody a caller.
The villager wants to marry you?
Not yet.
Let me do like a mission first.
Why am I walking so slow?
Take this.
She's still following me.
Bower Lake Tomb seal.
Are you gonna keep following me?
Oh.
Okay.
Enter Bower Lake Tomb.
Throw it out.
Jock it out.
Big spot.
Oh, cool.
Nice.
All right.
Let's dig.
Give the dog the caller.
What'd I get?
A rubber ball.
You can find books that will train your dog
to find even more valuable hidden treasures.
All right.
You want to play with the ball?
You want me to throw the ball, I think.
While near your dog, you can throw the ball.
All right.
Come here.
Let's do it.
You ready?
Here we go.
Go get it.
What?
Go get the ball.
No.
All right.
I'll throw it this way.
Go get it this way.
Come on.
I want to throw it for you.
Come here.
You threw it off a cliff.
It just dives.
All right.
Well, how about this time?
Oh, the jump is safe.
Okay.
All right.
Come here.
I'm not going to throw it that far.
Ready?
Go get it.
Get it.
Did you get it?
You're kind of stupid.
It's like right there.
Go get it.
How many balls do I have?
That was such a good job.
Let's go.
What'd you find?
Treasure?
Oh my god.
You found a treasure.
It is a jet.
Nice job.
Good job.
Good boy.
Good dog.
Such a good dog.
You did such a good dog.
Did the dog swim?
All right.
Let's go.
I love that dog.
Is there like a aim?
Okay.
You called him dumb?
I mean, I said he was kind of dumb.
I didn't say he's dumb.
Therefore, I hate this dog.
I said he's a little dumb.
That's okay.
He's a doctor.
Find the Chamber of Fate.
I'm speaking to you through the Guild Seal.
He's scared.
You will need to jump into that.
It's okay.
Don't worry.
The water at the bottom will break your fall.
This dog is...
This is a dumb doctor.
Well, we both have...
We all have to go in here, right?
All right.
Let's go in.
Let's go.
Where is he?
Holy shit.
Uh-oh.
Time for the first battle of the game.
Besides that kid.
Oh.
That was sick.
Lock onto your target.
Tap left or right to change which target you're going to focus on.
You can attack any object or person that glows red.
Yes, you can.
Those poor beetles.
Oh, that's right.
I forgot about this.
You have to kill things with a certain specialty
to get experience for that specialty.
I remember now.
I get it.
Yep.
I remember.
Use magic?
I don't have any magic.
It's like Warframe.
Silver key.
Look at the dog.
I love it.
Is that Warframe was?
Warframe?
Warframe.
Sorry.
All right.
Look at my health bar.
It's so small.
That's ridiculously small.
That's a joke.
It's like I died 15 times in a row in Dark Souls.
Easy.
It's a baby health bar.
It is tiny.
That's so small.
That's just stupidly small.
Anything in here?
No.
Quite a small health bar you have here.
Yeah, it is.
It can definitely be increased, though.
Don't worry.
If I remember, melee was actually pretty fun in these games, wasn't it?
Don't you have to string together combos?
Yes, you do.
Be sure to explore the world around you.
Following the glowing trail is extremely useful,
but there's so much to find off the beaten path.
We're exploring other corners of this cavern.
Is there going to be something for me?
Where's the bones?
Brendan's Diary.
It appears to be a page from an explorer's diary,
recording the details of an expedition into this cave.
My hand is shaking from exhaustion, but I must remain vigilant.
I almost nodded off last night as we camped around the fire.
I still manage to keep an eye on Eric and Drake.
I have seen the greedy glimmer in their eyes.
They mean to make the treasure theirs.
Oh, maybe it's time to make use of the poison.
Oh, shit.
Not Aaron.
Eric.
I just hit my head on that.
Brendan.
No.
Everybody hates that.
Eric's letter.
Soon we'll be rich.
Whatever.
There's not very many people that like the Aaron.
Wait, can I go up?
Can I get up there?
Nope.
How am I supposed to use magic if I don't have magic?
Do I get blessed at some point here in the minute?
I hate Attack on Titan so much.
I'm sorry to hear that.
I don't know.
Range weapon.
I like the ranged.
I really like the ranged, though, guys.
You just ignored that guy?
No, I would.
Okay, I've seen Attack on Titan.
I got through the first like five episodes and I was just like,
it was just like, I just too much for me.
I was just like, I can't do this.
Liar.
Outstanding fight.
Thanks.
You watched it till 3 a.m.
You don't know anything about what I've done.
Please watch anything but Attack on Titan.
What is that?
What's that from?
That's from something.
What is that?
Is he serious?
No, I like it.
I feel like I've heard that somewhere.
That like it's not.
No, no, no.
Not the song.
I know like the I'm talking about like the zoo, zoo, zoos.
It's from Jimmy Neutron guy.
Okay, listen, listen, listen, listen.
I got to clear this up.
I know that that's like the intro to the first season.
I'm talking about not the tune I was doing.
I'm talking about the zoos.
Like that's from something weird.
And I can't put my finger on it.
What is what is what is it?
Choon.
It's Jimmy Neutron.
The French song from the 80s.
What?
Oh, 150 gold pieces.
I think it's a random noise that you just thought of.
Yeah, maybe.
The hero of Oakvale.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, whatever.
No, it's real.
Oh, a mood ring.
All right, I have a ring.
I can get married.
It's from Augie and the Cockroaches.
You just made that show up.
That you made that.
You made that up.
That's not a real thing.
I've never heard of that show.
Hmm.
No man alive today remembers the night the guild burned.
And now it lies forgotten.
But the heroes are not all gone.
You are here.
And that same heroic blood flows through you.
It is.
It's real.
You're for the mightiest heroes who ever live.
At a young age, he suffered a devastating loss.
From which he never is alert alert alert.
Hold on.
But when the world tried to crush him, he fought back.
He grew strong, strong enough to reshape the world as he saw fit.
You must do the same.
What is it?
Y'all are weird as fuck.
The guild has reacted to you.
Step into the light.
Learn the true power of you.
Y'all are weird as fuck.
I need to...
All right, where is it?
There's no more links allowed.
But Maude's gonna have to do it.
Into strength, skill.
Strength improves combat.
With skill allows you to shoot faster and with greater accuracy.
Will gives you control over the forces of magic.
I'll give you the cockroach's intro.
Okay, hold on.
It reacts to the will of...
Yeah, yeah, I got strength, agility, or...
You have not been able to use will yet.
But the simple act of reaching this place has given you will experience.
You need to learn a will ability to activate the color's gate.
All right, is this it?
Where's the zzzz?
I don't hear it.
That's not what I was...
That's not what I was doing.
How would you even know that?
I don't even know...
How would you even remember this?
There's no way you could even remember that shit.
Fuck, it is that, but that's not it.
That's so funny.
You should buy a will ability so that you can activate that color's gate.
Sorry, I'm sorry.
Hold on.
Okay.
No, I don't want to throw the ball to the dog.
No, don't...
Will.
Shock.
Inferno.
Time control.
Blades.
Oh, hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Okay, area damage, target damage.
Inferno.
Calls forth magical flames to scorch and burn your foes.
That's from Frasier.
No, that's not from Frasier.
In the Frasier intro, he doesn't go...
It's...
He actually talks.
It's like a song.
He's like...
He doesn't say, like, zzzz.
I like this one.
Oh, fuck.
Okay, I gotta stop.
This one's cool.
I like that.
Okay, vortex.
Vortex creates a powerful windstorm that will pummel your enemies.
Ooh, alright.
This one's good too.
Vortex.
Chaos.
Chaos confuses your foes, making them unpredictable.
They may flee, attack their fellows, or even fall in love with you.
Chaos.
Force push sends a blast of energy towards your enemies,
hurling them into nearby objects.
Mm.
It is very effective in confined spaces.
Raise the dead.
Raise dead causes the bones of the recently deceased to rise and fight for you.
Okay, that's cool.
I think I want chaos.
Chaos confuses your foes, making them unpredictable.
They may flee, attack their fellows, or even fall in love with you.
No, do lightning.
No, I'm doing chaos.
What?
Oh, I don't have enough.
I can only do shock or inferno, and we're doing shock.
Shock stuns your enemies.
Okay, shock.
Abilities.
Strength, okay.
Brutal styles, physique, toughness.
Locking?
Brutal styles unlock special moves for use in close combat.
You still have a shit in your pants.
Yes, and I had unprotected sex with a big dump in my underwear.
That's when you want to get gross?
Go ahead.
Physique is just HP, right?
The stronger your physique,
the more damage you will cause with close combat weapons.
No, it's toughness.
I don't have enough to do anything.
...is able to withstand more damage before...
Brutal styles unlock special moves...
I can do this one, brutal styles.
Lock.
You can now hold down X to block enemy's melee attacks.
All right, let's go.
All right, so now I have my skill.
Can you feel the power coursing through you?
I can.
It is only the beginning.
Use your abilities to hit the split switch and power up the gate.
Click the switch.
Once activated, it will allow you to travel back to Brower Lake.
Whoa.
Come on, this is Chester.
Go to www.fable2.com to access the golden items.
What is this, a fucking ad?
Now you are ready to begin your journey.
Use the color space.
Oh!
Power up!
Oh, voice crack.
Too much power in my hands.
Not enough power going into my vocal cords.
That's understandable.
Damn, that was embarrassing, dude.
No, it's all right.
Did you see how much lightning I shot out of my hand?
Use your newfound abilities to defeat them.
All right.
I've never done magic in Fable, but wow, this is pretty good.
Wow.
That's pretty good.
Those two orbs hold the knowledge and experience of the creatures that you kill.
Cool.
All right, I did it.
Seven dollars income?
Oh, somebody's renting the house.
That's not very much money.
Can I die if I jump off this?
Unlimited power!
Is it mana?
I guess there's no mana.
Pretending?
Wait, what?
Oh, shit.
Reload?
How come everyone said I was...
Wait, because I didn't...
I thought somebody said I could...
Right trigger?
No, I think these are just glitched out from old right trigger.
Yeah, no, I can't pick these up.
Yeah, this is just...
Yeah, this is not...
I can't pick this.
This is like a glitch from the lightning.
Yeah, what are you guys talking about?
Watch Frasier on stream.
I didn't...
I never got into Frasier.
I didn't get it.
I just couldn't.
I was just like...
I couldn't follow anything going on.
I think I was just too young.
I was too young to care about Frasier.
The only thing that's in my brain from Frasier
is...
I don't know why, but like...
Him doing like Kramer-esque entrances into rooms
and like erratic movements and stuff
is like all I can see in my head.
I don't know why that's in my brain.
He's like opening a door going like,
What happened here?
I don't know why I'm making him and Kramer the same person.
Like in my brain right now,
I'm watching him open the door to Jerry's apartment
and like be Kramer.
I don't know why.
Can I eat those?
This is a silver key chest.
The number of keys needed to open it shown on the chest.
Oh, I can open it.
I only needed one.
Dog tricks.
The bunny hop.
Dog trainer and circus owner Rufina Musket.
Oh, shit.
Teach the dog a trick.
All right, come here, you.
Come here.
No, I want to...
Come here, I got to train you.
Come here.
No, come here.
All right, come here.
Watch this.
The dog can now bunny hop to see him do this.
Dance, laugh, whistle, play the lute or strike a heroic pose.
Okay.
Do you dance?
Is it?
All right, let's look for more treasure chests.
What's in here?
Keep it out for dive spots.
Oh, shit.
25 gold.
Nice.
All right, I can marry somebody now.
He's trying his best.
Yeah, he's doing fine.
He's doing great.
I was going to shock that guy.
Activity.
I'm afraid as long as the bandit tag is alive, the road stays closed.
We got to get rid of...
You could always take care of tag yourself.
I mean, when germ is streaming right now.
Okay.
The road to barstone is closed.
It would seem that has been capturing traders on their way to the bow lake camp.
He is a danger to all must be dealt with.
He's giving money.
You should be able to defeat him and his gang and continue your quest.
No doubt they are at his camp near bow lake.
All right, let's go get him.
Yo, when's this guy streaming?
Put it out.
How mad is he?
I just got here.
I'm not mad at all.
I'm perfectly fine.
Why do you guess I'm not...
I am not angry.
I'm happy.
I'm playing Fable 2.
Super nostalgic right now.
Having a lot of nostalgia fun.
By the way, don't miss next Sunday's stream.
Just want to make sure everyone's aware of that.
It may be a trap.
Sunday stream is going to be interesting.
I have an obligation.
Somebody has been blowing my phone up for a long time.
Finally going to get this person the opportunity they wanted a long time ago.
They're very excited.
Of course they are.
Just I'm not going to be on the stream.
I'm just going to let them do whatever they want.
And hopefully it's good.
I don't know.
Bandits.
Oh, that was easy.
Anybody else?
What do you mean I've been hurt by an enemy?
Oh my god, magic is awesome.
You can now afford force push.
It's just Jedi Academy again.
Yeah, it is Jedi Academy again, isn't it?
Oh shit, that was cool.
You got to keep like a combo going, right?
They're just waiting for you to kill them.
Whoa!
Oh shit, one, two, three.
Watch out!
Wait, did I kill him?
Why did I kill him?
Oh dog, are you all right?
Just shooting in random directions.
Okay, I got him.
You're now famous.
Dog, you hurt the dog.
I got him, I got him, I got him.
Come here.
The new hero.
All right, come here.
Come here.
You good?
There we go.
All right.
Good boy.
You all right?
Yes, you're okay.
Oh, that keeps it in his chest.
Don't worry, stand back.
That's not hurting him, is it?
What do you got in here?
Cage key, rancid beef jerky, and a money bag.
Nice.
All right, anything else?
Dog tricks.
I don't know, whatever.
Hey, mate!
Don't even think about letting them out.
Those slaves belong to me.
I paid for them.
Are you?
Okay.
Look, I don't want any trouble.
Give the key to me and I'll make it worth your while.
No, don't listen to him.
Never.
Shut up.
You wouldn't do that to us.
What'd you sparrow?
I said shut it.
I'm not gonna tell you again.
Uh.
Sir, what do you say, stranger?
Do you like giving a living?
Am I this bad?
I can't hit him.
Kill this piece of garbage, no problem.
You're right, I could, couldn't I?
Now you've gone and earned it.
You gonna say sorry?
Are you gonna say sorry or should I give you more juice?
Say sorry.
There is something you must see.
Come on, guys, let's go.
Thank you so much.
Free to wander the paths and byways of the land.
No, master, but the wind itself.
Time stretched out before is like, like, that's the word I want, Reg.
I don't know.
Turn safety on.
I'm going now.
Thanks again.
Should I turn safety back on or leave it off?
Oh, yes, thanks.
All right, I'm turning safety on.
All right, let me, hold on, let me look at what else we got.
They might have some fucking goodies.
It'll be funnier if it's off.
Not yet.
Let me at least get to, like, level two magician and then maybe.
All right, let's go back.
I can level up.
Can I level up right here?
I was at nothing in any of those.
House, house, house, house, house.
I'm looking at the house.
What's that?
Buy and move in.
This thing is 5,500 bucks near the door.
Is there money?
I can sleep in this guy's bed?
Oh, I thought that was a pot.
There's one gold in here.
Thanks, guys.
I'm glad I went back for it.
All right, where do I want to go?
What does, what's over here?
Is there anything ever in barrels?
Is there no reason for me to do this?
All the crates are always empty.
Okay, thank you.
Exactly what I was looking for.
Look at that pop in.
Do you get a horse in this game eventually?
This looks like, okay, you know what this looks like?
This looks like the full motion, pre-rendered,
like, advertising material for the game.
Do you know what I'm talking about?
This always seems really interlaced.
It's like a pre-rendered video of something,
but they have the settings all wrong.
But it's not even like, it's like a trailer.
Okay, it's me.
Well, it's my first one.
I'm just starting out.
How's it go?
Listen to this.
A hero went to Bower Lake and gave the thug a bellyache.
That's all I've got so far,
but maybe if I walk around Bowerstone with you,
I'll get some inspiration.
Really is quite foul.
That wasn't even a song.
You can't go to class with your book report,
with the title of the book report.
Come on, you're going to stop me
before I get in the hero of Bowerstone
and give me like, the fucking title of your song.
You know how much value my time is right now?
Trophy.
What was that?
Oh, thank you.
Hello.
Have you seen how big my muscles are?
How about a dance?
Oh, plus 24.
Holy shit.
Am I a chicken chaser?
No.
What else have we got?
Okay, a victory arm pump.
Very good.
Okay.
Thank you.
Hey, how about you and I get a coffee sometime?
I was open to see you today.
What?
This is so exciting.
Oh shit, where am I?
Where am I?
I have a ring, don't I?
I have a ring.
I'm already married.
No, I'm not.
More info.
Rachel, the housewife.
Middle class straight flirt.
Likes Fairfax demon door.
Homemade apple pies and dancing.
Doesn't like the bloodlust roar.
What did I just do?
Did I just give her a ring?
Did I just give it to her?
I just gave her the ring.
I gave her a book.
The Hero of Oakvale.
Harry.
Rancid beef jerky.
All right.
All right, come with me.
Follow me.
He doesn't like the ring?
It's a shit ring?
How much money do I have?
You gave her the ring pop ring.
This guy's chasing me.
Get away from me.
That's a cool bridge.
Just want to make everyone really clear around me.
Safety's off.
I just want everyone to know that here.
Anything I can help you with?
Cheers.
I'll pick it up tomorrow.
Okay.
Drinks trader.
What can I buy?
Uh, gotta be a box wine.
It's my favorite.
Okay, how much is this?
Eight bucks?
I'll take one.
I hope you enjoy it.
Have some value water.
Concentrated apple juice.
Oh shit, I'll take it.
Regret that purchase.
What the hell is this for?
Atness?
Bowerstone beer?
Yeah, I'll take it.
Deluded tomato juice.
Gross.
All right, what else do I got?
What about this guy?
Remember, it is a crime to hit innocents.
Is it now?
Okay.
Resliced mutton.
Salty beef jerky.
Atness.
All right, chicken fried button?
Oh yeah, let's go.
I hope you enjoy it.
Thank you for your custom.
Come back anytime.
Fish trader.
Treasure.
I know it's a crime to hit somebody.
Why is it so scared that I'm going to do something?
And I say, Jeremy, remember, if you hit somebody, it's a crime.
Don't do it.
Get out of the way.
Hey, safety's off.
That's right.
Oh shit, it's right there.
300 gold.
Holy shit.
Nice job, Doug.
Art until they pass out.
What the hell are you talking about?
A gold dump.
Town square.
I have bad news.
I'm afraid I will be delayed for a while.
In the meantime, you should buy some new equipment and prepare for the challenges ahead.
But you'll need money.
If you need money, there are jobs to be found.
I believe the blacksmith has an opening.
Town crier.
What are you looking for?
Sparrow.
Chicken chaser.
There it is.
500 bucks?
Get the fuck out of here.
This is a thousand bucks?
No, I want to be dumpling.
How is this not free?
It is free.
What's this?
What is this one?
That's me.
Dumpling.
Oh, this guy loves that.
They all lean down to get a better view of that.
That was disgusting.
Who's this?
I need some...
I need this to work.
Jeweler.
All right.
How about mood ring is...
How much is a jet?
Oh, fuck.
Sell that.
I don't need this thing.
Keep the mood ring.
Porcelain doll.
Poshness.
Wedding bells.
What's this?
A book of tips to make anyone fall in love with you.
Marriage and how to survive it.
Becoming a parent.
Beggar's ring.
Keep flowers.
Perfume.
Chocolate.
I'll buy some chocolate.
All right.
How about civil ring?
Okay, cool.
Total gold earned.
Required for promotion.
Take jobs.
What is this?
Tap A when the target is over the sweet spot to score a good hammer.
Make a perfect sword.
Okay.
I'm gonna go somewhere romantic?
Where could we go?
All right.
I gotta do...
I have to work.
Goodbye.
Hold on.
My leg is really itchy.
Old multiplier?
How do I get that to go higher?
Or...
That's it?
What?
Just don't fuck up.
Nice bit of forging.
It's closing time for all the shop.
I'm gonna just have a close sign.
Gold till promotion.
Okay.
This is like 30 FPS.
So the thing is actually moving really strangely.
You've been promoted.
Oh, let me do one more.
24.
Let's go.
Okay.
Take the next level.
You are now level two blacksmith.
Nice.
All right.
Let's do it again.
Bards of the past.
Back when there were heroes everywhere.
Human eye can only see 24 FPS anyways.
I know.
Out of my way.
I can't see.
Get out of the way.
This person just like breathing down my neck.
Get out of here.
Look at how shitty that is.
It's going so weird.
He was talking to shit.
You're all revolting disgusting animals.
We should close your web chat.
It's revolting.
All right.
Teresa's coming.
24 HP.
That's pathetic.
The 24 FPS thing rich behind the light exposure.
Computer monitors a bunch of lights.
Yeah.
I mean, all right.
If it's not 60 FPS, then I did get just get it out of we'll get it away from me.
It's a bunch of atoms.
Play VR at 24 FPS.
Cool.
Yeah.
That would be that would suck shaping up nicely.
That would be really awful.
I got promoted.
All right.
Take the next job.
Let's keep the multiplier going.
Level three blacksmith.
Let's go.
Seven thousand bucks.
That's how you make a blame.
Am I about to just make like 10 grand?
I'm going to buy a bunch of houses and stuff.
He's addicted.
Yeah.
I'm addicted to money.
I have 1500.
I want to have like 10 grand and I'm going to go buy like a really cool wand.
How many there's five levels.
This is going to take like 30 minutes.
No, it's no one.
I'm just going to do up to level.
I'm just going to get to the next level and that's it.
I'm going to go meet Teresa after I buy some new clothes.
I'm going to go buy a bunch of food.
I want to get fat too.
Like, of course, I'm going to do that.
If you're going to give me the opportunity to do that, you know,
I'm not going to be like the fat guy in the game.
Are you serious?
Why would I not do that?
I'm going to be like a big fat magician.
Oh, by the way, I got weighed recently at the doctor.
I'm 161 pounds.
I'm gaining and I'm gaining.
I've got to cut it down.
I've got to like, I got to change the diet a little bit, I think.
We don't care.
I do.
So I'm going to tell you about it.
I almost blew it.
Why are you telling us this?
I don't know.
Hey, but yeah, you screwed me up.
What do you mean?
Why wouldn't I tell you this?
What is this like stream?
I'm just, I'm going to tell you stuff that happens in my life.
You choked.
Yeah, because I'm talking about how fat I am and somebody said I don't even care.
And I'm like, well, I care how fat I'm getting.
No, I'm all screwed up now.
I'll get it.
I just checked your BMI.
Yeah, my BMI is probably like 70 or something.
70.
Yeah, 70 would be, I'd be made out of like butter.
I'm not even sure that butter has a 70% BMI.
BMI is body mass index.
Yeah, it's a nice fancy fucking thing that guys with the big fancy degrees
tell you to stop eating Doritos every day.
Okay, sure.
Oh, that, look, that was, that was fucked up.
That was fucked up.
You see that?
The FPS, it like skipped.
Remember, if you're 10 pounds overweight, you win.
What?
I believe I'm like five pounds overweight.
Which I can fix that.
That's easy.
I'll just, it'll be fine.
Running for my prostate exam was a, wait, what?
Just go in.
All right, I'm almost, I'm, I'm, I'm, my multipliers are getting pretty good.
This will be fine.
Don't screw it up.
144.
Let's go.
Five grand.
God damn it.
All right.
Wow.
That was a complete fake.
That was a total.
I should not have gotten that.
It was not even in the green, not even close.
I need to do 30 more.
No, I don't mean 30.
Fuck.
All right.
That guy fucked with me.
Whatever.
I'm done.
All right.
This Teresa.
All right, Teresa.
I'm here.
All the places you've been.
The people you've known.
Okay.
Up and down.
Everything you've done.
Make comments.
How many moments?
How many memories?
Fag and his men.
They had just as many.
And now they have none.
Because of you.
Do you feel the weight of responsibility yet?
No.
You will get used to the burden as all heroes must.
The world is better off without Fag.
And certainly Bower Lake is in your debt.
But to really see the impact of your actions.
You need look no further than Bower's town.
Consequences?
Uh oh.
It has changed much since you lived here.
Particularly old town where you spent your childhood.
I almost just pressed triangle and just shot that lady with a crossbow.
Even the simplest choice can have far reaching consequences.
That's going to happen eventually.
I know it is.
Oh, it's my old can.
Whatever this is.
That is where Lucian is now.
Hattered spire.
Where?
I thought it was in the moon.
The spire was intended as a conduit granting the kingdom's ruler a power so great
he could bend reality to his will.
The day it was completed.
And the first wish made.
A light bloomed inside.
Though its nature could not have been darker.
Being shattered.
Centuries of civilization were wiped out in moments.
Its people erased from existence.
Some say that this was the first wish.
An end to a hollow and corrupt world.
And for a purer one to take its place.
And now the spire rises once again.
Lucian found documents which foretold the coming of one
who would stop him using the spire.
That is why your sister died.
And that is why you will face him.
The cards have shown me this.
Here, take a look.
Eight cards.
Each of the three heroes you see in the cards
is a step on the hidden path to Lucian's downfall.
And the life force of heroes will itself is the key to the spire.
Why is he running?
Wait, what?
Lucian's agents scour the land even as we speak.
You must find the three heroes before Lucian does.
Because you are the fourth.
The one who will bring his downfall.
I have seen a vision of a holy ritual in Oakfield.
Salvation, though bittersweet, is delivered by one of incredible strength.
Speak to the abbot at the temple of light
and see what you can learn of this pilgrim.
The road to Oakfield will be dangerous.
You saw the poop in your pants?
Good luck.
How would you have seen the poop in my pants?
All right, I have money.
I want to buy some stuff.
What's that?
Oh, shit, look at this.
By Richard the Stonecutter.
Final price, $5,500.
I buy this?
Kill the owner.
Where is he?
Kill the owner?
Eliminate that guy.
All right, so if I tell somebody to follow me
and then I walk them into a bunch of bandits
and they just get killed.
I am not...
I don't kill them so I don't get bad person points
but I can just take the money that's on them
and then buy their empty house.
Is that accurate?
Pretty evil.
Sounds like a serial killer.
You're better off just being pure evil.
No, but then I don't get the benefits of being good.
Which, by the way,
what are the benefits of being good?
I've never done it in any one of these video games.
I always accidentally just like
start murdering people in the towns
and I've never seen what a good playthrough is.
Never.
You look less ugly.
Is that it?
Just less ugly?
People will constantly want to marry you.
I guess that is a little annoying.
There we go, I've got a good multiplier here.
New sword, what do you think?
$250, let's go.
Thanks.
Ooh, that was risky.
Evil is funner.
I missed, but it's okay.
I mean, evil is always gonna be funner
because I can just walk into a store
and just take everything.
I don't even need money.
I can just kill the guy behind the register
and take everything in the fucking store.
Of course it's funner and easier.
There's good, evil, and then pure and corrupt.
Should I be good and corrupt?
Or evil and pure?
What does that even mean?
Evil and pure?
Pure evil.
Oh, I see.
Oh, that was a mistake.
It means evil and vegetarian.
I fucked it up.
Yeah, I got too greedy.
It's all right.
Should I just be an evil vegan?
No, I won't be able to get fat.
Should I be a fat vegan?
How is a lawful vegan?
I don't know why that's making me laugh.
I don't know why.
Because you could be fat anything.
It's just based on calories and fat content.
You know how to use a hammer.
Yeah, I'm going to be a good, fat, pure, evil, vegetarian.
All right, almost there.
Good fatty acids only.
That's how you make a blade.
Damn it, I was reading chat.
Shit, I was so...
I'm almost done.
I'm almost done, please.
Yeah, I'm going to be chaotic, monounsaturated fat.
Holy shit, that was awful.
What was I doing?
Nice bit of forging.
All right, almost done.
I promise I'm not going to do this.
I need money though.
Jeremy, this is too much.
I'm just playing a blacksmithing mini-game.
I'm not electrocuting your seat.
Oh shit, I didn't even test if the audio was synced.
I'm almost done.
Everybody relax.
I'm doing this now because I wanted to do this later.
You know, you realize if I do this now,
then it's a super simple way for me to make a bunch of money later.
Every time you hit the hammer wrong,
I receive one-fifth of a lethal injection.
I really hate to tell you,
but one-fifth of a lethal injection is a lethal injection.
You're gone.
There's no such thing as that, I'm sorry.
That dude's dead.
No, he's not.
I haven't missed.
All right, there we go.
We're good.
Now we're going to go till I lose.
What's going on?
Just go until you lose because this is a ton of money.
Next level, not yet, not yet.
All right, now we're done.
We're done.
I got 9,500 bucks.
Time to get some more equipment.
I want a better outfit.
I'm going to eat a shitload of food.
I got a good bunch of stuff.
Yeah, let's eat.
All right, let's have some fucking mutton.
Ugly.
Okay, what if they don't see me gain weight?
What if I just show up later and I'm fat?
They won't see like me turning fat.
Tomato juice, chicken fried mutton.
No, I can't give you any of this.
Wait, that kid just says school gives me too much homework.
Dude, you do have school.
Does getting fat make you slower?
Okay, now we go drink a bunch of beer.
Is there a way I can see how fat I am?
Look, look in a mirror.
No, I'm talking about like, holy shit, what's going on?
I just got, I want more like bread.
Here we go.
Pies.
This will do it.
Oh yeah, you better believe it.
All right, give me some apple pies.
Beef pie, country beef pie, crab apple pie, kidney and friends pie, crumbly pie.
Let's go.
Okay, crumbly and friends pie.
I'm leveling up.
Oh, thanks.
This is the shame corner.
I'm leveling up by eating.
This is great.
Okay, crab apple pie.
Well, get out of here.
You're not supposed to be watching me.
Stop watching me eat.
Get the fuck away from me.
Let me eat in peace.
What?
Is this as big as I can get?
How big can I get?
I've gotten a little bigger, haven't I?
Apple pie pocket.
Your love for food and your aversion to exercise
have earned you the right to be called salad dodger.
Salad dodger?
Okay, country blueberry pie.
What was that?
Why did I just freak out?
I almost tried flirting with you.
All right, let's flirt.
She's happy.
Oh my god, I have gained a lot of weight, haven't I?
I need more food.
Is there like a way I can tell how big I am?
What about Zaffer?
I'm getting close to just hitting...
I'm just getting close to zapping this lady.
What do you sell?
Steel.
Wait, I can be a good person and steal.
Don't call yourself the dump.
Dump?
I'm not serving you.
Not nicely anyway.
What?
7% markup?
No, look, it's the dump.
Okay, how do I just take things?
I can be a good person and steal furniture.
Wait, is this guy rated?
Who's rated?
Oh, it's San rated.
Oh shit.
What's going on, everybody?
Thanks, San.
Welcome.
Welcome to the stream.
That's a lot of people.
Thanks a lot, dude.
Raid song?
I don't have a raid song.
I don't.
I can't.
There's too many people to embarrass myself in front of.
If you're just joining, I'm playing Fable 2.
I'm in the middle of trying to make my guy very large and strong and heavy.
I'm just feeding him.
He's a magic user and now we're going to go do the quest.
Thanks for the huge raid, dude.
Welcome, everybody.
I'm a pretty normal guy.
I'm pretty like...
You know, I'm kind of, you know, I'm normal.
I don't...
Whatever.
All right, thanks for coming.
I don't know what to say.
That's so many people.
Can I steal, please?
Okay, how do I turn this person around?
Oh shit, here we go.
All right, I want to buy clothes.
Here we go.
Can I buy a wig?
All right, I'm going to buy the Mickey Mouse gloves.
And I want to...
An eye patch?
No.
How about...
Okay, how about like the...
Yeah, I'm going to do like a wrestler mask.
And these things.
Yeah, definitely these.
Oh, the wizard hat's awesome, too.
Can I get a wizard hat?
Yes, I need the wizard hat.
Of course I do.
Okay, I want headgear.
Can I not wear the mask and the...
Yeah, I can wear...
Can I wear them both?
Really?
Okay, I like those.
Mask.
Here we go.
Oh, I have to have some...
I have to wear something up here.
How about like the big gown?
Wow, I'm attractive.
What?
Afraid of me?
Yeah, the Archmage robes.
That's perfect.
Okay.
Perfect.
What do you think of me now?
Thank you.
Robe and wizard hat.
Not yet.
I like how this looks.
You were about to steal from a villager.
This is a crime.
The eye icon tells you if anyone can see you.
The perfect crime.
The dog distracts them.
It was four gold?
28 grand.
All right, I'm gonna do a mission.
Bad boy time.
Yeah, we're big good picture, bad small picture.
That means I can steal from registers.
That means I can punch people in the face if I don't like them at all.
But I'm gonna be a good person in the grand scheme of things.
Stealing $40 from the register, but I'm gonna like save the town.
See?
I'm gonna shock somebody accidentally.
Does the game save itself?
Chaotic Hungary.
Oh, shit.
Thank you.
Have a good day.
I will.
I appreciate that.
Thanks for the discount.
Digspot.
Where's our digspot?
Over here?
Where is it?
Where's the digspot?
Is this illegal?
Um, what the hell is going on?
Is it because safety's on?
Oh, okay.
Oh, by the way, I want to make it clear again.
Uh, don't miss the stream next weekend on Sunday.
Percival peanuts?
Okay.
All right, what do you want?
Oh, they they know that I'm the swordsman.
Okay.
Am I streaming Saturday too?
I am not.
I am streaming tomorrow, but next Saturday, no.
Next Sunday only.
All right, let's go find this guy.
I need to level up.
How do I level up?
Do I have to go to like the guild thing?
Surprising.
You gained 200 pounds.
Just drink it right now.
Nice job.
You found me ground wine.
Can I open this?
Is it five?
Oh, damn it.
Wait, you're streaming next Sunday?
Well, this channel is going to be live, but it's not...
It's not going to be me streaming.
I have to...
It's a whole lore deal.
All right, what do I want here?
Chaos?
Or just shock 2?
I think I want chaos.
Chaos confuses your foes, making them unpredictable.
You've learned the chaos spell.
Summon a mask of madness to scramble the minds of your enemies,
and you never know what might happen.
Cast your spell wide to catch more enemies.
Okay.
How do I select which one I want to use?
I can do time as well?
Time control allows you to slow the world around you,
or to move with incredible speed.
Oh, I can buy this too.
No, I'll save it.
I don't need it.
Extra style accuracy speed.
The greater your speed, the faster you will be able to unleash it.
Oh, I can learn roll.
I want this.
Tap A while moving.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's a huge deal.
I need it.
And physique?
Upness?
There we go.
More health.
When there is a sail on, the thing will flash.
Press it now.
Sails.
Blacksmith sail?
Oh shit.
Oh my god.
All right, let's go.
How do I select the spell?
Is there a way I can select the spell?
Left bumper?
B?
Watch out, dog.
Hold B.
Push down on the D-pad well with a weapon drawn
while facing a potential victim to turn off safety mode.
Okay, so this is a bad guy.
Oh, all right.
Is it bad?
Oh, that's nice, that is.
I'm sure they'd want you to have it.
Is that evil?
That guy was a bad guy.
That was a bad guy.
He probably ran him off the road.
That was a lie.
Yeah, okay, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Saint Peter can fucking judge that guy, okay?
See, you can go up and Saint Peter can judge him.
Not me.
Ow.
Crossbow?
Who needs a fucking crossbow when I got unlimited power?
Oh shit, give me that stuff.
Damn it.
Give me it.
All right, let's do chaos.
Hey, who is it?
Whatever, they can't even hit me.
One spell, Andy.
It's effective.
It's a really good spell.
Oh, I like that one.
That one, I feel like I should be like,
Avada Kedavra.
What does he say?
Avada Kedavra, okay.
Let's fight each other, who cares?
Is he even doing anything?
The spell sucks.
What am I even doing here?
Why would I do that when I could just do this?
Everybody fight.
What just happened?
What?
Doctor Strange?
All right, fight each other.
What are they all standing around for?
Am I even fighting bad people here right now?
No, no, no, no, I don't want to fall.
I want his stuff.
Is he dead?
Oh, fuck.
Oh, God, no.
That's what I want.
I want to confuse him then shoot him in the head.
All right, that ability is terrible.
I got to go to bed?
Well, have a great sleep, man.
Thanks for watching.
Hopefully, we see you maybe tomorrow.
And we'll see you tomorrow.
If not, then I really hope we see you on next Sunday.
Oh, the dog's book of war.
The dog is now a two-star fighter.
Oh, nice.
Okay.
Okay, he reacted to it.
I'm trying to go like right in his face.
How come he's not getting up?
What is going on?
All right, that was the last brawl.
We're going to ignore this guy.
He shit in my face.
He shit his pants in my face and that was it.
I'm not going to fucking stand for that.
Oh, my God.
They're kicking the shit out of me.
Oh, eat this.
Okay.
Oh, what do you got?
Dig spot?
Let's go.
And a treasure right here.
This game is fun.
This game is really not that hard, but whatever we do is fun.
Oh, money.
That was a real fart fecal funny moment.
Well, it's guaranteed comedy.
Hide snout.
Your dog can now hide his snout to see him do it.
Belcher fart.
Well, I have to do it.
It's so stupid.
Sus guy shits his pants.
I can't shoot these people.
Why?
Are you afraid of heights?
It's scripted.
Yes, it is.
Oh, bandit cave.
Let's go.
My son Joey's in there.
I don't know why I just thought this was Diablo 3.
I thought this guy was going to be following me around in the cave
and eventually show up in the camp with something.
Be like a merchant.
I don't know why I thought that's exactly what was going to happen.
All right.
What do you need?
What's going on?
I don't suppose you want to go in the cave.
Should we go in the cave?
Please.
Okay.
I hear cats meowing.
I know I played this game,
but for some reason I have zero memories of it.
Yeah, me too.
I think I went to the midnight release of this game.
I remember getting this super early.
Strength potion.
All right.
Super forgettable.
Oh.
I mean, yeah.
It was very...
Yeah, I don't remember any of this.
I remember the...
Oh, it's the sound of your own heartbeat.
That's it.
There's a sale going on or whatever.
I need some better items, though.
I can't just shock people all stream.
Oh, come here.
It's okay.
Come here.
What the fuck was that?
What the hell happened?
Oh, sorry.
I've never seen anything like this before.
Does this guy possessed?
This guy's going to die.
Oh, you're back.
Uh-oh.
All right.
Stay behind me.
Are they going to die?
Bum this guy.
I'm going holy shit.
This guy's really weak.
That was fucking awful.
I don't...
I'm the silent protagonist.
Get up here.
Let's go.
Come on.
I'm trying to save you.
Don't worry.
I put every single point in one move.
I barely know how to walk.
I don't know how to read.
I have no idea what a fucking pen does.
But let me tell you, when I was a little kid,
all the way through my early adulthood into my 30s,
I put every fucking birthday worth of points into lightning bolt.
We're going to be fine.
You're just going to have to guide me around.
Where's this dig spot?
But where is it?
What are you talking about?
And then I hit him in the chest.
I'm like, hey, hey, don't bring me near water, though.
Don't bring me near water, though.
I love myself a useless.
What's that one doing?
What's wrong with that guy?
Why is he shimming around his stomach?
One move, Andy.
That's right.
That's me.
This is how you gain magics points, though.
Dude, I mean, on all your birthday skill points,
you didn't put any into like even walking or running?
Nope.
Or thinking or like strength?
Nope, none.
I've actually I've had to be fed at a baby seat my entire life.
I don't even know what I don't even like.
I couldn't even tell you what food is.
I'm just saying somebody just gives it to me.
OK, I could power the entire city of Las Vegas if you let me.
Hey, let's go.
Shit dog.
What the fuck was that?
All right.
I'll handle this one.
What the hell is that?
What the hell was that?
Oh, shit.
Is he alive?
Where is he?
Oh, whoops.
My son into.
He dead.
You should get out of there.
Head for the surface quickly.
Oh, shit.
They got sick of my shit.
Shit.
OK.
They can't do that to me, right?
What am I doing?
Turn around.
What the fuck am I doing?
Oh, my fucking God.
Why am I stuck here?
Thank you.
All right, there we go.
Good.
Is he dead?
Nice.
All right.
I got a lot of points.
Force Lightning Andy.
I'm going to get new abilities.
Don't worry.
I need to get Vortex.
That's what I want.
Shock.
I do need to do melee, though.
I can't just not do melee.
How am I ever going to have health?
He's so bad.
Why am I bad?
Shut up.
Give these guys migraines so they fight each other.
Fight each other.
Do something.
All these level one spells are awful.
There's no mana.
No, there's no mana in the game.
That's right.
Look at this wooden ass sword, too.
Yeah, I'm going full Vortex.
I'm going to make Vortex my number one move.
Let's go.
There are no health bars other than your own.
That's true, too.
Watch out.
Don't die.
I can't die in Fable 2.
Not in the first two levels.
That would be embarrassing.
I'm stuck again.
Why am I stuck doing this again?
Fuck.
This is fun.
This is a fun game.
Let's go.
I'm not as experienced as whatever.
What the fuck is this?
This is Fable 2, man.
Fable 2.
Wait.
Give me that.
Did I miss?
I admitted something.
What did I admit?
Buy Vortex.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Let's do that.
Will.
Shock 2.
I could do Shock 2, though.
Vortex.
Yeah, I want Vortex.
Powerful Whirlwinds.
I can get level 2.
Done.
All right.
I have level 2 Vortex.
Let's do it.
You have several level one spells.
Oh, shit.
This is level one.
This is level two.
What does it do?
Oh, fuck.
Now it's level two.
Oh, my God.
All right.
This is going to be kind of insane.
I can't just cast Lightning Bolt exclusively.
No, apparently not.
Do Lightning and Vortex.
That sounds pretty good.
Grab them in the Vortex,
and when they're spinning around,
lightning the fuck out of them.
Yeah, I'll be Storm.
Storm Mage.
Do I have any food?
Throw potions.
Oh, here we go.
Yeah.
What's this?
100% natural state ingredients.
Combat drink?
What?
Oh, it's these guys.
It's the bridge guys.
All right.
Let's Vortex them.
I can just shoot them when they're doing that.
Oh, that's kind of cool.
It's a cool move,
but I will tell you that's really loud
and really annoying.
That's very loud,
and I have to do that every time I want to do a move.
Do Storm 2, then Lightning 1.
All right.
Where is it?
Good job, boy.
You look like Cosplay Jack Sparrow.
I look like any convention Jack Sparrow.
You know that guy that just dresses up as Jack Sparrow?
Doesn't really matter what the convention is.
Like, this could be like a lawyer convention.
A meeting of the attorneys-at-law,
and there would be a Jack Sparrow there.
The Association of Restaurant Managers Conference.
There'll be two Jack Sparrows there.
Eat more food.
I will.
I just had to do some quests.
You'll find it.
Come on.
Where is it?
Get it.
Pick up the scent.
You can do it.
There we go.
That's a good dog.
I saw Jack Sparrow at 4th of July once.
Right.
It doesn't matter.
Any large gathering.
Guys, if there's too many people in line at the ice cream store,
a Jack Sparrow will show up.
Okay.
So what do we got here?
Let's go.
This is Manure Manor.
I can buy this right now.
Owners killed.
Knock on this door.
If you want to commit vandalism, you could just...
Good evening.
Someone just tried to flirt with you.
Who's flirting with me?
Oh, you still want me to leave?
Oh, you want me to leave?
Leave?
Are you sure?
Did you see?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, you liked that a little bit though.
Are you sure you want me to leave?
Well, I can do this.
You love that though.
What?
You love me.
All right.
Take what they have in the fridge.
Take everything.
Got more shit?
I'll be gone before they fucking even know I was here.
Holy shit.
What else they have?
Take it all.
There's no guards in this town.
There are no guards.
Rancid water.
Anything?
What else you got?
Sleep?
Wait, I'm sleeping in their bed?
No, I don't want to do that.
I want to get out of here.
All right.
Let's get the fuck out.
Go, go, go.
Out.
All right.
We got to like hide.
I'm like a squirrel.
I just stole a bunch of food in their house
and I ran around the corner and like
Hob water.
What does this do?
I don't know.
Drink it.
What are those bells?
Are those like rancid water?
Smells like eggs.
50 gold.
Fine.
Take it.
Get out.
That's nothing.
Take it.
What is this?
Woodcutter.
What happened to being a good boy?
I can be a bad person,
but a good boy.
No, I can be a good person,
but a bad boy.
There you go.
I'm a good person,
but I'm a bad boy.
You can also be a bad boy,
but a good person.
Good person, but...
No, no.
What is...
Say that in reverse.
A good person,
but a bad boy.
A good boy,
but a bad person.
That's not me.
I am a good...
What's going on?
Get away from me.
Slow down and say it.
Okay.
You can be a good boy,
but a bad person.
That's not me.
I am a bad boy,
but a good person.
Did I say the same thing twice?
Say it slower.
No, you get it.
You know what I mean.
Did I just get wood chips
in that girl's eyes?
I work for your dad.
Get out of here.
What?
How am I going to get...
I don't want to do another
get promoted job.
How are you a good person?
I unlock that cage
and let the person out.
Let the people out.
All the time the bandits have been like,
I'll give you free gold
if you just give me the warrants.
Nope.
I'm only getting eight gold
for this shit.
This is a horrible amount of gold.
How have I been a bad boy?
I stole a bunch of stuff.
I made a fart noise
in front of somebody
in front of the person's...
I went in their house.
I farted and danced in their house.
Multiplier has stopped at three.
Oh, I've been promoted.
Shit.
That's bad person behavior.
No, it's not.
Bad person...
Bad person behavior
is if I did not let them out
and I made a deal with the bandit.
You can be a good person,
but a bad boy.
You can be a bad person
and a good boy.
You drove a family out of their home
and you stole their food.
No.
I danced so widely,
entertainingly.
By the way,
all three of them loved it
that they ran away
because they couldn't believe
how fun it was.
And they needed to go find
all the people in the town
to come watch me.
And I just helped myself
to the stuff that was in their fridge.
Somebody said,
go watch Megamind.
You'll love it.
Why would I like Megamind?
Why would I watch...
I don't want to watch Megamind.
You know, I wrote Megamind off
because I just figured
it was Will Ferrell movie
number like 55 or whatever.
Megamind's a villain like you.
Why am I a villain?
What did I do?
Well, the only reason why
you guys are saying Megamind
was a good movie
is because that's where
penis music is from.
That's false.
That's not.
Yeah, I probably would like Megamind.
You're right.
Maybe I'll watch it tonight.
I'll watch it.
I'll watch it later.
I will give you guys
my assessment of Megamind tomorrow.
Just kidding.
I'm not watching that tonight.
I don't need any more money.
I'm good.
I am going to buy this house, though.
I'm buying the farm.
This thing's...
It's only 2,800...
4,600 bucks.
Did I buy it and move in?
I want it.
It's mine.
This is my house.
Animal magnetism?
All right, cool.
So now I have a house.
My house is the farm.
I could rent it out, though, couldn't I?
Rent out.
How much could I rent?
This is not a bad idea.
I'll get $50 every five minutes.
I'll take it.
All right.
Where am I going?
You can improve it with decorations
to increase the price.
I slept in it for one day.
Yeah, well, I don't...
I need to like make...
I need to have like a family first.
How much is this place?
Please.
6,400.
Anybody here?
Open the door, then.
Open the door.
I have something very important.
I'm the goddamn quest guy.
I'm saving this town.
I need to ask you stuff.
My head.
Oh, shit.
They opened the door.
Hello.
Thank you.
I have a master woodcutter.
You're right.
You think so?
Why would you run to their bathroom?
They pay me?
Quality item.
Why would I run out of their house?
Run to the bathroom?
Oh, man.
All right.
What am I...
Where's the breadcrumbs going?
Oh, I need more breadcrumbs.
You're an adventurer, right?
What's going on?
Why are the breadcrumbs not...
I need breadcrumbs.
I can't function without them.
What do I have to do to this guy?
Whoa, put it back.
Put it back.
How do I put it down?
Put it down.
Put the gun down.
How do I put things down?
Quick, quick.
Make somebody laugh.
Nobody liked that.
All right.
I have to get out of this town.
Put that cookie down now.
Oh, look.
This person likes me.
You want to have tea?
You all right?
Okay.
Do I have any presents?
I do have a present, don't I?
Oh, thank you.
Thank you.
All right.
So now how do I...
I need info.
Social.
Follow me.
Come with me.
Wait, what did you say?
What did you say?
Who said that?
Did you say that?
What did you say?
Yes.
A game master?
I can't.
Play Spinner Box a tutorial.
A spinner box is a decorative box
containing several devices called flit switches.
A flit switch is a magical spinner
that will randomly cycle through a variety of symbols.
To play this, just place your bet and spin.
What do I need to do?
Okay.
This is cow and corset.
A three-switch spinner box.
Raise your bet to six gold and spin.
Okay, spin it.
I want to bet more than six.
As you can see, not every spin is a winner.
Four more adjacent symbols of the same type.
Here we go.
Look at that.
Bigger chains.
Okay.
Oh, nice.
All right, let's go.
Why can I not do a more than 10 bet?
It's just fantasy slots.
Yeah.
Look at that.
Look at how much money I just made.
600 gold?
If I had bet 20 bucks,
that would have been like five grand.
Imagine needing a tutorial for a slot machine.
Okay.
Free spins.
This is just a slot machine.
Why do I even need a tutorial?
Cool.
All right.
Yeah, I get it.
You pay out.
It's cool.
Are we ready?
Let's go.
All right.
Adjust bet.
It's a max bet.
10?
I can only put 10 bucks in here?
Here we go.
There we go.
All right.
Let me make...
Let me get a bonus and I'll leave.
Pack it up, boys.
No.
Pack...
Stay here.
To make the amount of spins larger.
What is with these spins?
How am I not winning any money?
What the fuck is that?
What the fuck?
Build a bank up.
All right.
That's a super bonus cow spin.
That's 500.
I'm good.
I'm still here.
Let's go.
One more of those and I'll leave.
House, house, house.
Oh, come on.
Timed?
It better not be.
As far as slot machines go,
this is really dull.
It kind of is, isn't it?
Here we go.
Guys, I made 100 bucks.
Oh, he's hyper speed spinning.
Somebody get him off the machine.
Get him off the machine.
He's hyper spinning.
Get him off.
All right.
Cash out, cash out, cash out.
Grab him.
Just grab him.
No, what happened?
All right.
We're good.
I'm losing your money.
Hey, debt.
What the fuck is this?
What do you mean?
How much debt do I have?
What is that?
What?
Why do I have debt?
I'm going to take this to zero
and I'm going to leave.
Come on.
Do it.
Yeah, I want to see.
I want to examine the machine.
I want the gaming board to look at this
and see if it's actually real.
This is bullshit.
That's the last one.
All right.
This is bullshit.
This thing sucks.
What?
Points to next level?
Why do I level up my gambling?
Is this like when you get the cards
at the casinos
where you build points
and eventually after like two years
of gambling,
they give you one free night
at a room at the hotel?
Imagine being a level five gambler.
I kind of want to do that.
I kind of want to be level five gambler.
I need to get to the next level.
I have to.
All right.
There was a...
We're supposed to be going on like a date.
Come with me.
Come on in here.
And gold to hear the bard.
What?
Ever leave me again?
Holy shit.
Oh, let's dance.
Beg.
That was really nice.
Thank you.
That was wonderful.
Why are we all stuffed here?
Okay.
I want to know what you like.
How do I get...
I want to know her needs.
All right.
Come with me.
Oh, there we go.
Gwyneth...
Wait, the farmer?
Wait, can we sleep somewhere?
Oh, barman.
All right.
This is a pretty good date.
Yeah.
Let's have to take a few of these.
Get some beer.
Rum.
Okay.
Here you go.
Do you want a drink?
Here.
I got you a drink.
Where's a gift?
A gift.
How about a...
Um...
Would you like a glass of rum?
All right.
Wait, this is the person that was already drunk?
Oh.
Well, I thought it was a different person.
All right.
Well, I'm going to drink something.
Oh, shit.
I almost just did the whirlwind.
I don't want to get drunk because I don't want to be like,
oh, you want to see a real cool trick?
Watch this shit.
And then cause a tornado inside of this place.
Level five gambling addict.
No, it's fun.
That's not going to actually destroy everything, will it?
More info.
Okay.
She likes to be seduced.
She currently thinks I'm kind of attractive.
She thinks I'm funny.
What do I do?
How do I stop this?
How do I stop?
How do I stop from doing this to them?
What's cancel?
How do I cancel?
How do I cancel a spell?
How do you cancel a spell?
Does anybody know how to cancel a spell?
I'm going to throw it into the bathroom.
I can't cancel it?
Oh shit, his bar.
What is this?
What's wrong with me?
They liked it.
They liked it?
Holy shit.
Why do they think this is cool?
You thought it was stupid?
You sure you want to tell the guy?
I would kill you right now.
If it wasn't for the guy that just pet the dog behind me.
So he just saved you.
He just saved you.
I was about to just drop the vortex right here, but he pet the dog.
Lucky fucking day.
All right, I want to let's go.
Ladies kind of freaking me out.
All right, let's go.
I let's I need to have I'm gonna buy a house and we can go sleep.
Is that what like what we're gonna do is am I gonna I have a ring.
You already own a house while I'm renting it right now.
Okay, you ready?
You like this ring?
You're engaged.
Wait, who the fuck is this?
We only had a house.
You want to set your property manure manor as your target.
Yes, let's go.
What a name for a house.
Yes, my dear.
I'll take you back to my esteemed sedate.
Manure manor.
Which lives for only a few decades before producing a single golden acorn.
The monks of the temple of light replant this acorn and as the tree is reborn.
So are all the lands and farms around.
The Abbot is quite nervous about this year.
Get away from wait, wait, wait, should you not be here?
I feel like I'm afraid like doing moves.
Did she fight?
She didn't care.
This is weird.
All right, where's the house?
Where's our house?
Wrong way.
Where's the map?
Where's my house?
In the middle of the street.
I don't, what street?
Like going towards it?
It's over here, right?
Is that it right there?
Where's this breadcrumb?
This breadcrumb trail is not loading properly.
Oh, here we go.
It's up here.
All right, here it is.
Here's my house.
All right, come on in here.
This way.
Come on in.
It's our home.
Get in here.
All right, we did it.
We are here.
Okay, so now we're engaged and now we're going to...
What are we doing?
What do we do now?
Okay.
How do we make, how do we...
We're going to have...
Are we going to have like a child?
All right, so we're going to go to the sign outside the house.
Evict tenant.
Oh, set as marital home.
I met this person the last night.
I destroyed a bar and then we got married.
You've received a dowry of cash and a renowned boost.
You get better bonuses from your house.
You might also receive gifts.
Use the house sign to set your household budget.
Maybe a household budget.
Household budget?
Uh, zero.
Daily deduction?
What?
What are you talking about?
This villager has a reward to give away.
Use the appropriate expression or give them gifts
to move the slider towards the gift icon.
What did you get me?
Oh, it's a will potion.
Thank you.
I got you this gift.
Another one?
She's still drunk?
No, she's not.
Swap, what can we swap?
Oh, okay, whatever.
She's not still drunk.
All right, we're good.
Missed you.
Hello, darlings.
All right, all right.
You're the best.
Here, you want some...
You want a snack?
A boat?
Hey, uh, for some boots.
She's still following me around.
Who's this?
What do you want?
Are you clapping and saying nice to my wife?
What the fuck is happening right now?
Are you kidding me?
What?
She's drunk.
She was congratulating your marriage.
I know.
All right, time to celebrate with some pies.
Let us see what we can do.
Oh, nasty nuts.
Rotten apples.
Rancid apple pie.
Dude, whatever, I'll eat it.
Wait, man flesh?
Oh, I'm not eating one of these.
No, that means evil.
That makes you evil if you eat that.
I think we're ready for our love to get physical.
Really?
Yep.
You finally got rid of that headache, dear.
Let's go.
That guy's not going to come in here, right?
I just ate like three pies.
I imagine I have like blueberry stain all over my mouth.
What?
Already?
Ow.
I'm speed running this.
Okay, so now we have a kid.
I got speed boost.
Wait, is that because...
Never mind.
Congratulations on starting a family.
Entertain your newborn by facing the cot,
getting their attention with left trigger,
and performing expressions.
A happy family gives you better bonuses.
Find out more about your offspring and name them if you like
by holding the left trigger pressing Y to see the personality screen.
Oh, a present.
What'd you get me?
What?
You got me a quest?
Oh, thank you.
Well, give it to me.
I want it.
Ooh, will potion.
Thank you.
Where's the baby?
Hello, baby.
This is Gwyneth the farmer.
Wait, is this a baby?
Wait, what?
No, it's not.
This is the baby.
How do I talk to the baby?
Likes beef jerky.
I kind of like Kiernan.
I don't think it's supposed to feed beef jerky to a baby
and loves toy boat.
All right, victory arm pump.
You got it.
Baby loves this move.
Yeah.
Oh, baby loves the arm pump.
Scream at the baby.
I don't think you can scream at the baby.
Wait, you can.
Oh, wait, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Remember this?
Oh, God.
Everything's okay.
No, sorry.
I am not going to vortex the baby.
All right.
I love how he's scary.
Whoa.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Does the baby like farts?
You like to dance, baby?
All right.
So is this the part that we all have to come to terms with?
I probably ain't ever coming back here.
I'm going to forget where this house is.
So this is like all the only time I'm probably going to be here.
What happened?
Turn safety on, please.
Can I beg for money from the baby?
What about dog?
Come on, baby.
I need some cash.
Something.
Anything.
We're fine.
All right.
More info.
The baby thinks I'm ugly.
Okay.
We need to get beef jerky.
All right.
Let's give a gift to the baby.
And I'm going to leave.
What is this?
Quests.
Families.
Wait, what do you mean?
Families, plural.
Family has a gift for you.
They do?
Who's got a gift?
Let's see it.
All right.
What does the baby want?
Some beef jerky, right?
I mean, I buy all the expired food.
I don't care.
I want to get huge.
How fat can you actually get in the game?
Feed the baby the flesh pie.
Well, you're crazy.
No, I don't think I'm not gaining any weight.
Look at the log book.
Yeah, I'm as fat as you can be.
Good.
Okay.
Look, I'm good and I'm pure.
My renown is good.
My attractiveness is okay.
Where's my fat skill?
Where's fatness?
Minus 26.
It can be more than that.
It can definitely be more than that.
What's the fattiest thing in the whole game?
Level 26 fat guy.
Five.
Ten.
Oh no, it is working, isn't it?
Yeah, it's working.
Minus 30 is the lowest you can go.
All right.
Well, it's probably there now.
Let's keep going.
Let's do the quest.
Move close so we can see.
No, I like this outfit.
I'm keeping it on.
Drink the EXP potions.
That's a great idea.
All right.
This is Will potion.
Oh yeah.
Strength one, two.
Okay.
I've got enough experience now to do what?
I do physique.
It's just more damage.
What about tough now?
Let me do...
Yeah, I'll do physique.
More damage.
Let's go to Will.
All right.
I don't have enough to do very much anything.
14,000.
Jesus.
I should do shock too.
Time control sounds cool.
Yeah, it does.
All right.
What is it, honey?
Yeah.
You see how many fist pumps I did?
Here.
Do you want something?
Take...
Here.
Have a piece of chocolate.
All right.
What does it want me to do in here?
What do you want me to do in here?
I got to change the quest.
Okay.
I'm going to do...
Talk to the abbot in Oakfield.
Sculptor.
Let's do the...
Yeah.
Oh, weapons guy.
What do you got?
How much money?
I got 4,500.
Iron axe.
That's pretty good.
Iron blunderbuss.
Ooh.
Steel axe.
Can I take it?
Give me the gun.
And give me the...
Iron axe.
You're paying top gold for top quality items.
Here we go.
All right.
Let's take a look at it.
And a clothing trader.
What do you got?
We have some new things in stock, you might ask.
Condom.
No.
Autograph card.
Ah, that item is discounted.
Yeah.
I'll take a couple of these.
You've bought a fine item.
Dog treats.
Yep.
You've bought a fine item.
Wedding bells.
Sheep flowers.
Yeah.
Just get a bunch of random gifts.
I hope it brings you great happiness.
You've bought a fine item.
Oh, I like this.
Is this a hat?
It's on sale.
Oh, bargain.
I like this.
You're making a great saving on that.
Rock bottom prizes for rock bottom times.
Okay.
This looks like I had to become a superhero really quickly.
And I just kind of threw on everything I could find
in like the closet for everybody that lives in my house.
All right.
Let's do it.
Model for the sculpture.
Yes.
Let me take a good look at you.
Perform and hold an expression.
Well, I mean, we kind of have to.
Wait, am I supposed to hold it?
Keep farting.
Hey, I got to get out of there.
Oh, wait, I didn't win.
Did I win?
I hope it's me grabbing my butt.
This is going to get me in trouble.
I'm going to shock somebody in the face.
It's going to get me in a lot of trouble.
Oh, cool.
All right.
Nice.
What's next on the quest?
All right.
The ritual.
Let's go.
All right, dog.
The demon door over here.
Oh, yeah, I remember those.
It's like you have to do certain things in front of it.
Oh, yes.
You must be fat.
You must be strong.
You must be wise.
I forgot about demon doors.
Where is it?
Yeah, the demon doors were the coolest part of the whole game.
They were everywhere in the first game.
Where are they in this one?
Demon door.
Come on.
Usually on the side of a rock, like clip, right?
Like something I can hear.
Honestly, the demon door was probably the coolest concept.
I'm surprised nobody else decided to just take it and make a bunch of stuff.
Make a game based around demon doors like Fable 1 was.
It was such a cool idea.
Follow the coast.
Yeah, because it forced you to play a certain way.
And if you didn't, here we go.
All right.
Oh, hello.
I wager you have never known a love truer.
I'm married.
Open the door, please.
The purest vibes of such love, even for just a few seconds, would inflate my soul with delight.
A delicate kiss between pledged lovers is all that I ask.
Such a sight would surely unlock my pain.
Okay.
All right.
Honey!
Honey, there's this weird thing in our backyard.
Where's our house?
My children speak of all great adventures, but they never utter your name.
Honey!
Follow me.
We have to open this door.
Where is she?
Where'd you go?
All right.
Honey, I need you to come with me for a minute.
Come with me.
Follow me, please.
Um, follow me.
Can I even kiss you?
I can't even kiss her.
How do I unlock kiss?
How do I kiss her?
How do I get the kiss expression?
What?
I have to go to the bookstore?
Oh, God.
Okay.
Well, just stay here then.
Remind me if this exists.
The time is very late.
Okay, let's go.
Remind me if that exists.
She doesn't even like you enough?
We're married.
It's a loveless marriage.
Oh.
Bandage.
I have two keys.
Minus 25.
Oh, for the house.
Temple of light.
Who are you?
The sacred texts clearly say that only two monks might enter the cave.
No one else.
I'll not send my only child into unknown dangers.
What do you need?
Hello there, my child.
I wonder.
Brothers, leave us.
Let me take a look at you for a moment.
Quite imposing.
But I can't send just anyone in there.
I suppose danger is not everyone's cup of tea.
You look imposing all right.
But I can't entrust our community's survival to a complete stranger.
Why not?
Perhaps if you built up a reputation, I'd be more inclined to trust you.
Yes.
Rookridge has been having a horrible time with bandits lately.
Why don't you go to the tavern and see if you can do anything about them?
That would be a good start.
The blessing must go forward if you're to find the pilgrim.
You must gain the abbot's favor.
Oh, fine.
Perhaps you can find a way to impress him in the town.
Impress him?
Use your map to see where quests and jobs are.
He has a quest.
A bridge too far.
Fight the bandits in Rookridge.
Sure.
I don't have to go up here.
Let me help you.
Can I help you?
You want a deed?
You want to get a deed back?
I can get a deed.
I got you want to get a deed?
I can get it.
You want to get the deed?
I can get the deed, man.
Bet your ass I will.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, I don't even need to...
Look, all you need to say is get rid of the people at this location.
That's all you need.
I don't need any other info, man.
I'm gonna go literally blow their heads off with a shotgun
and I'm gonna kill them with electricity and shit.
Just wait.
Don't worry.
I'm the hero.
Any Aaron chatters?
Probably.
Or your shit load of you.
Okay.
Bandits.
Let's go.
You didn't say it in the funny voice?
No, that wasn't even the right one.
Aaron!
There you go.
You get that like once a week.
Any treasure?
Nope.
All right, what's on my bar right now?
Vortex.
Yeah, you better believe it.
Vortex into shotgun.
Tell the boss?
All right, let's go kick some fucking butt.
Bring back Super Frog.
I love Super Frog.
It's like one of my favorite characters.
That's it?
Get him.
Okay, come on down the stairs then.
Let's make a tornado.
This is slow motion.
How?
Don't even use the weapon.
What's the point of using the weapon?
Oh, that's purple.
That's beautiful.
That's awesome.
That's just shit.
Fly him around.
Zapper.
Shotgun.
I love this voice.
I love this guy.
Come on, boy.
His voice is so wild.
I love it.
I've never heard that guy before.
What the fuck?
And Vortex is pretty helpful.
I'm just eating.
He's in a- this guy's in a lot of TV shows.
Really?
When is he going to kill the baby?
I know most of you are probably only still on this stream.
You're only probably still here.
Because you are thinking at some point I'm going to have safety off
and I'm going to kill the baby.
I- I think that's why a bunch of you are still here.
Because you don't want to miss when like the guy kills the baby.
You know what I mean?
Like, it's not going to happen though.
I'm just- I'm not happening.
Like, I really doubt that's going to happen.
Why do you think they call me Dash?
I'll be a moil away from you before you-
He'll die already.
Ow.
Is he dead?
Thank god that guy took so many hits.
Imagine getting your ass kicked by a guy that looks like this.
I mean, this- if anybody's shooting lightning out of their hands.
Whoa.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
It's in the fucking tornado.
Let's go.
Heal the dog?
I'll get it.
I'll get the dog.
All right.
Come here, dog.
I have a dog treat for you, right?
Come here.
How do I do it?
Can I not do it?
Use dog elixir.
I don't have a dog elixir, do I?
It says feed and kill the bandit dog.
What the fuck?
All right.
I want shock too.
Yep.
I had to spend all my money but I want it.
How about speed?
Accuracy?
Yeah.
All right.
How much better is this?
So if I have level two.
All right.
So we're gonna have to change this, I think.
I want this to be lightning and we'll do-
Yeah, that- because that's kind of cool.
And then we get them with the thing and we just fucking zap them.
Perfect.
All right.
Let's go.
Oh, do you like this game?
Yeah.
It's keeping my attention.
It's funny.
Resurrection file.
Keep one of these in your inventory.
Should your health drop to zero, the resurrection file will automatically revive you.
Well, that's kind of a big deal.
All right.
Let's go.
It's a funny fart game.
Of course we like it.
I mean, that's the- I mean, that's how I keep you guys here.
Have you noticed that I've done a fart?
I've like farted into the microphone.
Like every maybe 30 minutes or so as it gets to keep you here.
Ooh, I like it.
It's good.
Where's my dog?
You can tell the health of the dog by the tail.
We would be here regardless.
Hey, that's- hey, thanks.
Would you- that's cool.
Thanks.
Oh, the dog's on him.
But I killed him?
What?
I guess I- I mean, I guess that death would kill him.
Oh, okay.
Whatever.
No boss fight.
I guess not.
100 bucks?
Bandit bandana?
Bandit shirt?
Bandit trousers?
I'll just sell this shit.
I don't want to get- I want to have like a big gown on.
I need a big like mage gown.
All right.
Well, that was good.
So now I go back and talk to that guy.
Okay.
Return to Bonham.
He killed him and took his clothes.
I pretended to like this game because my crush liked it.
Yeah, but it's really- it's not a bad game.
It's fun.
All right.
Hey, look what I did.
Hey, what do you like?
Yeah, what do you like?
I'm trying to hit triangle for more info.
I don't want to shoot the guy.
He likes- what do you want- he wants a gift?
Heroic pose, sock puppet, and shoulder length hair.
How do I- how do I get the present?
Does the guy have a present?
Scare him.
You have to scare him.
Ain't so I might, but I'll bounce back.
Always do.
Anyway, here's my trusty Thesaurus, as promised.
Thesaurus?
You never know when you'll be caught in a lexicological quandary.
Doesn't tell me how to kiss.
You got 250 renown, dashes, goggles, and Barnum's Thesaurus.
Thanks to you, the way to Bowerstone is now open again.
The archaeologist?
All right, hold on.
I'm gonna scare this guy?
You've done it.
Almost everyone in Oakfield has heard of you.
Just slap him?
Now you can go- did I- I missed?
What I- I'm trying to do this- the thing on the left is changing.
Okay, we're almost there.
All right, now give me a present.
Give me a present.
He's re- give me the present.
Okay, so give me a present.
I'm on the present.
A little bit more?
A little more.
You trying to give me a heart attack?
Oh, accept gift.
There it is.
Just give me $71.
Hey, thanks a lot, buddy!
Thanks for cheering me up.
I love this one.
All right, um, let's go.
I just- oh, I so badly want to throw a tornado in there.
You know what I mean?
I just want to throw a tornado in there.
Any new clothing?
Wait, I am gonna sell.
I'm gonna sell the, um, another bandit shit I don't want.
Bandit shirt.
I don't want this.
Bandit trousers.
Don't want it.
You know what I mean?
I know.
I said that a lot.
All right, do I have enough renown to do what this guy wants me to do?
Will death do us part?
Speak to the ghost of a jilted lover and become the- its instrument of vengeance?
What do I mean in looking for a new model?
The statue's in front of the inn?
Oh.
Well, I'll do this and come back.
All right.
Oh, that's right.
I gotta go back to the blacksmith and do better blacksmithing.
I need to buy another house.
Later.
I'll let him get the jump on me.
Come on.
Get in the head.
I can now afford speed.
Not yet, though.
Just want to let you know, I bet my house on whether you're gonna die to the bandits in 30 minutes.
Please.
Well, it's been four and a half hours, man.
I don't think I'm gonna die to the bandits.
I am.
Glad of you to notice.
Oh, good shot.
Uh-oh.
All right.
I gotta run.
I gotta get up there.
Hey, why are you roleplaying?
I can't pretend like I'm in the game and just be like, oh, gotcha.
Sit down.
Why not?
I do this shit all the time.
Even when I'm not falling off.
Makes it more interesting.
E3.
You know, I still can't figure out the life of me.
Why they do that?
Why do they do that?
Have they ever played a video game before?
Why do they do the pretend actor wearing a vent call thing?
Nobody talks like that.
We all have played a shitload of games together.
We've played games in parties, online, even in just random lobbies.
People don't do that.
No one has ever...
I don't think the people making that have ever played a video game online.
But I mean, what's the alternative?
The alternative is, I guess, how it would really be.
Which would be turn your volume down really low
because somebody's going to have a horrible microphone and scream into it.
You're going to hear somebody get yelled at by their mother.
You're going to get like the lapel microphone sounds.
That is the alternative.
And maybe every like two or three minutes you'll hear...
The fuck, dude.
Fucking help me.
Fucking idiot.
Fuck.
Is it?
Or this.
What's more interesting?
Watch out.
Watch your six.
I'm right behind you.
I got it.
Going to the alt?
I sure am.
I guess that is kind of more interesting.
Oh, my statue.
Oh, it's a German 985 stream.
There's going to be a fat guy if it's possible.
Oh, my God.
Kubrick's there.
What happened?
The big day came and what?
All right, I'll help you.
Oh, I have a wife.
Then when she's ready to accept your proposal,
when she can't imagine her life without you, give her this.
Why don't I just like tell this guy to fuck off?
Rejection note?
Dear Alex, it's time for you to know the truth.
I don't love you.
I've never loved you.
This was all a game for me.
You are empty and deceitful,
and I hope you never find the slightest glimmer of happiness in this life.
I've spent a long time thinking of the exact right word,
and even longer getting it onto paper.
I am, which makes it all the more impressive that I managed to get this too.
Are you blue?
Wedding bells?
Oh, okay.
In case you need the help or no idea.
The art of seduction.
I have to read all these books.
Books.
The mage.
The mage follows where wisdom leads, but always into conflict.
Making an ally of this hero will cost you much.
The pilgrim.
The relic.
The thief.
The rejection note.
The temple of shadows.
The end.
Hold on.
Temple of shadows.
Can't read it?
Journal.
Wedding bells.
Read it.
Oakvale.
Thesaurus.
Seduction.
What did I just do?
Seduce.
All right, let's go seduce.
I think that was a really weird path that I just ran.
Trey the ghost?
We'll see.
We'll see what happens.
Thaustun.
Has he killed the baby yet?
You'll have to go.
You'll have to watch.
Fifteen.
Is that fifteen or five?
Wait, I have five silver keys?
When did I get five?
I thought I had like four.
Oh shit, nice.
All right, let's go seduce.
Here we go.
Where is Alex?
Who did that?
I didn't do that.
Get the kiss emote.
It's a book in this library.
Okay, I'll get it.
I feel like the breadcrumbs in this game were made for gamers like you.
They were.
I wish it was in every game.
What was that game where you could, if you pressed like down on the d-pad,
it was like and it did a little line on the ground.
Dead space.
Dead space is like the best game ever made.
You don't, you only use it when you need it.
It was awesome.
You never got lost.
It was perfect.
Oh, I want you to pay attention, gamer.
No, I don't care.
Just show me where to go.
All right.
Hi, I'm here to talk to you.
Hi.
Okay.
Wait, what?
Oh, gambling.
Hold on.
Keystone.
Oh, it's roulette.
I don't remember all this shit in this game.
I think I have an idea of how this works.
Okay, I want, let's go 15 inside bets.
Let's do 15 and then let's go.
Seven.
All right.
We're going 13.
Red.
Trips.
I don't even know what this means.
Go.
What's that?
Eight.
What's that going?
Wife and child are at home eating rotten food.
Fifteen.
Twelve to seventeen.
Run.
Roll dice.
Eleven.
Oh, fifteen.
Thank you.
This is close enough.
What's that pay?
Twenty-five.
Hey, you can't lose if you put it on like almost everything.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, get more chips.
Eleven.
I got it.
I got one.
What's that get me?
Twenty-one and twenty.
All right.
Look at that.
Let's go with eight.
Seven.
Got it.
All right.
What's that going to get me?
One hundred and forty.
Let's go.
I need to level up my gambling skill.
Ten.
Pair and keystone.
I don't even know what that means, but sure.
There it is.
Oh, eleven.
Keystone.
There it is.
I can't fucking count.
I know.
I can't do math.
I can't do math ever.
It's impossible.
Ten.
Eleven.
Keystone.
Pair and trips.
That's trips.
No, it's not.
Come on.
Put it on there.
I mean, if I get triples,
that's probably like a hundred and one.
There we go.
All right.
That's a big deal.
That's eighty.
That's forty.
That's a hundred.
That's not even that much.
Trips will hit huge if it lands.
All right.
I'm done.
This is just stupid.
Okay.
Sixty hundred points to the next level.
Build up a ton of debt.
I feel like that people will come after me.
All right.
Where's the lady I need to seduce?
I don't remember even who it is.
Alex.
Okay.
There we go.
All right.
What do you like?
He doesn't like play dead.
Oh, I have flowers.
I actually picked flowers.
I have them.
All right.
I have cheap flowers.
Here.
All right.
Let's go.
Come on.
That was the magic bullet voice.
That was absolutely fantastic.
And you have here a virgin strawberry.
Why does it want me to fart now?
Creepy.
Okay.
Convince her to marry you.
I almost got married once before.
He was a sweet boy, but we were both so young.
Too young.
I got scared and ran away the day of the wedding.
I hurt him so badly.
He took his own life.
I've carried that guilt with me all these years.
Never dreaming I could love again.
Can I get some fucking space?
Get away from me.
Uh, what do I do?
Destroy the rejection note and marry-
I have a wife and kid back at the-
At the house.
Somebody just wrote, dude, what the fuck?
Why is your character so gross and weird?
I don't know.
I don't know why that made me laugh so hard.
Kill this person?
No, although I didn't kill her.
Can you be married twice?
Would you like a drink?
The temples of light and shadows are always at each other's throats.
Being low on gold isn't much fun, is it?
Is he-
Look at the size of you.
How do you go adventuring with them all?
You're engaged?
What?
I'll be your wife.
Wait, can I bring her back to the m-
To my house?
Wait a minute.
That-
Okay, you're joking, right?
Perhaps you should apply for gender in the same way.
Do I need to, like-
I don't understand.
Can we go back to the other property?
Can I bring her back?
Let's romantic for a second.
Leave me the fuck alone.
Can I evict myself?
Can I evict myself from the other house and then move in?
What happens to the baby?
I have to buy another house.
Oh god, okay.
I don't have any money.
How much is this one?
Okay, I don't have enough money.
Just hold on.
Let me go blacksmith for like a half an hour.
Okay, hold on.
I'll be down in a minute.
Have another baby?
So wait, you're telling me that I can just have like a bunch of children
with a bunch of different people?
I don't remember doing any of this in the game.
I just need to get to like six or seven grand.
This is not gambling.
This is done.
It's a job.
I can do it.
It's not gambling.
Create your family line.
I feel like I'm going to get confused.
I'm going to forget who is who.
All right, this is going to not take that long.
I just can't fuck it up.
All right, don't screw it up.
All right, wait for one rotation.
No need to rush.
You idiot!
I just told you not to do that and you did it anyways.
I was just talking to you.
Listen to me.
Why did I do that?
I'll get it.
It's because needing to wait that extra one second for some reason
is an eternity in my brain.
It's like, oh, it's so much.
It's so long.
I have to do it.
You know what I mean?
It's 100 years in my head.
Oh, OK.
I need what, 10 grand?
I'll get it.
OK, we're good.
We're going to be here all day.
No, we're not.
We have like another five minutes.
Holy shit.
OK, I'm screwed up.
Look at how shitty that is.
Look at that.
Do you see how weirdly that's moving?
It's like we could framey.
Oh, that sucks.
Oh, somebody's going to make me laugh.
You just made me laugh, but I have to pay attention.
I don't even want to say it out loud because it was really, really funny.
OK, I'm going to say it, but I'm going to make sure I pay attention to the game.
Somebody said this is the music from British Bake Off.
And it is.
It is.
I can't believe somebody found that.
This is a good combo.
Don't fuck it up.
600 per sword.
Oh my god, I'm stupid.
Why would I do that to myself?
There's no reason to do that.
Oh my god.
Why am I doing that to myself?
I'm sorry.
I had to.
Just a man working hard to cheat on his family.
You're doing a good job.
10 grand.
All right, don't...
I'm not...
All right.
If I...
I have to do this.
I have to say this, otherwise I won't stop.
If I don't wait for one bounce, add 50 billion dollars to the debt.
OK, that's the only...
I'm forcing myself to do that.
It has to be one bounce.
That's how you make a blade.
See, now I forced myself to do it.
It's like a devil in my brain that's like,
press it, press it now.
Nope.
I won't do it.
I'm not gonna do it.
We're good.
There we go.
It's gonna be funny if you didn't do that.
Well, it's not gonna happen.
So does this ghost know that what I did?
Your new wife is watching you right now.
Yeah.
I'll buy a house here in Bowerstone.
That blade's complete.
He's a ghost.
Who cares?
I really do like this fact that I'm forcing myself to wait.
It's very helpful.
All right.
Now I don't care if I lose, I lose, but I have 10 grand now.
OK.
Goodbye.
Don't you know how to use a hammer?
I'm out.
Everybody loves me.
What is this?
Oh my god.
Everybody thinks I'm so attractive.
OK.
How do I get this present from you?
All right.
I'm gonna be funny.
If you were really a proper adventurer, I would have heard of you.
All right.
You think that's funny?
What else do you think is funny?
Good.
Very good.
Dancing.
It's funny.
It's because I have a bunch of money?
OK.
I want my present.
Wait.
Am I gonna put a ring on you?
How does this work?
What?
Like I used to?
Wait.
What happened?
Give me back the ring.
Can I have the ring back?
Oh, thanks, kid.
All right.
Give me that present.
Watered down XP potion.
OK.
Am I gonna have a new wife in front of the old new wife?
So I have a wife with a kid in a different town.
I married, I engaged this person over here.
And then now I have, this is a wife now.
Are we good?
Find a good ring.
Oh, shit.
OK.
Hold on.
Give him the electric chair.
Not, I can't do that.
No.
I need a ring.
Where can I buy a ring?
Somebody.
Somebody sell me a ring.
Who sells the ring?
Can I buy this meat shop?
Oh, shit.
It's Paul the stall vendor.
Wait, can we, can I?
Wait, who wants to be intimate?
You?
Who the hell are you?
What?
What's going on?
Whose house is this?
Potion shop.
No, I need a house.
How much is this house?
Uh, the silk moon.
OK.
It's a, yeah.
Buy and move in.
Let's go.
This is my marital home.
All right.
Come with me.
Get in here.
What are we doing?
Who just like wanted to like come and like have sex with me?
Is that what she was asking?
Somebody was like, oh, let's go find somewhere private.
Who was that?
Miriam the traveler.
Who is coming into this house?
Rachel, the housewife?
Room about trees.
It has to be Alex.
Does it?
OK.
Well, where's Alex?
Alex, where'd she go?
It has to be Alex.
Well, where's Alex?
Have to find her now?
I don't even know who this is.
Rachel's the lady from the beginning of the stream.
Oh, I look like it's gross.
Why are there two beds?
Then we could get my.
Well, you don't like the ring that I have.
Oh, I'm about to start throwing lightning.
All right.
Remember, you're not a good boy anymore.
I know.
I'm not a good boy anymore.
You're right.
OK, wait.
Where's right?
Where's Alex?
Hey, pretty good.
That's 22.
Holy shit.
Stop trying to seduce people with TikTok dances.
OK, so how are we doing?
We good?
All right.
You remember we're a genius, right?
You kind of like me a little bit.
I need a better ring, though.
What can I buy a ring?
Town criers over here now.
Did you ask how did I do it?
Well, you see, you take your hands and you make little waves.
Pretending that you're like you're you're strong.
Like that's like the body.
OK, it's time to open it.
I got to go to the jeweler.
OK, all right.
Oh, everybody here is in love with me.
Oh, my God.
This is ridiculous.
What's going on?
Like you and maybe over here.
How about you?
I like you too.
Oops.
This is weird.
It's this weird, isn't it?
All right.
So when is the stores open?
If somebody's giving me a gift.
Who is this?
Oh, that's the town crier.
But still, it'd be nice if yours were a bit better.
What?
My clothes are fine.
What are you talking about?
All right.
When does the jeweler open?
Nice.
I can say I like that a lot.
That's well done.
This is just the icing.
This is just so lovely and sweet.
OK, where's the jeweler?
I'm done fucking around.
Jewelry stall.
Here we go.
No, I don't want to buy the property.
I want to buy jewelry.
I mean, I want to hit the guy with the fucking axe.
I want to hit him with an axe.
All right.
Come on.
We're almost done.
We're almost ready.
Open the stores, please.
Oh, look at the size of him.
Bad and ugly.
I'm not bad and ugly.
Look at the pie stand.
What's wrong with the pie stand?
Adjust prices.
Setting the prices lower is an act of purity.
How much are they?
A pie is what?
All right.
Open.
Here we go.
Open the stores.
Thank you.
Hurry up.
All right.
I need the jeweler.
Get to your posts.
Let's go.
Where's the jeweler?
Should I just buy 10 rings?
Stop.
Where's the person that sells me shit?
Get...
It's you.
Get over there.
Can I buy shit from you, please?
You're the stall vendor.
All right.
Get behind the stall.
Holy shit.
I just missed that lady.
There's the jeweler.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Come here, come here, come here.
All right.
I'm going to buy the ring and give it to her.
Okay.
Here we go.
Becoming a parent.
Civil ring.
Okay.
There we go.
Eternal love ring.
No.
Now get a forever ring.
Just in case.
What is this one?
Love potion?
I'm spending all my fucking money.
I don't want to spend all my money.
Where's that kid's parents?
All right.
Oh, it's time.
All right, Alex.
Come here.
Alex.
No.
There you are.
I don't want to give you the expensive ring.
Whatever.
Let's go.
What do you think?
Come on.
Okay.
Now let's go home.
Hey, look at that.
Marital home.
On a sunny morning.
Under a clear sky.
What's a bigamist?
The villagers crowded together to witness two people stand.
Is that if you're married to more than one person and you have fat?
Some say they were a strange couple.
Others that they saw a story of true love.
Only time would tell.
Okay.
I just know we're going to be so happy together.
Yes, we will.
Hey, you.
You are a lovely elite.
I got a nice house.
All right.
I want to get close to you.
Yes, really close.
Yes.
Let's go upstairs.
All right.
Here we go.
How about we find a quiet place and have some fun?
What do you think I'm trying to do?
I'd never say no to you, darling.
People find me more attractive.
Wait, we didn't even do anything.
Just plus 20.
What was that?
Plus 20 disgust?
What happened?
What do you mean over there?
You're saying that I have a gross house?
Oh my god.
Your house is fucking disgusting.
Uh-oh.
Oh, a baby.
Is this kid's name?
What does this kid like?
I wanted to do more info.
Put the gun.
Exit game, exit game, exit game.
How do I get out of this?
Oh shit.
Are we all right?
No, no, no, no.
I'm sorry.
Is the baby still in there?
It likes the loot.
Okay.
Where's my loot?
I had a loot.
Where is it?
What do you want?
Are you fucking serious?
How do I do this?
Okay, come over here.
The other bed?
Why can't we do this?
Switch targets?
I just had some seafood earlier.
Tell her to follow you.
Damn it.
Did I miss the opportunity?
That would have been fucking hilarious.
You used the thumbs up on the baby.
I can still do it?
Do I have to go find a different bed?
Oh my god.
Damn it.
Do I have to flirt?
I need to hurry to leave.
I'm too tired?
It's on cooldown?
It can't be.
Damn it.
Oh, we had such a funny moment there.
Oh well.
Just keep flirting with her.
Come on.
Well, what do you think I'm trying to do?
What are you waiting for?
He makes me go goo.
Oh my god.
No, don't.
Does she know?
Do you want to send your property gypsy caravan?
No, wait.
What?
Where are we going?
Wait.
How many people in this house looking to get fucking married?
Who's this guy?
Who is this person?
What are you doing?
Rob the house husband.
Wait, did you just get a new husband?
Who is dating who in this house?
Who are these people?
I have no idea what's going on.
All right, I gotta go.
Go back to the ghost?
Oh shit, that's right.
When she came up, she was like, oh, you want to go somewhere nice?
Oh, if I could have had actual sex with her in there.
That would have been the stupidest thing ever.
You ran away from it all?
Well, I need to go back to the ghost.
That was an actual wife's boyfriend in there.
The house husband.
What?
Why are these people following me?
Oh god.
Is this quest even tracked?
Yeah, this is tracked.
You need to kill them.
I can't.
I can't do it.
It's evil.
I can't.
What was that?
Oh shit, she's got shot.
Oh god.
No, wait, wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Please, please, please.
Don't.
Oh no.
Get out of the way.
Oh, run.
Run away.
My god.
Get out of here.
Holy shit.
They're still alive.
They're fine.
Oh my god.
That was horrible.
Okay.
Where am I going?
All right.
She got shot in the neck.
That was horrible.
All right.
No, I can't.
Where is this?
Why is it making me go this way?
Till death do us part.
I want this one tracked.
Power stone.
Isn't that where I am?
That's where I am.
Oh my god.
That's so funny.
Okay, let's go.
So much.
You think it's time you got a ring?
I'm working on it.
What?
All right.
I have to get her safely out of here.
Is that what was dead?
You all right?
Where you going?
Ow.
Okay.
Well, there's an interaction to tell you to stop following you.
She's dead?
Hey, well.
For your trouble.
How about a ruby?
Hold on.
We gotta bury this other lady first.
There's nothing in here.
What's wrong?
Am I not close enough?
There we go.
Instant Java potion.
Cool.
All right.
Ooh.
We're almost there.
Where are you?
Oh, god.
All right.
You know what?
You have to go.
Okay.
Wait.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I said you gotta send you back.
Send you home.
Where are you running towards the people with the guns?
This way, please.
This way.
Excuse me.
Yep.
You're fine.
Oh, my god.
Okay.
Go home.
How do I tell you to go home?
All right.
Go.
Dismiss.
You're not...
Okay.
Don't...
Why are you going this way?
Okay.
Thank god.
All right.
We're good.
Let's go.
Where are you going?
Honey.
You need to go the other way.
Oh, my god.
She's fucking so stupid.
Get.
Dismiss.
Yes.
You're going...
Do you see what's happening over here?
Not a good place to run.
Don't come over here.
Okay.
Good.
Oh, shit.
Oh, my god.
Honey, I'm gonna die.
I'm gonna run this way.
New plan.
Run.
What are you doing?
I lost the game.
I did not lose the game.
I'm fine.
What do you even do in this game?
Kind of a combination of everything.
Nice.
In the head.
All right.
Good.
You know, I'm going back to lightning.
I think she's still following me.
Okay.
I guess you're just gonna keep following me,
so might as well let you just follow.
Here we go.
I'm back.
And I was a dick.
Treat her well, will you?
Or I'll be back to her.
Wait.
What does that part mean?
He takes a step away and comes right back.
Oh.
Well, that didn't take very long.
Beware the ghost.
All right.
That's 100 renown.
Is she still here?
If she's still here, then we can probably leave.
Are you still here?
I think she left.
Okay.
Now I have to go back to that town
and then travel with her to the other house.
She's dead?
What do you mean she died?
What are you talking about?
Where?
Probably one shooting at you.
Okay.
Well, let's go.
That is a gigantic quest marker.
The sculptor.
I want to go back to...
What is it?
Bowerstone?
The girl that died.
One of them died.
I have to get the kiss book, you're right.
I don't think they both died.
I sent one of them back, remember?
What's going on in the house?
I've been gone for a little while.
Hello?
Okay.
Where is he?
Where'd he go?
Put the gun down.
Hello?
What's your name?
Hello, Amy?
I thought I had a loot.
I swear to God, I had a loot.
What are you...
I mean, who am I even doing that to?
Just anyone in the area?
Am I doing it in the mirror?
All right, where's the kiss book?
Onion!
All right, I need to pick a new quest.
I have to go visit...
No, where's this other person?
Where's the other...
Where'd the other little girl go?
The other lady.
What?
The other person died?
Okay, well, I need to go back to my other house
and see how my other, like, family's doing.
Right?
Like, I need to see the families, too.
Alex is unhappy.
Gwyneth, your family has a gift for you.
Holy shit, you ever gonna play the game?
Oh, that's right.
I did the ghost quest.
That was...
That whole thing was the ghost story line.
All right, let's see how this family's doing.
All right, family.
Dad's back.
I'm back.
I'm here to chop wood.
Watch football.
Hello, honey!
Thank you.
Oh, it was little baby Kieran.
Right, Kieran is the baby's name.
Right.
Kiernan.
I said it wrong.
Okay, we're good.
Now let's do the quest.
The ritual.
Walk to the Abbot in Oakfield and press the Abbot by earning Renown.
How much Renown do I need?
I'll return to the Abbot.
Okay.
I'm pretty famous now.
I think you'd let me do whatever you wanted.
What was I supposed to do?
Walk with me a while.
What the fuck are you doing?
I'm sorry, you're very large.
Second monk.
I have chosen to send a protector for the first.
And that's you.
If you're interested.
The cave is just at the end of this road.
You have to talk louder when it's your waterfall, dude.
You probably passed it on your way here.
Our strongest monk will be waiting for you when you're ready.
All right.
Are you the...
Are you the monk?
Even if they do not yet realize it.
Benjamin the monk.
Easy game.
Just dance.
That's all right.
What are you...
Honey, what are you doing?
Wait, what is he doing out here?
What the fuck is going on?
Why are you out here?
What?
I'm so confused.
Who is that?
Is that...
What?
What if we kissed at the demon door?
Hey there, boy.
Hello.
Oh, you're a strong, handsome fellow, aren't you?
I feel better having you with me in that cave.
Yes, I will.
I feel...
Are we related?
I feel like...
I feel like we're related.
We, like, look alike.
We have the same face.
You solemn vow never to bash anyone's face in.
Did my father mention that?
Yeah.
Whatever fighting's to be done in there, it's all yours.
I have to do all the fighting?
We require a hero, not a pacifist monk.
We'll need her to find a reason to fight.
I don't mind telling you, I'm a bit envious.
All the excitement that I get to carry this bloody thing like some sort of new.
I mean, look at it.
It's enormous.
Golden or not, how much water does a bloody acorn need?
I love...
I love water.
I like how, like, American English...
Water.
Does that sound nicer?
All Americans are from Boston.
Well, I said water and then I said water.
I said water.
Don't worry, I've got an axe.
How much longer am I going to scream for?
Um, what do I just do?
I just drank something for no reason.
Where's the dog?
Am I puking?
What's wrong with me?
I don't push or I'll split.
Sorry.
Violence.
What's that?
Uh-oh.
Stay on guard.
Open it up.
Stand on that and now I'll get in.
Fable one, fable two, fable three, three, three, fable three,
fable two, fable three, three, three.
Is Diablo 2, uh, remake out yet?
I wish.
Yeah, oh, say it again.
Water.
I-I-I get it.
Is your character portrayed by John Candy?
That's it.
I really hope they find someone else to do this next time.
Mind you, I'll be an old lady by then, so I'm probably off the hook.
You know, this is probably going to be the highlight of my life.
The day I carried a jug through a cave.
Shit, give me that.
Did you hear something?
No, probably just my imagination.
Don't talk much, do you?
You did hear something.
Right, I reckon that's all the water we're going to get from this one.
Oh, a silver key.
Oh my god, you guys, did you farted?
Did you hear that he farted?
Fuck, I didn't even test to see if the audio was synced.
I didn't even test to see if the audio was synced this entire game.
God damn it.
I need to test this.
Okay, ready?
Down, down, down.
Is it synced?
Is it major desync?
Is it close enough?
It's like one and a half seconds off, delayed by like 0.6 seconds.
Down, down, down.
Why one second?
Okay, so do you hear me first?
Do you hear the game?
What happens first?
How about this now?
How about ready?
Up, down, down.
Let's go.
Super, Superman.
Oh shit, people are giving me a ton of fucking subs.
I haven't even been paying attention, I'm sorry.
Oh no, somebody said it.
I have to say it now.
Ah.
Okay, I'll do it.
Gabi J!
Yay!
I just ate a bunch of fucking rotten pies.
It was like, I like this game, but it's kind of really fucking annoying.
That, like it might look like very simple on the screen,
but every time to do a spell I have to go up, up, up, up, up, down, down, down, down, down.
Hey, it's like Mortal Kombat, it's fucking so annoying.
Spells in this game suck.
Why'd you tell me that 71% of you told me to be a magician?
Behind you!
Wait, what?
I think the gifted subs.
Thank you, thank you.
Thank you.
Thank you, Val.
I appreciate it.
Thank you, Balsin, for the 20 community subs.
Thank you, Chef Lazarus, for the 10 subs.
You unite your workplace, thanks for 20 community subs.
Thanks a lot, guys.
It's not their name.
Their name is Balsin.
I'm gonna stand up here and use my fucking magical tune.
Oh, the bard who plays magical tune.
I don't know, I kind of feel like Connect Dad right now, I'm not gonna lie.
Easy, game's easy.
Get the blade spell, maybe next time.
Oh, let me come down there and help you.
Are they gonna kill her?
How do you miss point blank?
I can turn safety off and kill her?
What?
Toughness.
Hold on, they get a shock three.
Blades.
Let's do blades.
Blades one and blades two.
And let's also do speed.
Blades are broken.
Oh, nice.
Low level spells are now more powerful.
All right, what do we got here?
Let's do blades two.
Oh, shit, okay.
Holy shit, that's cool.
All right, so should I keep...
All right, here's what we're gonna do.
Oh, that's awesome.
All right, blades one and vortex two.
So I'll vortex two everybody.
And then we'll drop fucking blades everywhere.
Yes, I'm always ready.
Turn safety off.
Uh-oh.
Just unlearn chaos.
Chaos three or chaos five is probably really good.
He's back.
Here he comes.
Dina, what'd you find?
Oh, God.
Horse pose is cheap and OP.
I'll check it out.
I have her boss, right?
Yeah, this is awesome.
Why did I not just...
Okay, why would I ever use another move?
Why would I ever use another move?
Bro, I've been trying to tell you.
Yeah, I know, but still.
I need to level up like strength.
We have to get strength up.
Does any more health?
This health bar is so awful.
Sick.
Okay, I played Fable three or maybe like an hour or two, three hours or so.
And I thought it was absolute dog shit.
Am I misremembering this or did I just get bored of the franchise or something?
I remember not being good.
Should I play it?
No, it does suck.
Headless Hollow Man.
You have enough experience to buy something.
Okay, well, why is this so hard?
He's like the easiest enemy in the whole game.
Why is this like...
Why does he have his own cut scene?
The guy can't even see us.
That was a boss?
He was the worst one, but it was still...
I still liked it.
Fable three is still worth playing.
Yeah, I just didn't...
They added like a follower system or something, right?
Where you could open chests if you had a thousand followers,
2,000 followers, 10,000 followers, something weird like that.
No, it isn't.
What am I...
I'm...
That happens.
That's the level system.
The monks are evil.
I got one too.
Let's go.
I wish I could run faster.
Thank you, Balsin again for the 20 community subs this time.
Thank you, Balsin.
Fable one is the only one that's worth playing.
I think this one's good.
This is a good game, but if you played this when it came out...
This game promised so many things.
I remember looking at developer commentaries and hype videos about this game.
Everyone thought this was going to be like the world's greatest video game.
There was going to be like an entire living, breathing earth in this game.
And it ended up being like a 12 and a half to like 14 hour action game
that had like a marriage system.
It was not that big of a deal.
I remember watching a video of like...
Holy shit dog.
I remember watching videos of like Peter Molyneux talking about
if you plant this tree here, it will grow and you could have a forest.
And I think there's one cutscene that happens in the course of this entire like 15 hour experience
where like trees grow in a cutscene.
And that's it.
That was Fable one.
No, it was definitely Fable two because Fable one was good,
but he didn't have time to really hype it up like he did.
Wait, who's talking?
Why I'm missing important shit.
Where is this person?
Oh, God damn it.
I missed an entire thing.
Where are they?
He hyped it up the same way.
Yeah, but I remember thinking Fable two was going to be the world's...
I missed that too.
World's worst cameraman.
Oh my God.
I'm sorry, father.
Not that I broke my vow.
I'm sorry I didn't break it sooner.
What is this?
I never did fit in at this place.
We both knew that.
And now I'm making a new vow.
Lucian would die for what he did to you.
I won't break this one.
Why am I doing like the you put another t-shirt on in The Sims character creator?
As new life rises, so shall we.
As the seed returns to the earth, so do we all.
No, don't step on it.
I'm trying to move.
Okay, there's like an invisible wall right here
and it just fucked me up and I walked on it.
I didn't mean to do that.
I swear to God.
There's an invisible wall right here
and it like blocked me and fucked me up and I walked over here.
There's an invisible wall.
Look, I'm proving it right now.
I can't.
There's no farting.
I can't do anything.
I was in Renan.
Holy shit.
Cool.
I'm not going to fart.
That's no, I have to.
I'm not doing that.
That's not nice.
That's not a good boy move.
You know, so this game was cool.
I think Dark Souls.
Games like Dark, especially just when Dark Souls came out.
That like changed everything about how like an action adventure
melee kind of spell game was played.
Man, would I love a game that has this kind of
able to like world and systems, but Dark Souls level of game kind of mechanics.
Imagine a game that has like the world with all these like different like
permanently being able to kill people and
the quests and stuff, but it's like Dark Souls.
I would love like a fable slash Dark Souls.
I would love it.
Isn't this my house?
Holy shit.
I'm so sorry.
Oh my God.
I got to get out of town quick.
Wait, hold on.
What's?
Oh, they're out while they're out while they're out.
Just steal everything quick.
No, get out.
Just get out.
No, they might have something under the bed.
I can buy the house.
I can buy the house first and then it's not illegal.
How much is this place?
Holy shit.
Macho.
Are you okay?
Swim to Mexico.
All right.
I'm good.
They're like bees.
They're not going to come in the water.
Oh, what are you going to do?
What are you going to do about it?
Oh, no.
What happened?
You can't come and get me in the water.
Is the dog going to bite him?
He's like, should I?
What should I do?
Should I bite him?
All right.
Bite him.
Bite that guy.
Bite him on the leg.
Bite him.
I wonder if I can get him to go in the water.
Will he drown if he goes in the water?
All right.
I'm going to try something.
They're running in circle.
Oh, all right.
All right.
I got to go.
Fuck it.
Where the fuck am I going?
Oh, shit.
Why am I going this way?
Oh, my God.
I just shot him.
I shot a guy.
What happened?
Wait, what?
What just happened?
It was 200 gold?
Oh, all right.
I got to relax.
Relax.
I don't want to get into like a fucking coughing fit here.
Imagine shooting somebody in the fucking chest twice.
And the guy turns around.
He's just like, well, you can pay me $250.
That's so fucking funny.
I can't kill him.
Settle down.
I'm going to settle down.
That was that was...
I could have started to overthink that and laugh about that.
I got to relax.
Very well.
You've paid your debt to society.
Now then, you better not be planning on using that weapon.
I don't even think I can kill anyone again.
I want to put this weapon away.
It's closing time.
Is he about to limp?
What the fuck?
Hey!
What's he doing?
Who did he shoot the gun at?
What's going on over here?
What the hell is happening?
Wait.
Oh, they were bandits.
Oh, they were bandits attacking.
Wait, why is this happening?
Why are there so many people?
What's happening?
I don't understand.
Oh, shit.
It's like a fucking brawl.
Who's dog?
Oh, that's my dog.
This is just the purge.
All right.
I'm done.
I'm done after this.
I'm getting out of here.
Okay.
Safety on.
I mean, the guy like literally was like,
ah, thanks for paying the fee, bastard.
And then he aimed the gun and just started firing at somebody.
Oh, shit.
He's a guard.
I don't know.
I thought he was like shooting at my dog.
I thought he was firing at somebody that I was connected to somehow
because he was like still aggro to me.
I thought he was still aggro to my character somehow
and like was shooting at the dog.
I don't know.
Okay.
We're good.
Still, I still think that's so funny.
Two like fucking slugs in the chest and he's just like,
I'll take 250 if you just want to keep walking.
That's got like 12 holes in his body.
How do I get out of here?
I'm sorry, your honor.
I thought he was still aggroed on me.
Your spouse is threatening divorce?
Where do you see that?
Keep walking.
My reputation is already awful.
What's wrong?
What's going on?
I got a gift.
Pretty necklace.
We're fine.
And I'm going to do your favorite thing.
The fist pump.
Oh shit, that's wrong.
Wrong wife.
But I think you'll still like it.
Isn't this your daughter?
What?
No.
What are you talking about?
What?
No, it's not.
All right.
Sure.
How's the baby?
Okay.
Everything's fine.
We're good.
What do you want?
Okay.
We're good.
Let me check on the baby.
How's the baby doing?
Hello.
It's me.
Hello, Amy.
Okay.
You like the loot.
Let's play some loot for you.
Oh, plus 22.
I really like that.
Let's do it again.
Okay.
See?
I have a good reputation with the baby.
With the wife.
I'm going to sleep for six hours.
Get some health.
Feel much better.
Okay.
Yeah, I can check on my business.
How's the business doing?
I have made $29.
That's awful.
Check the sculpture.
Where's the sculpture?
Oh, wait a minute.
This is Alchemist.
What would you like?
My turn.
For anything in particular.
All right.
Stay there.
I need some health potions.
Come back any time.
You're all hob strength.
Let's just buy a bunch of these.
There you go.
Skill potions.
Will potions.
Yeah, I'm going to drink.
I'm going to just cheat.
One of my nephews will.
Okay.
Potions.
I want a will potion.
Excellent.
Drink all the potions.
Steal the money back.
I can't.
Skill potion.
Your wife looks ever happy.
Nice.
Strength.
I have three strength potions.
Whatever.
You know the word I'm trying to say.
Oh, my God.
Well, I'll be able to upgrade a ton of stuff in strength.
What time is it?
It's been six hours.
We'll probably stop soon.
I'm probably not going to beat the game tomorrow,
but you know, we'll see.
I didn't take a piss one time.
No, you're right.
I didn't.
You most certainly will not.
No, I probably will not.
But we'll still play at a bunch.
Okay.
Let me, I can level up.
I've got four, like 5,000.
How much is blades?
Three.
All right.
I'm saving up for blades three.
It's too good.
But I can do, I need to level up this.
It's awful.
Flourishes.
Flourishes are really, really cool, actually.
From what I remember.
Save the game.
Oh, my God.
Have I not done that the whole game?
Sell chaos back.
Yeah.
Can I do that?
I don't think I can sell this back.
I'm just going to scare this guy.
I just feel like it.
Reach over.
Pull money out of the register.
Oh, press Y.
Wait, what?
I hear like the, why do I hear those bells?
All right.
Let's do some blacksmithing.
Everyone's going to be pissed.
I know.
Whatever.
Everybody hates this shit.
Nobody wants to watch this.
I know.
But whatever.
I don't think I didn't remember.
Oh, yeah.
We'll play this again tomorrow.
I'm not going to start at like four o'clock like today.
It was just a bunch of stuff I had to do today.
Before we start around two o'clock Pacific.
Yeah, that sounds good to me.
This is a lot of fun, though.
It's fun just, I mean, I don't feel like I haven't really done very much,
but I've enjoyed the whole time I've been playing.
We'll do more missions tomorrow.
We'll do some more story stuff tomorrow.
I spent the whole time just fucking around.
It was very fun.
I'm a good boy, too.
Yeah, I only got one hero.
I need two more heroes.
And look, if I don't beat it tomorrow, you know, it's all good.
I don't need to beat Fable, too.
We'll play it for like another six, seven hours tomorrow and see where we are.
Yeah, you know, everyone knows it's coming.
End of the stream voice is right.
Yeah, Hassan raided the stream.
If any of you are still here, thanks for checking out the stream.
And again, I will reiterate this next Sunday.
Is it going to be something very interesting?
I don't know exactly what it is,
but I've been told it's going to be a nice, really, really great time.
I don't really know what that means.
He's going to play Among Us next Sunday.
Oh, God, no.
He said he's going to raid the guy who never streams and it was you.
I mean, I stream once.
I stream like once or twice a week.
Raid the guy who never streams.
Now, I told you the only way I would play Among Us
is if I did an Impostor is Sus guy plays Among Us
and tried to get like a hundred thousand community subs
and just do like a massive sellout like I'm the Impostor is Sus guy.
Like, look at how cool this is.
I'm playing Among Us.
But the reason why I never decided to do it
was because that means that all those people stay
and it will never go away.
You know how many people,
if I were to do an Impostor is Sus guy stream,
they would show up and they would be like,
Impostor is Sus guy that they would never leave.
And it's the only thing I would be asked to do for the rest of my life.
What about the numbers?
Yeah, some things just aren't worth that much money.
You know what I mean?
Some things are really just not worth it to me.
That's one of them.
I don't really care.
I don't want like a fucking hundred thousand
Impostor is Sus community subs.
It would be wicked cool.
This is a thousand bucks for every single one of these I'm doing.
I haven't missed once.
Think of the debt.
No, I'm not.
I would never do it.
That's integrity.
I don't think so.
I think I just don't want to have to look in my Discord
and see 500 messages a day saying,
Is he going to do another Among Us stream?
When's the Sus guy going to do it again?
Where's Sus guy?
Where is he?
That stream was so good.
Do it again.
Why is he not doing it tomorrow?
Do it now.
Every stream.
Where's Among Us?
Why would the Among Us guy not play Among Us?
That makes no sense.
It would be a tear through this community.
Don't know.
It would be funny.
I think it would be funny for like a couple hours,
but I really don't want to have to bait people into being here
thinking that I'm going to be streaming Among Us
and that they stay.
I'm almost about to be level five blacksmith.
You're over exaggerating on the impact it would have.
I know.
Why do I think that's such a huge deal?
It just isn't.
That meme is so old and like dead.
It doesn't even matter.
All right, I'm going to be level five for tomorrow.
There it is.
Level five.
All right, I might as well just go until I can't.
It's not dead.
It's on its way out though.
Is Among Us still relevant?
I don't know.
I really don't know.
Okay, I thought I was married to the town crier for a second.
I was like, how did that happen?
All right, let's see how much money I can get doing it at level five.
I fucked it up.
Yeah, I'm going to I'm calling it here anyways.
We're calling it.
We'll pick up tomorrow with like 20,000 gold
and we'll do the next mission.
Change the title of the town crier.
People don't like salad dodger.
Nice bit of forging.
Oh, I also want to talk about this too.
This is very brief, but this is things to be excited about.
I am pleased to announce today that the third quarter of this year
is going to be fucking insane.
There are two streams.
I'm not going to go into detail of what they are at the moment
because I don't really need to.
I don't want to.
In August and September,
both of them are going to be bigger than the carnival.
Both of them.
So in August and then right after that in September,
there's going to be two streams.
And they're both larger than larger in scale than the carnival.
And you know what?
Fuck it.
I'll just say one of them is baseball.
Yeah, we are so close.
We are so close to completely locking that stream down.
And I'm so happy that we are.
I can't fucking wait.
I don't have any hard dates yet, but like we are so close.
But there's that's going to happen somewhere in like quarters three.
There's another stream that's going to be bigger than that.
That's happening somewhere probably in quarter three as well.
I can't wait.
You will get dates for these streams within the next,
I would say the next two weeks.
I will have probably hard dates for both of these streams.
There's also the grotto beast cards.
Oh, is it coming too?
Hopefully soon as well.
It's going to be fully loaded.
I told you back in because of COVID,
like three streams had to get completely just dumped.
Oh, that's it.
Now let me get 20,000.
And now we're really kind of turning the book in the chapter on that.
A lot more opportunities came up
and a lot of these streams were pretty much done.
The baseball stream was ready to go.
We were two weeks away from it happening before it was just too risky.
It was like we there was a bunch of the spikes in a lot of the places
and it was just we can't we just can't fucking do it.
I don't want to do it.
So we lost.
I spent money on that stream and it just never happened.
But I can't fuck around.
But now that's coming back and I can't wait.
So there's a couple of streams that were pushed forward
and you'll see them at some point in August and September.
All right, 20,000 and I'm out of here.
Oh, see you next weekend.
See you next Sunday.
I'll be live tomorrow, but still see you next Sunday.
You promised to watch Megamind.
Well, I didn't promise to watch Megamind.
I said I would consider it.
All right, only a few more.
Is that Otto?
Did Otto just bark at the door?
Hold on.
Otto, is that you?
All right, that's it.
I will see you guys tomorrow.
We'll call it here.
You promised to watch Megamind.
All right, I'll watch Megamind and I'll let you know how I think.
All right, let me save the game.
I'll see you guys tomorrow.
Let's run the credits.
Thanks for all the community subs.
There were a lot of them from that Balls.
The Balls guy gave a lot of money.
It was like 50 community subs from Balsin.
Thank you.
And as always, everybody else today.
Thanks to Hassan.
Thanks to Chibli.
I missed this as well.
This is a raid.
I think I was in the middle of doing something.
I didn't see it.
But Chibli, thanks for the raid.
There's about 500 of you came from Chibli.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Yeah, see you guys tomorrow.
Let me save and continue to go.
Credits are off center.
I know.
I'm just terrible.
Let me see if I can fix it right now.
Got it.
There you go.
Look at that.
Perfect.
864p, Andy.
That's me.
Ooh, did I just turn this stream off?
Nope.
Can't wait for more polygamy and blacksmithing.
No, not so much.
I'm going to do missions tomorrow.
I'm going to actually go bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, and do story stuff tomorrow.
Because I want to progress the game.
Am I going to finish it?
I don't think I'm going to be able to finish it.
We'll get pretty close.
But I don't think that I'm not going to do a 10-hour stream tomorrow to finish table two.
We'll see how far we get.
Do 1080p?
No, you don't want to do 1080p on Twitch.
To have good 1080p video, you need to have a bitrate that's higher than Twitch allows.
That's why I was in 720 for so long.
720p, 6,000 bitrate is good.
The more resolution you go up, if you don't increase your bitrate, it just looks worse.
So I have not increased my bitrate because I'm at the maximum.
What I did is I dropped my CPU preset until I can do NVENC.
And then I'm going to make it so that runs essentially through that.
So yeah, 1080 just is probably never going to work until
Twitch like I guess officially allows for like 10 to 12,000 bitrates.
I don't think that's going to happen anytime soon.
But 864 is where I'm going to go for now.
Thanks again, everybody.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Have a great night.
Your server costs would just go way up.
Yeah, I really doubt that would happen.
Do you have any plans for the 10th anniversary of your career?
You made it sound like huge plans were to be had, the big anniversary milestone.
I mean, not particularly, but there's like two or three streams that you're going to see
like after June, July.
That, I mean, there's just massive, massive amounts of work and time going into them.
So I guess you could say that these couple of streams coming up are kind of big
deals, at least for me, being here for 10 years.
I don't have anything particularly planned for like the exact day.
We'll probably, I'll probably just be like, oh, nice.
Yeah, it's been 10 years.
It's insane.
I can't believe people have stayed watching this channel for 10 years.
That just, it blows my mind.
Hey, thanks to you.
Thanks.
Thanks, you boy.
And 10 community subs right at the end here.
Appreciate it.
Have a great night.
We'll see you tomorrow.
Take care of yourselves.