Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with Facecam Fortress 2, playing on CTF Turbine. Almost forgot the name of the map, but I did not headshot that guy.
There's no way I headshot that guy. I went like three feet to the left of his head. But anyways, playing on CTF Turbine, using the Huntsman Sniper, one of my favorite classes in the game.
A lot of you guys already know that, but let's get right into this here. No, no, no, no, no. Ah, come on. Give me that shot in the head. Close, close.
Are we going to get the cap? Are we going to get the... I almost said cart. I almost said a lot of things today. You are standing still on there and you are a spy.
Welcome to the show. He's going to backstab me. I almost just got backstabbed. Another one! What the hell?
Whenever that happens, that always scares the absolute crap out of me. I get in a lot of those situations where you kill a spy or you knock a spy into Dead Ringer.
And then another spy just appears in front of you like they both were coming at you at the same time. It is terrifying.
So let's respawn now. We got two caps. We might just win this right off the bat. I'm okay with that. Anybody, anybody, anybody? We're going to win right now.
Oh, I thought that was going to be a long range headshot. That's going to hit him. No, it's not. But he's covering in P and I'm going to get the assist.
All right. Let's go again. Scramble the teams. All right. I'm fine with that. I'm cool with that, man. Launch it. Ready? Ready? Ready?
I thought he was going to go this way. Scramble teams. Here we go. You are now on blue in red letters. What? I'm on a red team. I'm on red team right now.
Valve, why you be trolling? Can't even get your colors right. Come out of there. Come out of there. No, he's going to be right here.
No, that guy is though. I'll take that. Oh, spy. I'll take that as well. P. P in his face. That's a spy pyro. If I had aimed a little bit higher.
Wow. Wow. Wow. Wow. Wow. Whoa. We got it. We got it. We got it. Oh, get his head. I'm just trying it. I will get this guy. I will get this guy in his face.
Yes, I got him. And that guy. Oh, my God. Crits. Oh, my God. Crits. Oh, it's always so nerve wracking. I still pinned to the wall up there. Oh, my goodness gracious.
Is the medic still up here? Pyro is right here. This pyro is going to get it right in his face. Oh, man. That was not good for him. Oh, you want to play this game? Let's go. Wow. Wow. Wow. Awesome one.
That was awesome. I give you props for that one. You waited that one out. You played for it and you got the kill. So if you're watching this right now, awesome one. Good kill. Oh, my God.
There's nothing in this cup. There should be Dr. Pepper in there. Damn it. Heavy is going to cap it. Absolutely, my friend. Headshot right off the bat.
No, I will crit you. Come here, you little scout. Oh, bam. My God. I could never. I could have never prayed for a shot that good. Holy crap. It's on tonight.
There's a century. Can I take that thing off from out here? I had it. I had it. That's a lot of death so far. I kind of just keep getting myself killed. Sir, you've got a scout right next to you. Is he going to do it? Is he going to do it?
Place your bets. Place your bets. Who's going to win this fight? Was there a spy behind him? I just don't know. You can never know in Team Fortress. That should have hit him. I should have not. Just come here for crying out loud.
Oh, you. I'm going to. Whatever. I'll kill him right now. Ready? Ready? Damn. This guy's being a weasel. Oh, my. Oh, I'm so bad. I am so bad. I wonder how many misses were that? Like seven in a row? Good game. Let's cap this last one.
This heavy is so toast. There it is. Heavy, I'm not going to kill you. We're going to have a tea party in here. Wait, just come here. Let's do one more for good measure here. Walk into that. No, you didn't walk into it.
How did you not get shot in your face? This guy's so dead. Wow. There's a lot of you in there. Wow, Pyro. Oh, my God. I got to get myself out. Put me out, please. Put me out, please. Please, sir. Thank you so much. I love you.
Demoman is this guy's name. I should probably be getting health right now, but damn it. Oh, somebody would have just got wrecked. Wow. But get me back in. Get me back in here, please.
I need health, please. Is there a medic on the team or anything? That's two in a row. Are we going to just win this right off the bat? Come on, health. Wow. This is going to be three caps, literally, in a row. All righty then. Bang. I should have hit him. I'll get this Demoman, though.
We turned into it. Well, that's three. Can I get this Pyro? Is the real question? Yes, I can. Well, that's just three just bang, bang, bang, bang caps in a row. I guess I'll just end the bet. So thanks so much for watching, guys. I really do appreciate it.
And I'll see you guys all next time. And of course, take care, everybody. Trying to get that into the microphone. I hopefully it did.