I hope I haven't saved in the right spot because right immediately after, I believe it was
some poison it has to be disposed of coming up here at the birthday party. Otto's good.
Otto's fine. Just needed some routine checkup and he needed his shot. So he's good. If you
don't know, Otto has Addison's disease. So he needs, essentially for the rest of his life,
he needs to get a injection to help stop some of the symptoms. But he lives a perfectly normal,
happy life on the medication. And he's coming on, I think, 13 or 14 years old here. He's doing great.
But anyways, what up? Pod watchers skip. It's the intro. Actually, if you could skip the intro,
you could. Actually, I don't disagree with what you said. But you're going to miss a very important
announcement. Very important coming up here. Ladies and gentlemen, I present to you,
the nominees are open for the end of the year awards. You find your way over in the discord.
There's a channel there is going to be some rules you need to follow.
Please submit any clips over the year for new viewers. This is actually we probably should
talk about this. So a lot of people here may have joined this community in the last six, 12 months.
So let me just break this down if you don't know what we do. At the end of the year,
we do an award show for the channel. And it's not just the best things that have happened here. It's
also the worst things that have happened here. We're talking best joke and worst joke. We're
talking best stream and worst stream. We're talking worst face worst hair. So it's it's usually pretty
much you're trying to find some of these things that make sense those categories. There are a
couple of new categories this year. Some of you might be really happy to know. For instance,
uh, we didn't know whether the title of best or worst, because it makes sense both ways.
Best face, no, no, no, best, um, best overdone Boston moment or worst overdone Boston moment.
We really didn't know what to call it. It's kind of just best overdone Boston moment. And I'll give
you an example. Oh, I got a fucking Starbucks here, dude. Good luck, because I don't even know
what you're gonna find. I don't know. There's only like three times this ever happened. I think
we literally only know of like three. Who knows? Maybe some of you might find a bunch of them. I
don't know. That's the fun with these awards is a lot of them are just kind of horseshit.
And trying to figure out what people actually find is part of the fun, right? Like worst
Boston overdone moment. It's like, what the fuck are you? What are you talking about?
Good luck. Best sound, worst sound. Yep. And yes, some best sounds will be on the worst sound list
and some worst sounds will also be on the best sound list. I don't make the rules, except I do.
I made all the rules. So follow them. Of course I made the rules. What about the example you just
gave? Can we nominate that? Yes, nominations. It's going to be kind of like it was last year. So
because this is happening not on New Year's Eve anymore, this is happening on around Christmas
time. So it's going to be pulled back a week or two. This show we need to. So I think it was,
what was it? December from December, I think like 15th or something last year and forward till we
close nominations in a couple of weeks. So we, I think what we need to do is figure out what was
the cutoff period last year. I think it was like December 10th last year. So anything December
12th or 15th forward, right, is what way you can pull clips from. When are you going to play modded
Skyrim? I installed like 150 Skyrim mods and bricked my computer. So I just was like, I just
uninstalled everything. You know, it wasn't a virus. It just like a Skyrim just wouldn't open
anymore. So I was like, fuck, this is, I don't even know what's wrong. But anyways, yeah. So
the pinned message that you just saw in the chat, there is a nominations channel.
That's where you go. We have a form after the nominations close, kind of compile everything,
kind of vet a bunch of the responses and you will be able to vote as of the second week of December.
I would say that we're trying to have submissions close for nominations on the 4th of December,
which then you will be able to vote from the 6th or 7th of December all the way till about a day
or so before the show. Go check the channel. And if you don't even, again, this was a lot
of new people here probably. If you don't know what I'm talking about, go, go skim through some
of the previous years. This is the fifth year going on by the way. All right. I don't care.
Do a Mario voice. Okay. Hello. Now go nominate something. Okay. I just did that for you. So,
you know, go do something for me. Go nominate something. All right. We're going to go back
to the McNulty house. We are going to open this right where we left off. We were in the middle
of my birthday party. Well, it's not my birthday party, but it was McNulty's birthday party.
Invited all of his friends. We're going to continue this saga. I'm ready to go. Oh, by the way,
there's a, there's an a hundred thieves video that's on the hundred thieves channel.
I was on the JHB show, TBH with JHB. It was pretty fun. It was cool. You want to go check it out?
It's on the hundred thieves, uh, YouTube channel. It was a fun time. You didn't answer one question.
Yes, I did. I answered like 10. There was like, it was a lot of questions going on.
You just lied the whole time. What? No, I didn't. What do you mean lied the whole time?
We were talking about our favorite foods and that like AI is, is getting really weird. Isn't it?
What do you mean lying and making up? What are you talking about? Do I like pappaginos?
Pappaginos is the best chain pizza you could possibly eat. It is the best chain pizza
that is, that's available for you to eat. People are saying wrong. Stop it. I I'm telling you right
now, pappaginos versus something like Domino's, not even a contest. It's not even close. It's not
even fucking close. That piece of sucks. You are so wrong. I can't even believe it.
That's dog shit. That's a dog shit take. No, it is not. If those view that are telling me
that Domino's is better than pappaginos, one of two things is, is the problem. One,
you've never eaten pappaginos because it's mostly a Northeast thing. So you,
you were just making it up. Oh, Domino's is better. I've never eaten the other one,
but that's fine. The second one is you got pappaginos before and it was at a party and
there were 10 pizza boxes lined up in a row and you ended up getting in line to get your slice of
pizza an hour and a half after the pizza showed up. So you're like, oh yeah, there's pizza isn't
there. And you go in the back and there it is. Okay. There's like the line of pizzas, like six
pizzas here. We're all like sharing it. I'm waiting. I've waited an hour to go get a slice.
You're going to give me that kind of review, play the game already, play the game. I'm gonna
play the game already. Change your pinned tweet. I can't, I can't. That means I have to log on to
Twitter. Well, actually I was on Twitter. I retweeted the 100 thieves thing. But anyways,
Domino's doesn't even stand a chance. I'm sorry. Pizza Hut, I will say, I don't know, I was stalling
for a minute because somebody angered me immensely in this chat by saying that pappaginos was a shitty
place. Pizza Hut, stuffed cross pepperoni pizza. You got me there. You do have me there.
Every single other item at Pizza Hut is awful. Pizza Hut, stuffed crust pepperoni pizza is
S plus. Every single other thing there is bad, but it's worth going there all the time because
they have that one item. I feel the same way about Taco Bell. The multi versus panel is still up.
Oh, God damn it. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Give me a second. Is it really there? It is, isn't it?
It is. I'm removing it. I'm taking it off. There it goes. It was posting the link every 15 minutes
since that stream. What? I didn't turn it off. It was posting the link every 15 minutes since that
stream. What? Hold on. Wait a minute. You're telling me that whatever. It's fine. Hey, hey,
Warner Brothers has been really good to me. So it's, I don't know. It's about it. I don't care.
That's fine. I don't care. Warner Brothers has been wonderful to me. That's fine.
All right. I'm done stalling. I've got my fucking Starbucks trying to give you some ideas. So where
you, you know, if you go fucking find something back like last year when I was like fucking talking
like this a lot and you can put it in the best overdone fucking Boston accent moment, this could
be one of them, except it's not because I'm going to, it's going to be deleted even if you nominate
it. Cause I was giving you an example. I'm looking, I actually am looking forward to that
category. I can't wait. I can't wait to see. All right, let's go. Yeah. There is worst stream.
You can nominate worst stream. Go ahead. Whatever it is. We'll see. We'll see if it wins. What's up?
All right. So last thing. Oh, by the way, this was really funny. Actually. You see this up here. I,
I was like pissed off because I was like, why does it say that? Why is it doing this?
It said, it said like itty bitty German nine eight five. I was like, why does it say that?
That's not cool. Why does it say that? I didn't know that they cycle through these
jokey things up here. I thought for some reason, I thought somebody was like fucking with me.
All right. The last thing we did is people were, I got to, I got to catch this. I got to catch this
because I believe we were in the middle of the party and I believe I was about to poison the cake
which don't ask me why I was, people were saying like, Oh, poison. Hold on. All right. All right.
No, no, no, no. All right. Put it away. I right when I put it away, put it away, put it away,
put it away, put it away, put it away. My birthday party can't be ruined yet. Put it away.
Why is it lagging so much? No, put it away. How do I put this away? I'm just going to delete it.
What is it? My computer's crashing. Why is my computer? It's my PC crashing. There we go. That
was weird. I don't want anybody to eat this. It's a 10,000. This is not a $10,000 PC. All right. So
no, I don't want anybody to eat this dude. My computer does not like this game right now.
Why is it running so bad? All right. How do I hold on? I got to like,
I think my games like cash is messed up. Help me. This man wants to punch me and steal my money.
Where? Why is this running so bad? I'm not punching anybody.
Maybe. All right. I don't want anyone to eat the cake, but I'm going to blow the candles out.
All right. It's time to celebrate. Nobody eat this. I just said I hated the organ.
You've ruined my birthday party. All right. Well, how do I blow out the candles? Stop, stop,
stop, stop, stop, stop, stop. All right. How do I fix this? Just take it out of his hand.
How do I fix this? Okay. We're good. Nobody can eat that cake. I don't want anyone to die right now.
No, no, no, no, no. Shit. How do I have, how do I get rid of this? Fence the cake in.
I just want to celebrate the birthday. I don't want anyone to eat it. Make a new cake.
How do I just get, how do I like do the thing? Blow out the candles. Where the,
how come I can't blow the candles out? Go away from here. Go away. Don't eat this.
Whatever. I don't even care. I have to take it from him though,
because I need to finish the birthday party. I have to delete the cake. Okay.
All right. So I did it. Why can't I throw it away? Why can't I throw it away? I can't sell it.
I can't put it in my inventory and I can't sell it. There's no trash. Whoa. What are you doing?
What's the, isn't there a DJ supposed to be here? Don't touch this cake. Nobody touch this cake.
No. Do I need a trash? Buy a trash. This is a laundry hamper. Okay. All right. I don't want
the party to end before the DJ gets here. That's incredibly important. All right. Throw it away.
What was that? All right. Throw it away. Throw it away. Imagine throw it away. Your birthday
cake. That's kind of, how do I fix this? Don't eat it. Don't eat it. She has to put it down
somewhere. Don't eat it standing up. There's no room to sit down, but don't eat it. I thought
she's going to start taking bites out of it. Okay. Oh, wait, we have a compromise here.
That's been a compromise. Somebody take one. It's the every road led to this guy taking a piece.
Nobody got one, right? Get rid of this cake and make, make me a new one. I want just throw it away.
Okay. You need to stop doing that. All right. Everybody's safe. Leave one. What do you mean?
I need somebody to make me a birthday cake. Who is that? Somebody make me a cake. Wait, what?
It's you? What? Wait, you're the, you are the caterer. You just haven't been making any food.
You've been dancing. They are the caterer. I just hired him again. Okay. Birthday. What?
What? Wait, did he eat a slice? No, he didn't eat a slice, right? Santa's just fuked. What?
Oh no. Why did he puke? What happened? I, he did not eat any cake. So what? I just don't get to
have a birthday party anymore. What? He didn't eat any cake. Oh my God. That was crazy.
He just like fuked and died. I was so diligent though. I don't know what happened.
I didn't, there's a grilled cheese on this counter. It's like, dude, now is not the time
to make a grill. I'm trying. I want to make a birthday cake. Wait, can I, let's see if I can
bring him back. You're going to bring him back? While you literally just saved my life, words
cannot begin to describe how grateful I am. I won't forget this. Well, he's still dead.
Did they? I don't think that's accurate. Why is he still dead? They're a little late. Don't
get that close. When is it? Okay. Repair this. What? What do you mean? Why am I turning blue?
What? How do I stop this? I need clothes. How do I put clothes on? How do I put clothes? I'll put
some clothes on. What are you doing? Okay. There you go. What can? Oh, the caterer is back.
How are you? No, don't do that yet. I'm not ready. Can you make a cake? Can you finish this cake?
What are you doing? This scared the shit out of me. All right. Get up, get up, get up, get up.
Are you going to do it? Actually, I need to blow up my birthday candles. Okay. Um,
interesting. I know I lean directly like that. All right. So let's just have a conversation for
a little bit. What's your likes and dislikes? It's annoying. Wait, she's flirty. What?
Following traits about hot headed. Okay. Um, should I have a single?
Okay. Married to what? You're married? What is? Oh. What's going on here? You don't like bugs.
Tell tales of galactic conquest. All right. Well, you want you looking for a funny conversation.
Uh, let's do, I'll do an impression. That sounds good. Uh, I would not take your phone.
It's going to be ruined. Your phone is ruined. I don't know why you took it into the hot tub.
That was really not a good idea. You can tell knock knock jokes. What do I do? I wait. Aren't
you married? And they're going to ruin everything. Oh no. Oh no. Oh no. I'll put
your hand in that. Don't do that. Okay. Can somebody say something? Okay. What? Planning
for retirement and midlife crisis away. It's the perfect time to start wrapping up those
lifelong goals. Are you leaving? I didn't even bake my cake. What do I do with all this shit?
Do I have to sell this stuff? How do I just leave it here? Have you done any of your goals yet?
We changed to rocket scientist. I'm getting close. I have to read three books in my whole life
and that'll get there. You just an olive oil cake. I just, I need to blow my birthday candles out.
Okay. There it is. Nice. Now add birthday candles. If no one's going to be here with me,
I don't care. I'm doing it. You did it. What senior already wrinkled bellies party. Wait,
what happened? I got older. Wait, that's what happened. Okay. All right. Can I reverse that?
How do I reverse that? I did it last time. I don't, I don't remember that happened the last time.
Did it? I thought it was because the guy, I celebrated it. I didn't know if like blowing
out the whatever. What are you doing over here? I don't care. What a sloppy fucking,
actually that looks pretty good. Dude, you made, okay. That's very strange. This is not poisoned,
right? Am I old? I could just die at any minute now, right? Lord forgot to have a party for his
birthday. No, I didn't. I want to do that too. Why did I make a tomato sandwich? Why did I make
this? If I'm just put it away, put it in my inventory. I'll bring things home. These will
be fine at the house. Oh, he never got the pizza. He wanted to order a pizza. All right. That was
fun. Time to go home. But first let me go check this out. Wait, burn? Why can I burn these leaves?
That makes me happy. She's not going to light on fire, right? I thought he was afraid of fire.
Play with? What do you mean play with? What am I doing? Why am I doing this?
You're feeding the fire. Why is she still doing this here? Let's get this shit out of me.
I think we're all right. It's cold out. It's chilly. Yeah. Let's talk about the weather.
Uh, I got it. I got a cake over here.
All right. Well, I had apparently two birthdays. I, I'm not going back.
What? All right. I got to go home.
That was fun. Thanks everybody for coming to my double birthday work.
Oh, wait, I stayed up all night. I don't want to leave this here. Oh, just go home.
Oh, get off your phone. Just go home. Oh, going to work covered in, wait,
GeekCon is in GeekCon is in town again, guys. Disgusting. Yeah. It's a trash plant.
It just started growing. So I just kept it. Your house sucks. Oh, you don't have to live in it.
So why do you care? You're in the perfect state. No, I'm going to rest up. We're going to take care
of the dog. How are you doing? Daily cap for a lifestyle. I don't even know what that means.
I got promoted. Look at, wait, I came into work. I shit my pants. I haven't showered in three days.
I haven't slept and I got promoted. All right. There it is. Apprentice inventor. New clothes
and I can do journey to the stars. Why is this person dead? Congratulations on your recent
birthday. Why is this person dead? What are you, what are you, what are you doing? What do you want?
Yeah. Can I help you? You, you're here to, you want to see the dog? Why did you just take a selfie
in my driveway? Um, hello. What do you want? You want to, you want to come take a picture with the
dog? Wait, does this dog have a friend? So what, what can I do? How can I help you? Okay. I don't
know why you're here. The dog has a better social life than you. Yeah. This is one of the dog's
friends. Okay. Well, we need to clean up a little. I'd never said invite in by the way. What if it's
a vampire? Could be, could it be a vampire? I never invited this person in. Okay. You think
she's a vampire? I'm drinking a coffee at nine o'clock at night. I haven't slept in two or three
straight days. Why is this guy still going? All right. So this, this girl just came over the house
to take a picture with the dog and then to use my computer. All right. There we go. Take a shower.
Take a thoughtful shower. Okay. Oh my God. This is taking a long time. All right. All right. This is,
this, this is not a library. Okay. It's time for you to go. This is, this isn't a library. I'm sorry.
Um, bribe for friendship. No, no. It's time for you to leave. Thanks for coming. Send home. Goodbye.
Get out of here. What am I doing? Why did I wake up to do this? I'm just looking at the,
I'm looking at the Christmas decoration. All right. You leave the house. Get out. Why won't
she leave? I should really get going. Yes. Get out of here. She's been living there.
What's the matter? What's wrong? You okay? Oh no. What's wrong? We need to go to the vet.
Everything all right? Where you going? Wanted to get some exercise. Oh, it's okay. I got a, um,
decent bar. No, wake it up. Wake up, wake up, wake up, wake up. No, no, no. Oh no. This is actually
sad. No, wait. How do I, can I, wait, pause it, pause it, pause it. Hold on a second. No, I wasn't,
that wasn't, I wasn't ready. I was asleep. Save him. I can't, I can't save the game right now.
No, it's okay. Okay. Everything's going to fall apart right now. Oh, he was a good dog.
Look at, look at, she was very happy at the end. That's all right. I'm not going to work today.
Be serious. Do something. She lived a long life. We're going to put this somewhere. Nice. That's sad.
Where should we put this? Here. Right here. I'm not, the bed's not going away. Reload? Um, I don't
think it matters if I reload because I've had, you're watching TV. What is this? Oh, it's the
taco casserole I made. Bro's got to check on the Cowboys game. I'm going to, let's see if we can
annoy death out of the house. No, turn this all off. I don't like this. Get rid of this. Adopt a
cat or something. Ask for advice. Ask for advice about death. That makes sense. Flirty. It's going to
work. We can't get a word in here. Okay. Gloomy compliment. This is death, right? This is right
up death. Oh, okay. Well, sad day, but I mean, look at, we're getting older too. Remember you
can't flush the toilet. That's sad. Oh well. It's too bad. Oh no, the food bowl. You can use,
go use the computer. There. Look, it's like nothing changed. See, you got your spot.
Pay your bills. Oh my God. Right. There's no electricity. I can't use the computer.
How much are the bills? $584. What? All right. Can you turn my lights back on?
Wait, is geek con right now? I'm not ready for geek con. No, I'm not. I'm not ready for geek con.
It's, I mean, I guess I could take my mind off things, but I, should I go to geek con?
Should I? All right. But this is not geek con. This is meet a celebrity. That's not,
when's geek con? Neighborhood brawl. We do it. We do a purge. I don't understand.
Neighborhood brawl? That's going to be fucking wild. Okay. Well, I need to make sure I have
high bars for the neighborhood brawl. Why would we do this? Do that now? It's not until this weekend.
That's a very strange thing to be invited to. I feel like I'm going to get my ass kicked at this
event. I'm an old man. All right. No, we missed geek con. I think it was yesterday. I need to prepare
for a harvest fest. Thanksgiving, right? All right. I need to prepare. Decorate. Brand meal.
I'm going to have a Thanksgiving party. So I need to decorate. Place holiday decorations from build
mode. Decorate the house exterior by placing and using the attic stack decoration box. How do I do
this? I need a, I only have 113 bucks. No, I'm keeping it. That was a stupid telescope. I said
it's, wait, I have bees. I forgot about the bees. I don't need to get rid of the telescope. I don't
want it there. So you can see out the window. Okay. I need some harvest. What's it called?
Harvest fest. What do I do this? Outdoor furniture. Outdoor activities. Which, what do I do?
Attic. What do I do that? Styled rooms. Where's attic? Search it. Attic stack decoration box. Oh,
okay. All right. So we need some, uh, some things to do here, which is, what do we got?
Outdoor activities. Active. Oh, a, what does this have to do with Thanksgiving? A styling station?
The green one. Oh, and put this outside. Okay. So now I can, will they just be in here? Okay.
Select holiday decorations. Decorate freezies. Decorate foundation. Decorate. Should I just
put up everything? Decorate fences. Ooh, okay. This is harvest fest. Let's go with, um, something
with the, something with the turkey on it. Oh, this is kind of, this is like whatever.
Do you not know where it is? All right, cool. Now let's do, um, foundation. I guess this.
How's it look? Get it. What are you doing? You don't have to use the bathroom. And wait, am I
seeing things here? He doesn't have to use the bathroom. Why is he saying he has to use the
bathroom? Foundation. Come on, do it. Dude, I don't have a foundation. I don't even know what
this means. Why are these like weird, made up words? I don't even know what that means.
Like decorate the outside, decorate the, the spandrels? The freezes? What is a freezes?
The spandrels. I feel like this is just made up words that I've never heard before.
Eaves? Roof? Siding? What is a spandrel? Just whatever. Just have the thing out the front.
Just like sniff this. All right. I apparently I don't have any spandrels. What day is it? All
right. I have some decorations. I need a holiday gnome. Find gnomes around your lot. There's no
gnomes in my lot. Where there was a gnome. Okay. Well, I don't see any gnomes. Grand meal. A most
delectable feast awaits stomachs. Growling in anticipation. Make sure someone else
volunteers to do the dishes. Cook a grand meal. All right. So I need to hire somebody.
Let's have a party. I got money, right? Let's throw an event tomorrow. All right. Here we go.
We are throwing a dinner party, right? Yep. Not, don't do it yet. Wait. Oh, wait. It's tomorrow.
Okay. What time is it right now? Just get my bars up. It's tomorrow. It's tomorrow. He's throwing.
I didn't do anything. I backed out. Oh, this is sad. Mourn furry buddy. Oh yeah. Yodel died.
Yodel died. Lived a good life though. Was very happy. Do you have mods? I do have mods. I have
some crazy mods on. I'm just using them sparingly. Why are you not farting? I don't know. There hasn't
been a, there hasn't been a pants shit in at least, at least like 10 to 15 minutes of in-game. Oh,
what's going on here? Losing control. Oh, it's all right. Put on the lullaby music. You'll be
all right. Take a nap. I don't, stop calling me to ask if you should hang out with somebody.
You're the do or you don't. Cloud gaze with Jimmy Phipps. Okay. Well, we need to invite Jimmy Phipps
to the Thanksgiving party tomorrow. All right. Take a nap. I go to bed, man. What are you doing?
Now he wants retro music. Does this count? Okay. Um, how about you want to listen to music? Yeah.
I'm listening to music. You'd be getting happier. Play a game. Play Sims forever. Just play a game.
I hate this guy so much. When he dies, please make someone who isn't explicitly dislikeable.
You guys are rooting for this guy to die. Why are you guys rooting for this guy to die?
No, we're, look, we're going to geek con next year and we're going to go to space. What's wrong
with this guy? This guy sucks. He's fine. Make someone worse. It's fine. All right. It's about
eight o'clock. Turn this off. All right. Let's get ready for tomorrow. Tomorrow's Thanksgiving.
We're going to have a big Thanksgiving party and I'm going to make sure there's a big
turkey. That's enough of the computer. Get up please. Here's the bathroom. We've got a
breakthrough. That's exactly where I would have had one too. All right. Now we need to just take
a quick shower. Quick shower. Then we need to eat and then I need to go to bed. So let's,
what do we got? Oh wait, no, I have food in my pocket. Why does this guy have so much food?
Why does he have so much food in this? Why does he have an old coffee from like a year ago?
I don't want to eat it. Is this cake fine? Why is the cake spoiled? Well, I'm asleep.
I made the cake two days ago. All right. We got to get rid of some of this stuff.
Oh my goodness. Give it a, what do I give? What do I give? What do I give? How about a future cube?
A pie. Probably a pie. Coffee? Pie? I think pie would be pretty good. Or a toy. Let me say pie.
Okay. Where did I get this from? What just happened? What? Get this fucking thing out of my
house. Get this thing out of my house. What? I just got struck by lighting. What just happened?
I'm not letting him out. I gave him an apple pie and he freaked out and turned off my speaker
and then struck me with lighting. What is going on with that? No, no, no, no. Oh no. This is bad.
Okay. Um, you can see. Jeffrey Landgraab is available. How? Why is Jeffrey Landgraab the
sing together with Jeffrey Landgraab? Where is he? I don't think he's coming.
All right. I got to clean that. Wait, appease the gnome. Um, I don't know. Toy. Give a toy.
Stop singing. Give a toy. Do you like? Okay. So you liked that. Okay. Cool. Everything is broken.
Oh shit. All right. I got to get ready for my party. Hurry up. Come on. Good. Good. Good. Good.
Trash. I need to just replace it. I don't care. Did you break it again? No. Uh, 700 bucks.
What am I making? Stop making BLTs. What the fuck? What is going on?
What's okay. Something weird is happening. Just eat your BLT and it's Thanksgiving. Hold on.
I got to hire a repair person. Okay. Good. What is this now? All right. Thank you. Please come in
here and help me. I, okay. Let's, I got to invite people over now, right? Bladder, go to the bathroom
and invite people over. We have to cook a grand meal. How much was that? A hundred bucks. All
right. That's not bad. All right. Clean up. Uh, eat that. And then I got good hygiene. I'm going
to take a shower and I'm going to invite everybody over for Thanksgiving. More gnomes. Yeah. They're
just everywhere. Polish this up. Quick shower. Let's go. Okay. Now I'm going to plan an event.
I don't have a table. I had another breakthrough. I need a table. Okay. I did the gnome thing.
Grand meal. Uh, okay. I need a table. Even if it's temporary. I'll sell it immediately after
the party is over. Table. I don't want to table lamps. Okay. Let's invite some people over.
Why are you going to bed? All right. It's 1 PM. We got to get this going. All right. Here we go.
Everybody come hang out. It's time for a Thanksgiving dinner party. Let's go. All right.
And we're going to do it at my, at the McNulty residence. I'm going to be the host. We're going
to invite of course, Jeffrey Landgraab. I wanted to do, I wanted to hang out with, uh, where is it?
Jimmy? Um, what else do I really want here? I hate me. Santa, Santa's dead. You might, I don't know if
you hear you. I don't know. All right. Caterer. No, the whole point is we're going to make the
turkey. No, there's no caterer. No caterer. We're making the turkey. That's the whole point. We're
going to make the food. What is this? Did I invite this person? Why are there random like
packets on the ground? Come on in. Just throw your coffee on the ground at the beach.
Come on. What the fuck is that? All right. Welcome everybody. We're going to cook a grand meal.
Cook a grand meal. We're going to cook a turkey dinner. You guys ready? Come on. Let's go. We
have to celebrate. Are we going to leave some presents for these gnomes or what? The very weird
turkey. This is a really boring party. We need some music or something. It's going to be like,
hold on. Is there something fun we can do in here? Like activities or something fun or I don't know.
How about a mega cooler? Bird feeder? Do a bonfire. Skeez. No, I don't think so. A bird feeder
party. I mean, we could just put like a bird feeder in here and just watch. Just open the
wall of the doors and windows. Will this work? Can a bunch of birds get in the house? Does
somebody want to help me cook? This is not Thanksgiving. There's like a bunch of people
cooking. Everyone's like, is somebody bringing something? This is a dinner party. Why did they
not bring anything? Oh, like Jeffrey's going to bring the casserole. You're going to bring
the green beans. You're going to bring the mashed potatoes. It's a dinner party. Where's all the
food? She farted and I left. Can we finish this? Nobody brought anything to the dinner party.
I mean, even a box of Pop Tarts or something. No one brought anything.
And I'm just sad over here cooking the whole turkey dinner. Oh my God. I need to finish it.
Stop. We need to finish that. You have to be a good host.
Everyone's just crowding over. Everyone's just watching this guy play League.
They're just all hovering. Stop dancing and finish it.
Can you finish the slop, please? Give yourself a pep talk.
Can somebody help me do this? Oh no, this person's coming in to give them some pep talk.
I wonder what's going to happen. Finish it. Finish the turkey dinner. Stop getting distracted. It's
just, I don't think he knows what he's doing. Can you move to UFC world or something? We don't
need you in the Sims world. What? You moved to UFC world? All right. Turkeys in the oven. Everybody
shut up. Oh, he's pissed because there's no food. Oh, we know he's helping. He's reading
the instructions. Oh, okay. I get it. Looks good. Almost ready. Do we have any crab? No,
we don't have any crab. We have a, we have like a 17 pound turkey in here. There's no crab.
No, there's no seafood. Why do you think there's seafood here? Everyone is stuck. Get out of the
kitchen. Stop crowding me. There's no seafood. It's only turkey. Oh my, I'm going to punch
somebody in the face in a second. Get away from me. Get away from me. That's why I can finish.
They're reading the ingredients. Stop. They're all back seating me. All right. I get, is it ready?
Dude, the shit's in there right now. Serve it. Italian meatballs. Open the oven. What? Dude,
people need to get away from me. Why am I making another dinner? Why am I making a second dinner?
Am I making a side dish? Where's resume? Resume turkey dinner. Why are you cooking up
watermelons? I don't understand what's happening right now. Why do I have watermelons on a plate
here? What am I making? Why did he stop making the turkey? Okay. What are you going to do with that?
Right. Okay. And it's a fruit and yogurt parfait. Happy Thanksgiving. Are they all complaining?
Okay. Good. Season it.
You would have started cooking this turkey like six hours ago. You wouldn't have started
when people showed up. Oh, everybody enjoying the fruit and yogurt parfait. Eat up. Thanksgiving is
here. Everybody come get a slice. Here it is. Happy Thanksgiving, everybody. Oh, hey, wait,
hey, make sure you leave a little bit of real estate. All right. There's still a little bit
of real estate on that plate, right? Oh, come on. Yeah. You're going to pile that. You still got
a little bit of real estate on there. Dude, do you want to go stargazing? You're all so annoying.
Oh, thankful spirit. Discuss what you can be thankful for.
Let's complain about the local youth instead. Here's what I'm thankful for. These kids don't
even know how to throw footballs anymore. Oh, big bullshit. I could throw a perfect
spiral when I was younger. Excuse me. What happened? Why am I a rejected gangster? I don't
understand. Oh, my God, what a mess. Thank you for staying this whole time. Wait, be thankful.
What are you thankful for? Hector.
What?
They're our only friend. I'm not doing it. What? What the hell? You're a disgrace? What did I do?
Dude, this is a vampire. 100%. 100%. This is a vampire. There's no way that's not a vampire.
There's no way that's not a vampire. Give me a break. All right. Invite in. Come on in.
Come on in. I got me and my buddy Hector here. If you're getting thirsty. What? I'm going to
invite this person in and I'm going to leave. Oh, what? Who are you? Yes, of course. It's
Thanksgiving. Come on in. Why did I punch this guy? Oh, this has to be a vampire. Lock the bathroom
door.
This is a vampire. Did you just show up late to the party?
I didn't speed that up. I'm staying locked in. Oh, my God. I'm not going anywhere. I'm
staying locked in. I'm ready. I'm ready. I'm ready though. I'm ready.
What did he just do? He just like, what did he just do to him? He just like did like a move at him.
What did he do? He just like held the change up to him and changed his channel. Wait,
do you live there? Wait, OK, I can leave now. OK, stop doing this. What a mess. Put it away.
I'm going to eat turkey dinner for like the next six months. Turn this off. What an absolute mess.
I'm going to put this outside. We put it right here so we can see the birds. OK, what a mess.
There's some bird seed in there. How come you're still here? That's what I'm going to take. I have
a gnome in my inventory. OK, I'm never taking him out. OK, birds are coming in. How do I get
them to leave? OK, this is such a mess. Wait, this is still all right. Put that away. I get to clean
up. Harvest Fest was awesome. Blorek had a wonderful time and got to do everything he planned to do.
Nice. All right, we did it. Pease the gnome. No, I'm not doing anything. When I wake up,
I'll clean up. I'm not doing anything. What am I saying? I'm going to sell the gnome.
Holy shit. OK, that's 300 bucks. What other shit can I sell? Journey to the Stars. Unlocked at level
two and a cheese pizza. Where is this? Let me sell the other gnome that's in my actual inventory here.
I could sell all kinds of stuff now. This thing's rare. I love presents. I don't need that anymore.
Message in a bottle. Oh, gems? No, those are my Kyber crystals. Why do I have a bunch of people's
earns? OK, I got some money. When's the community brawl? Tomorrow. OK, tonight is the talent
showcase. I'm not going to work. Wait, I have to go to work, don't I? Just go to work. Whatever.
Oh, boy. Jesus. OK, this house is disgusting. Just retire on your phone. But I want to be a
rocket scientist. I'm not ready. I'm not done yet. Spice festivals in town. Spicy challenge.
All right, so this is going on. There's also a talent show tonight, too. The festival of
light has started. There's all kinds of stuff going on tonight. I have to jump around. Jesus.
I hear the festival t-shirts are out of this world. Let's go to the festival and buy one.
I'm not ready. I got to get a cold shower going here. I need to clean up. I'm not ready. It's 7
p.m. I got to do something, though. Whatever. I'll clean this up later. I got to go. There's
a bunch of social events going on right now. I have to do it. I'm going to do the talent show.
I got to hurry up. Talent show is going on right now. We're going to go talent show.
I'm going to go do the spicy festival. Let's go. No one. No, I'm going alone.
I want to do the talent show. Am I going? All right. Talent show. What do I have for skills?
There's so much going on in this game. It's crazy. Crazy frogs Twitter. What's happening on crazy
frog Twitter? I mean, look at it. Why? OK, I have not saved the game since we started. All right.
So talent show time. Sign up at the bar to participate with the thunderstorm. All right.
Sign up at the bar. It's time for the talent showcase. Join open mic. Couldn't we have done
this out indoors? Why are we outside doing this? I would not be in the pool right now.
I've been signed up for the talent showcase. Use the mic or instrument once it's time
to get on stage. OK, what's going on right now? Why is there everybody scared of the toilet?
All right. When did we start the talent show? This person should not be in the pool right now.
Should I go first? Oh, wait. OK. All right. Let's watch. I can't even hear what they're saying.
OK, now it's my turn to perform. OK. Should I hire a comedian? Practice acting. It's my turn.
Get off the stage. It's my turn. Get off the stage. Get off the stage. It's my turn, they said.
Get out of the way. It's my turn. They just called my name. Here we go. I got nervous.
This is quite the awful talent show. No one's doing anything. Oh, my God.
Stop looking at the toilet and get over here. Your name has been called. Practice acting already.
Do a talent. Play the guitar. Pick up the guitar and care. Oh, do it. No, you're not on stage yet.
You need to be up there before you do overdrive. Having a bad time. Literally nobody did anything.
Who am I calling? Someone's going to die. That's a vampire. Wait, that's the vampire that came to the
house. Take a pretzel. Yeah, nice. What time is it? I missed the spicy festival for this
bullshit. Everybody was too scared to use it. OK, here we go. Here's somebody. Talent show's over,
man. Let's just talk. This person's going to get struck by lightning and they're going to get
struck by lightning. They're standing really still. They're going to get struck by lightning.
It's going to hit this person. It's going to hit this lady right now. Someone's getting
struck by lightning. I'm telling you. Do karaoke. This guy sucks. I can't. I don't like the fact
that there's a thunderstorm so I won't do it. Wait, what is wrong? Having a really bad time.
Am I actually going to order? Why am I having such a bad time? What's fun?
Fortnite? Why am I having such a bad time? Is there anything I can do here that's going to make me
have fun? Anything. Anything at all. I mean, I'm listening to talk radio apparently. I
thought there was blood all over her hands. Having any fun. Do anything. Is there like a TV
I can turn on? This guy needs to shut up. This is not fun. Shut up. Shut up. Seriously, shut up.
I'm just going to steal money out of his pocket.
Oh my god. That guy had a lot of money.
He won't stop. He won't stop. What the fuck?
Okay. All right. All right. Watch karaoke. That's fun.
Wow. Why? Why am I a heckler? I'm heckling. I shouldn't be heckling. Why am I heckling?
Why am I having such a bad time? This is unbearable. Why am I, why am I heckling somebody
at karaoke? Can I scare this person? Shut up. How do I stop you from doing this? Stop talking. Stop it.
Okay. Good. It's only so long you can take somebody going
It's like, holy goodness, man. Holy shit. I actually like this guy.
Where is he? Why can I not pick him? He's not leaving, right? Let's do a duet with the Banthar.
Nooboo, Kalka, Flair, Boo, Oopsa, Blard, Isni, Bavoy,
Brunchy, Oopsa, Blard, Simba, Boo, Sue, Isni, Bavoy,
Burby, Laploo, Crick, Simsteeba, Kimagoo,
Laploo, Rimboo, Yix, Brunchy, Crick, Boo, Zerva, Fleece, Dela, Blink, and Nea, Boo, Spish.
This is going to be so uncalled for.
All right, I won't.
I'm just going to turn and like punch him in the stomach. It's still kids music playing. All right,
that was fun. It's time to prepare for the neighborhood brawl. It's time to prepare.
This is going to be nuts. You guys think that this is something I'm making up?
It's today. It's between six a.m. and two a.m. Neighborhood brawl. I don't know what that means,
but I know it's today. It's all fucking day. It's yeah, it's from six to two. I got to be prepared.
I need to sleep. Neighborhood brawl begins in neighborhood brawl begins in 30 seconds.
Hmm. Neighborhood brawl begins in 10 seconds. Here we go.
Fight. Today is all about starting fights with other Sims. Pretty quiet out here. A whole lot
going on. Hmm. Who's going to make the first move? Interesting. Anybody shows up at my house,
they get punched in the face. I know what today is. We're just going to show up at the door though.
Oh, it's a big guy. I brought a casserole. Oh, you did? You brought a casserole to the house?
Yeah, right. Definitely like a knife in your back pocket. I know what today is. Get ready.
That's so expensive or whatever. All right. Eat something. Have some leftover turkey. Okay.
Look, I'm in top shape right now. Let's brush our teeth and let's get to it. I need a much
better outfit for this. Change outfit. I think that looks pretty good. Okay. I think it's perfect.
I'm going to call a cleaning service here. All right. What are you doing over here?
All right. I need just a one-time maid. Okay. Here we go. Where am I going? Should I just wait
until somebody comes to the house? Where should I go? I'm going to go. Where do I go? All right.
It's neighborhood brawl time. The bar? Spa? Should I just walk around the neighborhood?
Just be like, yeah, I'm ready. Just like scream in the street. Click the event. What do you mean?
I think it's just, yeah, I think I just have to do it because like there's nothing to click on.
Unless I go in here, you mean? Yeah. It's just, it's not, it's just, just fight somebody. That's
going to find somebody to fight. All right. So I'm just going to go to like the, I'll go to like the
bar or something. I don't know. I'll go to like the, we're, I don't know. I have to like, I have
to fight. It says fight anybody. It says I can't participate because I'm too old. What if I just
invite a bunch of people over? Hey, I'm having a, I'm having a TV watch party for Game of Thrones.
Everybody come over. Costume party. All right. I'm throwing a costume party. That sounds good.
I'm the host and we're inviting everybody. Right. Should there be a caterer? No, there's no caterer.
No, we don't have a mixologist, but we could go back to the ruins, right? Island Bluff. We could
go back to the ruins and we could, but people could bowl and stuff. Hire a bunch of services.
I think I just wanted it at the house. Okay. Island Bluff. Okay. This is like an open area.
So I should hire some services. Okay. Island Bluff. Just an open area for us. Cause we all know
it's a bit, it's a fight. There you go. It's an event built in. Here we go. Am I in a costume?
Why am I, I'm in a pizza delivery costume. This person's a, wait is that, no, why?
Does this person even have a costume? Holy shit. We're going to go over here. Everybody follow me.
What? Okay. I thought I was going to go. How come nobody's fighting? Why does my piece stink
so bad? Uh oh. Why is nobody fighting? It's a neighborhood brawl. Complain about the
neighborhood brawl. All right. What do you got? Let's go. The first punch has been thrown. Good
luck to everybody. I won. Wait, what? Oh wait. Why are we happy about this? I missed. Why is
everybody, ever it's a surprise. It's a neighborhood brawl. Why am I the only person fighting? Wait,
did I just not get it? Oh, it's a neighborhood brawl. I just don't get it. It's a fun costume
party. I just didn't get it. Wait a minute. Why did I just puke? Why did I just puke?
Why did I just puke? I don't know. Everybody hates me. Somebody's stopping me. Why is
nobody stopping me? Stop me. You're a disgrace. Oh, here we go. Here we go. Here we go. Here we go.
I win. He punched this guy in the stomach. Does anyone know why I puked?
Don't come near me, violent scum.
Can you move? Why is nobody else fighting?
What was that? What the fuck? What happened? Somebody just throw something at me?
Wait, why are they all freaking out about her? Everyone turned to her now.
Something wrong? What happened?
Let's share the neighborhood brawl spirit. You ain't shit. Okay. All right. Hey, be careful.
We're gonna eat that grilled cheese that fast. Oh, wait, what? What's happening? What? No,
I thought they were gonna eat a grilled cheese and choke on it. I didn't click on. What? No,
I thought I was trying to click the hot dog. I thought he was gonna eat a grilled cheese and
choke. I did. Didn't I click this other person? What the fuck?
Do you see? Can you stop? Catch me outside.
Dude, it's neighborhood brawl and nobody's fighting.
No one else's neighborhood brawled. Catch me outside. It's time for you to suffer. What?
I'm sorry, but when you give me this option here that's neighborhood brawl,
how come nobody's... I go into the gym. I had to turn off the Fortnite shit. Is that death?
Oh, what else can I even do? I don't want to like hit me. I don't want to hurt anybody. I did.
Apparently, I still... I was never supposed to do this in the first place because it's too old.
I'm too old. Whoa. Whoa. What? I'm arrested? How long am I in jail for? Winter. Nobody's clicked
this. Broke out of jail. That's not what I wanted to do. My God, dude. How does that happen? I don't
know. Just go home. Just go home at this point. What the hell am I going to do now? Okay. Prison
break. That's what? So what now? What? By the way, the maid didn't even come and I paid for it.
Oh, nevermind. You ain't shit. Birds. It's a cardinal. Cool. Okay. So what's coming up next?
Oh, Winterfest is back. Starlight accolades. What does that mean? I don't know what that is.
All right. I actually really do need to clean. Ridiculous. Take these decorations down. It's
over. We're in winter. So how's my career doing? I did four breakthroughs. Okay. As of tomorrow,
I think I'll be all right. Yeah. Yodel died. Yeah. A couple hours ago. Do life goals, not dreams.
Okay. I need a logic. Finished reading three books. Just read a logic book. I think I have
to buy a book, right? I need logic. Logic two, right? Logic volume two. Let's go ahead and read
that. I'll read logic volume two. Pretty sick. Need to read a couple books. Is that working?
Oh, I don't care. Why won't I finish the book? I need volume three. What? Are you serious? 250
bucks. Are you kidding me? Why not? Why? Because I punched the, punched that guy in the stomach.
Why can't I read this? And I had, there's somebody coming. Can I cancel the maid service?
Because I'm just cleaning up the house. I need volume one. What is this? The festival of youth.
Ice cream crepes. Blessings and a void critter hunt. This is cool. It's Pokemon Go. You're too
old. I think I am too old. I'm too old. I am not going to that. I'm not going to that. I'm sorry.
I just, I don't think, I don't think I can go there. All right. I'm getting rid of this. This
is just bringing the mood down. Well, good thing I did that and I just paid a service to come and
clean the house and they're not going to do anything tomorrow. I have to go to work tomorrow
anyways. We have to do aspirations. I'm not fucking around. I need to finish reading three books. Does
it matter what the book is? How about Crisis Barn? Does the book matter? Yeah, you get it.
You get it. I need two more books. Have a child. I'm, guys, I'm like 80. I'm like 85. I have a
child. What? It's for a different sim. All right. I finished that book. What time is work tomorrow?
All right. So I got time. I'll get promoted. Adopt, adopt, adopt, adopt. What? No, I'm not going to
adopt a kid and die. Buy a youth potion. What else am I doing? All right. I need some food.
I got to get promoted. Check your rewards. I need to own a business too. How do I buy a business?
Flirty potion. Happy potion. Um, where is it? Speed cleaner. Storm. Wait, potion of youth.
Drink this to turn back the clock on your sim's current age. Should I drink one of these?
Oh, I feel like that's going against the natural order here. Do it. No, let him die. Isn't this,
this is going against the natural order, I think. Do a poll. All right, let's do a poll.
Do you want me to keep Blorg McNulty around or do you want Blorg, well, let's get this cleared up
here. Do you want Blorg McNulty to drink the potion of youth? Get a poll up. Yes or no. What
are you thinking? How do you feel? What do you think? No. I'm seeing a lot of no's. There is a
lot of no's coming out right now. There's a lot of yeses too though. That's a lot. You guys want this
guy to fuck off so bad? That's the 75% almost. Dad, we're not doing that. Thanks for voting
those of you that voted. Um, no, we're not. Should I buy something else though?
Instant fun. Eh. Eh. All right, I need to read another book. Where am I? I'm gonna need logic
to go up. Get a cat. We'll see. Let me get my work stuff done. This will be the third book
and then I can do logic. Where's the dog? Sorry. Get a hamster. There it is.
All right, now I need one more logic skill and I have an aspiration here. What's up?
I'm gonna give you a funny gift.
What is it? Oh, it's just a joke. By the way, if you imagine going over to somebody's house
and they come to greet you with a plate of Thanksgiving dinner and it's January or it's
like late December. I don't know if that stuff's still good. We're getting into, it's been like
two or three weeks. I don't know if you still should be eating Thanksgiving dinner every day.
Can I get you some?
No, I could do fucking garlic noodles.
All right, I need to get out of here. What book do I get for logic? I'm just gonna get the
chess table, right? Oh, there's honey in here. How much did I get for this? Are they even still
here? Jesus, a hundred bucks. What was that? What was that for?
I'm gonna bond with the bees. This is like so scary. This is a weird guy.
Oh, I'm like computers.
Okay, that can't make the bees do anything.
I need to go to bed. Thanks for going. Why does everybody use my computer? They come over and use
the computer and they sit here all night. I thought she got in the bed. Okay, so what's
coming up here? I want to make sure that I have 10 hours. I can't get logic in 10 hours. I might
get promoted though because I'm doing all right. I need to be focused. How do I get focused?
Programming or something, right? Like write research. Okay, that should do pretty good.
I'm focused? No. Ghost? What? What do you mean ghost? Where? No, no, no, no. Oh, shit. I missed her.
It's okay. Check inventory for logic. I have volume two. What's the difference between volume
one, volume two, and volume three? Should I read this? I think I already did this though, didn't I?
Oh, wait. No, it's working. I'm just gonna make sure I get the point and then I'm not gonna get
it in time. That's fine. Eat some of the turkey dinner. Who are you talking to eat? All right,
I'm in a pretty good mood. I think I'll be all right. All right, go to work. Now get out of the
chat room. Go to work. Out of the chat room. No more chatting. All right, go. Oh, wait, this is
the cleaning service. Okay. What day is it? How much was this? That was 55 dollars. Wait, I just
picked just two plates and it was 55 bucks. Shit, it's all right. I'll be back from work in a minute.
How long am I at work for? It's too long. What's up? Bills have been delivered. Okay, I should be
able to buy it. I couldn't reach your mailbox but I managed to throw the mail in there. Good luck
getting it out. What? Somebody in the bin? What do you mean? Somebody in the bin. What do you mean?
Somebody's in the bin. Oh, you're talking about. No, that's the bees are sleeping right now.
That is kind of funny. It does look like somebody's just in the box. All right, keep going.
I want to visit werewolf world. No, I want to go to werewolf world. Let's go light fireworks.
But I'm too tired. What was in the mailbox? Was it like a screwdriver? What was that?
All right. Okay. All right. All right. Fine. Fine. Fine. Let's go. All right. Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go. We just light some fireworks and it's the humor festival. That's fine. I will see. I'll
see where I can't. It's a hard word to say. Where were you? Okay. I thought this was a
humor festival. Why are we at like an art gallery? Where are we going? Where am I going? What? What
was that? What did I just take? I don't have anything. I don't get it. I didn't take anything.
That's weird. All right. So we're here. Uh, let's why don't we we're supposed to be doing
like humor and hijinks. Why don't we come over here? Okay. All right. I'm going to join the
pranksters. Worst party ever. Well, you went into the art gallery. You didn't even go to the party.
Now I got to light fireworks. We can spray graffiti. Did you even join? Join the pranksters.
All right. We're going to do some graffiti. This is going to take the entire evening.
What does it say? We're like, we're like choking. You're going to help. I feel like 10 people
should be doing this. I need to finish this. I can't, I can't just do it halfway. Right. We've
got to go watch fireworks. Cool. I got to finish this whole thing. This guy's fucking crazy.
Okay. So it's not done. It's one o'clock in the morning, dude. The only people that are still
employees. It's not even close. Do I get anything for this? Painting level three. Wow. Almost done.
Under like 34 hours and should be done. I think it's good. This person walking around with a knife.
Finish the painting. Look who it is. Almost done. It's almost done. It's not time for bed.
Mural art style graffiti. What do you think? What do you think? What do you think? What's so funny?
You like it? Okay. I just made it darker. Order food. I was defacing my own graffiti.
Is anybody going to help me? Oh, the clap woke me up. Okay. Cool. Well, I was that really,
I guess, I guess it's cool. Yeah. It's, it's there. I did that. All right. I made it. What do we got?
I'll take some, um, what do we, what am I ordering? What? Whoa. You ain't shit.
I bought that. Give me those two sausages. I, I bought that. Wait, where am I?
Did I steal it? No. Okay. I took it from behind the counter.
You hate shit. What'd you get?
What's your food? You don't want it?
Whoa. What's wrong? What?
No, I'm not going to, no, I'm not. I already have a really terrible reputation. I'm not doing that.
Our reputation is so, why did they close the stores for five minutes?
All right. What's this spicy food? All right. Get up, get up, get up, get up, get up. I gotta go home.
Get up. Get up. Wake up. New Year's Eve is tomorrow. I gotta be ready.
I'm going to werewolf world for New Year's Eve. By the way, I'm just like quitting my job.
What? I'm retiring. Where is it? Business, right? I'm retired. There it is. Where the hell am I?
No one plays the holiday events. You know that, right? I want to experience it.
You have no money? I'll be all right. Why don't you come with me?
All right. Bathroom. Yeah, I'm going to retire. It's time. Come on. Get some sleep. Get up.
And then I'm celebrating New Year's Eve. Shit. All right. One more day of work.
Winterfest is tomorrow. I'm going to a werewolf party. I'm going to a werewolf party tomorrow.
I'm just going to go find one and we're going to. Well, how am I going to get invited to anything?
Why can I? I need to get invited to a party. I might not get invited to anything.
They're enraged. I need the money. They were cool. I'm going to, I'm going to sell them to a
beekeeper. I just sold them to a beekeeper to take care of them. All right. I got a thousand bucks.
I'm going to sleep and then it's time for New Year's Eve. Get up early. Pay your bills. I will.
I got it. Wait till he wakes up. Then we're going to go to werewolf town for New Year's
Eve and it's going to be awesome. Pay bills. Take a shower. Eat. You can take a bath. Whatever.
Better mood. Watch TV. We need to clean the fridge out. Clean out the spoiled food and then I'm going
to make a delicious breakfast. Winterfest. Oh, it is Winterfest. Yeah, I'm going to a werewolf
Christmas party. Why? Unfulfilled dreams. What are you doing? Oh, a nice yogurt. Okay.
Eat the yogurt. What's wrong? That's so just trash. Oh, it's because clean. I gotta clean the fridge
out. Wait, what if I bring a turkey somewhere? All right. I'm going to bring a giant ham dinner,
a grand breakfast. How about a grand breakfast? I'm going to bring it with me in my inventory to
werewolf land. Ham dinner, fish dinner, turkey, grand breakfast. With what money? I have 70 bucks.
Vegetarian safe. What? Oh, it's a tofu turkey. All right. We're doing that. I'm bringing a,
I'm bringing tofu to a werewolf party. How do you make this? Let's see. Yes. Fun. I'm glad
you're having a good time. Just finish it. Stop with this dancing. Yummies. I love tofu. Oh my
God. It's always when he's cooking. Let me guess. Wow. No. All right. Here's the tofu turkey. Um,
it's dead. Very cool. Here it comes. Yup. Yup. Uh huh. Good. Take it out. Grand meal. I have it.
I've got it. Oh, is it burnt? No, no, no, no, no, no, no. Don't go near it. Don't go near it.
Call the fire department. This shit is burnt. Fire, please. Oh my God. It smells in here.
It stinks in here. You didn't even finish. You didn't finish. The house is still on fire.
Oh my goodness. You're not finishing the job. What are you complaining about? What are you doing?
Thank you. All right. Let's take this burnt ass turkey and let's go. I just need to pee and then
we're out of here. I don't have to pee anymore. That's fine. Okay. So I need to take a shower
quick. All right. Turkey. Sabotage food. Okay. I want to put this away, right? I'm going to put
it in inventory. Okay. I got my, I got my tofu burnt turkey. I'm ready. I just need it. Okay.
All right. Let's go to werewolf land and, uh, let's go have a holiday party. So let's travel
to somebody's party. Okay. I'm just going to go by myself. So where is werewolf land? This one
here. Moonwood mill. Okay. Library. Bar. Okay. Residence. Where should I go? I just go see if
somebody, like anybody, does anybody live here? I'm just going to go to the werewolf bar. It is
holiday season here. There's nobody here. This place sucks. We're going to light this on fire.
Where's the party?
What the fuck is this? We're going to go on a mountain climb excursion. Weenie roast. Oh,
that's not a bad idea. Let's do a weenie roast. I'll be hosting it. Um, everybody's invited.
Jeffrey Landgraab looks different. This person is still in their costume from the neighborhood
brawl event. The grill master. Um, that'd be, uh, that'd be you. The grill master. And we're
doing it right here. Wait, we should go to the, let's go to the Landgraab residence,
right? Why not? Look at this place. This place is huge. Can I even do it here? I don't think I can
even do it here. Let's go to the Landgrabs. They probably have Christmas stuff up too.
There's no campfire. I'm just walking in the front door. We need a campfire. How do I get a campfire?
It's not a very good weenie roast without a campfire. Check for gifts in the mailbox.
All right. Let's see if you have anything in the mailbox that I can take.
Anything delivered? Excuse me? Whoa! What's happening? Somebody's stabbing me. What?
What happened? What? Cheering. Am I dead? Right when I got a gold bar, I wouldn't even get to have
my fucking turkey. I'm going down. Everybody is. Wake up. Get up. Wait, where's my, where's that
poisoned cake? I want you to bury me with my lightsaber. We'll be in the coffin with it.
I want to be buried with my first order of uniform. What do I do? We need to make a new sim?
I, dude, did you see what it said up there? It said I took like a 24-garret gold bar out of this
guy's mailbox. I don't understand why I got stabbed. There's no, there's no autonomous killing.
It's off. I don't know why that happened. We're making a werewolf. Well, there goes McNulty.
Everyone say goodbye to Lord McNulty. Now we're making a werewolf.
Nature. Outdoor enthusiast. Yep. Animal. Oh, no, nevermind. Oh, wait. Okay. Yeah. I want
werewolf. The sim wants to unleash his inner beast and become a werewolf. He seems to get
an initial relationship boost when introducing themselves to werewolves. Okay. Baking. How's that
sound? That sounds kind of cool. Fitness. I don't want to make this guy, I don't want to make this
guy a fucking just complete and total loser, right? Like we have to make this, they got to be cool.
Move your camera. Baking. Piano. Rock climbing. Rocket science. The violin. That's interesting.
Not a werewolf. I'm making a werewolf. How about just, um, how about, I don't know, baking?
How about photography? Now we're doing rock climbing. Oh, I have to, right, right, right,
right. Okay. Okay. Baking. Fitness. Fishing. Rock climbing and the violin. What do you don't like?
You don't like, um, you don't, I mean, you like DJ music. That's fine.
No lullabies. No kids music. Uh, also you don't like, uh, gardening. You also don't like, um,
photography. Snob. Loves the outdoors, right? I mean, I'm a werewolf. Bro. Bro? Bro. Okay. Here
we go. How do I make, how do I pick werewolf form? I didn't make him a werewolf? How do I do it?
Make a normal guy. I don't want to make a normal guy. How do I make him a werewolf?
Add to sim. Oh, we're, we're, is it a cult? Werewolf. Oh, okay. Here we go. I mean,
I can't, can he, he's got to live with this guy. Okay. All right. All right. All right. We have,
we need, this is going to take a while. Okay. This kind of looks like a guy,
this is a guy covered in whipped cream. This doesn't look like a werewolf.
What is this a werewolf? It looks like somebody has a cool whip all over him.
All right. We're going to keep the cool whip man. Noses. Oh wait. Teeth. Okay. Hold on. Teeth.
Okay. I want these. I want these for sure. Or these ones. I don't know. Yeah. This is just weird
looking. All right. I like this. What about ears? You know, when you're in the bubble bath and you
just do a bubble bath, this is a bubble bath werewolf. Okay. Faces. No, it's perfect the way
it is. I don't want to change anything. This one is, it's good though, but no, I can't stop doing
that. Goodness. Okay. What else can we do? Wait, I don't want to add this many things. Oh wait. No,
I don't, we, I don't want, no, no, no, no, no. Those are cool accessories, but I want to be
accessory-less. You made Brian Griffin? Okay. But dude, so this is what your human form is.
If I change anything, will the werewolf form change if I change anything?
So I can't change this. Okay. Oh shit. All right. Um, unlink them. Oh, there we go. Okay.
So this is where it is now. And now we can, these eyes need to change. Oh God. I think,
I think it has to stay. I don't, I don't, I don't think it changes. Maybe let's see what
the different hair is. It's the, it's the hello neighbor guy. That's good. That's pretty good.
But the hello neighbor guy would have hair like this. I need, I actually like that. I like that
a lot. I don't know how much longer I can listen to this. I mean, I need, I need to have, I like,
okay, this is perfect. Keep it red. Okay. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done.
All right. We need to do aspirates. Just please stop doing that aspirations. You're a werewolf.
That's what you want to do. You want to be that your favorite activity is you like baking. You
don't really like bowling. You like DJs. You like fitness. You like fishing. You like the violin.
You like rock climbing. You like the violin. You don't like snowboarding. You like, you don't like
rocket science. You like the organ and you don't like programming. Sounds good. Okay. Now we're
going to do, what did we do before? Adventurous. We're also going to do of the outdoors. We're also
going to do snob loner. No, anytime you do loner, it's awful because you can never hang out with
anybody, bro. All right, bro. Okay. I think we're ready. Let's, let's, let's maybe add a cat.
There's a lot of cats. Cap you. All right. All right. Ears more like a frog than it is a cat.
Looks like a dog. Fluffy, friendly and a free spirit. All right. I think we're ready.
Do I, should I just delete this guy? Delete this one? My name is, I don't know, Fred. Um, Anthony,
Anthony, I don't know, Anthony, Anthony, Anthony butane. He's, I don't worry. Anthony, Billy,
Anthony gasoline. No. All right. How about just like butane? Let's fuck this guy. All right. And
your Jerry, Jerry snarl. I hate it. Jerry. Um, Jerry. I hate it. Any, not Jerry. Oh, just big
teeth. How about Thomas teeth? Tom, Tom teeth, Tom teeth. That's fine. I don't care. I don't do
names. I've never got it. Tom teeth, Tom teeth and Anthony butane. Make it Tim teeth. Timothy teeth.
Timothy teeth is fine. I don't care. Jerry teeth. All right. It's Jerry teeth and that's all as it
cat snowball snowball teeth. We're ready. How much money do we have? Like that's what I look like in
pictures. I, I do that shit. Is there a picture? Can I have, can I have the cat? How come I never
get the cat? Whatever. All right. Why is, why is this guy in, why did I not delete this guy?
Is anybody going to care if I eat this guy in like the first five minutes? Are you going to be mad?
Uh, wait, where the butane household is moving? Wait, what do we move with the butanes? Wait a
minute. Um, uh, what's going on on? Oh, there. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. We want to be here because
this is werewolf town, right? Okay. How do I turn into a werewolf? It's winterfest. Oh, that's right.
Time didn't stop. This is a good spot, right? Like right here. Yeah. Time didn't stop. Save the game.
Bro lesson. Jerry is a bro. Bros love watching sports, being around other bros and know how
to handle their juice. Oh, what's up? Hey, what's up, bro?
We need a house. I'm just going to have a house. I'm going to make like a pre-built house, right?
Yeah. I just want a pre-built house. How do I, how do I get a pre-built house?
Can I, I can drag a whole room. Can't I do this quick? Look at this. Not a bad house. All right.
Doors. I need a door for here. Not doing a public bathroom. Does this make sense? Because
this could be like the kitchen or something. Yeah. I need stuff for the animal. All right. First
things first. Let's do the light. I got to get that paint, paint, paint, paint, paint. We're
going to get this right. All right. This is outside. Just how about this? I don't know. Like
that's too dark. Is that even showing up? All right. That looks good. That's not that light.
All right. That's, this is the kitchen. This is going to be living room here. We'll just go with
like, I don't know, like a gray and it's the bathroom. No wallpaper in the bathroom.
I may, I'm going quick. Okay. This is the, so this is the kitchen, living room, bathroom.
This is a bedroom. We need two bedrooms, two bedrooms because we're a roommate here. All right.
Roommates, bedrooms. I need another bedroom. No, I'm going to eat them. I'm going to eat the guy.
I'm going to eat the guy in 10 minutes. Go to the, click the light bulb.
What? Use the gallery. Oh, well it's too late. I'm too late. I'm doing this already.
I'm already building. Delete the house. I'm already building. I'm building. It's too late.
Well, now I'm into it now. Now I want to do it. All right. So this is, uh, I want a second bedroom.
No, who cares? Just, I just have two beds or who cares? I have one bed. What? Who cares?
Who gives a shit? This guy's getting eaten within 24 hours. I'm just telling you what's happening.
It's just, I don't like him. I don't like that. Don't put wallpaper. This is a kid's bedroom.
Put him, like, put him next to each other like this. Somebody said, dude, this is a Burton Ernie
room. I, it's kind, yeah, whatever. Fine. It's Burton Ernie room. That doesn't, I don't care.
There's a bookcase in the middle of the Burton Ernie room, isn't there? All right. That's fine.
Put a lamp in here. They just need to sleep in here and who cares? All right. I just need,
I'm putting wallpaper up. I'm not going to listen to you weirdos that are saying,
don't put wallpaper in here. Why? Hey, what about, that's not bad. That's not bad. That's not bad.
Be a little lighter. Look at this. Okay. Now we need some windows. Look at that. We need some
doors. So this is the bedroom. This is a, um, it doesn't matter. Whatever. Who cares? Okay.
I'm not screwing this up this time. So now I need some wallpaper in here and I need some,
I need the floors. All right. Floor time. We're going to go with something nice. Maybe a little
bit of carpet. That's cool. Um, sure. And then kitchen. It's that easy. Uh, what about the
outside? Yeah, it doesn't look good. All right. I need paint for the outside siding. Where is it?
No, no. It looks like a, like a warehouse. It's a, it's all right. Okay. Now I need a roof. How do
you do roofs by the way? I don't understand how this works. And like, I just honestly kind of
don't care because nobody sees it. Nobody sees it. It doesn't matter. You're the only time you're
ever going to see this is when we're in this menu right now. So no, it doesn't matter. There we go.
Look at that. It's fine. Oh, we need to have like a little back, uh, area here. Okay. Let's have a,
go to the outside to get to the backyard. All right. Now we need furniture. Bathroom. We can
have a piss bush in the bathroom. All right. There's a, you can have, I can have a piss bush.
Should we go to the bathroom? I mean, I'm a, I'm a werewolf. I am a werewolf. Ooh, I like that.
I need the walls up. Uh, there's the sink. Now I need a shower. I have to extend this a little
bit better. A little bit this way. That's better. Hurry up. This is half a game, man. I need a mirror.
That's in a weird spot. I don't like that. Uh, I need a shower. Just a regular shower. Something
nice. Spend the money on it. This thing's not bad. This thing's all right. All right. Good. Um,
bathroom is set. I want, could they actually use this bathroom? Is it a shit bush too? Because
that's actually pretty funny. All right. I need a litter box. We're going to get the automatic one.
This one's way more expensive. What's the difference? I think it's way, why is it so expensive?
Okay. Now I need a couple of toys. Let's do this. Uh, over here. And then I got a cat toy.
Did I get, oh wait, wait, wait. This is cool. Wait, let's get one of these. Okay. Now let's do,
let's get a rug. Why not? What a rug. Wait. Okay. Now I got the bedroom done. I just need a living
room. Did I not have a couch the entire last person's entire life? It wasn't a couch the entire
game. The three streams of this game that I've not had a couch. That's it. Okay. That's probably a
lot of the problem. All right. I'm going to get just something nice. How about the mega sofa?
Hmm. This thing's pretty nice. Pretty modern. This one's all right. Let's get a, I don't know,
just like a, that's fine. All right. TV is going to be here and then we need a table, a TV right
there. I need a table here. The kitchen shit over there. All right. Uh, TV. I want a good TV this
time. How much is this? This is 4,200. This is $10,000. Oh my God. No, too small. Too small.
Why are these so expensive? This is so expensive. Whatever. It's fine. Okay. Now I need just like a
table. Ooh, that's cool. Let's do this. Right. Or like that console on there. Look at that. I need
lights. I will. I'll put lights in just wait. Uh, it's like why does this seem so cramped? Now I need
a big rug. That's big rug. Uh, now I gotta get a painting or something. Get in there. Nothing's
too big. I don't want that. Um, I got lights in there. Lamp Andy. What? I can't have lamps.
Everything has to be a recessed lighting. All right. Kitchen time. An expensive ass bridge.
No, I don't want to go broke. All right. That's fine. There is trash. Perfect placement. There's
sink. Something nice. This thing is huge. This is just a coffee maker. This thing's fine. That
thing's also huge. These are so big. How about this little thing? All right. That's fine.
All right. So I've got, I need a, I need a stove. Oops. All right. I am ready to move. I got a
counter space. Should I have one more counter? I can get into the fridge still here. Right. Okay.
That's good. I need a space. Okay. Now I need a table. Oh, cabinets. Yeah. Sure. Why not? This
is kind of too much. I, yeah. Nevermind. I need the money. Um, anything worth anything here? What?
I can sell my mailbox. I need a trash can. Okay. Now just a table and I'm done. Just a little one.
Just something shitty and then a couple of just shitty chairs and I'm fine. That's bad. All right.
Let's go. How do I turn into a werewolf? Oh, it's winter fest. Right. Oh, wait. Oh, wait. We need
to light that. It is winter fest. Fest of spirit. Open presents. Grand meal. I mean, we don't,
we don't know how to cook. I'm crying. Where's the fire alarm? Um, oh, okay. All right.
Does he know that I'm a werewolf?
He didn't like that.
Okay. Um, why can I hear? I can hear them.
We're going to have to hold on to that for a sec.
Does Santa actually show up? No, we need to cook a grand meal. I gotta give presents. Here we go.
Like belly laugh. We have to like, oh, that was funny. We had fun on winter fest.
Cool. He's in a row. Okay. Now we're going to sing. Let's sing together.
Okay.
What about the turkey dinner guy? This is a different character. That other guy got stabbed.
That's a pretty good Santa. Oh, I need a gift box, right? Pet obsessions. Oh, right. They get
obsessed with random things. All right. No, no, no. Don't cook. Um, we need to cook a grand. No,
I don't want Franks and beans. I want a grand holiday meal. We're gonna have a fish dinner.
I'll take care of it. I'll handle it. We're both going to try to go get this on the same stove.
Okay. It's so dark in here. What's, what's wrong? Oh, it's a Fortnite dance. I thought
I thought he was poisoned. Okay. I wanted just to eat that raw. What was it just going to do?
Oh, right, right, right. I'll give you some more light. All the complaining light Andes here.
There you go. Look at that. Everybody can see. Wow. There was a cat going to eat this.
We need to make a grand meal. So gross. What? Where? Already? How does this keep fucking
happening? What? Help. Put me out. Put me out. Stop playing with the cat. Put me out.
What the fuck? We're good. Put it out. What are you doing? No, no, no. Call the fire department.
Call the fire department. Call, call, call, call, call. Get out, out, out, out. Run, run, run, run,
get out of the way. Where are you? Somebody has to call the fire department. Pick up the phone. How
do I call the fire department? Why can't I call the fire department? Oh, there it is. Okay. Do it.
Don't go over to it. Help. Stop standing near the fire. For the love of God. Where's the fire
department? Come put the fire out over here. I would be very appreciated. It's the whole backyard.
Help. Thank you. Go get it, please. There's so much fire. There's so much. Who is this?
Where's the cat? What are you doing in here? He's back. What, what is he doing here? He's back.
Okay. This fire is still there though. Sniff and introduce? Is that a werewolf thing? I don't
understand. Wait, what do you mean sniff? This is a different guy. This is a different guy.
I'm going to find him for presents. How do I turn into a werewolf?
It is a different person.
Listen. Holy shit. A knife set?
What did you do? Why do I hear fire? Oh, thank God. I was going to say.
I take a wild shower, but I can smash it. What is a wild shower? You need to eat Santa.
He's still here. I feel like that's kind of mocking. Isn't it?
Oh, oh, oh, so you are. Get on better term.
Feed the cat. Oh, it's the automatic feeder. Right. Um, you get up and you do it. Oh,
Santa. Do you want some, uh, a plate? I love how it's a different guy. I can't get over it.
Somebody else. Oh, is he leaving? All right. Well, goodbye. Thanks for coming, Santa.
Well, that was a fun winter fest. One ability. Oh, I have ability points.
Wolf nap. Territory marking. Okay. Personal grooming. Okay. Wait, hold on. Can I piss on the
couch?
How many times can I do this? I can't just do that everywhere, right?
What's wrong? Why am I glowing? Oh, you want to do a fart off, don't you? You want to do a fart
off. I got you. Okay. I can't, can't. All right. All right. All right. All right. That's enough.
Why is it so dark? This is ominous. It is dark out here. Like really dark. I don't know. I can't.
This was an expensive stove too. That's such bullshit. I don't, I can't replace it.
Play. I need to take a bath or a shower or something. This is funny. This was funny,
but it's time to, it's time to buy an actual toilet. I don't, we need to have them be able
to go to the bathroom. Actual toilet time. Okay. That's better. All right. How are you doing?
You need to go to the bathroom. Go to the bathroom. Sad. What an awful holiday.
How long do you sleep for? Like four hours. That's actually not very much time.
Still, I have $96. This sucks. What the hell am I supposed to do about this?
This shit still works. Whatever. Was he gonna have to eat microwave food for a little while?
Fury. As fury grows, their animalistic instincts begin to manifest and will eventually take over.
Fury gain is constant and is hastened by Werewolf Ability's full moon
preferences. Wait, so I, I, I, I turn? All right. Well, you gotta clean this up. What is this?
Port of potties? Portal potties. Weird. What is this? Okay. Cool. We'll check that out tomorrow.
Snowing. First snow of the season. Oh, that's cute. You should go to bed. Bert and Ernie.
Anthony's a bro. All right. Get up. Look at the snow. Get up. Get up. It's snowing up. Look at
what is going on with my guy. He's supposed to go hollow. Come on. First snow of the season. Let's
go. Let's go. Coming together. Eating it. Attempts similish communication.
Pretending to be human.
Oh, this would be weird. This is weird. This would be very weird. It's at this moment where
this roommate kind of just goes, how much is for me to break the lease and leave? Come on, dude.
The beast beckons. What? Wait, he's just, he's lost control. He's kind of just being taken over.
I don't know how to use a phone. Where's the cat? How is this fridge already broken?
It's been one day. How is it already broken? What the fuck? It's been one day. He's already
going back to bed. Why? Awful holiday. Is it because I was licking my hands? That thing's cute.
Okay. I need to, I need to, what am I doing here? I need to eat something. What? He's going to start
rampaging. That is not until. Oh my God. Where's he going? Oh my God. He's going to watch out.
Jerry's transforming. Okay. Are there other werewolves coming over here? I look like I belong
in a Wallace and Gromit movie. A police cruiser has been dispatched. Oh shit. I definitely did it.
Oh God. No, are these people? What happened? Wait, what did I do? Why is he dead? Why is he dead?
Why did that guy die? Whose guts am I ripping out? This guy's not dead. He fell asleep. This
guy's asleep. He took a book off the shelf. Okay. Well, why, why won't this guy get up?
It's in regular clothes. Where did I just go? I don't know what's going on here, but you need to
go home. Okay. Well that was cool, I guess. Where's the house? He got up. He got up. He woke up. He
woke up. Oh, well that was kind of crazy. Do not save. That was wacky. A helicopter like, I don't
even know what happened there. Wait, I'm enraged still. How do I stop? How do I stop? Play with a
silver sword. I don't know what to do. How do I get him to actually, when does he stop doing this?
Two more hours? Well, all right. Whatever. Good luck. I got points. We'll just hang out in here.
Just lock him outside. That's actually not a bad idea. All right. Just chill out of there. Bored?
There's no decorations? All right. Somebody has to get a job and it's definitely not going to be you.
Why is this person in the house? This guy sucks. Why is this person in the house?
This guy's a fucking dork. What?
Why you don't like the cat? Who are these people? They've shown up twice.
Gary's now a werewolf runt. Oh god, where am I going? I'm chasing this guy down. Werewolf hangouts?
I can't do any of this stuff.
Oh, I'm back to normal now. I'm back to normal. Oh no, no, no. That's not happening. We have no
money. What did I spend up? We've got a stupid plasma screen TV. Just get rid of this. God damn
it. We have to do this stupid shit again. I have to start over again. I have to start over.
I have to start over. I have to start over. I'm going to start over. I'm starting over.
I can't just in the house, right? Wait, why is it you?
Why did he do that? With a bowl of fucking cereal. With one hand holding a bowl of sausage. What are
you eating? What is he eating? What is in his hand? He's already what? Excuse me? The car come
bro. I got to stop. All right. No more. We're not doing any more. We're going to, you're going to
do your time. We're not, we're just going to relax now. We're going to get, we're going to get a job.
I don't want all these everywhere. We need to get, I don't want these urns everywhere.
No, it was cheese crackers is what it was. Clean up. Clean up. We're going to reset back to zero.
Of course, this fridge is broken already because we had a fire. This all went off the rails
because of the fire that happened in the first 10 seconds. I actually, I need you. So somebody has
to repair this. You repair that. I'll repair the coffee maker. TV is fine. I might even just sell
the TV. Jerry is adventurous. We don't have enough money to do anything. So we need to do this.
Death, please get out of here. We're going to clean the house. That's fixed. Coffee maker is
about to be fixed. Things are getting a little better. Clean up. Throw this away. You also,
you know, clean up a little bit. How's the coffee maker is fine. Okay. Everything looks good. Take
a shower. You take a shower too. And then we're going to get jobs tomorrow. Oh, maybe one of us
will. How do you still, why do you still have blood all over you? Oh, there it is. Okay.
What am I doing? This is worse than my torque. Who is supposed to pay the money though?
When was I, wait, when did I get electrocuted? We lost $8. How? Oh, cause you're making a coffee.
This is not working. All right. At least make a salad. Very good. Did you only make one serving?
Come on, really? You actually don't need to eat. Uh, you go to bed. How much is it? It's 11. Yeah,
go to bed. I need to shower, use the bathroom and go to bed. No, why would I want to smash?
So far so good. Werewolves. I hear them. Have a sim do nothing solider for 24 sim hours.
Really? I feel like we did a lot of stuff. Oh my, look at, look at how cute that is.
Oh my goodness. It's on the calendar today. Wait, it's New Year's Eve. Oh no, no, that's tomorrow.
All right. New Year's Eve is tomorrow. We're going to go celebrate. Lunar peace. Oh, all right.
Both get up. Yeah. You want to have a drink at the club. Okay. Catch a fish. I don't know.
We're not going to really do that right now. All right. Is there still any salad fridge?
How about a fruit salad? That sounds good. Go make a salad.
We got to be ready for New Year's Eve tomorrow. Is there a door open?
I don't get it. That solves a lot. It solves everything. Yeah. Let's kick stuff. That's fine.
All right. Prepare for New Year's. Turn this off. I don't want a fire going. Fire is causing so many
problems. Clean this up too. This is a mess. Stop that. Stop that. Stop that. Stop that.
Stop that. Stop that. Stop that. Stop that. Stop that. Stop that. Stop that. Stop that. Stop that.
Causes so many problems. Clean this up too. This is a mess. Stop. Don't do that. You don't like
cooking. That's fine. All right. It's New Year's Eve tomorrow. I don't want any of this stuff. We're
going to go out anyways. You good? Your passion is baking but you don't like cooking. That is
really weird. I thought I was a run. Gross. All right. Who's hungry? All right. Just eat it.
Spend the ability point. I will after eats. Eat first. Why am I doing that? Oh, okay.
These eyes. How do I do first person? Oh, no. What have I done? This is a HUD-less camera mode.
This is fucking weird. Will you go sit down? You're freaking me out.
Sometimes they just do the random dance stuff. I don't know why.
Okay. Hunter. Wait. We have to buy food. I'm going to go do that right now.
All right. I'll be back. I'm going to go get his food. You do whatever you need to do. I'm
going to go hunt for food. Okay. Hunting. Will I get anything? This takes a long time.
Anthony should have a job. Yeah, Anthony should have a job. You're right. I'll look on my phone.
Something easy. Something just easy, right? Not a lot of time. Let's see. All right. We can do
be a critic. This doesn't work, unfortunately. Politician. I'll do critic. Level up writing.
Yes. All right. So I'm a critic. I work in two days. I need to level up writing. I can do that
with a computer. You get any food? Make coffee. Did I get any food? Raw meat? Can we cook this?
Raw what? Well, no, that was a person. Okay. Well, we can make a steak. Are you hungry? You want
a steak? No, we're good. Why are you so bored? Read your book. Purchase the vampire home,
whatever this is. This is, we don't have any money. Nevermind. He's so bored Fortnite dancing.
He was trapped in there. You're going to sleep on the bed? I thought I said raw something,
but it was actually the name of the person. Sell the TV and buy a PC. That's a good idea.
They don't need television. It rots your brain. A desk. This is for little kid. I need a PC. This
thing is all right. This thing's a piece of shit. It's fine. Okay. So, uh, you need to practice
writing. Practice writing. There it is. And you are, you have the muscle of the operation and you
are the cool mascot. We've got the brains, we have the muscle and we get the mascot.
We're good to go. When is New Year's Eve tomorrow? Okay. Let's rest up because we need to make sure
we celebrate. Can you sell the urn? Weirdo. That's my snowman. Yeah. Get out of here. What was he
doing? He shows up. He shows up to my property. I can throw snow at Anthony's face. Oh, I'm all
the way over here. I've got a lucrative opportunity for someone who doesn't ask too many questions.
I need to do one. I'll take it. I want to shove snow on his face. Stop working. I want to put
snow on your face. All right. Wait till you get one point. There it is. All right. Okay. That was
good. You got two points. Uh, we're going to do some mischief here.
Wash. That's so rude.
That was so rude. The urn is ugly. Um, what do you want me to do? I can't sell it. Come on.
Come on. I don't want this 30 FPS. Come on. Come on. Stop it. Stop it. There we go.
All right. So we, what time is it? Seven o'clock. Let's get ready for bed and let's ready to go out
and have fun on New Year's Eve. So you need to go to the bathroom. Sure. Why not? Then go to bed.
What is a feral poop? Doesn't seem very feral. How about you? You need to eat. Uh, I made.
Yeah, you can eat the leftovers.
Eat the leftovers. What are you doing? Um, well, you need to cook it first.
You're just going to eat raw meat. What? You better not throw that away.
Why is he eating raw steak? There's no stove. Fix that. Stop lagging. It's annoying. All right.
So we have stove again. Uh, what's wrong with you? Yeah. Go to the bathroom. Cook the steak this time.
What are you doing? What are you doing? What are you doing? What are you doing? What are you doing?
Stop that. Don't eat the raw meat. Stop doing that. Why is he doing this? Cook it. There's a
stove. Cook it right. Cook it. You know what? Just eat it. Whatever. He's not a werewolf. He is.
Go to bed. That snowman's been there for a long time. Carnivore diet. Oh no, you're starting to
turn. No more of raw meat. What do we do? Would I take a cold shower or bath or something? He's
doing this thing again. How do we stop it? Oh, he's going hunting. All right. Well, whatever. Fine.
Bring back some meat. Um, it's almost time for you to get up. Wait, what? He already has it?
Oh my God. He's got four. No, no, no. We need to cook these steaks. I need to learn how to make a
steak. These two are fucked. I'm going to eat raw meat at the New Year's Eve party and scare the
shit out of everybody there. Okay. Uh, how are you on sleep? All right. Get up. Let's get prepared
for the day. Time for New Year's Eve. Can they cook something? What are you making? Garden salads.
Not that. Okay. Well, whatever. That's fine. The dancing is making him turn. That's enough of that.
How do we, how do I calm them down? How do I calm me down? Practice singing or something?
So bored. All right. New Year's Eve. Let's go. Oh, God damn it. Really? Okay. Well, whatever.
Should I not take them out? Three hours. What are you doing? We just need to just ride this out
for another couple of hours. It's going to be fine. Go hunt now. Oh, that's a good idea. I can't.
No, I can't. I've lost all control currently.
Don't fuck this whole thing up. Just, I need just six of AM, seven, eight, nine AM, right?
Do not. This guy. Gary T is the worst character. Are you done? This guy sucks. Eat anything.
I'm going to eat the coffee machine. Oh my God. What else can I eat? All right. You're coming down.
Stop peeing. All right. He's coming down. He's coming down. All right. There he goes.
You ready to go to New Year's Eve? Let's go pee and we'll go. That's such a weird thing because
this is all official. This is all official Sims 4 shit. That's not a mod. This is the werewolf
stuff is officially in the game. I almost feel like this is still the mod. It's not. Okay.
Are we ready? It's time to go to a New Year's Eve party. Where are we going to do it? Countdown to
midnight decorate party spirit. We're going to go. We have to go somewhere. Where are we going?
New Year's Eve. Let's plan a social event. Let's go. All right. This is going to be a
mountain climb excursion on New Year's Eve. We're going to get to the top of the mountain and
everyone's going to make their resolution on top of the mountain. I only know two people.
How do we only know two? I've killed people, right? Whatever. This is going to be cool.
He actually did come with. Wait, he hates me, but he doesn't hate you. He doesn't. All right.
When did we get to the top of the mountain? Gather excursion members near the trail map
marker at the top of the climbing route. All right. Where's the climbing route? Over here.
Okay. Have a sim perform any exercise to warm up. Oh, don't do anything weird. Don't do werewolf
shit. Stop. Why do I have my clothes off? Oh, okay. Is this also somebody that's going to come with
us? No, no, no. Don't leave. Oh, you're not leaving. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. We have
to go together. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Don't go without us. We have to go together.
What are you doing? Don't just go on your own. Okay. I need to do, we need to do an exercise.
Hurry up. Uh, is it like dog here or something? I don't have anything. All right. Well, whatever.
Let's go. Okay. Gather excursion members near the trail. Oh, climb up rock wall. Let's go guys.
Let's check it out. Wrong way. This is a filler episode. Why? How do I get it? Excursion members
trail map marker at the top of the climbing route. Where is that? This is not canon ride to the top.
Check the board board. What do you mean? Like in here? God damn it. I want to go on the rock
climb. The yellow board. You mean this over here? Where's this yellow board you're talking about?
The yellow board. Where's the yellow board? Who is, who is this?
All right. We're going up. Ride to the top. All right. Here we go.
We're going to the top of the mountain. That's who just wiped out. Who just climbed a rock wall?
I didn't do that. Where is everybody? Where the, where are you going? Santa already got up somehow.
How did you do that? I need climbing gear. He doesn't have any climbing gear on.
I need climbing gear from any computer. Hold on. Can I, from here? I definitely can't, right?
No, I can't reach him. He's saying I can't do it. Santa I think has to pee. I can't reach with
anything. He's just taunting me. No, I can't do it. How is he going to get down is the question.
He's so stupid. This is stupid. Santa gets up there with no class. How do I get, what do I do here?
I guess I could, um, I want to, I just want him to, I'm not going to suffocate him with a diaper.
I can't reach him. I can't suffocate him with a diaper. With flamethrower. No, he's safe up there.
I can't do anything about it. Artillery. There's no, I don't have artillery. Drop a meteor, run
him over. I can't. The group wasn't prepared for the climb. They showed up at the mountain.
Where did he go? Where did he go? Where's Santa? That was weird.
He's going. Damn, all right. Well, he made it. He actually made it. I have no idea where Santa went.
That was bizarre. All right, now we're gonna, I'm gonna ride to the bottom. I just wasn't prepared
for this apparently. I didn't know you had to have a climbing skill. I guess it's a new skill
because I was building a meter. Hey, fancy some, um, okay. Pony deserves better than Jerry.
Let's go get some tea. Okay, so we're all here. Santa here too. All right, so drink tea.
Where's the, how do I get tea? All right, let's go get Sakura tea. It's right here. Get some swag.
All right, so what do we want? You didn't even take, you didn't drink your tea.
We all good? All right, look at how old he is.
It was just yesterday, I feel like, when I tried to poison you. Here you are.
Finished the job?
No, I, no, no, that's not, that's not what we're doing.
I'm going to drink this tea. We're gonna have a good time.
Okay, B. I thought I drank the tea. Did I not? Where's my tea? Why can I not get it?
Drink it. Finally. Jesus. All right, we're good. It's freaking me out. Okay. Why?
What are you doing over here? So wait, it's almost New Year's, right? We have to sing.
You think he's gonna like raw meat? Hey, Jeffrey. Brought you something.
It's a stinky raw steak.
What?
I have no idea what just happened. What, what, what was, who was going where?
I don't understand what I was watching. Oh, that was cool.
I want to do a New Year's Eve. Let's blow some horns.
I feel like I'm in VR chat right now.
Discuss being a werewolf. The metaverse.
He's his spirit is fading away. Oh my goodness, man. That was a lot into my own piss.
He made a splashing sound. Um, uh, let's wake up here.
Is that a big cigar? Oh no. Wait.
That he's trying to kill a werewolves and vampires.
I should stay away from this guy.
I want to see what he says. If I go over there, I'm going to be really werewolfy in front of them.
Oh, they hate me.
This is so stupid.
I'm going to hunt for food right now. Where would I even hunt for food is my question.
It's kind of hard to move here. I'm having a little bit of trouble moving.
There's no other werewolves here. That's bullshit.
I'm going to eat the karaoke machine. I'm going to eat the table that I'm sitting at too.
The person's a fan. Oh, I destroyed it all.
Somebody said, please, can you make one sane character?
I think this character is pretty sane actually. Prime werewolf?
Oh my God. That's scary. What am I doing? I think everyone's leaving.
All right. All right. All right. Let's finish this up.
That lady just put that gun. Oh my, that was awful.
Where'd the table go? What?
Where am I? Oh, okay. How you doing?
Oh, you just did that. You just did that to me.
All right, we're good.
Everyone's so sad. It's all about who died. What death? It's all about death.
Somebody died?
Well, that's okay. It's the people that I killed. Why did I do that?
All right. Let's go home. Back to the house.
That was a wait. We didn't even count down the new year.
Oh, well, just pretend we did. Just pretend we did. That's fine.
Jerry ruins the another holiday. Okay. Back here.
So if you're curious what we're doing tomorrow, tomorrow I'm streaming.
Tomorrow is obviously Thanksgiving if you celebrate it.
Probably going to start the stream a little bit later in the day
because I figured people will be, you know, eat your turkey,
have your stuffing and Thanksgiving. And then later on in the evening,
guess what came out three days ago? Hatsune Miku Picross.
Hatsune Miku Picross is out. So we're going to chill, eat your food.
We'll hang out for a few hours tomorrow evening on Thanksgiving.
It'll be a chill stream. There's been a few wild ones here.
So chill it out. That's the plan. Are we all in the house?
Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Good. Good. Good.
I'm playing it for a few days. Is it any good?
I'm not going to the flea market. I don't care.
Turn this off. I don't like having that there.
OP. Go on. It's Picross. So it's fun. Cool.
Does it play music? I would imagine it probably does.
Oh yeah. Let me just say one more time before I start to cool it out here.
If you want to nominate something, the end of the year awards,
nominations are open as of right this very moment.
Go to the Discord. Go check the nominations channel.
Read the rules. It's going to be, the nominations are open until December 4th.
After December 4th, if you don't know what happens here,
I would go check the previous, the fifth year running.
Go watch the previous awards, skim through, see kind of what it's all about.
We do a best and worst of the channel.
And it will be not on New Year's this year.
We're doing it in December. Should be a really fun time.
It's going to be a Christmas special.
If you have something, if you look at that category's list,
go look. You might have something to nominate.
And I'm going to probably call it here.
I feel like these two characters are, they're just a little too fucked up.
So I'm probably going to call it here in a second.
You learn how to make an egg and toast BLT.
What the hell are you, what is that?
I'm going to save it though, because we'll come back probably.
This is, these games are so much fun with the mods.
It's just, I know that if I have the ability to do this, for instance, like,
what's one that we didn't see that I want to see?
There's only those two.
Steal money.
No, I'm not clicking on some of these.
Okay, so what about, I want to look at Deadly.
Bash head with axe.
Burn with flamethrower.
Chainsaw guts.
Death from above.
What does this mean?
I'm going to be on a motorcycle?
I need to know what this does.
He's getting out of bed.
Oh no.
That was a little elaborate.
That was a little too much.
Okay.
Stop killing Sims.
I don't have all day.
I saved it right before.
Don't worry.
Lead.
Come on.
He's been brought back to life.
Very cool.
Brought back again?
Oh my God.
He's back.
We're all good.
Tombstone Piledriver?
What is that?
That is so stupid.
It plays the music too.
He's still alive.
How is he still alive?
Oh shit.
Quickly.
Hurry.
Cat, get out of the way.
Why am I bald?
Where's my hair?
Okay.
I just want to see.
Wait.
Death took my jupe?
He ripped my...
What?
Let's have some raw meat.
Where's the cat?
Oh, cat's fine.
That's been fun.
We've completely gone off the rails though, unfortunately.
Thanks for watching everybody.
That's gonna be it.
I'll see you guys tomorrow.
Have a good Thanksgiving if you celebrate it.
That was the...
All right, that's it.
I'll see you guys tomorrow.
I'll see you guys tomorrow for Miku Picross.
Probably somewhere around...
What's a good time?
Maybe like later in the night?
Just like a chill night stream?
I think that sounds like a good idea.
Maybe like 5, 6 p.m. Pacific?
6 p.m. Pacific?
Have like a late night just chill Picross stream for a little bit?
Line down from Thanksgiving?
That sounds like a plan to me.
So see you tomorrow at 6 p.m.
Late night.
Thanks everybody for watching.
Again, this has been The Sims 4.
We'll probably play it again.
We just kind of...
It just went off the rails.
And actually I'm getting hungry so I'm gonna go eat some food.
I'll see you guys tomorrow.
Happy Thanksgiving.
Have a good one.
Goodbye.
Good night.
Thanks for watching.
Thanks for the support.
There were a ton of subs today so thanks guys.
Appreciate it.
And we'll see you tomorrow.
Please play Sorcery.
What about your internet dropping it?
Oh, that's a good point.
It's Picross.
There's not much going on on the screen.
Even if I drop some frames it's not very much going on bitrate-wise.
Sorcery?
Yes.
So...
I don't know.
We kind of need to figure out what's going to happen with that.
I did say that I would get into the third game and see if I was still into it.
See how people are into it.
Maybe we'll do some just chill late night streams or something.
Get some of it done.
Breath of the Wild?
Oh, we played Breath of the Wild a few days ago.
I'm still into it.
Please play more Sorcery.
What date is the actual award stream?
I don't have a hard date for you.
But I can tell you it will be...
It will be near...
It'll be before Christmas.
It'll be at least a few days.
At least three or four days before Christmas.
That I can assure you.
But see you tomorrow.
Have a good Thanksgiving.
Good night.
See you guys later.
Again, the awards are open.
Nominations are open.
If you think that's something you wanted to keep,
you want to make sure that you made the nomination aware.
Go do it.
It's in Discord.
There's a channel in Discord right now.
radobeasts.net
Go check that out too.
That's very close.
If you haven't checked it out,
haven't signed up already,
it's a great way for us to understand how many units we actually really need.
radobeasts.net
End of the year award nominations.
Christmas show.
Battleaxe.
Quite a few things going on in the next month or two.
So see you soon.
Take care.
Have a good rest of your night.
See you guys later.
Call your mother.