Good afternoon. How are you? Welcome to another live stream. I'll be your host for the evening.
So I listened to the radio the other day. And I didn't I was gonna bring this up yesterday,
but I forgot to. People that do radio, talk radio, they talk for probably five to 10 minutes.
And then there's five to 10 minutes of ads. They do like two to three hour long blocks.
And they actually only speak for about 40 minutes. I'm sitting there going, what the
fuck is this? And we're back. And sometimes sometimes they do the and we're back, speak
for 30 seconds, and then do 10 minutes of ads. That's a what the fuck is going on there.
That's unbelievable. I'm sitting there going, people on Twitch sit here and they broadcast
for like eight hours sometimes. Can you imagine if I every 10 minutes took a 10 minute ad break?
We would never get anything done. How does anybody on the radio get anything done?
Like when you get when you get into a conversation, you start really talking.
It takes longer than like six minutes to have a conversation. Like that's you can't have a
conversation six minutes. He hates ads. No, I don't hate ads. I kind of do. Who likes ads?
Nobody likes that. I'm just saying sitting there going, what if I ran a fucking commercial every
four minutes? And the commercial wasn't 30 seconds long. It was six minutes long.
You guys would run away. I didn't even give a fuck. I was supposed to. I got I got I was
I was gonna say Resident Evil three tonight. My tweet and I didn't do it. Here we go. I almost
hit send. People who run ads like ads. Yeah, I guess that's true. Because then that's you get
paid, I guess. I don't like the title. The title is dog shit. But what do you want me to title this?
I thought I'm like streamer number 450,000 that has played this guy. I don't got it. What do you
want me to do for a funny title? All the funny titles have been sapped. They've all been done.
You've already seen them all. E. I did write E. He's in the title. It's E. Resident E. Resident E.
How about just Resident E? Just E. Just title it E. All right, just E. Is that better?
Just E. All right, now I'm keeping I'm keeping it. We're gonna play Resident Evil three tonight.
Just E. I've been waiting for this for a long time. And yeah, I've been waiting for it. But it's I
I'm keeping my expectations pretty low. Because for every one person that says it's all right,
there's 100 people that say, don't play it. It's gonna ruin what you like about the second one.
So I'm gonna keep myself at a very, very I'm gonna be low energy tonight.
I'm gonna tie I'm gonna be dialed back low energy. I don't want to be fucking high energy
right now. Because what if I don't like it? Low energy. Oh, shit, I forgot to get my extender.
Hold on. Where's my extender? No, no, this is a big problem. Where's my extender? This is a major
problem. I can't start without this. I need my extension for my headphone. Oh, wait, this is bad.
It's bad. Why is it not plugged in? And where is it? You're going to understand why I need this?
Because it's going to build it all stream. Extender. Thank God. Stream saved. God, I would
have taken a fucking week off. All right, we got it. So we're gonna play sorry, I'm not hitting you
there. We're gonna play Resident Evil 3 remake. I think I'll stream for a little while. And the
goal, by the way, is to try to beat this in one stream. If I can't beat this in one stream within
the next six to seven hours, then I'll just YouTube the rest. All right, that's fine. That's
what that works. Good. Good. My extender is in. All right, let's go. Are you ready? I don't think
you guys are ready for Resident Evil 3. Did I hype you guys up? I mean, you've probably played
this game three times now. I haven't. All right, let's go. I know, I know, I know. Yeah, yeah, yeah,
I know. It's a it's a fucking scary game. By the way, worst hair arc ever. It's I just have to
accept it. This is just worst hair arc. Every day is worst hair 2020. But as long as I stay like
this, I could I could look fine. Once I turn this way, you see the real damage. See the real damage
of this hair will just stay this way for now. All right, let's go. New game. Nope. Sorry, not
going to happen. Don't care. I'm not going to play on assisted. I'm going to play on standard. I'm
going to play regular mode. I know I get bullied into picking the hardest mode in every game.
That's not going to I'm not going to say I don't even know. I don't even know what it says.
I saw stronger enemies and no, I don't care. All right, everybody shut up. Cut scene. Is this real?
It's an FMV. Any disease in modern. Authorities are bracing for more.
What the what? A citywide emergency has been declared. The CDC has quarantined the lower
Midwestern. Why did that happen? Commitment, honesty, integrity. These are the core values
that Matt Corkus for umbrella. It's this foundation that will continue to build a brighter future for
all of us like they bought that on fiber. I'll say anything you want dressed up as an umbrella
employee. All we need is a happy birthday Larry at the end of that. Turn it up. You got it. After
the cut scene. This game suck. Hey, cards. Thanks for the $50 cards. 5000 bits from cards. Take
these and shave your Lego hair with them. I've got a I'm going to have a new haircut. All right,
I have to pay attention. Thanks for the $50. That's a fucking huge amount of money. Here we go.
This game suck. What? No. Okay. I have to pay attention. Pay attention. It's not Resident Evil
2. Pay attention. I get yelled at for this all the time. It rain. This first this first person.
Why is the FOV so close? I don't like this. Wow, this must be third person. Is my camera broken?
Okay, I'm too close. I don't like this. All right, get me out of this as soon as possible.
I don't care about any lords. I don't get way to nothing but this is like 60 FOV. It's 40. Oh,
hey guys. Right. Wait, who is that? Who's the character in this one? Am I gonna brush my teeth
with a gun? I don't think that's a good idea. Can't trust the tap water. What's going on? Why
is this happening? It was a dream and rip up. You're waking up. They're all gonna brush your teeth
after all that. It's not how you brush your teeth. Told you it was a dream. Aim over.
gets worse every night subtitles they're on no no more fucking first person oh look at that dog
oh all right let's go three more days then i can kiss this town goodbye
okay good what's the way to avoid having getting sick by this you look at the ground right
no that makes it worse close one eye how do you like not get sick by the first person
close both eyes uh somebody's hit final fantasy 12 and hello thanks for the five was it five five
community subs i almost missed it thanks for the five subs fucking door okay because then your
depth perception doesn't kick in but we all know what's gonna happen we just have to be ready for
it right satan face into the mirror it's the it's classic okay no september 28th 8 07 p.m
raccoon city eddie the penguin thanks for the what was it five community subs all right let's
get the controls down it's too dark coming wait what's this bill's report this has already been
two months since that mess with umbrella thanks to the suspension investigations haven't progressed
exactly as i'd hoped perhaps this written record of what i found will prove the final duty of stars
officer i can only hope that it helps it those infected by the virus seem to become literal
zombies they bite you they get in contact with you and they are strong it should be noted that
those who survived the incident have not yet developed symptoms it's unclear whether this
because the virus has a long incubation period because we just happen to be resistant to the
infection we ought to remain vigilant as for me aside from my minor difficulty skip all lore
are we okay with that skip all lore like you guys are all right with that right i don't want to
read like we all know what happens are you i mean did i don't do i need to read every memo
game will last two hours if i don't do this what do you mean this lighting makes me look
fucking like way grosser than i am in real life whatever just a sec isn't somebody just calling
pharmaceuticals company industry leader yeah well wait it's gonna be a two-hour game
they're very patient turn the lights off it's the daytime here are you brad is that you it's
it's daytime what are you talking about i don't have to explain you gotta get out of there
all right let me grab mine let me go that would have scared me i wasn't even looking
i was looking at the chat room that would have been horrifying is that um this nemesis
oh silly girl you think you can kill me with a mere toothbrush fuck pose it that thing no
just missed holy shit you're strong i couldn't do that i gotta get i gotta get out of here
here how do you jump help him help this guy somebody catch him i tried is there a dodge
roll in this one when do i get to go tap tap tap tap i can't wait to click click click click
wicked fast does he know this is a movie look i got low expectations okay i waited like two months
until everybody played it and then i was like you know what escape i got now i know what i
can expect so my expectations are at the ground they can only go up from here it just got out of
there man i gotta say wait i have a i'm playing as i'm playing as the nemesis now that's what
you guys understand wow is he pretending he can't even fucking get close to wow she's running so
slow germa you suck fucking i got it was scripted she's in a slow old lady job you can't even catch
up to her you missed three times fucking awful all right which one of these is the main character
that's gonna break into song that was a great play we just watched oh it's brad i know brad
it's the helicopter guy what was the thing tim the final right now it's got a hard on for the only
two stars left in town you and me are you brad i'm not sticking around just look around here we wait
the more screwed we are this is actually bread this all happens so fast that thing always leads
to another you want to something really really sad this is not making this up brad was my favorite
character in resident evil that's really embarrassing because it was just he it's not a joke i swear to
god i just thought it was cool he's like the helicopter pilot he like saves everybody and
rescues them and stuff i did i really just get bit scripted i didn't i didn't even make it
10 seconds into getting control of the character script that's what would really happen though let's
be honest everybody has like this fantasy of what would happen that that all right i'm good
nice brad no brad we all yeah we do actually all of us do
don't fuck up like i do go everybody knows what happened sorry brad but you just you're dead
oh this is how you aim a toothbrush i would i didn't want to say it is a toggle it's not
feels pretty good out of bullets oh no what do i do i was wasting ammo that was teaching me how to
shoot under the bus up here under oh all right i'm gonna sneeze nothing i can do about it
oh i tried to fucking help you my chair just got electrocuted oh minus two oh sorry
don't run
it's gonna be a zombie in it hey any food in there no it's just a big steel box oh have fun
you had guy in 20 minutes that fucking guy's gonna get hungry in like 30 minutes and go
out and venture to go find like a hamburger wrapper and get fucking killed that's how it
always happens always have at least on you at all times at least 50 of those fucking cheese snack
dip things with the crackers and the little stick that you spread the cheese on they'll last at
least three or four months with those what are those things called what's it gross i i don't
think so why why those why is that gross those things it's cheese and protein
crackers to keep you going and a stick you can use as a weapon against those fucking zombies
it's a scripted bite okay we're going to our group we lost the tutorial but i did earlier
uh i don't have a map yet right now get that eventually well uh that's not gonna work out
why why is it always the helicopter that happens to you know sorry the helicopter always gets like
shot out of the air with a fucking rocket why is this a faux letter grade it has to start first
started okay it started why would you drive into him of all the places to drive you don't drive
at the mutant turn go down at the exit why would you drive into him you could have probably gotten
out but no oh i'm gonna kill the guy that weighs probably more than the car you were probably
better off running into him yourself which is your body now sorry it didn't work he's not a helicopter
only hits helicopters i'm actually surprised that that rocket didn't fucking swing around
306 degrees go the other way and home onto a fucking regular helicopter in the air
i think we're in the clear hope so we've been bringing survivors here here where
if i guys have converted i could do that into a shelter that's my shower that's what i get
that hair looks like after the shower personal space okay i get it do i go take a shower and
come back and have that hair who's the dipshit to close this sorry we're gonna have to go around
hey do you have any bullets i've never seen anything like it but it's no zombie i'll tell
you what it wants it won't stop till it gets it when nemesis becomes an actual problem in the game
it's gonna be it kind of really yeah it happens that happens though they can't what are they
gonna save that i'm with the umbrella biohazard countermeasure service ubcs for sure are you
kidding me are you fucking kidding me he doesn't show up again whoa whoa whoa what are you talking
about yeah what the fuck are you talking about you don't have to trust me but i'm going to the
shelter you coming this way even he was surprised wait wait hold on nemesis ain't in the game what
the fuck are you talking about wait what he doesn't show up again are they assistant jebaiter or what
the hell that's kind of we both have the same idea all right let's go is there is there anybody
bullets check every area on stretch gameplay stretch gameplay an extra hour so i don't have
a three and a half hour stream use our help you didn't even think to ask fine young lady your
she is an elite operative of rpd special tactics and rescue service
her name is something valentine it's jill nice to meet you jill i am ubcs platoon leader michael
victor my team was sent here to rescue civilians great how's that going for you this city is
completely cut off isolated most of the hundred thousand civilians will wind up dead correction
undead my platoon has suffered serious losses just a cutscene you don't need me here i have
nothing to do with this well you can thank your corporate overlords for that yes well we are doing
all we can if we can get this subway train moving we can you guys just have to write
game on when we get to a gameplay portion and it turns it back on
my men cannot do this alone right i'm in their side it's a pre-recorded cutscene yeah they're
not actors doing this in my living room right now oh god yeah of course it is it's a video
game it's not real all right super cop here you go you can use this to stay in contact
i know what a radio is we need to get you geared up head up to street level you'll find supplies
there okay all right activated the game on camera all right let's get to the street level is there
oh there is a map the map screen is useful for more than just your current location and surroundings
i can also show you any points of interest and items you have found but haven't picked up yet
okay three points of interest items you have found but you haven't gotten
all right so we just got to get up to street level okay just go to street level is my oh
knife and gun now what about these uh what about these npcs over here
okay street level uh let's go up i can't stand this hair i can't stand this dude's hair
you could be a brand new viewer that came in and talking about me or a long-term viewer that hates
this game all right okay i gotta ask a question for those of us idiots in the audience uh does it
good i was gonna say does it highlight things or do i have to physically go look around
okay tabloid front page there are cannibals eating people thousands of bite marks covered
her body when she was dismembered okay you and people ask how the fuck does he read the one
comment why does he read that one fucking gross messed up comment i don't know but who did it
uh i don't know it's just lore veto i after you are gonna not gonna like that working on it
so what's the plan the old tanks got me clearing that you might get in the subway infrastructure
back online and how do i do that let's start by restoring power store power to the substation
once you hit the main road copy that let's do this fast okay reactivate power at the substation you
got it uh what's the quick knife i mean what's what's quick knife is it f quick knife is f
is there a quick knife or do i actually have to have it equipped f there isn't one it's a rare
herb oh this is locked what the fuck you're gonna give me a locked chest in the very beginning of
the game oh this is fantastic because when i get the key for that in four hours i have to remember
where this is wait no it's a simple lock what does that mean i shoot it off wait why am i
pressing f i have to shoot it off anything else no all right wait wait wait wait whoa whoa okay this
gunpowder over here uh you combine two of these and you make what i almost just walked by all this
shit okay what is it somebody's gonna be combining with the other yeah yeah yeah resident evil is a
video game that we've maybe have heard of uh okay use the plus to combine into command just okay
combine a double herb uh this is standard grade to combine two and these create handgun ammo
it wants me to do that 15 ammo oh come on it was supposed to be a remake i can't just instantly do
it in the menu everybody's to fix his graphics what's wrong with what's wrong with what do you
mean what's wrong with the graphics something wrong with the graphics rainy your camera is grainy
it's grainy it's sandpaper game is that i think turn on turn off the film grain how do i where's
that i did this i didn't see that
which one subsurface subsurface film grain out of quality i got things on medium okay i don't
mesh quality high i just i always put things on medium because i want to be able to stream them
at 60 fps my p i got a 1080 in here i look i know i could look i'm gonna get about i'm gonna get
another pc soon i'll get a fucking 280 rtx whatever it is but for now i do i want to be able to
play it like 120 what if i can't play it 120 though look see 120 hertz he's on an i3
no this is like all good high quality lights i hate high quality lights ambient occlusion
on i hate ambient occlusion it's it makes it ugly i don't want you want bloom no bloom you want to
talk about blur lens flare yeah i want that no i don't want that i this is like the counter
strike settings you put everything on low so you can see what the fuck you're doing
hey put it on this is the counter strike pro way to play these games and that's how i do it
put bloom back on i don't want it on i don't want depth of field on this extra blur this one just
distorts your eyes all right and i i increased it it looks better i increased it all right okay
how about this i'll turn on what if what if we do rendering mode super no that's interlaced
oh yuck um i got anti-aliasing on bottom most option upscaling off fidelity fx cas plus upscaling
what is that turn it off why are you so scuffed i'm not i'm just trying to figure let's see what you
tell me better use more anti-aliasing this looks like it's on the nintendo ds image quality rendering
normal 100 frame rate variable vsync off anti-aliasing t a a t fx a a n t s a
it's sma a whatever it is the tsa use sma a okay texture quality was put on um higher than that i
guess texture filter filter on it's 16 on my computer is not going to be like i'm not confused
gonna break good hold on this is green high potency yeah green ever is too green urban
yeah maximum potency just wait this is one green and one red what about the blue oh they deleted
blue from the the remake right please make your resolution 480p i don't know what the
fuck you guys are on about all right let's go here's the storage unit uh i'm gonna keep this
stuff for now let's make a save file remove it's the frames i mean the frames watch it through our
eyes all right let's figure this out i want to see he's getting upset all right put it on
fucking source wait is this your guys way to pad the stream or is this uh add the stream or is this
is it all right hold on is it all right what's the what's the problem what's the what's the problem
i missed another fucking jump scare gotta get that train moving quick step it actually looks
fine i i people just try to try to find ways to like make me do wait they would run up the
volume it doesn't it's bad i do it on i put on v sync it's the fps hold on a minute where is
the graphics okay rect x12 nobody everyone uses 10 still variable i'm gonna cap it at 60 see what
is that a variable does that look better it's literally fine shit i don't want to try save
bullets i missed bullets okay well all right the game just looks the way that it looks all right
we're done i'm playing the game i would have been already fucking through this
all right how would i go this mood is gone all right we're gonna get the train turned back on
break this it's not a take off a simple lock do i actually need a simple key okay wait can i shoot
it no i can't get in here either fuck i'm gonna keep going i gotta get the subway back on where
the hell do i do that carlos i've reached the main avenue which way do i go see a big transmission
tower that's the substation you'll have to circle around through an alley to your right to get there
you mean the alley that's we got to press apply you have to shoot the lock 14 more times
i have to pay attention i have to pay fucking attention to this game
otherwise i'm gonna get stuck okay reactivate the power put out the fire why are you climbing
that i gotta find a lock pick i want what's in there okay i want what's in there oh get away
from me come on gunpowder that's it red barrel god damn it can i help that i'm all right use the
knife on the fire there's a generator where okay i can go this way let's go over here
i can't see the my left can i go in here shit of course okay we this is the donut shop
i can't open doors right no need a simple key let me check the rest of this place
come on it could be something in here yep always explore you never know what you might find
that's it all right somebody's listening to music back here all right i'm ready for whatever's in
this door it's safe green herb fancy box oh um i'm gonna all right cancel i gotta take that
green herb i need it pick up that fancy box take the bullets you can examine an item from
different angles by selecting and using the e button you might reveal something okay so pick
it up jammin it's in here you know in a normal circumstance i would be freaking out right now
about that what are you gonna get for that now i need as well just fucking wash it down the toilet
it's just heavy and big it doesn't do anything i mean you could use it as a weapon
worth nothing now my kids i'm not doing this now i was gonna go off on like this really sad rant
about how things used to be before i could sell this must be high as fuck prices is he
yes you'll figure it out no the uh the answer is no by the way how many times did he blink
they must be a liar okay uh red jewel i'm gonna hold on to that i might need it or a door coming
up here right let's go he put cbd in his hair i think people do that it don't people don't
need people use like hemp oil or something for all kinds of stuff right now we got uh straight
up this way i missed an item ah give me it oh shit how do i oh boy this is gonna be bad
oh my god i decided they were gonna lose okay well that was fun oh they get one gun powder
this is locked too if was there a red fucking barrel right there all right here's the railroad
i don't even fucking think about it hold on there might be nothing
something else to pick up like an item or something trying to shoot the fucking barrel
what's that oh high grade somebody outside still caution i thought i was on caution it's okay
all right i'm out can i run and kick this guy in the head r and g at the same time is that like a
let go of gun wait what's that what am i missing here ah all right subway he's back here have you
something up here all right go up here should i the subways over there wait i can just go to
this person's house need those nobody coming behind me right fuck yeah if i'm gonna push
and you're gonna pull at the same time man it's not gonna work oh my god you fucking dick
i have an off path here he's gonna get up i know it i'm in the bag nothing in the bag i need this
code for the safe god it could have been but if they were a fan i don't know drugstore owner's
journal this new hair tonic from umbrellas flying off the shelves the stuff they make always works
wonders it's no surprise the new safe is just perfect nobody knows the code not even my wife
it's a secret between me and my beautiful aqua cure queen you never give it up for a thief
aqua cure queen aqua cure queen one shot just to make sure he's dead 140 174 milligrams of cvd oil
okay so i don't know that i don't know this code aqua cure where's this going back out around
side hello all right this brings me i kind of just want to i want to get a layout only there was a
pharmacy nearby if only gosh darn it if only there was a way what's that get up warning keep out
on the uh scaffolding oh i don't think i can do anything with this there's no jump
safe point oh i thought there was a typewriter did i get hurt by that did i get hurt by that
i didn't right no not really gunpowder again uh wait we're gonna combine cancel combine these two
oh we got a mixture when you were saying g and r i thought you were telling me to hold those
buttons down so i let go of the item like it's like weapon drop that's yeah that's what you meant
by that right d plus r not like lol make him drop his gun thank you for the help all right where we
going i've explored everything here if only there was a place called the pharmacy can i kick this
down hey bombs there it is that's why you explore now i can get up here he has no faith in us okay
now only there was a pharmacy okay i'm gonna go to the pharmacy red barrel it's a it's available
good turns out it was a good thing i didn't shoot it before okay we got the donut shop pharmacies
down that looks like a pharmacy to me god damn it i went the wrong way i have to go that way okay
guys that's the universal symbol for one of two things drug container or peanut butter i don't
think there's a peanut butter store down there that's a clearly a like drug icon like a drug
container i don't think it's a peanut butter container saw me do it thank you all right drug
drug drug drug store drug store save the game and i'm gonna store how do i want to do i'll get mom's
knife i can't believe you let brad die and we got combine these i store the gunpowder
let's put this away but put the jewel away too what the hell do i need this one
taking up space brad brad brad this is better store the knife yeah but i need the knife to
slash open boxes all right for a second i thought that was game completion and i was like we're
already 20 of the way through the game i was like that's fucking shocking and then i was like wait
a minute we are 20 of the way through the game that's accurate i'm ready all right now we need
to put the fire out we gotta get up there more like 30 percent
all right i gotta how do i put the i need to get a fire extinguisher hey i looked over here
um let's go down here red barrel the railway all right the rail wait no i'm gonna did i go down
this way yet yeah i did yeah yeah let's go to the railway um red barrel it's like i tried to get
this fire i was trying to like do like i had like a running back play where i go to the left
all right i made it wasd space yeah i know i've been doing it haven't you seen me go
he's behind me isn't it nice na aim i don't want to go in here yet fire hose i'm gonna put this in
my inventory wait hook up the fire hose to the water and spray them and grenade now how these
work gunpowder why don't you just shoot them in the knees is he supposed to hit him shoot him in
the head when you need to use an item to unlock a door so i'll have a puzzle select the item
and then select the use command well i don't think the uh i don't think the party horn thing
that goes is gonna end up doing anything for us so we're gonna go with nothing it might subway
employees memo violence getting worse and worse they've got a shotgun for when it hits a break
it's back there walking it up in the gun rack that should keep it safe for many would-be loot
as well i go and try to find some more shells if things go south cut the chain and bust out
that sucker i pray we make it out alive need to cut the chain the chain i don't have that
uh i don't know why everything is a typewriter that was just a small one
okay let's go this is a pretty hardcore sandwich shop in case you need to get that sucker out of
there are you gonna get up i even said it he's gonna get up this must be the subway company's
offices
everyone hated that of all the things you guys fucking ate that that was really rude
i walked in i would have known it was a subway office okay wait it is a subway office right
the sandwich shop upstairs wait hold on a minute it is a subway shop wait is this a sandwich place
is this a railway station somebody said that you're gaslighting us sometimes it's fun for me
somebody said oh what a what a hardcore sandwich shop but they were they were talking about they
were making a joke but it is it a sandwich shop no it's not okay uh i'm gonna put the fire out now
because uh there's nothing i can do in here i can't like turn the machine on i can get points for
that can't open this so i have to go put out the damn fire he's losing it it was because somebody
was like dude because i in my brain we passed a sandwich place well no it was like a donut place
right and then for some reason i thought i was upstairs there not still in the railroad station
because we may not be in it anymore all right i got the hose let's go don't laugh thinking that
i thought that that was the door okay i need to put the fire out we need water see the donut place
where do i get water i gotta put the fire out down here where is water do i have to run this like
do i have to get a bunch of slack and run this shrunk and okay this is not gonna happen let's
go this way we got no water the water shop can i get down from here no i it's right there all
right do you anybody see any water this is over there right is it like a hose somewhere over here
or like a wall socket for water wait what's over here just wait for it to rain holy shit
how did you guys get up here i gotta get the hell out of here just use i gotta get the hell out
of here now like give me the hell out here i'm i'm running in circles this is the safe room right
okay let me i gotta burn this into memory that this is where the safe is this is important for
me to do okay that's the safe where the safe is all right i need to go i gotta i have to go out
that way i'm not going this way i'm not going all the way around i need to i have to just dodge
oh shoot if i need to the game has you have a gun i can use it nobody gave 50 dollars and i missed
it was palmer palmer thanks for the 5000 bits sorry i was the one guy for the watch through our eyes
sorry i was the one guy for the watch through our eyes i think my internet is messed up love the
streams oh oh okay we got one guide that was like a long okay wait wait wait they're going to pharmacy
oh in the pharmacy i did didn't i yeah i did this i've already been in here but why don't we go in
the pharmacy for what the poster you guys really gotta get your fucking head out of the gutter
that's uh nine three seven that's the code and guess where that safe is well just gonna
fucking lock it in nine three now here's the problem i have to remember how to use a safe
so it's this way first you go nine then you pass the seven you do one full rotation land on seven
and then back to nine back to three back to three what what was the number nine three seven
what did i what did i do all right what did i do nine over three seven no no that's how you do it
that's how you use a safe don't do a full rotation that's how you that's how you open a safe
they wait are they away forgot this game there's a remake fucking like 16 to 20 year old crowd
don't even know what this is you've never seen a dial like this before why would they know that
yeah that's oh yeah that guys if you don't know you actually have to pass the second number in a
full rotation when you open a safe i get yeah it's a remake the red dot sight holy shit really
that's not wrong though that's that's actually true yeah that's how you open up a dial custom part for
the handgun is it on nice oh well there we go i got the first cool unlockable why does everyone
here hate when germa is right because the streamer always has to be wrong i could tell you that
it was five o'clock in the afternoon right now and you'd find a way to make it be incorrect
you'd figure it out it's 5 11 it's 5 12 p.m there you go you've passed the test uh i'm gonna go
down here now i got my red dot sight plug that fire hose in all right fire hose just get just run
just go down whatever you got to shoot somebody you got to shoot somebody at like a probably 60
headshot ratio i think maybe a little bit more okay where's that fire is the fire down here
where's that where's that fire down here isn't it shit yeah let's see on the side it's in the
pharmacy he's got a jello brain cvt brain silent serenity gave 5 000 bits 50 more dollars and they
say thanks to the huge amount of money first of all germa i just want to let you know that it's
okay to be high i'm high and i bet 30 percent of chat is too gamers unite i cannot speak to the
validity of what you just said but i'm not even i'm fine all right so now i need to go down here
streamer admits to doing drugs all right what fire do i need to put out this one drop something
yep you did all right that looks like a fire and you put out all right where's the water hose
fucking stay dead down here supermarket can't open what is this little corner thing over here
can i go in this no so where's this fire out of this supposed fire put out the fire at this
at the station like all the way back to the very beginning my right because they there are no
hose here how to put this out yeah i know oh there by the way if that was real you would fly
you'd the thing would whip you around like in a tom and jerry cartoon in fact this probably been
like old comedy movies where that has happened but like mr bean i all right mr bean probably
has a segment where he's doing a firefighter thing and he flies around when the hose is on
full blast has to be he does of course he does why wouldn't he there's the thing to cut the wires
it's gonna drip feed me this bullshit okay there actually is i i would have i would bet on it
okay i'm gonna store the grenade keep the gunpowder keep the heal keep these up no no i don't
want to store the knife i have to pee so bad i knew i shouldn't have drank like three of these
i'll be right back very quickly it's gonna go pee i am back told you wouldn't be alone
uh does this game have the feature where uh you need to use ribbons is that like is that what
hardcore mode is you need to use the ribbons you actually can't only save once or something
they get rid of that the ink ribbons that was a pain in the ass back in the old games if you
don't know you could only save the game if you had an item in your inventory that there was
a finite amount of them in the game it was a pain in the ass i'm glad we never have to see that
again resident evil 2 remake has ribbons i thought yeah i think so uh this is good
for now i'm going to use that one bullet is someone in here open it up i don't know i just
paranoid brad here you bcs yeah careful careful come on don't look at me like that all right i'm
not an effective no no no wait please what the fuck he was infected he might have been infected
oh stars dissolved i wonder so many of you did and what are you ubcs killing your own people
he would have turned there's your sense of self-preservation hey palmer thanks for the
10 subs go back to the on top of your 50 dollars we don't need a bleeding heart like you getting
in the way a haircut turn the game off game off i here's oh shotgun shells i'm running out of room
all right i need to put these shotgun shells into that burning log four pages too many
i've absorbed it okay we can go up i don't want to go up i want to go back in here because why
would i keep this with me when i don't have a shotgun wait a minute i can cut that all right
hold on no it's all right i'm gonna go up and cut the shotgun out right that sounds like a plan
anybody remember where the hell that was i do not remember where uh that was sandwich shop it was
in the subway station remember the person that made this the sandwich shop reference
but they said this is a heart turn off the film grain there is no film grain uh how i what do
you want me to do here
article quality
i can't talk to you whoever you are um it doesn't it doesn't make any sense
go to display yeah what are you talking about i'm i don't i don't answer the phone on broadcast
everybody knows that all right let me go get the uh donut shop thing and which was in this one yeah
it was that you do i don't when when have i ever answered a telephone on stream all right it was
this way but down into this into the donut shop no where was that shotgun in there i think it's
in there right i think i'm gonna i remember up there there's definitely something to cut here
though i know for a fact one of these yes yes something's something's cuttable here
where is it i know something's cuttable in here shit so i know something was cuttable
really oh are you serious is that actually just wrong here we go got it okay that's there
but wait i'm about to reactivate the power this is progress i don't i don't want to do game
progress i want to go get the shotgun that's upstairs subway here it is progress yeah i'm
getting there okay where is that there you are got it nice m3 shotgun find those bullets
okay four that was a warning shot who they got the shotgun i'm ready to go i'm ready to go down
into that subway i mean i hear shit out here all right was something i can cut in here
oh just that dumb box starting to hear things kind of in the game stop you guys i'm making him
paranoid now i don't want to use the shotgun okay anything else any random no i'm good let's move
red barrel there big bits on from yeses online another 50 dollars in bits that's five ten
this is 250 dollars in fucking bits in the first hour and 10 minutes of the stream thank you all
of you and thank you yes is online for the 5000 and you say glad you're finally getting around
to playing this the weekend it came out i put 40 hours into it and i 100 percented it because i
had so much fun that post game content is based i mean how what do you mean how did i do that
i'll be completely aware of every every single part of fucking small vapors that are around me
thanks for the 50 fucking dollars need to reload how many is this three hand grenades shit and
shotgun shells oh my god what do i do about this i have to leave this stuff here all right back to
the box i'm gonna get rid of the all right back to the box i'm gonna get rid of the um hold on
pick up the shells wait oh you can okay you can have more than all right i don't know why i
thought these are separate stack how much is a stack of shells i thought it was five or 10
okay all right i gotta i can't i can't pick up that grenade but is there anything else i could
even do back here that was it huh besides the grenade okay i'm gonna go get the grenade
with a donut shop dream is not playing the game the way that i want him to
no and i won't like you gotta come in here with some expectations
i just as i have expectations for what i think the game is gonna give me you've got to have
expectations for what you're gonna get out of me okay let's store the get rid of this no keep that
that's gonna come back and bite me in the ass isn't it not taking the knife is just i mean i'll
store this i use it okay that's enough slots to get that grenade and then run back here and
deliver it life is worthless get a vacuum and suck up the zombies um okay luigi let's go straight
here get the grenade put the grenade in the box and move on with our lives here that's all that's
here it's gonna be blue yep okay minus two that was a softball joke don't have no they don't have
to be home run i'm comfortable with this now let's look at the map something something's still going
the donut shop has this bullshit in it i need a key this still needs to be taken care of somehow
up here needs to be taken care of and then the subway station needs to be powered then what the
heck's going on over here go find out so donut shop can't i can't finish this i can't finish
i'll go take a look though just to see what's in here i love this movie did i miss something
over here today is it like done or something or a look at or do all right well then i'm done with
this let's there we go now this area is done oh this is gonna fuck with my add i'm gonna
have to fill all these in blue okay reactivate power at the substation but first go this way
there's this shit in this pharmacy right there's a door i can open it was not blue run an add
i do not i shot you three times no don't shoot it with a shotgun pick it up different but
i didn't want to use it i switched to the handgun i switched to the i my hand you saw that
i can't even pick this fucking thing up why do i have the knife why do i have the knife for
okay blue keep going now back to the uh the station right is there anything else i could
do at the station where's this power i can cut the cut it's not i can't cut it it's a stupid
regular lock damn it this is where i got the shotgun right for your forehead so big uh it's
just the angle of the camera by the way that means i have a huge fucking brain
it means i'm way smarter than you you'll ever be it ain't so much bigger than yours
shit how do i turn the fucking power on where's the only place i haven't gone
your forehead's so big yeah but i think that's a good trait all right i'm gonna go back down
this way shoot it find a couple i gotta find a power grid or something reactivate power at
the substation oh chain door all right let's go do you want help no not yet not yet don't give it
to me yet i will absolutely look over here and go help me please chain door over here help him
you don't have to help me oh don't help me don't do it don't do no no i know where i'm going i'm
just trying to find the way there there's two chain doors don't ever help him well that's a
little mean okay here's the first one no what don't help me help him please no i'm good i found it
fancy box there's another gem in here isn't there okay hold on high grade gunpowder
what the fuck do i have right now you can discard items that have served their purpose
or any of the items marked with this trash mark if i select trash oh i don't need it anymore trash
okay good now i'm i'm good to go discard all items blue jewel i have a red jewel and a blue jewel
okay i can't pick that up so do i am i done with the jewels let me
oh first aid spray too i gotta go back to the i gotta go back to the box and store some stuff
where's the nearest box right here all right hold on i'll be i'm gonna go get the bolt cutters turn
the light off in my room it's not gonna do anything you're a hoarder all right hold on
i'm ditching the knife i'm ditching the jewel i'm coming back here i knew he was there i knew
he was there i just i knew you were there i didn't even come on no oh i'm trying to how long is the
dodge is it take a second let me see you're gonna use the knife oh wait a minute it's a green all
right the home of this all right there's a great wait a minute do i i need to put this a green one
too that's how you get the power back to the station you put all the weird shit in there okay
let's go throw the grenade on let me i'm never taking the knife out ever again okay so um how
many grenades do i have can i not put the red one in oh there we go all right put the red one in i'm
gonna find a green one discard all ammo and play like a real gamer tactical shotgun nice
okay custom part made for the m3 reduces recoil there we go upgrade now i need
a green one fine find the gunpowder store this is another high grade gunpowder in the other store
okay now where is the third jewel right here probably somewhere in there or right here
padlocked door gunpowder first aid spray padlock door i don't know i don't have a
key or anything two simple lock is a monument typewriter well whatever um let's save it
i'm gonna go back and get the stuff am i at caution yeah all right just don't get hit i just
have to go this way and just get this these couple items and then get the fuck out of here
there's a pleb jupiter all right what about did i already go in this store can i go in this store
oh i gotta wrap around here i don't know why even
now let's get this shit i can make shotgun shells now first aid spray yep here it is nothing else
in here we are blue can't open this door subway control room this way okay i got everything i
needed the subway control room we gotta go out and back down around this way right yeah
you haven't turned it on um isn't that where the control room wouldn't be wouldn't it be power in
the control room no one plus i haven't gone this needs to be loud turn it up from what up
turn the game or which one want me to get closer like this i keep going around because i want to
go this way this game is too grainy and cringe sorry oh there he is there's the uh the guy that
owns this place right i'm okay somebody else in here somebody else in here no are there no i'm
losing my mind okay down this way to the control room see if i can do this got one earbud in yes
he does okay so is this something i didn't do in here yet no garage no that's the only place
it's gonna go that way i guess imagine playing games without directional sound omega lull
garage stacom's brain oh when i already in the garage and didn't it didn't wasn't there anything
stacom's brain omega lol stacom's brain that's 100 for your beef what are you eating
back of that box my bunch of chemicals on that box what are you eating stacom's what's in your
wallet hopefully not shaved meat a garage all right let's turn it on power turn the power on
just checking all avenues making sure there's nothing there anything in the dumpster
oh let's check this side handgun bullets and a dead guy and a notebook what does it say uh
i thought i knew it was hell if you're gonna one with 30 guys and it's gonna sit in the
arse all right and we wiped out in this 48 hours holy shit we have a coward i don't care this is
the only way i have left i just hope my body doesn't get back up after i pull the trigger oh
that's that's pretty heavy yeah okay well um thanks for the uh thanks for the uh
four bullets um okay now we go this way wait no can't go that way what's on the wall
electricians notice public use generators provided by raccoon city electricians guild
due to the ongoing power outages the guild has decided to previously provision place a number of
electronic generators throughout the city everyone is welcome to use them but remember these
generators are running high voltage currents if one were to be struck or impacted by gunfire
anyone standing nearby would get electrocuted wink you got that don't go near generators that
spit sparks don't do anything stupid safety first electricity right that's what they look like
okay bye okay any ammo bullets yep oh today you don't have the knife who needs a knife
and you can just do that why i have a knife it's just a slot it's the shit that takes up a slot
all right we're at the generator already sprinting i'm running out of ammo now i
can take a look around anything of interest in here probably but are you
oh fuck it go i carry this i'll come back for it axe from substation chief while employees
in response to the violent outbreaks across the city we have implemented an intentional power
outage once the situation has been brought under control please activate the four breakers
once that's done turn on the main power switch all right intentional power outage
all right let's store i'm gonna store this wait i can combine this
make some shells right oh wait a minute do i make shotgun shells or should i make mag uh ammo
magazine and store it i like shotguns magazine ag ammo oh it's for a magnum right well i want
to be i want to i want to kill the last boss in like 30 seconds so i'm going to store like
50 of those okay put the ammo out okay that's good for now permanent pog oh thank goodness i
was gonna say hopefully that's in this game i was about to be like please god let me have this
okay let's go how do i make a second pile germa poggers coffee poggers cheetos poggers chicken
poggers chicken poggers sounds like chicken nuggets but it's like like 30% rat meat like
i don't know if i would eat chicken poggers if i were you guys all right how do i turn these on
turn on the four switches i have to actually go down there and do this okay oh it smells like oh
i don't even want to think about it all right i got plenty of ammo this is a boss isn't it yeah
it's gonna be the green herbs they work starting to look like chad was never gonna come back from
his round so i poked my headed in there and buck me next thing i know i've got some kind of maggot
squirming down my throat i was gagging and heaving but those little bastards didn't seem to mind none
they just wouldn't come up i was staggering around like a madman then i saw it a green herb
my grandma once told me the green herbs are a natural bug deterrent i grabbed one shoved it
down my gob and swallowed and what do you know the little things didn't want to be in there anymore
i've been so happy to throw up i'm gonna head back out there to look for chad and
anybody who sees this eat your greens okay combine these or should i keep it out just
like that and rub them in my mouth and stuff when i need to during this absolute boss fight
i can't get in here if only i had my lockpick yeah that'd be nice
kernel memo key to the high voltage area has gone missing and the
year earliest we'll be able to get a replacement in the next week a lockpick will be provided to
the senior employee on duty i only have one lockpick and can't afford to lose it please
keep it in its carrying case find the lockpick that shit's gonna be down here i wonder if that's
a lockpick well you guarded it with your life he grabs me i'm gonna be mad because i pre-shot
okay open it looks like a special made case for some kind of tool something's inside open it
okay there's a bunch of locked doors and shit back in the other area uh go back and do those
there's probably stuff in them backtracking andy what you do in this game i'm gonna go at
least get a couple of them because why would i not it's just free shit in there i don't remember
where they are credit cringe keanu reeves what okay there's one right here i remember walking
by it hold on hold on hold on where is it fun do i i'm gonna store some of this stuff for now
but just in case i find some cool stuff backtracking brad what a mega wholesome
buffer yeah i need i want to get these items i don't want to be a fucking dope and not get
the items i need i need to get stuff i'm gonna be so under prepared for the next area if i don't
get some stuff let's check it out look this one right here this is a minigame we're doing
okay oh thank god and gun ammo perfect cool combine gunpowder oh yeah this is why i need
to do this be clear yep all right let's keep going let's get back a little bit more out here
there's one over this way one out this way i just want to get this one what's with the guy
somebody in jail that's a crazy emote combination what the fuck that's insane
okay keep going i need to go this way right all right i just want to open that one door
and then we're just gonna keep going i know why am i going all the way back but like it's
fuck it's like shit i can open okay like this one right here you're padding the game whatever
first aid spray that's a huge deal all right store it store this too wait no yeah no no no no
no no keep them i don't need it right now okay save it inventory gameplay yeah that's that's
resident evil man all right only one more the one that i want to go get is out here it's this door
right there it's like a toy store you guys don't want to go to the toy store of course you do okay
fancy box that's the third gem i knew i was supposed to i knew i should have came back
here let's go put the gem in box art megaman yeah that actually is box art mega megaman isn't
it just didn't i might they might have done something okay bobbing head dolls your charlotte
is gonna explain you shoot them you get stuff this too all right now we get a fun question of
where was that device right there okay we're gonna go back to the subway station where we're
there right put this green gem in dude do the donut shop oh that's right the donut shop has a
locked door right i don't yeah he's padding a short game i'm no i'm just experiencing the short game
out of here okay donut shop here it is open it a hand grenade i don't want a grenade
well if i store enough grenades maybe i'll be able to use them eventually
i have like five already okay what's coming out keep it all in store it all take this green gem
back up to where i needed to go store the shotgun i'm one of my tiny tunes in waiting room that's
tomorrow all right now we just to get back to the station put this green gem in and then i can
call it a chapter one complete that's faster this way he's got 13 saves in the first area yeah
because i'm like i'm a save spammer if i sometimes i save three or four times in the same room before
i leave but i will go back to the machine three times before okay i'm done i'm ready to go so
that's i probably only really saved really like five times what's with this fucking shadow
wait is the sun coming down what the fuck it was just so much turn shadows off this is why
counter-strike pros don't even use them okay i'm gonna heal with one of those sprays
i'm good i didn't even need to do that but i just did anyway hey put the green one in turns out
that was a huge deal nice i have made it to wait oh hell yeah get it open i'll take the shells
anything else i can go down here okay let me hold on save it hold on how many shotgun shells do i
have 13 hey take out a first i have the room for it so take out a first aid spray this is two full
heels make another full heel i'll store i only need two full heels just get scared holy shit
this is boring ah oh no there's nothing scary yet why would i get scared to something that's
not scary nothing scary happened all right this this is the same five nights at freddy's guys this
is like resident evil 3 remake what were you expecting actually resident evil 2 was actually
really scary is that a complaint with this game it might be okay i was down here now what's that
the locked door can i open it with a lock pick potentially is there anything down here that i can
backtrack and look at i sent carlos to clear rubble from tracks
there's a door up here from his brain i wonder if uh there's a lock on it maybe there's something
in here uh oh it's the beginning of the game nice gameplay this is why i was afraid of streaming
this game because i told you for every one person that said this game's kind of cool
like 2000 they're like this game sucks but i'm gonna make my own goddamn case i haven't made
that case yet i'm not ready to say that yet apparently a lot of you are game's kind of cool
all right let's go back to where i was i did it i did i got the extra bonus shit go back to where
i was wear cranky don't eat a fucking snickers go eat something like rice or something go like go
fill up on fucking macaroni that's an ad here it is all right where where the fuck was i going
before i turned if i turned like around it was like no let me go all the way back where was i
going the garage okay it was up here yeah i went all the way back excuse me it was worth it though
i got the extra two slots into the garage walk pick screamer i want to get more items and now
i'm gonna save it here 17 saves in the first area yeah i know go ahead laugh it up already
okay here we are turn the subway station back on watch out for the electrical little sparks
no dogs i got rid of the dogs that's good time for game progress they say save it here 18 saves see
these are unnecessary saves but i need to do them otherwise like wow i don't want to go run through
that if i get hit by him what if i get killed all right it stinks down here yes it does
okay got the items i'm ready here's the lock pick open it probably it's probably gonna be boss
box locks locks and subway rub a green herb said eat a green herb right
get it out oh five i made him into i'll be all right i'll be all right you want to do it
oh i need a green herb just i'll be okay what the fuck is that parasite parasite parasite but i'm
fine use red and green no but that's i don't want to use both all right i'm gonna go back and i'm
gonna take a all right i'm gonna go back and i'm gonna take one of the green herbs up i'm gonna
take both green herbs out i got i want to be efficient just walk it off to save scum yeah
whatever i want to do it efficiently why am i alive what he's doing holy shit that was insane
no what are you doing i wanted to go from oh my get back in the room just climb up the stairs
and go in here and go open the box and eat it this is just just make it to the bathroom okay
all right we're good see i didn't have to use a full heel on that all right we're good i'll
save it right here let's go i think this is a shotgun time no it's not it's an electricity time
all right i'm fine i gotta turn the power back on that was a real stacom's idea wait how long
does it last for i'll just take it whatever we know you want to save scum it's a shotgun level
here i'm i'm using the shotgun i'm it's a shotgun level i'm gonna use it i'm gonna make sure i use
it well i'm not fucking around right now one out of four circuit breakers i ain't fucking around
right now get shotgun out all right no more shotgun is it gonna land on my head from up here
oh gross okay keep going goddamn maze why am i using the shotgun on these guys they take
where'd he go because it's a shotgun level two out of four you're gonna come through the fucking
wall aren't you two out of four let's go where'd he go we're gonna come this way they're gonna be
right here stop making thing noises aim better dude na aim by the way i've been pretty good
come on i've got these fucking lightning reactions come on out okay i'm fine where it's gonna get
over there where's they blend in with the background i don't think about anything about it don't move
okay i gotta be careful i gotta conserve ammo wait electricity explosive here i'm willing to
shock myself wait how do i get this last one i gotta go over here all right this is here comes
behind me behind me something behind me something behind me turn it on uh turn it on is it a full
moon tomorrow it might be it was full moon today all right get the hell out of here leave it's a
shotgun level i think you little shit how many more are there leave me the fuck alone mine caution
i am i don't want to use a healing herb though because oh fuck all right let's get out goodbye
ammo oh yeah i mean what was i not gonna shoot him i'm not fucking around i don't want to die
where is it where is it where am i going um the exit chad uh those strange bugs building their nests
yeah yeah yeah bosses i can't leave till i drop all the breakers oh we already did this so i gotta
go out this way okay worm brain so then we're just what bang a left and okay i gotta follow the road
here right down this way and then hang a right and just go straight bye all right okay turn it on
okay that leaves us the main power switch nemesis is going to break down the door three two enjoy one
here we go i'm ready for it this time okay subway is good uh i'm gonna take this heel out
okay let's keep the gunpowder in there now this is fine i'm in caution but you know whatever
it's not ready i mean i'm definitely ready carlos it's jill i've restored power to the subway
that's all critical information it should be in the subway company's offices right i think i know
the building not your partner bring the trains online in the office yeah i know where that is
i know where that is all the way back here burn apologize what by the way that's the third time
that i've looked over a chat and a scary thing happened can you get in wait he can cut he can
come in the doors just walking in normally all right here we go this is where it's
oh he no he's he's coming back we don't hear footsteps what is in here this is the part
where i turn around there's like a fucking dragon's mouth behind me just like ready to just close and
kill me no no no don't need that put the door all right where do i gotta go through the garage down
to the subway station call the police please you can't help me it's after me
not until i get traffic control online okay she did call the police that's true okay
what do i need here i might need some more gunpowder here or i can make these into now i
need them go i mean you got to do what you have to do take out a grenade oh yeah i can throw it at
nemesis i'll take how many grenades can i have in one stack all right i'll take out all three
grenades how do you use a grenade i know that that's a really dumb question i'm talking about in this
game what's like the protocol to throw the grenade is it cook tilt throw how does it work is there
am i gonna get like a like a golf game thing that shows how far it's going how does it work
okay i need to remember where i gotta go this way oh fuck is that him what did you just do
all right i'm good where's the grenade how do i throw a grenade i need to throw a grenade g
doesn't do anything e what did it work he dropped he dropped a crate what's in the crate
holy shit i got a supply kit all right run he's gonna get back up what do i need to go fuck i
don't remember what's it where stop calling me uh subway station yes open the case dude a case
opening right now all right let's go extended magazine for the handgun nice okay now i'm gonna
heal bring the trains online in the subway office subway office is this thing down here that's the
station the office is up here right i don't fucking remember i have to go up it's right here right
that's the office right there right this is the office right here we're gonna go through the
donut shop okay bye and then right and there we go it's up here good thing i didn't shoot
that fucking red barrel turn it on credit funko pop yes sure all right let's turn this shit on
oh he's in chat who me i'm of course i am i'm the streamer is there a safe thing in here
please get out of chat oh i'm not gonna okay let's get this subway station on
oh carlos i'm in the control room now what okay give me a sec i'll open it open it's a
shotgun shells but okay how are we doing on bullets 14 shotgun 18 33 25 i'm good on bullets i need i
got some health here so we're good i was gonna turn this shit on plan a route all right where
are we heading the train has stopped at redstone street we need to reach fox park station
i'm super cop consider it done okay so we please enter our route president evil rest safe unable
to establish route please try again okay uh we need to go from re where's re re is um re one
redstone one two uh f is it fa2 what do you mean what's all these numbers for fa2 if we go
top left down to fa2 that's blocked let me go there between fa2 we go to raccoon center station
no we don't you go to yes we do raccoon center station wait no one to it before right no no this
works raccoon center station and that's number one and that'll go down here to saint michael's
clock tower which is saint michael's two ended fo i didn't do it well show me if i have oh
oh no there's different okay are re1 i need fa fa2 then op is a little dark write it down re1
to fa2 to ra2 no no ra3 ra3 to need to get to s no ra3 that's down to sa2 and then sa2 to fo1
ra3 so2 can't change the bottom one though i have to do some three goes uh okay hold on i can only
change three of these so where's re we start okay wait no no it's like dark up there it's dark up
there listen okay we start on our i got it that's dark up there i was gonna say i didn't like i'm
fucking i can't it's no it's blacked out okay so re we need to just replace these fa2 goes up here
ra1 oh no sorry yeah ra1 and then what's this next one uh all right so ra3 sa1 okay good sa1 ra3
okay go for it all right three two sa2 go for it hello it's me i finished inputting the subway
i didn't i didn't see the top part back to the station turn to the subway station watch out for
the guy right outside the fucking front door let's plug us open your mouth open oh well i don't mean
holy shit you're sucking out all my intelligence not much to take yeah okay bread uh back to the
subway station we're gonna go down here we are here around this thing up around oh wait i can
shoot you in the back oh you son of a bitch oh you mother oh you don't stand up and have a
thing on your head i thought that was shotgun shells just diapers down to the station this way
down to the station this swarming with people over there i could just fucking ran
wait he's just oh hi oh i forgot i was chasing you i went up the worst possible way oh look at my
head let go of my head shut up game you're not gonna luigi me i'm not gonna have you do with a
luigi oh it looks like you're having some trouble let me take over please don't luigi
okay out this way bye all right excuse me fucking holes you're gonna have in your leg
all right give me the grenade now i'm ready by the way i thought i had four
no i had three i had three we go there's a cut scene then throw a grenade what i don't
what's the point of the dodge doesn't dodge doesn't even dodge it just it makes you move
slightly differently for a second let him dodge am i going box buddy he drops a box every time
wait he drops a no i gotta get the fucking loot i got it i got it i got it i got it i got it all
right i got it run get out of my way run run run run run run run run run run excuse me all right
wasted i got it all right what's in this box custom part for the handgun in addition to dampening
sound but also tightens the firing pattern for greatest chance of crits imagine if i didn't pick
that up all right i got it all right we're good save it here take knife take knife take the knife
take the knife take the knife take the knife take the knife take the knife guys are gonna get me
killed you got you're gonna get me killed why is the shotgun smaller than the handgun weird i'm
ready don't listen to chat and i'm what am i listening i'm not listening to chat it's a
foldable shotgun nice job super cop i'm impressed we back in business yeah mostly
but we need 30 to 40 minutes to finish maintenance nicolai how are we doing status report scrolling
with those freaks no chance of fighting aware of the city why is she here she's helped me get
the trains running again bedtime to start what's going on with the hair you think he's talking about
can't pull the trigger when it counts hey take it easy she'll get you killed
sorry about that everyone's a little worked up okay not again he's back it's me he's after
hey i'll buy you some time hey wait wait joe no damn it lure the creature is that car wait
where the fuck did he come from i thought i thought that was i thought he was punching me in the back
like cover the fuck up and get in there and run you want just don't taunt him just run away
you want is he dropping drop a box give me a box i want loot that's what you do right
leave me alone you creepy ass stalker you want stars i'll give you stars it's like a hundred
i don't even know where the fuck he is man
yeah stalker you want stars i'll give you stars does he drop something or not where the fuck am i
okay um this might work give me that crate over the fucking door why are you taking it with you
oh no that's okay turn the gas on whatever this is oh it's a big door okay am i safe carlos do you
copy find a way above ground i can try heal yourself fucking heal i don't need it right now
i'm on caution caution doesn't mean heal caution means you're fucked if you don't heal soon
not right now but soon what caution is oh the case how many 12 six i need more handgun ammo
i want to get rid of the fucking knife so bad i know it's probably i should get rid of the
dumb knife or this till i find a green herb
uh that's gonna come back to haunt me i know throwing that away
okay uh we're gonna play you respond to it the recoil we got the sewers map
let's find a way perfect okay let's go all right gotta go have fun thanks for sticking around
i why is there always have to be a sewer i hate sewer levels they really are the worst
nobody ever says oh boy a sewer level that's a little shortcut eventually a big um big slot
for something but looks like it needs a power source big power battery increased sewer security
we've been receiving reports of unauthorized personnel in the control areas of the facility
in response we're replacing the aging mechanical locks with new protocols we need a battery pack
they would be battery packs to open these doors where does that leave us that leaves us with going
at just down here now i'm gonna turn the light on in my room not off i'm definitely burning these
to be bugs down here probably right straight up some kind of animal animal bug hybrid
shotgun level okay so it's a shotgun level it's just a sewer alligator yes it is still have the
items oh no i'm good all right i got a battery pack before i fall down this nothing over here
i can't grab anything no it's just a goldfish that's just how big they get okay let's try this
again this time shotgun in the face is there a gun symbol on the ground over here oh hand grenade
oh let's go equip it all right yeah let's try it here we go too early how do you throw a grenade
too early it what do you mean it blew up the whole hallway there's two ways to go here
was to get the grenade in the mouth really oh whatever i'll remember that for next time
close to b combined with explosive thanks for the fucking tip i'm with explosive a to create
flame rounds or combine with another b to make acid rounds right they come in handy especially
when i hoard them all till the very last moment in the game and use every single round of acid spray
on the last boss oh just kidding i left it in the storage box i'm using the default handgun to end
the game ooh grenade launcher that's pretty sick hold on invoice from the gun shop thank you
purchasing the xxxxxx we're in the future this is welcome to what every graphics card is going to
have to start doing in like 200 years when we're on like generation 80 of nvidia gpus what are they
going to do start over at zero like a thousand times i think they're going to drop the numbers
in the names all together it's going to be it's going to go by year i don't know i'm actually
confused as to why they don't do that already like you know the nvidia g force 2020 like a car like
yeah i know what a g force 1995 is like i know what a car that's like you use cars why don't
they just call them by car name why i don't understand why do they have to add like rtx 2180
no no no just it's 2020 it's a fucking 2000 it's a bit things are not in great shape but it's all
right it's got a few miles on it it's a fucking like 2013 nvidia g force gonna get the kelly
blue blue book value god okay explosive resistance yeah i know how to do this only one graphics card
per year well no even if they didn't have one come up for like a couple years it would still
just be like the 2022 the nvidia g force 2022 they're gonna do that eventually they're gonna
get so sick of fucking naming shit uh do i bring this this is too big it's huge i feel like i might
need it though i'm gonna bring it yeah i'll bring it i got two heels uh ammo ammo lockpick and then
the super grenade launcher i have two rounds in it two flame rounds okay good to know hopefully
i don't accidentally use that research log which are the water and ph level is not that great
this might be something there's something in the water apparently all right let's go let's find a
way back out so what does this do for me i gotta go back to the split keep the shotgun out i want
to get these two killed it's gonna pop out one of these which hole is he gonna come out of that's
the guess none he's just gonna be down the hallway hey hey hey hey holy shit these guys suck real
wink shot it with his mouth i shot it one time with his mouth closed i didn't know i had to be open
fuck i don't like this what's that who splits again okay
oh i thought i was done right there that was horrible still at caution okay i just gotta make
it to a what's this coffee cups flame rounds hot coffee there's another this splits so i gotta
remember that any of the bullshit over here i would love a save point fantastic give me a
save point in here well you and i will be so happy battery pack i don't touch that yet because it's
gonna summon you know who the love letter my beloved hunter gammas really superior i think
that's the thing that we're fighting right now i'm gonna make uh shotgun shells i think i think i
brought this oh explosive a hold on a sec explosive a i'm making i'm making shotgun shells
i want them i'm a shotgun user make acid rounds people happy um we'll see i have to be very
careful here because i'm gonna touch this and then something to break the door down and i
have one safe point go this thing is huge why is it that big i gotta have to take one of the heels
um i'm just gonna go to full health that's the worst that happens okay here we go oh you have a
rare lucario oh wait that's a reference to the second video game from last year or two years ago
i get that reference actually yeah i can hold on a minute my space cams gotta get a little brighter
i'm kind of just i'm just silhouetted out here let me help you out here all right you can see me
uh good uh i'm ready to go you can see me right what the fuck can happen to the guy in the corner
wait what is this wait what is that why is it listed as something i didn't touch
oh that's why oh i used the full heel and this is just sitting here all right i won't i won't i
won't i won't fine i'm just gonna block i was gonna just get rid of nine rounds okay i gotta
be very careful what shot is right in the fucking mouth why what oh thank god it's an auto save
nice tuber thumbnail yeah i just like pulled a quarter from behind your ear and i was like
look at that wow sonny can happen again i gotta fucking just stop talking how do i skip this skip
skip skip skip use the grenade no i want to keep those rounds they're fucking very valuable
i have to do good shotgun shots but i've only have four what if i when nemesis shows up i gotta
kill nemesis with this thing open your mouth oh he's dead for a second i thought he wasn't
safe for the final boss that's what i'm saying i gotta say i want to be able to shoot the final
boss like 15 times with a grenade they're not even at the final boss okay explosive a and explosive b
i can make um flame rounds i use flame rounds or should i get the other ones i get acid
wait for explosive c and get acid that's fun uh battery's about to be gone bullshit in here
i don't have any mother uh all right i gotta get that herb and make a big herb then dump this
battery pack stacom's hair now just start banning people start banning them just and and and make
sure when you're in your band message you say and don't ever come back all right like in all
capitals okay go get the herb combine it it's gonna run back and forth in circles and shit
hopefully i don't think anything else is gonna spawn why would it it would be very really sad
if it did then i have to use another one of these that would be very sad sponsored by stacom no it's
not it's not you just took a freeze frame from every uh commercial from somewhere in the mid
90s when the product was very very very sour i was in the middle of like just just just like
changing and and and into a like fruit based person like my head was about to turn into like
a weird strawberry or something it's a pretty good freeze frame okay pick this up bring it back to
the box back tracking just never-ending backtracking the game i know that's what
we're playing you knew what you were getting into when you signed up for my weekly newsletter
padding padding padding padding padding it's not padding it's just the game adding parry
i don't even is that a name parry's not a name harry matthew parry no um a last name but like
who's what is her first name that's parry not like barry parry p a r r y percy no that's not
that's not what we said we said parry harry potter you motherfucker okay let's get this
shit out of here combine with open the fucking door door this temporarily take this out combine
you and you i'm gonna keep this because i'm about to get two slots now two full heels
a little bit of ammo lockpick and i need it i'm gonna okay battery goes in let's go save it
blueberry parry you guys saying parry p e i'm sick i'm saying pa rockin shows with no shotgun
what why is there no shotgun in my hand you and why it's so small it's freaking me out every time
harry was the 14th president you're a dumb screamer no dude no dude no dude his name
parry what's it short for like bernard all right hold on now i gotta go here because
barry short for bernard bernard bernard what is barry short for it's it's like bernie bernard
barry potter uh open this please thank you shit how many can i how many are here
two i gotta come back for that shit you gotta eat yeah you gotta eat all right i know all right
all right right right right right right right right right now i just gotta go back
turn this shit on find a way out of here your hair different no it's just looks it just looks
bad because i haven't had a haircut in like four months here we go put the battery in excuse me
i'm not clicking on any more links after this one your last link of the evening
your last link it's pretty good it's a really good one it's i'm glad i clicked it because it's
very good so sour man put this thing in wait did i even examine over here yet
yeah i went up there before okay look at it oh my god that's actually kind of disgusting
wait what's disgusting wait this isn't even the right door wasn't there another door yeah there
was another door that i could use this with yes yeah there's another door down here wasn't there
probably something good in there your hair looks like wood yeah this is the manager's office right
shit wait how do i can i get i can i get up there i can't get up there no i can't i have to do this
i have to yeah i have to go through it ah don't change the subject your hair looks like wood
does i mean it it's a little hard but i wouldn't say it's wood wood head dude you put you get like
one harsh direct light on your hair and all of a sudden you may as well be a cartoon character
open show show i don't feel like showing the shelf i'm not going to show the shelf
sorry not showing the shelf um what is that wait is it did the nemesis leave me like a
present on the ground can't go in there this can i pull this open all right now this is open now i
can take you out between the other door well let me just check over here see what's over here oh
hooray now i'm gonna go oh wait i don't know um should i get the thing that was in here first
this is the manager's office right wait there's this one all right open this one
special edition funko germa oh this looks like the way out i don't want this yet
it is back adding this stuff up here in this room i want to get it although guys i'm going
to be so absolutely useless if i don't like get items in rooms what do you want to lose
imagine if i didn't pick this up oh my goodness explosive a and it's going to be probably a
save point here too right uh gunpowder that's it okay good i got the extra hip pouch the saving
sally now we can leave now i am comfortable leaving this area everybody said fire hose has
one inventory slot a dinky battery is two budge power source give me the fucking ghost busters
ghost container that thing was so i used to want one of those things so bad a little thing where
they slide it in and the in the ghost gets stored why haven't they made a they they did make a decent
ghost busters game for mine that's still a long time ago though is it like 2007 a long time ago
all right epic game store exclusive can you hear me now yeah i'm alive i lost him they remastered
i'd love a new ghost busters game that just had nothing to do with the movies
and all the ghost busters games and go they just want to tie it back to the movies
it's got to be part of the movie friend no just have a ghost busters game and have to be
talking was talking interruption what's that hey what do you know come on down
give me my free shit no can use weapons close the app fuck i was right whatever lesson learned
lesson learned like get this thing out of my sight take the grenades all right we're good
store these pick this shit up do i have any other things to combine it with
i could do explosive i'm making yeah i can do let's do it i have a lot of a's let's make an
explosive round don't eat it three explosive rounds cool i'm gonna store it i don't think i
needed we gotta wait for the fucking boss big boss i'm happy with this keep the lock pick i
got two heels and then when i find a red one combine it or another green one will do too
that's fine i thought there was a fucking typewriter it looks like a typewriter
every time ready like just walking in the room what do you see in the cat that's a typewriter
right there he missed the master sword i think i'll be all right anything else in this room
jeremy jeremy master knife is he upstairs downstairs there he is this whole place is
lighting up on fire do it could have jumped that i probably could have jumped it okay the above me
how uh hot hot hot hot i don't get time to fucking look at items um let's take it notice of
demolition delay decided to delay
want to be office building demolition in response to the ongoing public can i get my elbow and my
arm rest please uh ongoing public unrest for safety reasons all electrical equipment including
generators have been moved to the roof entry to the premises is prohibited until the current it's
all on the roof head to the roof okay i'm ready to go i'm stacked up there he is you want another
eat this shit got him box did you drop a box still kicking
give me the box okay good thing i brought the explosive grenade
holy shit i'm on the regular game mode
and then nemesis okay i just got an achievement that says nemesis down with a question mark
he's not dead guys that's not even the fucking real boss
it's gonna be a big boss fight coming up here there's gonna be like a bunch of
bullshit that i have to do carlos it's jill do you read me yeah bastards dead
it worked it worked don't start i did what i had to the subway is ready to go back to the
subway dude i've moved on from that uh do i climb up on top of this sub uh ammo somewhere what was
that there's ammo down here so you don't know how to climb back down how do you not know how to climb
back down back to we're going back to the other side be easy un-shop turn off your pc jambo quick
there's a i can't open it wait the lock that's every single video game you can shoot the lock
every single one that's every single video game b herb a semi-auto barrel that works
i will definitely take it designed for semi-automatic fire m3 shotgun is now
oh now it takes up two slots now i get it that's good but not good at the same time
is there a safe point in here not immediately uh
kendo you're all right you're all right it's a stretch only loads your shotgun
didn't know quite what to expect no shit look we're using the subway to get people out of town
you win subway well that's good thinking when we get out there's gonna be a lot to do
we could use a man of your skill set for the party what's wrong nothing just uh just bad
timing is all look um don't worry about me i'm gonna make other arrangements okay
you better you're the best gunsmith around oh no don't do anything stupid oh that's that's
your job right huh people still like make guns by hand take care jill if you're heading the best
gunsmith service the shop okay the keys hanging on the wall okay yeah i need to i gotta combine
these there's a red one right out there no wait wait wait wait wait there's a red one right there
what am i at am i at fine you hear me out i'm gonna take this one i'm gonna combine with the
red one out there let's check and see if i missed anything in it okay okay i had to do that anyways
now what have i got for bullshit i got so much bullshit i'm gonna combine these flame rounds
oh handgun ammo now i can do what i wanted to do go to the door the door the door the door
what are you talking i'm i'm just getting my inventory ready i'm getting my inventory
like corrected and ready the door lock pick the door wait hold on a second i'm um dude i've got
items to get through hold on for the bomb i'm just i'm just i'm taking a one moment flame rounds
again let's play can this hold it's gonna hold six rounds uh door what door what door what
what do you want to do with you what you're gonna miss it what am i gonna miss i
i don't how do i know things that i'm gonna miss if i don't know they exist in the first place
i'm gonna miss i missed it i don't even know what i was he was like all right it was like it was
like daddy yeah i'll take care of you my my girl right and i just thought it was just the npc
random ai dialogue behind the i thought that was just like all right let's hunker down here
sweetheart end conversation npc says three words well i mean i am going back for this
open no heart i got stuff i got shit is that one time use how did you let that happen
i shot him like one two three i'm not gonna let that out here is that fucking herb where's the herb
where's the herb what's it doing in this box take it out save it here just in case i need to do it
again wait the door all right take two kill this guy no don't even just run by him pick up the herb
and get the fuck out of here oh get the fuck out and shit i gotta have to shotgun this guy
no you're not accidentally shoot a fucking grenade in here we're upset because germa missed the
chance to save them all right now you're gonna spoil resident evil 3 remake excuse me hey
i'll go upstairs under the bed raccoon times i'm writing to you because i'm troubled deeply
troubled anyone who's been a parent knows that the crystal promenade is the place to take your
kids for a trip downtown on saturdays there's no more and there's no store more popular or harder
on a parent's wallet than toy uncle however i've noticed that on windy days the big statue above
the entrance wobbles like the only thing holding it up is a couple of screws and that statue's
head tumbles loose one day children will be hurt i've complained about this many times glad i've
took the time to read this one i'll take it i got tons of rounds in the snow i thought that was a
fucking tongue coming down to like grab me by the shoulder oh it's just a ceiling fan we're good
that is going into timeout mode uh-oh shut him up shut him up take a deal with you
where we at herbs yes herbs that's right crash back to the fire truck now look at this funny
link i made he's back now he has a different weapon what is this why does he have all these
cool things he missed holy shit your aim is bad i thought this guy's supposed to be like a super
mutant did i just dodge it oh man uh you guys think my aim is bad are you calling me
they might be more than one carlos wow nemesis holy shit man uh like a three-year-old can hit
somebody this close give your brother the controller trust me it's a bad look they are any
am i dead or is that supposed to happen never just give mr rex the controller that's good
i'm doing danger but anymore he's still chasing me wait just going up here again
ignored the spray she snorted some herbs and now you're good as new that's kind of what happens
and lead him right to you it's okay trust me okay back to the station so we gotta go down
here as we gotta go left left right left left right he is really bad
it was really bad he didn't even mean to do that he doesn't even see his name on the kill feed he
wasn't even looking he holds down tab in like fucking 20 minutes and goes how did i get like
30 points what the fuck did i even do i was just spamming down the same hallway i guess i heard
hit markers at random times but i don't know the fuck i was doing go my safe it doesn't roll back
right no hello it's okay he's fucking terrible but i'm not is he good is he dead give me my
box i can't believe he hit me why i want the box i'm loot hungry god damn it i know how this works
skip this oh fuck okay this electrical box right here it's gonna drop down i'm gonna shoot the
electricity box and i'm gonna run it's gonna drop down i'm gonna get like can i hear the
star shoot where is he it's me sir can you he's behind me shoot him why would i shoot
the guy in front of me you okay go get in the safe place get it let's get out of here
uh tag team now cool tag team reload this do i have no i oh i can switch the rounds okay
let's go what a chad of a sim carlos i know we didn't get off to a great start that doesn't
make any sense thanks for the safe hey you saved my ass first you're a hell of a lot braver than me
well what matters is that we can get everyone out of the city now simp chad you'll be safe what
about you from the side where you go i won't be catching the train why not there'll be new orders
if it means i can help save the city i was really hoping for a
hey carlos has died and then get a start from that point didn't happen oh well good work your
reputation is well deserved get inside the subway is about to leave carlos tyrell you have your
orders you need to go back out into the city and find nataniel part this isn't the last ride out
right do not worry once the civilians are safe the train will be back it's all right you're going
ahead i'm not gonna die on you and leave you in a cold cruel carlos's world okay so we leave you'll
need to find this scientist his vaccine research could save us all wave goodbye to them say bye
everybody you see you're learning you're the only life that matters is your own good luck
let's go bye guys it was fun september 29 2 a.m in the subway car you don't really think a pencil
pusher like part of the still alive do you i haven't done good authority this is the turn
the hill turn right
why are they russian well um you can very easily replace any interesting potential
character with they're a russian guy they're gone come this way nicolai what are you doing
it's not after you i'm russian we're evil in all games how could you not have seen that
get off my train shit barred up escape from the city complete this is the later on meanwhile wow
subway's gotta be clear of the city by now along with your hot date i don't know it's weird like
soap opera um like filming style why is this soap opera this is like this is a set this is not even
like a real was the weird transition there and then just right up the close-ups keep your head
screwed on release station you sure looks like a cemetery to me oh it's not funny it's not funny
i'm sorry i i was gonna scream zombies and and i i lost five bullets who cares i'm done
let's go game on game on game on t what about all my items there he is not you too
shit it's locked
you stay on the door i got this fucker no brad come get some
oh got him id card these stars wait i'm being a real lip fighter right now
stop doing that i gotta put on my anti lip biting oikman this is really what this is for
because then if i do it it'll be gross and i'll go ugh and i won't do it
nintendo switch cartridges oh this is from the second game remember no no don't care we got a
job to do if our intel's still worth a damn then bards in the star's office let's find him and
take him into custody custody i have your gun i thought this was a rescue so we're back to the
um to the police station alt rifle okay g18 hand gun take a look at this i've located the star's
office remember bard had access to umbrella's darkest secrets brad why they're saying to keep
him under our thumbs i think brad like that our mission is really more like find and detain it's
like malicious compliance there was a typo good to know i'll open the shutter so you can get
through you stay here and find out what's been going on here at the station call you if i find
anything predator hey be careful yeah you too does that mean mr x shows up here okay so uh here we go
find dr bard go to star's office saved it and take everything i need here we go
what's this uh the key for this key wait oh they've upgraded why do we go from
we went from locked with a key to locked with a key card each member of the force has been
issued an id card from now on the same card we require to access all storage boxes don't lend
your card to anyone so this is just the key what's this uh some kind of note take my help
hello what the hell was that thing i know what it is i played the second game
yeah i hate these things too bow couldn't have been a zombie but open this fucking door oh right
this hasn't been opened yet in leon's playthrough didn't stick around that's gone here we go
it's one zombie don't psych yourself out man and that didn't kill it that happy cake day here's
an upvote stop i didn't like that website big warm rp welcome okay this is the operations room
something in here it's on this table oh flash grenade i'm gonna use that on nemesis
thing that's in here that is all right i wish carlos had his own game kind of is his own game
isn't it his game he shares it with somebody else t wait i'll just hold on there's something
real nasty in here i don't know what it is game's over in like an hour when you when you play as
carlos isn't it like that's like the second like into the second half of the game right
or like two oh and open this to unlock it the lock is right in front of you it's right there
unlock it unlock it i don't even know what i'm where i'm supposed to go west office here we are
thought rifle scope now it's more accurate i have plenty of ammo right punch zombies as carlos
oh that's cool doing that who's doing that he's dead you open the fucking door close the door
let's go in here all right grab the um there's a safe in here uh i played the last game like
two years ago what was the safe password on nine eight five it's gotta be like on a note
somewhere how are you guys still getting up yeah all right i'm running i need to go to uh i'm
gonna go over here and open this door can't open this door yeah welcome leon bet you had a kick
ass first day oh okay he he kind of didn't all right is that everything i can really do in here
besides the safe safety deposit room dark room oh it does okay so that leaves the dark room all
right this is so dark in here i mean don't answer that i know it's a dark room but like it was very
dark exceptionally dark right uh office supply internal relocation heat resistant three number
combination safe moved from star's office to the west office left nine right 15 left seven
nine fifteen seven nine fifteen seven let's store these for now
till i get another herb turn this on if cameras killed those things i'd be set right okay nine
15 what was it 15 oh that was fucking extreme reaction time he's safe is what was it nine
left nine i went okay just get out nine fifteen that makes me happy okay now we need to go upstairs
wait a minute press report the explosives collected from the suspect's person and
residents appear to be extremely powerful as a safety battery was removed from one detonation
device upon its admission into evidence the battery was secured in a safety deposit room
okay i was really late to come in here get away from me sicko oh candy that's coffee never mind
fucked up shooting cops oh ah green herb i'll take it need to get let's go back and make a
heal full heal am i going the right way yes how could you not like this game uh i see what you're
doing there it's uh it's it's good i don't hate this game we'll see in another couple hours
we'll see how i feel in like another hour or two i know probably gonna get attacked
copy that it is up ahead no to a friend if you're reading this i'm already dead if you hear any
noises coming from the locker do not open it uh while you're on patrol i focused on finding
a way to get to the other side i realized that explosives might be our best bet i rigged up a
pretty good bomb but we don't have any batteries sent one to the safety deposit room right we need
that battery if we're gonna knock this wall down so i headed upstairs to find you then no you have
the safety deposit room we had five with five subs just come in yes they did from curly boy
thanks curly boy appreciate the five subs better not uh this is i wouldn't have this info nobody
in the shower electronic gadget okay guess we'll be doing this the explodey way wait why would i
how would i take this just keep it there i have to get the batteries for it anyways right why
i even carry it like i put batteries in it and put it on there right why don't i just bring the
batteries up here i have the inventory space okay let's go into the star's office fuck's sake
why is it blocked so the only way to get in is i gotta go up and get the okay yeah we gotta
blow through the fucking wall i get it get the key from the guy go get the thing battery bring it up
here below the oh i got another key oh rifle ammo um not the key ban me i even looked at him for a
second i looked at him okay let's go open up the safety deposit room get the battery out i'm in
caution right now fuck save it first do i have any more heels and this one and i there's a red
herb in there i'm gonna take it out i know i'm gonna be in a scenario where i'm gonna i'm gonna
really want this shit let's go suck at this game laugh my ass off what was the name of the thing
that i just was trying to open up there started with b bye bye i pressed m to look right when
the jump scare happened oh bye bye if i got banned from a channel and the streamer whoever was
did that was like oh bye bye you know i'd be like i fucking hate this guy i would wouldn't that
wouldn't you be like oh fuck this guy fucking dick oh wow you oh look at you you're so strong
and powerful here in your stream oh bye bye dick that's why i i no what was i doing right i got
oh right let's let's rewind it uh into the storeroom i wish i had my shotgun
bye bye okay where is this battery 106 one oh wait that's the battery just a regular ass duracell
nice entrance dude okay anybody else in here that wants to cause a fucking problem before i start
opening doors 108 has nothing 203 has nothing all right the code is 104 and 106 thank you battery
ammo 109 grenade and no uh key card for this oh it's still stuff there's something in here still
but still in here apparently something else in here oh let's go over them
oh dcm third floor locker let's go do it break through the glass save it save it save it save
it save it healed right here i told you i was gonna need this okay i'm gonna switch to the
handgun man i have so much handgun ammo i'm okay with this i want to use it anyways all right save
it everybody has weed everybody has weed whether i did or i didn't the las vegas now marijuana is
100 legal it's legal in the state in the city of las vegas didn't know third floor was it dcm
what was it uh what what what was it de saronne on the rocks not really worth it 20 bullets he
lives in las vegas yeah he's definitely high excuse me all right let's go put the battery in
you're committing a felony well um committing a felony in the jurisdiction of my state
i reside he is actually high when when when when when where i mean i take i take a little
bit of cbd for pain just a little just just a little this thing is this thing's done
ration let's move admission we already talked about this like yesterday got grow up all right
guys grow up all right we're uh we need to go uh up uh down up down up second floor and then over
here put the battery into the men's room i'm gonna get stuck with some guys copy that we get it do
we know what that lockers all right battery time detonator cbd let's go it's not safe
uh you stood right next to the blast man that's like not the place you wanted to be
hey hey get whoa the time take a number oh he's got comedy dialogue i like it
okay can we stop this now please first date's way okay it's all right good now into the office
watch out there's gonna be i have a knife on me
that you're not gonna get up right i got a big gun i'm gonna go all the way to the end of the
hallway and it's gonna be a mistake no it was good fine i let me in i know i did the germa
could hog this hard i won't believe it dr bard oh thank god do you know how long i've been trying
to reach somebody don't worry we're gonna get you out of there just tell me where you are
i'm trapped in a goddamn hospital surrounded by every kind of abomination
but just send in stars they're gonna know what to do now negative rpd is overrun too then figure it
out wow umbrella's gone crazy they're killing all the researchers i'm the only one who knows
how to make the vaccine to stop the zombies so you can either sit there with your dick in your hand
or send send somebody who's capable of getting me the hell out of here i like him already yeah you
would you heard what he said we can't turn him over to the company that's not our call to make
that's mihiel's call i'm gonna check the computer see if i can trace the doc's location
what do i do he didn't give me instructions this will take some time look around see if
you can find anything useful this screen just went flash grenade wait did i make oh i can't i
made the pc joke last game two years ago i can't do it again that would be not that would be bad
that would be not funny it would be stupid 50 bullets holy shit that's a lot of ammo so see if
i can find anything useful while he hacks the computer hey i think i found something report
on the mansion july 23rd bravo team was dispatched to the mountains to investigate a series of
grisly murders they went radio silent incident culminated in the destruction of the mansion
there were numerous casualties however all evidence was destroyed along with the mansion
no further investigation was it was very difficult to do that is that jill in the front row aim on
aim on all right i'm going aim on for fuck's sake now anything else useful in this place
uh storage box well i can destroy this or uh i'm gonna store one of the first aid kits
the flash flash grenades are kind of good they work out pretty well i have looked everything here
so i can't do anything else so i guess i'm just gonna leave good luck back to the shower room
can you say happy birthday to john hey john happy birthday john yeah yeah it was john yeah yeah
jill oh shit what happy birthday to you john jill what happened jill come in t i gotta go do what
you gotta i'll take care of barden new day new day several minutes earlier oh here we go it's
my turn all right for a second i thought that was nemesis and it was going to be one of those
scenarios where she was like oh i'm just getting up oh no it's the scary guy that would have been
kind of cool you would have laughed at that i'm going to go for a pee break here in a second
probably right now carlos come in carlos damn it i guess i'm out of range
mine rounds what do the mine rounds do blaster target using its own propulsion detonates after
a short period of time or if approached okay got a lot of bullshit for this key
don't need that much healing um stop stop it this is fine i can begin nothing out of the way there's
a lot of other random shit in here hold on bullets in here mine rounds more first aid why are you
giving me all this stuff this is boss coming up new weapon notice all the mine rounds
huh they're tough to find intricate handle they're worth it standard issue grenade launchers don't
get cute try to load them in anything else fire them at walls with the ground and they'll stay
accidentally approaching and it will explode when they get in range it's like a sticky bomb
all right it's time to pee i will be right back i have returned good to see you again
i refilled my drink nice water with some tea in it it's a light tea
but people are giving subs produces asan thanks for the five community subs and labster both of
you back to back five thanks a lot i peed yeah i peed and refilled my drink back to it all right
so we left off where i was thinking about what the hell i was gonna do don't need three heels
i got there's a i i better be good on heels oh that's gonna be embarrassing save it let's go
so we're going out here shotgun or i'm gonna abuse the grenade launcher i know it come here
hey oh that sucks sucks oh that stinks now i have to kill you all oh you don't oh this sucks up
don't move something on the beds that was three headshots in a row give me a break out of ammo
remember could you hurry up this is a long game stop pretending we're like 70 percent of the way
through the game right now what are you talking about only been like four and a half hours you
know what sometimes you got to use it this is one of those times 10 percent there's still a lot i
can't stay here well does he actually come and chase me escape the creature again where is he
he's in a boat that'd be so funny if he like if he just rode over in a gondola that would be
fucking hilarious there's so much shit over here he's all right wait wait wait wait is he in there
i'm ready with the grenade launcher i'm not messing around i'm gonna use this shit i'm not
gonna save it at the end of the game just win well he made some kind of mistake oh my calculations
were off it was two milligrams of sulfuric acid bitch can't even swim an idiot carlos respond
we didn't make it the train derailed everybody's dead mihael everybody well i saw her doing she
did a and b together i don't understand why this was so hard i left us to die am i fucking up
is this nemesis i don't remember him turning into this shit
nemesis why are you so huge good thing i got explosive rounds to kill you
burn him excuse me thank you oh i don't know what to do with these still going
did i stop him in his fuck what am i supposed to do shoot him don't you're about to take a nasty fall
i don't have any guns he's doing the shit again all right get should i not even shoot the gun
he's doing this again he's like i'm going off the top rope knocked up knocked the tower down
knocked down the tower knocked down the tower oh shit i just got more should i wait till he
climbs again okay all right here he goes he's doing mercy climb the tower and power bomb him
off the tower i need to stop it in its tracks i figured it out i know how to do it okay i figured
it out i figured out okay face no don't i want i am never gonna stop yes of course i'm throwing
because i've used every bullet i had when i just had to make him run into the wall
um you know i'm gonna i'm not gonna deplete literally a hundred rounds of ammo
no i'm i want to redo it handgun ammo that's not gonna help me go in the cars yeah but i
i i wasted like 15 shots that's too much of a waste where is he excuse me let's get him to run
one did i miss no i got him all right all right now we gotta get to the other how do i change uh
e mine round excuse me sir e let's actually listen to collecting collect he's gonna start
running around you guys just stop him in his tracks there he goes oh he still wants to fight
what the no all right do it he's not doing it do the run around how much more damage do i have to
give him before he does this oh shit over here can't pick it up start running start running on
the walls go for it go there he goes there it is here it comes here it comes all right all right
here we go ready i'm ready dump up and start running there he goes he's going he's up he's on
the wall all right here we go hit that shotgun out there it is okay anymore mine rounds lying
around somewhere pissed here he goes going going going going going fine runs right there
oh hit him in the egg sack and oh that was fucking close all right fuck off fine here goes
shotgun get it out all right let's do this yeah that was much more optimized you're right that
was very optimized okay now take the time on me now take the time now to use your knife
and just cut him into tiny pieces you're not going to come back beam up carlos and say hey
can you meet me in front of the police station and bring your knife we're going to make we're
going to carve this guy up into a fucking thousand and like you're going to take half in a backpack
and i'm going to take half in a backpack so there's no way it can be combined like it's
that's what i would do i'm serious i would sit here and that's fucked up is it though
i missed a bunch of ammo i didn't know i was gonna go into a cut scene right there
oh poisoned where the hell interesting you've done me a big favor roughly half a day later
so here holy shit carlos
is that implying that like holy shit dude that was a long time do you copy
jill's been infected i i'm taking her to the hospital maybe dr bard can save her
do i have to run i got you do i have to do i have to carry jill
it's gonna be bad isn't it i'm not looking forward to this okay thank god thank god i
wouldn't have wanted to do that at all came off bite it jill i'm gonna get you the vaccine
you're gonna be okay search for a vaccine i promise okay i'm going come on uh carlos mcculkin
is on the case i don't know what his last name uh should i no by the way i just combined macaulay
kulkin's name i don't even realize i just did that that's what i did i don't know why why macaulay
kulkin every person on earth on everybody on the planet this is like it's like seven
there's like 10 billion people on earth carol where's bard now i'll go on ahead what is it
seven point fucking four or seven point three whatever it is i round up here we go in the
hospital game on no no game on i only will game on if you can if you allow me to do my john oliver
impression when he compares somebody to an animal and looks over on his right and addresses the
imaginary animal that he's talking about okay do i have permission okay i don't want to do that
mr turtle i don't want to see that and i don't want you to come into my house okay game on i've
just been walking back and forth saving i told you this it's not what you think it is i walked in and
out of that room and saved like fucking i think it's there i thought that was peter griffin for a
second it is peter no it's not and all right that was that's peter griffin running by that okay uh
let's go a much better shot with crystal always have oh my god i don't see it right don't move
all right let's go through this door over here the heart of raccoon city's health care the
forefront of science something about state of the art outpatient facilities i need a lockpick
can i get it from jill is that too much to ask emergency vaccine research stuff there's a case
in there that sound got it i that scared the shit out of me but i got it please state your business
clearly into the intercom a player oh is this uh this uh i know what i get it so i've got to
record him giving his master plan or whatever and then have play it back in front of this
right like hey it's me password five five yeah i gotta okay i've got to record somebody talking
dr bard are you in there i'm here to rescue you open the door no voice match found voice match
what kind of sci-fi bullshit is this it's true i really hope i never have that technology anywhere
near any of the stuff that i care about because you guys could just like play a fucking youtube
clip of me talking you could just string together a sentence of like please open the door it's me
jeremy elbertson why do we want like voice technology it'd be so easy i know he's gonna
break the glass it's just a matter of when but you missed it get out no he's in i don't have a key
card all right i can't open that door uh let's go that's a window that's open this is locked too
fuck well what am i supposed to do this is locked this is locked off the stairs i guess
this is left for dead level there's a left for dead level that's exactly like this right
i don't you're not gonna fool me not gonna happen not after all the bullshit okay now we're back
this way all right let's go down this hall staff only i thought that was gonna be a
all right what's this nurse's journal mystery illness after young got bitten do some consolidation
yeah way too many health packs here keep two and hopefully i find another green one
uh all right that's fine imagine not being staff oh well there's one right there i might just use
this now i can take one more two more bites all right that leaves me with there's something else
in here touched or looked at picked up and what is it 50 saves by the way how many of those were
actually real i will never know okay right here i don't have a lock pick is just jill come in here
eventually journal i swear i tried to do it but there's nothing else to be done the chaos is
completely beyond control 9 p.m there's a helicopter above overhead and immediately i started crying and
hugging each other thinking rescue team was on the way but then a sound grew distant and we're
all left with now the moaning of the dead and the silent screams of our hearts something's coming
i want to say god i just like stumbled up more ammo let's go memos a lot of notes id cards are
not to be taken off hospital grounds under any circumstances all employees must store their id
in their own personal lockers before returning home the key to the locker room has gone missing
mm-hmm somebody dropped it in the courtyard so we need to go to the courtyard of course we do
i took it hey there is staff in here imagine not being staff to go to the courtyard how would i get
there was this open i think yes it was what the hell is that i don't like these sounds oh somebody
coming in through here okay it's almost don't open safe another key card hey whoa
okay um how do i get the hell out of here then wait why won't that door open it will
oh oh get off me they came out of that door i just i did a flashbang and it was so cool
i don't want them getting up yeah yeah yeah this is something loose i have to do all this
bullshit again i won't open i know look at this i got a note for you id cards just kill them
and that's what i should have done this ammo over here punch them save more often yeah i mean i
usually do i have i've saved 50 times it's not this dumbass time you're gonna get your grade
lowered to d um as long as i get an f for finish i don't doesn't bother me okay back this way
here we go i am going to heal i'm gonna top myself off with this good i'm ready same deal
remember this part they break out through the door i'm gonna throw a flashbang and i'm gonna do the
thing i'm supposed to do when i got here the first time here we go very nice all right cool
hey hey whoa they're coming this way somebody said okay for a second i thought you said overwatch
is the cure for baldness and i was like oh that's a funny joke but you said overwatch is calling
putting words in your mouth okay what's in here nothing in this sick room i gotta find my way to
the court i gotta get to the courtyard one of these lockers open it's not like a machine i have to
look at right damn it really can't open that door it's the only place i haven't gone is over here
this is it really fuck how do i get out there you're gonna get down here all right i'm gonna
back down that's the way to the courtyard so you just go down the stairs let's get the hell out
of here i have to walk all the way around i see i made it i found the key then here it comes
yeah what is it's not gonna be a snake it's gonna be a snake or something it's a snake isn't it it's
a snake it's a giant snake get it oh i thought he actually got bit by a snake or something that's
why i thought he was doing that like i know i was like punching but like with the first run i
thought it was him getting like bit by something in the bushes okay here we go i missed um whatever
now i gotta go back upstairs to here or the step which one was it staff room or was it
was that save point jeremy get in there and save it it just saved why did it just save
i know why here he comes um right now he's pretty much on his way he's pretty much ready to get you
hey does this work on a door wait is that herb oh come on that's a nerve note about tape recording
i think i know what happened to the missing tape of dr b his research assistant took it
move something from a locker in the nurse's station and walk towards the treatment room
all right the treatment room this is the treatment room over here all right i gotta go back i think
it's this way half room i heard some music cue that means probably yes staff room okay there's
no this is a point good secret stacom's to be a secret uh i'm going to put you no put you away
that means they only have one heel um take take two take two heels you find yourself unable to
cast sus because the stream is currently on now you didn't know if you just jumped in thinking
you're gonna catch the bod well that would be nice to get a hospital map all right well at
least i know everything where i need i need to go i know everywhere i need to go open this door
or yes holy shit there's a lot of um one of this is gonna be a dead body in one of these
there always is all right got an id card you can't have a resident evil game where someone
doesn't fall out of a locker that's gonna happen in every single one of these without a doubt
just have to go for it okay so i got what i was looking for here now i go back with the
the key card and the treatment room thing get the tape and then bring the tape over here and
then put the tape down i yeah i get it you said imagine watching a vod for five hours
um imagine watching a stream for five hours aren't you here what is that
dodge dodge you fucking moron dodge dodge him fucking grunting is so stupid christ okay i'm
fine i'm fine punch him punch into his face save it good save into the nurse's station
i'm gonna use a grenade on the next one because i have a grenade and i might as well you save
some ammo he's gonna drop from the ceiling over here somewhere i'm ready come on drop out of the
tiles two in here hey just be dead good okay he's getting in the damn way oh my what happened to you
how did you get behind me i thought that was that the same person that just gave me a stomach ache
i just got a stomach ache from that one okay here we go i still i'll take it i'm gonna be cautious
i'm gonna take it took it i'm taking it i want the better one give me this one ammo here and a
lock i can't do anything about this i'm definitely gonna be coming back here with jill then that's it
right that's a fact oh that all right here this is the part where the there's two frog men in here
here
he's standing behind the door just kick it open like shit wait a minute i have a somebody spawned
him in who's this who's this guy that they spawned in i bounced off his fucking head and came back at
me okay there's another one in here don't this is what happens when i play with my friend from
australia do this for about 10 minutes i say nice talking to you again and he leaves
punch him why would you go back to get out of the way thank god i didn't have to use every
bullet i had oh my goodness this is what i came in here with the tape put the tape in here all
right now i have to go to that door and play i don't have any i have pistol that's it this
is gonna get ugly if i have to fight anything else what else is in here why is it still um
this why is this red still something else in here can i say all right what's that thank you very much
written evil 3 master worst face nominee hold on i'll be the judge of that i mean it's the
fucking hair that makes this look weirder it's this weird hair that i have this fucking 70s hair
all right let's go back oh and i now i just have to actually plug this thing in
which that was here we have to get down to the lab reception so i gotta go down the stairs
or from the courtyard where the courtyard works too let's just go to the courtyard no more no more
no more no more no more no more no more i don't have enough ammo no more no more of these guys
right i don't i wow i wish what's the password ran by come on i was pretending i need to go
just just use just use the stairs that was a perfect youtube thumbnail that like hurt me
i just i just hurt i got hurt from that that was fucking crazy though you guys know what i'm
talking about he ran by the screen the fucking door behind you whoa flash grenade flash grenade
flash bang flash bang flash bang what's this lost items nine three pick it up pick it up
still fucking shit in here man i tried to punch it stomp step on head step do a sexy pose i was
gonna just go like bang and do a button no all right we did it i got everything i needed in here
let's get the hell out of here brew here something else i can do here though whatever it is
i hope i find it soon oh cool handgun ammo and a lot
did you get through that did you see that insane juice
i caution him okay this is my favorite vod to come back to what's up
okay play them play the tape this in the first place do you think you're talking to
i'm goddamn nathaniel bard best biologist you'll ever meet you bet pen changing waste of a nursing
degree of course i have connections higher up military consults with me i don't have to
oh i cut it off i don't know i thought maybe i had to put the whole thing up there
they already got the audio they needed whatever bard's dead he's been shot shit and the vaccine
i'm looking there's gotta be a computer right computer banquet my pleasure to cordially invite
you to a banquet on september 10th at the center hotel okay join us if you could
eight i'll be introducing the bill for that new drug of yours in mid-august bring the cash
all right we're looking for a vaccine i found it wait ammo in here and there's also there's a
first aid where's the first aid in the middle there it is all right vaccine give it to me email
from nathaniel bard greg i know you're watching the news the virus is going to devour the country
the dead will wash over the capital hilled into like a tidal wave i have in my position
one dose of a vaccine for the virus the holy grail and it's not for my family enough of my
my ladies no greg it's for you i know better than anyone that you're the future of the united
states but if you want the goods greg you have to go get me the hell out of here now without
umbrella finding out i'll lean on the pentagon i know you've got the clout see if someone can
rescue get a rescue team here without ubcs involvement scratch my back i scratch yours
which should sound pretty chasty after the parties we've been too hurry my time is running out this
is vrc chief nathaniel bard september 29 11 p.m i'm acutely aware that my time's running out
or just watched it and i hope and pray by making this recording and bringing the truth to light
that i can restore some small shred of honor to my name all of raccoon city's suffering began
with the release of a biological weapon known as the t virus my employer the umbrella corporation
engineered this virus and they ordered my team to develop a vaccine which we did now i keep
samples of this vaccine here in my office the rest of it is stored underground i gotta go
underground but those sons of bitches have to bore it they want to destroy it they don't want the
world to know what they've done so they're trying to erase all evidence that the virus ever existed
now i'm not a fool i know they don't want me to mom came in to end my rp session
that's the only one along and she trusted me anyway
easy vaccine was in there stupid is it here no it's okay he's just a counter-strike a pro
remember from yesterday remind it that joke right when he punched it i got the vaccine tight i'm
not just gonna be able to walk back with this am i probably not t i got it be careful have you
seen this town it'll be a fucking miracle okay i thought he was gonna grab me and
now i thought he was gonna grab me i thought he was gonna grab me i thought he was gonna
just grab me so i was getting ready for it does it work on me too just close your eyes
luncheon fuck i was stuck here i'm ready this time i got it you didn't shake the remote hard
enough careful hang up on him i don't even know what to say he just spun me around and
i don't know it was like a fucking warcraft rogue oh he died he's just behind you now
and now he does a kidney shot and then he just fucking burns you and kills you
minus two wild reference i played it for fucking 10 straight years of course it's
gonna be my brain sometimes be careful i gotta shoot this i have to i can't it won't let you
get a gun out oh my god it's running so fast back to jill where's jill there she is in the
makeshift sick room i gotta go down here i'm ready to run this is box how do i get that box
oh it's just a zombie it's gonna miss the safe how do i get it i i don't think i can i i'm gonna
miss it oh up the upstairs safe yet i gotta go left and then left i forgot about that hopefully
there's no enemies i have to fucking fight please nobody don't make this painful for me i just want
to get the hell out of here okay now i gotta go where's the station oh it's brain worms
all right here i'm one of those the guys where is it ah okay straight i'm gonna save the game
i got a lot of green herbs get rid of this i look at why am i still holding this shit
i'll discard that okay do i have any let's take another big heal out first aid spray out
ammo is depleted i'm in trouble i'm in big trouble save it okay now nurse's station
uh wrong door i guess okay so it's down here can't go this way so i gotta go
left left straight punch him and die all right uh clockwise nine then what clockwise nine
counterclockwise three open holy shit what is that cool magazine oh wow it's 64 shots
that's really good glad i came back up here um okay save jill i don't want to i'm not going out that
way again there's a guy out there that i don't want to see how can i i'm gonna go all the way
around you see okay so i need to go out this door kind of wrap around here left on the roof so out
and then left where's that box where's that box where's the box how do i get the box all right
back to what i was doing i'm gonna go oh my god this is a mess jump over the bench i don't think
i can oh i can't i can't get over this hit the box with jill all right that's what i was gonna say
okay i have to actually walk around in a gigantic circle great okay down into the reception all the
way through into the makeshift sick room okay go through here hello that can't be opened excuse me
get me out okay jill i'm coming chapter complete chapter one complete shit better work i don't
think it worked tyrell the hell happened attention all citizens the contagion spreading throughout
the city has been designated uncontainable i'm gonna get a timer first raccoon city will be
completely destroyed in a missile strike all residents capable of rational thought are urged
to evacuate immediately this is not a test attention all citizens i mean that's only a day away
there's still people in the city you think uncle sam gives a shit here they come sit tight i got
this better grab some ben jill sounds like there's a lot of them out there this is left for dead
need to get some gear okay here we go uh i don't have any gear do you do we have any ammo
because how am i supposed to defend this area without any weapons they're not going to drop
down from the ceiling right window shutters the less entry points the better and how do we do that
i'll try hacking into the hospital security system keep them off me in the meantime i thought that
we're gonna break in the door and defend jill in the bed because jill's here they come detonator
all right any more bullets all right thank god i was gonna say how the hell am i supposed to do
this with like no bullets all right game time started oh it's time for game night
uh i believe that's probably it right should i detonate something i don't actually you know
what right i'll i guess i'll i'm gonna take it what was that
did i just get hit in the face like a bug why did i spin around like that like didn't what where
nobody breached anything detonator how do i use it how do i do i attach it that guy wouldn't
even load it into the game they're not even loaded into the game breaker don't let him get in the
room breaker oh a backpack was a breaker in here there's no fucking breaker in this room i found
it wait that's just a light that's a light switch it's a breaker that's a light switch oh sit down
sit down sit down sit down sit down sit down i'll get them did we win did you do it kind of waiting
for you to finish okay dude my man just despawned i guess i thought i was pulled out until the
explosion what make my own times you gotta make your own explosions oh come on get out i'm not
locked in here with you you're locked in here with me i bet like i could be that guy at least it's
over you're right i could be that guy i'm coming back vaccines a real deal you don't work somewhere
you're damn right what do you think you're gonna do whole city's about to be microwaved
come on call the government tell them we found a cure you stalled for time all the government
bosey motherfucker it's like a 1-800 number it's just the government you know there's like
six thousand branches of our government all the government which one out of those two not just one
chill good news all of them it's over now the city's safe
ah what happened was it a nightmare
did i get bit too many times of course it was a dream where am i what's going on attention all
citizens the missile strike on raccoon city will occur in just hours the payload is designed to
eradicate all biological material you will not survive you you included first evacuate now repeat
no it can't be how long has she been asleep for two days three days hey get out just get out of the
sick room getting a little blinky i have all my old items right i do their store is give me the box
bring another first aid spray no i already have two bring the explosive rounds this shit out of
here for now keep the lockpick all right let's go oh he's tired um i'm all right i'm good
it's a different handgun fine i'll use it i mean just i'll use this one this one's just like a
better handgun it's time to move morning sunshine you saved my life i sure as shit didn't that was
all carlos he carried you here and he treated you himself crazy bastard where is he he went
underground barge stockpiled the vaccine enough to give this city some hope his ribs are gonna
explode himself i'm going after him wait did you see the broadcast they're gonna blow the city sky
high i'm trying to get a hold of someone anyone with the clearance to stop it leave this mess to
him he's a professional so am i right head to the underground facility what's this here
here we have some shit to do first and foremost okay i need to get down to the underground
facility this thing's actually really cool you're dead you're not dead now you are you can go game
on game on hold on game on hold on there you go this wait i gotta get that shit over here
can i get the they're not any more of those big insane scary fucking monsters right
because there's a couple things i can lock back up here this especially in here agma mo right
i gotta store this that'll be part of my eight hit kill on nemesis coming up soon here in about
20 to 30 minutes this is definitely the end of the game all right up here left up up up you guys
told me they weren't any more of those there are there are six rounds that's worth it all right now
we gotta go up here straight no not this way you believed chap sometimes you feel like sometimes
i feel like i should i wish i could believe them what are you doing all right i had to do a be
farting oh he's not farting can i get over there from where art there's two things there now
drop from the upper level yeah i can that's what i'm thinking i just gotta go up there and drop
in a few moments here i'm going to stand up and take a few minutes to stretch starting to
lock up a little bit there's one of these guys behind here in there okay now i can drop down
from where behind this door fucking guys behind i'll just take care of this
uh was i seeing his reflection in the thing here i thought he was behind this door
holy shit oh it's just a shotgun and where are you now okay that's enough of that i got a lot
of bullets for that lots of shotgun shells i got a ton of good ammo here that is that
save the game drop down get the briefcase i've done get the hell out of here so where can i
does it matter where i drop down there's been a specific place wait the linen room i want to go
in here there's something in here to open not this one hold on there is a box in here
or mag ammo the lot save it to the very last fight coming up here in about 15 minutes
all right which one do i have to fall down from is this one here and this one there
it's this one here right yeah it is this one isn't it because there's the
and then you walk around and wait is that not correct fuck that wasn't right purple gang
people happy have to crawl under a bed in the hallway in that hallway crawl under a bed in the
hallway bed it's bed this bed this bed probably another one um second floor wait on the second
floor or how wait i have to fall from a different angle or something crawl under a bed okay find
out that had too much sugar um i don't know what the hell they are eating i think i can squeeze by
oh but how the fuck was i supposed to look at how would i ever know that
here who is funny no all right was it worth it holy shit turns out yeah it was worth it
turns out uh that turns out that's the game changer right there because now i have my
end of the game only use the magnum end of the game weapon anything else in here all right let's go
okay am i smoke more crack is what somebody said i don't do that and not do any of that actually
all right same deal as last time i um forget everything underground facility which was here
okay except to go back this way take a right and then take a right and then go straight and then
take a right get up and stretch yes when i go to this next area i'm gonna get up wait something
in here what if i what if what if what if what can i not what have i not gotten explosive b
shit hold on fine but i should i take a heal i load this thing up this looks like nicolai's work
reload it flame rounds oh what do i get rid of i did it all i didn't even realize the lock pick
i can just get rid of it holy shit i thought i was gonna need it now yeah you know we're at the end
of the game oh now it's certain it's absolutely it's it's confirmed now that this is like the
last like probably 32 minutes of the game lockpick is gone it's over all right let's go
out he's gonna get up he's gonna this he'll attack me no no maybe an hour yeah maybe i'll be right
back give me like two three minutes i'm just gonna take a few moments to stretch it bear back
i am back i am ready we continue so high no no no no no no no no no no need to go down
get the big guns i knew the second that i came down here we're gonna be here what is this doing
up here i don't want to use this get rid of that i don't want to have that equipped what are you
crazy protest to demand the integration of wings back into the channel no i don't even need to read
the rest of that uh i don't need to read the rest of it all right let's go all the way to the
underground is it make sure i got something good out i'll keep mine rounds kind of suck
i'm gonna use them okay good underground lab this must be the way underground
okay anything in here that i can pick up something right yes of course there is
close to b i do crack but i but ironically i don't think you can ironically do crack i think you just
smoke crack i think that's just what you're doing all right this is i'm gonna get flanked
how is it no one in the hospital ever noticed all this
you know behind a door that you had to pull a certain book already pulled that certain book
why is this so familiar i feel like i've been here have we been here wait i can just combine
these acid rounds nice combine this why don't you guys take it half life one you did this
i mean i'm talking about this this game that i'm playing now remember pay attention to us
i am i'm giving you equal time uh is this the final hit pouch right when i needed it that's great
elevator notice there's an issue with the box if you encounter this problem and can't get the
elevator running please stay calm gather fuses from the sub generators situated around the warehouse
and use those to restore power to the main generator you gotta go get sub generators
go pick up three sub generators see you when you come back look at this disorganized shit inventory
i got 12 i got 20 shots with that thing three heels all right just for that guy weapons up
top can i rotate i can't rotate heels down the right an ammo over here there are you um
are you happy what you want to be doing three heels gunpowder i don't have any of the gunpowder
right no you're past your hourly stacom's quota you need to eat a stacom's because when do you
get so on board with stacom's i thought that was uh i'm a piece of crap thing any key key
that's albert wesker it's not it's the other guy i feel like there's gonna be a very big fight
right now i hope i'm ready for it does he can he see can we start talking
wave hi okay in here this is definitely a fight this is no way this is not a boss fight
one million percent yes i must admit i respect you but i'm afraid he was just waiting for me to
get the fuses what's this thing that won't die they not they don't die
get up on there and uh what does that do take his fucking leg out take his other leg out
put him in the can't kill these things they don't die our source use number one got it
or three the thing i had just enough the other two are there's one over there
let's not wait right here what the fuck oh okay oh a safe house good handgun ammo
is that it that's it that's in there okay you're my auto you stink all right so how
i guess i can go wait a minute i go around all right fool me once shame on you fool me twice
shame on you both times for using that same shitty fucking game design tactic i'm never at fault here
item dead end no wait i can squeeze through there but what about back here i can go up this
this is probably can i go up this wait what oh wait all right what maybe one day it'll come back
for like 10 minutes yes for fun one point do i unlock something for that that's what this is
for right that's what those do what did that do oh wait i don't want to get on again it's one of
those weirdos it's one of the weirdos it's one of these weirdos wait there's something over there
i don't fucking care who gets but a memo yeah all right nice this is right here store some of
these because i don't need them too many use i can reload that plenty of health this reload
the shotgun and let's go do wait what on july 30th not a bad idea it's not a bad idea okay back out
here what do you do with these guys what's the plan here what's the what's the plan i've got a
lot of time to examine them but he's speaking he's just trying to communicate needs to be a
magnum in the head oh feels good doesn't it you just jump scared chat into shell holder
faster reload speed really reloads faster i'm gonna need to heal in a second though all right
let's go it was pog relax i know it was look i know a pog when i see one all right looking for
another one of these fuse boxes which i see one over here turn this on okay then there's one right
there go get it oh yeah i can make more shotgun shells with that just finished a project i can
finally just chill and watch hey what's up welcome to the stream i gotta be prepared to shoot
what are you afraid of oh that's what you're afraid of
whoa that was fucking scary that's apparently all i have to say about it i'm going to heal
now that was horrible let's go what about in this little container oh we do have some stuff in here
gunpowder gunpowder gunpowder gunpowder all right do i make a bunch of shotgun shells or do i have
like 30 to 40 rounds in the magnum what's your favorite flavor of gunpowder uh blue raspberry
okay there's two where's this last one it's one more blue raspberry sucks what's wrong with it
i'm just trying to look and see where the last one is in there okay down there i can go that
way maybe up there and around all right who's making that noise can i get in wait a minute
i go down i go this way does this connect it does yeah i remember this fucking weirdo um
i go down by this way first it could be like a right there right fucking there
i sneak by i press this button not yet wait okay i'm gonna climb down that they're gonna go that
way how do i get on that side wait can i oh this is door right here oh go go go where do you go i
don't even know which way it's fucked up we're doing our health i'm fine all right this is the
last one free fuses here goes time to put the power back on which is under there how do you like the
game so far i think it's good i think it's a good game watch out for this guy right i think it's
good do i think it's i mean i gotta be honest do i think it's even remotely close to the second
game remake it's it's fun to play it's a fun game but i don't think it's even even close to
uh re2 remake so far i mean if resident evil 2 remake was like a 9.6 for me like a 9.4 this is
probably this is probably like a this is probably like a seven one like it's still good it's still
i think it's still a good game i think it's still fair game what's missing um nemesis i feel like
he's kind of just showed up to because in the last game like he would kind of chase mr x would
chase you around and you'd get attacked and it was he was always a presence in this one he just kind
of a cutscene will happen he'll like grab you and then you kind of have to run away from him for a
few minutes it's like it's they like show their hand before he makes an appearance because before
mr x would just fucking show up like you'd be doing something he'd be on like the typewriter
you turn around he'd just be there it's like holy fuck that's the guy but this one it's like
cutscene i'm here and you're like oh he's here and then you have to run away from him i think if
nemesis was a little more interesting to have encounters with i would probably say this is
be up a little higher but and that's that's kind of in my opinion that's a huge point of the whole
game i think right i mean nemesis is the bad guy they use him too early yeah they like kind of really
here he is it's been like not even 20 minutes i don't think it's bad i just i prefer the other
style of like he could kind of just be anywhere versus the like big extravagant here's a cutscene
and now fight nemesis for a few minutes i mean i still haven't a great time seven one might be
unfair uh we'll find out we'll find we'll find it at the end of the game we'll find out we're
good we'll be there soon now i'm not gonna give this 64 all right let's head down here all right
you ready you need the magnum for this oh 64 saves all right i have a prediction the amount
of saves that the game is when the game is over is my score for the game i think that's fair
those of a gunpowder gunpowder so i want to make some shotgun shells eventually hopefully
i need the magnum right no just make some uh pistol round i'm gonna lose these three
magnum coming out take it with my magnum ammo take it out i got look at all these bullets it's
gonna be fucking insane okay now i put away the grenade launcher maybe i just don't need it i
don't need the grenade launcher put the handgun away yeah that make actually that makes sense
keep yeah the grenade launcher keep the magnum i'm gonna lose this we have to make uh okay yeah
yeah yeah yeah two heals let's take a third one just in case i'm fucking terrible at the video
game here comes the final boss incoming i think it's a 65 so far let's do it this time i'm not
gonna get hit by you oh come on you're dead nope why do you have to fucking have i could have just
put the stupid um turn it on pursuit oh go go go go hit the button hit the button i got my magnum
out don't fire the magnum put the magnum away it's talking up shit he got away what was he doing in
here it's time unfinished activity log s run at university uh they gave it a 64 god eyes on two
stars a male infected in a female bioweapon is pursuing the female metamorphosis in the
bioweapon triggered by a hostile encounter with jv video attached baby's been infected
and his non-responsive collected samples per orders vaccine recovered and administered to jv
by co a soldier in mv platoon jv expected to be fit for combat approximately in 20 hours
seems clear the bioweapon is project n contact with jv causes to change and evolve will induce
further encounters to obtain more data jv germ of venus that face when your twitch email doesn't work
through they're willing to negotiate
they'll call off the strike gif and this is one big ass if we can deliver the vaccine to them
before they launch how long do we have hours maybe shut that last time waste one more second
this way everyone always says hours hours hours this was hours ago we'll find the vaccine up ahead
go back what oh shit he's going without me with the loot oh fuck good thing i turned around
and the barrel the magnum reduces recoil and extra speed increases damage
holy shit imagine if i didn't get the damage upgrade to the magnum
holy shit that would have been awful okay now i'm gonna this is gonna be i'm gonna shoot the guy
four times and kill him what if germa became a landlord i don't know what i'd probably i'd
fucking have fair prices what i would have i would have a fair price what are you talking about
i mean true stop and do what i got your back will you go forward all right let's get this done
you go first i played the thing for 12 straight hours man i know how this works go
i'm not gonna have this happen he's going to bite you there he is bro do i control this
all right so i'm gonna give you a case in point why not just have him show up through the hallway
and it's like oh fucking he kills the guy you're gonna mean like in game
don't need a cutscene for everything that was a very fast door yeah i would be scared to even
walk through this in normal circumstances sterile just stand up uh i need to open this somehow
i don't have anything save why any items in here shelf yes all right good now i can make
shotgun shells employee regulations attention nest two employees objective of the t-virus
research facility differ from those of the umbrellas main nest facility here we focus on
real world use cases which arise as new bio weapons are created and introduced such as the need for a
t-virus vaccine somebody else to read it the mass books of our work can be dangerous it's imperative
that all employees adhere to workplace regulations without fail somebody else will read this it's a
great honor to be a part of the finest research organizations in the world and we'll keep in mind
we stick to our rules any other items in here computer green herb okay uh should i just make
two green herbs how am i doing on health i'm actually okay not great but not bad not good
but not great will carry two with us reload this thing free reddit joke i made a joke
but what did i say i'm not i'm not even aware of what i did that what did i do
i didn't i'm not even aware that i'm doing it this is landlords in chat with dan's game
landlords in chat all right i'm good so need to find uh what this way all right workers break lab
one let's go this way first you're gonna get up aren't you not oh shit am i i'm supposed to open
had to open that box isaac's diary hey was generous the benefits were good somebody else will read
this well hindsight is 2020 because this lab is a den of monsters who couldn't there are barbarians
in here it's messed up the world needs to know umbrella owns this town there was this guy they
caught trying to smuggle out company secrets they essentially fed him to one of the betas
bed him i saw the whole thing fucked up should have brought the handgun i tried to dodge too
this is broken this is broken this is broken what the fuck was that it was a big grunt
oh more i can make more shotgun shells it's a happy happy day and gonna emo yeah it's a people
happy day oh shit we're going late huh i just looked at the time to begin vaccine synthesis
place the materials in the chamber hey shit it's been a long time i don't have i need vaccine
materials synthesis i have to make it myself all right that's dumb okay here we go uh the most
efficiently synthesized okay you need an antigen and an adjuvant sure go get two items and put it
in this box got it override key successfully generated what if we hear what is that override
key removed flash drive what do i pick up what head this way nothing else on the tables or anything
no let's go into the lab over here uh wait down stairs tension streamer it's time to stretch
don't worry i will let me go back down here but you guys what flash drive that's right
wait flash drive uh what what what year is this isn't it like 1997 or something
i see i'm under there i didn't why i shoot the shotgun okay i have to kill these guys with
the magnum you say right i might i don't want to waste up there's so many they're so valuable
make a count his head's moving around too much got him fucking asshole okay
they're dead oh my health is at zero what a bunch of bullshit all right no more of those all right
i think notice hazard materials take extreme care there's a fucking there's item one here
there's item number one you need here here what's that bye bye was it uh bye bye supposed to a
that's it huh all right a dying message from the scientist the virus is leaked prepared a culture
of the antigen yes where the adjuvant samples are stored in the incubation lab where the hell
is that top maybe oh acid rounds fun powder laptop wait i missed what i missed in the corner
yes i'm running out of space let me reload this thing here we go you gotta find the hev suit all
right inventory looks like shit i gotta fix this better hey uh here's the heels all right that's
fine oh this thing's tangled them they're waiting for you jeremy in the test chambers
or they are this must be what powers it yes this is what oops oh he was the fucking guy that was
gonna tell me how to do this i'm oh it's really easy yeah you had a really kind of shitty quest
giver job push push forward on the device well i'm sorry uh first aid uh let's go ahead and take
out the this thing because i don't feel safe in this one okay i gotta ask why put that in a
briefcase this big you could very easily just put that in like a fucking small jar somebody had to
place that right in the middle like a weirdo and close this why not put like 50 of them in here
why just one i think i'll place one bottle of tylenol inside of the center of this fucking box
we're scientists i don't know for what reason do i am i doing this there's just like an office
weirdo that's in every one of these games that just particularly places fucking shit everywhere
in random spots there's no reason for that to be there why is that there there's no fucking reason
why that box is on that table the video games now it's not just real man this is me anything
on this table that was a reddit youtube bit uh youtube has 700 trillion videos and reddit has
like 900 000 a post a second so uh yeah i guess it could have been on fucking reddit one day
oh this is bad give me a shot to fucking shoot no restart the whole game what the fuck
can i come in this way or am i going this way i don't i don't i came in this way okay have them
all funnel out of the fucking door have me shoot two explosive fucking grenades at them and nobody
dies so we call that we called that ridiculous down i thought he was on the ground i thought he
was on the ground there he is mr fucking guy that leaves the mustard around sure uh hold on
do i want acid rounds do i want explosive rounds or uh yeah do i acid forgive me father for i've
sinned i've accidentally made a flame round i'm in whatever they all do the same damn thing
i have to shoot him with the shotgun all right sample one liquid filled test tube an adjuvant
these are combined with antigens to increase immune system response
i have concerns about this virus that you're making you're making a virus viruses can be
kept in check i believe an effective vaccine can be developed do you know the name for parasites
however perhaps in your country consumers are willing to buy them sincerely we have a problem
we've fucked up so it's a missus you've already read it i i i got it i gotta pick that up i have
to take it i'm gonna i'm gonna do something really gonna be upset by this but i'm gonna do it
i will accept the consequences of my actions if i need to i can't even wait i i could i could
have combined them before i put it in the inventory i don't i don't want to make this i don't want i
don't want flame rounds i got one in the in the bank i don't want to make another flame rounds
yes you do i don't i really don't gunpowder just leave it i don't even want it i don't want
i want the other rounds okay i got one now i gotta go i'm just gonna put it in the thing
reload why the fuck would i reload because i deleted a green herb i think i'm gonna be all
right i think i'm gonna be just fine reload your gun oh shoot him what was that okay reload your
gun not reload the game i thought you guys are telling me to reload the game like holy shit dude
reload reload the save are you fucking idiot i can't believe it no you mean reload the gun
we were okay i got five acid rounds i got enough okay let's put this back in okay where's that
weird device that i can plug this into up here right thank god i killed these guys imagine if
i didn't uh all right where is this where is it up incubation no no where is it
sterilization room where am i trying to go here which for an antigen ducked up bro how close you
to beating the game up very very close very close this is i believe the last area from what i
remember of playing the original game from what i remember this is the last area one of we're very
close to got them both ultra sample an antigen sample i'll definitely need this weaponry
authorization request i'd like to formally request that the weaponry normally reserved for the
bioweapon synthesis team be made available to any employee uh reasonably some test subjects
have developed a new mutation granted them very high regrowth abilities our team referring to
these specimens as pale heads you need to kill them with a big magnum thanks chat okay now we go
down here this is the we go down this way remember it's your mother go to bed now how do i get in
here i'll go to bed when i finish the game which should hopefully be in the next few minutes
we're grounded i can't ground me i'm an adult i'm an adult mom can't ground me
uh you're adult is there another way to get over here like on the right way i'm trying to get back
to where the i put the samples in back here right until i get back here wrong way that's what i'm
trying freaked out uh can i go this way that's this way it's now from here we go i'm just gonna
save it this is why the hell wouldn't i got a lot of shit to make here we go explosive a
i want explosive rounds that's what i want thank you i want to do gunpowder and i don't
i don't want to do gunpowder sample sample heal heal heal magnum ammo stretch i'm all right i'm
okay i wonder if i should just bring them i should bring the handgun or is it well we too far in now
i think your Alzheimer's medication i don't want to feel good this is good this is acid rounds
explosive rounds and then i got three flame rounds i got a lot of firepower
load the fuck up all right i'll load the fuck up hold on okay i loaded the fuck up i'm stacked
i got three heals i'm ready let's move save it here we go it's time to go in the same door that
i just walked in um because i'm insane is this the right way no this is just a fucking
like missed room i'm here to get lost no i'm not lost that fucking thing's man at a titanium
be careful there could be one of those monsters all right here we go i'm loaded up i am to the
rim put it in okay put in the liquid filled test tube and put in the sample
either i've got this wrong or i'm missing a step culture sample
i have to shake them what's this oh that's too much red over there turn it down i'll take it
i was scientific complete please remove the vaccine canister
there we go i thought you're stabbing yourself in the face you guys have a glow stick okay escape
the facility i need a heal not yet oh look a little mouse hole i can go in here around the
neck again really really and again he's just we got a cut scene showing him looking grabbed you
tap w uh do i press another button what is he doing right now just letting that happen
oh you're bullying me stop stop it oh oh shit you have another arm nemesis don't you perfect
that's enough to make um shotgun shells i've gone powder right do i not have gunpowder fuck
i don't have any more gunpowder annoying that's really annoying when did i when did i use it let me
maybe take another heel this is fill up on heels i just take the other for i'm gonna take the yeah
let's go i'm taking all these cans of whipped cream we're going i'm ready save it oh there's
another one what else you got it oh fuck i can make more wait stay here stay stay stay stay
store this for a second i'm gonna make the um other magnum gun let me see uh
magnum combine now i got 14 i'm gonna spray myself in the face with this
pick up the other with this one i just i got free heal okay first aid first aid forget about the
rest of this shit this is it i'm ready let's fucking do it face and eye torture all right
what do we got first flame round sound good to me let's do it i'm ready what's this disposal
center potent solvents used will ensure that any biological matter within the vat living or dead
is completely dissolved all right i gotta dissolve the guy in acid what's the name is this place
true what is this place hello welcome to episode one of germa craft not quite all right let's do it
okay
don't lose that vial oh i'm not supposed to be on here
nicolai don't the city needs that vaccine more than i do i don't think
wisdom i've been trying to impart on you is getting through now i know you can't put a price on life
but i'm in this business to get paid so let's make a deal you go down there
battle the nemesis and i'll recall it all and sell the combat dot put on a good show and
maybe i don't need the vaccine agreed all right kill nemesis good
i think i can do that i have i have enough weapons i'm not supposed to be on now i am
go all right dump of acid on him i don't even i have too much stuff all right i gotta dump acid
on him i gotta get him underneath one of these things and dump acid on him let's shoot them
yeah all right i can shoot i can shoot these and then acid dump on his head look it's fucking
dread it's burning his head you're screaming you're doing a good job thanks okay so what the
hell am i supposed to do about this shit oh one did i have that right do i have to just
fucking break these all all right now that's that's that's that's that's that zaps all right i get it
i have to get him underneath one of these jumped over it how the fuck is that even possible
okay ready here he comes shock him uh can i go in one of these vents jill is that you carlos
you fucking games not okay can i remove save files spot for you i'm gonna remove save files i
want to remove them hi what was he doing why are you doing this again all right shock him acid
acid or his tendril what do that again what i've got the oh i've got i've got why are the ads
go do the thing again go shock him all right dump him in the acid and then
not what i intended to hit i'll take it why many more oh shit i don't
there's one well he didn't choose the thing he didn't choose why didn't he choose
imagine adding ads to this fight imagine imagine adding ads to this fight imagine
okay dude wait what the five
can't even why are there random zombie ads use it to climb up all right kill him he's not dead
he's gonna get up he's gonna jump up and he's gonna grab us yeah but he's gonna be in there for 12
hours how do you propose to keep him in there for 12 hours okay okay i only have
i got plenty of shots do i have enough health to do this i hope so i have to get that vaccine back
first aid spray weapon spec sheet next generation rail gun code name finger
ammo velocity progression of new bio weapons in case of outbreak supreme firepower provides
a secondary benefit of completely obliterating the target leaving no trace behind the thing is
thank you for the five community subs appreciate the five subs thank you the thing is totally rad
tyrants out alive just give him the finger and problem solved a pack's firepower where it needed
will be even better if there was a way to control the output mobility may prove to be problematic
multiple power sources i need power sources to use the ultra gun okay what's left in here
let's take the green herb out i'll sniff it and maybe get like a maybe it'll help me
eventually uh just take this gun out too right well just why not no that's that's
no there's probably more shit there it's probably way more stuff to take
donor gamer why my eyes red because the white balance is wrong on this camera all right let's
go wait on where is you can hear auto outside i can hear you're not going in you're not going
in his office you're not going into daddy's office that's fucking funny okay i don't i
i don't have any just store it i'm i don't even need any bullets i'm gonna use the super gun
i don't need to save the game again let's go it's done give me the vaccine you greedy son of a
bitch oh no no no you print money i like but we shall make ours an ongoing arrangement now drop
the gun i told you yet even in 12 hours and now he's a gigantic growth have you ever seen anything
so incredible the data on this would be worth millions but uh you know how it is city's about
to explode and you can't put a price on life good luck
go after nikolai wait no he died in my dream what about you we're running out of time i've got this
just so you know this is the last fucking time power source activate pick up big gun
fire a big gun at big enemy right uh there
i have to go push this shit in damn it needs power okay put it down i'll come back
this is the last time let's go go press the button wait go pick up all this shit so i don't like
spam like a plane diablo fucking two please get it all there's more on this side too pick it all up
watch out for the fucking big claw shit everywhere i don't i don't i don't even know what this is
all right do i have any bullets okay i'm ready make a different reference blizzard fanboy
cha i scare him give me the exact what's that tree's name from dark souls 3 one
shoot him i'm gonna put you right back on your four fuck oh there's another hand all right get it
just get it right in the heart i'm gonna put it in his mouth
take the fucking hits oh that went all the way down good riddance take back the vaccine well
first of all uh i'm gonna have to do a little bit of but just look around make sure okay everything
has been collected how am i looking here i'm gonna take one of these heals i could have just eaten
the fucking rain herb and take less than five seconds before you know take a second before
you click on fucking things all right plenty of ammo and okay reload everything i don't have any
more it sucks i'm a big trouble who's backing a truck up all right is he about to fly away in
a space shuttle i don't understand always go around the back and look that's not padding i
think it might be like a box of ammo right there it's not much left for me to pad a final save
point oh no info i don't even get a final save point you're not going to stop promised you this
didn't look it up what you've just done look it up suck it up and hold it in your mouth and don't
spit it out that's what i'd be doing right now i'd be going and i would just keep it in my mouth and
i wouldn't swallow it goodbye miss valentine shame you didn't listen to me when you had the
chance oh no you broke my cvd picture that's fucking fun jill shoot him i can't i'll hit you
do it you have to there's no other way oh i mean what you don't think i can aim i told you i couldn't
leave you in a carless world that would just be too cruel yeah like why not just walk forward hey
just can you drag him like come just put the gun up to his forehead what about him i'll hold him
why would you need to shoot from that far away why did you do it there's a price tag for everything
even letting the world burn who are you working for i'll tell you if you get me out of here
i'll pay you whatever you want wait didn't i shoot him in the head
didn't i just shoot him with a gun i shot him like in the fucking head why is he talking
chill did i win there it is good thing we're in a plane because it missed us
no way no wait is that how it ends oh i thought it was the helicopter got hit with the missile
oh it did happen technically it technically happened we got hit by the blast technically
wait the city got destroyed finally over how is that a good ending so long i felt empty and cold
as the heat from the blast washed over us all this death wasn't caused by a monster making virus
this human greed i decided made by man is a raccoon city would be umbrellas ashes too
i would end them once and for all it was man oh that is the end biggest villain of them all
mankind and monsters is there after the credits thing it was greed no no no it was greed it was
greed actually oh sorry what the game get how many saves was it 74 it is 74 that's perfect i think
remember i told you i thought it might be a little low at 71 74 much acid go to sleep i will i will
it was still a quality experience but wasn't even close to the second one and i know that
completely different games but they are made in the same vein they released within a couple
years of each other and they're ones a direct sequel to the other one and they're both remakes
i think nemesis was done very poorly i'll just be honest i think every time nemesis shows up you
don't have to give me a cut scene i think it's more fun if he just kind of scares you even near
the end there was a lot of cases where nemesis just kind of could have just broken a wall down
as the big guy or i don't know there was a cut scene for everything that's really the only
complaint i have that's it and that's enough to bring it down a lot for me the game was fun the
actual the video game was still just as good and just as fun and just as interesting as the last
one but i just i think there's just a little too much on the uh kind of showing your hand before
you put it down what the writing yeah but they're all kind of like that though they're all cheesy
i'm still happy i played it i still think it was worth playing absolutely but i don't know if i
would put this in the category of wow if i put this in the category of yeah that was worth it
it's no animal crossing no it's not it's animal crossing now you're gonna do the final fantasy
seven remake i'm not sure about that what would i say is a fair price for the game that's hard to
give you an answer for that because this did feel like sort of an extended campaign from the second
game like if you said this was resident evil 2 a full like actual five plus hour dlc campaign
and it's like it's just the third game and it was oh hey by the way resident evil 3 dlc it's kind
of i guess it felt like it a little bit i don't i don't i think 20 i think 30 dollars would be
no that's too that's too cheap 29 99 no no no no i don't know about that it's just 60 dollars
some games are four hours some games you can beat it you can go back and play over and over again
can't really i mean it's a triple a game that releases they're all going to be 60 bucks
20 or less it's a remake though yeah but it's not like it's a code of paint it's a it's a full
completely done video game that it's not like they just put it in hd textures it's a complete
remake of the entire game and i played the resident evil 1 remake i did not
that's from the ground up um no i mean i think i think it was worth playing but it's hard to
stand them both next to each other when this one is number three and the last one is number two
and number two was way more fun that's why it's hard to kind of score this because i just
experienced like a year and a half ago two years ago uh like the one before this and this is the
one directly after it so it's kind of hard not to be like oh well this would figure maybe the
three they learned some stuff from two and everybody fucking loved it maybe they'll make
three just a better two it'll be just better but it feels like a step backwards instead of a step
forward that's why it's 74 only been a year yeah zero post credits to find out but we gotta go
i i've completely ruined every rule i've ever made uh the bits i'm gonna i'll do the bits tomorrow
tomorrow stream is not going to be very long i'll be honest with you we're gonna play tiny
tunes for a little while maybe something else but we will do both bits tomorrow how long did it take
me to break the rule i broke it like a week ago as well but me needing to get up and stretch like
an hour and a half ago or so like i have to get up starting to lock up is there actually
an other thing at the end you're breaking rules well this might not be no i said i
yeah it's an eight hour stream a no more hero but tomorrow i'll see you guys tomorrow we're
gonna do tiny tunes wacky sports adventure the super nintendo one of my favorite games
for super nintendo it should be fun depending if i get my fill of that we might move on to
something else we might move on to um some other super nintendo game maybe there you go see
yeah game exactly what i fucking gave you for a score it's perfect six and a half hours clear
in time like you gave me she will fuck you straver you're a c i deserve it fine six and a half hours
completed challenges the shop has been unlocked shop what do i have recovery coin really increases
your defense when held carry two here's your attack power when held just start with bolt cutters
start with the lockpick get the outfit get the outfit get the outfit get the outfit costume
costume weapon hot dog whoa i can afford this oh like the hot dog or get the outfit hot dog
i want to see what it does uh new game right hot dog what okay equip i want to put it on slot four
i have to kill somebody with this wait there it is give me it four i want to i just i beat the whole
game to be able to put this thing on i have to kill something go to bed go to the hole just wait i
just want to kill one enemy with this i got this new sword i'm never gonna open this game again
don't you understand i'm not gonna open the game again this is the last time i'm ever gonna see
this character i'm gonna i'm not opening this for a second time like sucks looking for a
zombie an enemy in a zombie game i can't find them and you have school tomorrow hold on mom
why don't you stand up nice cool this is cool you well this is a cheat that's it broken this
makes the whole game hard to lose oh it doesn't never mind it's i thought it was a one-hit kill
i thought it was a one-hit kill it's not a one-hit kill it just does it just looks cool
how many what is it how many what's it three four five six seven i wish i bought the costume
eight nine looks like 10 swings to kill a regular zombie okay bye see you tomorrow
take care of yourselves i'm just gonna go we will do the bits tomorrow at the end of the stream
we'll do them both don't worry please remind me to do that i am going to go uh get loose see you
guys tomorrow that was resident evil 3 remake glad i played it now i can say all right i did it
this month tonight take care of yourselves get some sleep i know we went late we're not supposed
to be doing that anymore i did i wasn't gonna play this tomorrow you know i'm not gonna i didn't
want to stream this like an hour tomorrow i'm not just not gonna do that have a great night see you
tomorrow