Hey. What's up? I'm sorry. Um, yeah. I told you guys I was gonna be live Thursday and Friday.
I did say that. But here we are on Wednesday at 8 20 at night. I couldn't wait. I wasn't gonna wait.
I'm sorry. I couldn't. I've had the Elton Ring OST playing since the stream stopped two days ago.
And it finished. It's like, yo, I want to play. Right when it got 16 hours,
42 minutes. I was like, I'm turning the stream on now. Playing Elton Ring. I don't know how long
this stream is gonna be. I don't. It's not gonna be long. I maybe a few three, four hours. I just
want to play. I want to. And then I'm just like, you know, I want to turn the stream on. Let's go.
I wasn't waiting until tomorrow. I couldn't. Is it gamer? You said Thursday. I did.
But look, let me be fair to me and this channel. I would like a show of hands. How many of you have
seen me tell you that a stream is going to be on Thursday and the stream happens on Saturday?
Show of hands, please. Hmm. Seeing a lot of raised hands. I would say that probably happens 70 to 80
percent of the time. I'll be like, oh, hey guys, it's Wednesday. Yeah, that's it. That's it for
this stream. I'll see you guys on Friday. And then like Monday morning, the suss changes being like
Tuesday. So come on. I'm go for the first time in a long time. We are we're doing early suss changes,
not late, not delays. We are releasing the streams early now. Last week or so. So this is a reverse
delay. This is something you're not used to. I know something I'm not used to. But here we are.
Midnight is very early. Well, that's true. I could be for a lot of the EU crowd. It's seven,
it's like six, what, five or six o'clock in the morning right now on Thursday. If I stream for
like another, if I stream for like four or five hours tonight, it's, it's, I was early to the
stream on Thursday. Just think of it that way. That's it. So we, we're just, I got to be very
clear though. We're getting close to some real, I probably wouldn't say real end game stuff.
This journey is getting closer to coming to an end. I know there's still a lot to do, but
I'm getting close. We've received some info last stream that was like, okay, I wonder what that
means. We're in one of the final zones of the game, unless they pull some weird shit here that I
don't know about. So, okay. Let me just give me one quick second while people trickle in.
Grab it. We're good. Where's Otto? I will show Otto at the end of the night. He's comfortable.
He's not here. He's very comfortable in another room. I will show Otto before the stream turns
off. Okay. If I do not show Otto before the stream turns off, and if the three stooges are not added
to Fortnite by April 23rd, I will eat a glove on stream. Nobody showed that to me that I, you know,
all of you forgot about it, but I made, okay. I made a thing, a bet like a year ago that said that
I was like certain that the three stooges were going to be in Fortnite. Certain of it. Just know
like there has to be, right? There's no way that's not going to happen eventually. Don't you can
already see the trailer for it. And they'd be like poking each other in the eyes and shit,
and they would be jumping over. It probably will happen, but I might just be too early for it.
The three stooges are going to be in Fortnite. I'm, I will die on this hill. The three stooges
will be in Fortnite before, before the game turns off. I'm telling you right now. I'm telling you.
Why? Why is everybody else added to the game? Look at the Fortnite roster and you tell me that
that's not, the three stooges wouldn't be there. The Fortnite skin roster right now is like the old
Smash Brothers pretend leaks. Like Mrs. Deltfire was on it and stuff. Remember back like in 2000,
like fucking 10, 2012, whatever it was. When are you going to get added? I'm not getting added
to Fortnite. Three, three stooges are too old news. This is recycled. It's not recycled. It's
a rehash. Okay. It's a rerun. There's a lot of new people here that did not hear that classic
material. Anyway, they've removed building from the game. You want, I got a theory for you.
So I got a theory. They removed building from Fortnite like a, like an event. I think they're
testing to see if people like the game more with it off. So then they just don't have to ever turn
it back on. They're mick ribbing you guys. Don't you understand? Like they're going to keep doing
this. Oh look, no building for like a month. And they're going to keep bringing it back like the
mick rib. It's going to happen like once every like six months or so. Game is actually massively
improved without it. But here's the problem. They've never added the mick rib permanently
to the menu, have they? That's what you have to look at. I'm, I'm not so sure. As, as popular as
the mick rib is, it's not on the menu permanently. They did it in German Fortnite.
The mick rib is back. Yeah. People will be saying, Oh, building, building is gone again. Look,
the non-building game mode is back and you're all going to download it. You're all going to play it.
The amount of people on my Twitter feed that are going back to Fortnite because the mick rib is back
is astounding. So be aware of that. All right. I'm going to play Elden Ring. Let's go.
Well, I look cool from it. Oh, this is where we were last. He looks young. It's going to shaved.
I shaved my face and I delete like, well, here's the thing. When I shaved my face,
I, I like lose and gain 10 years. Like I always look like 10 years younger,
but I always like somehow look like five years older as well. Because when I shave,
like this part up here gets really much more defined. Do you see like how old my eyes look
and shit? Like I actually kind of have like really old looking eyes. This carries the whole
face for me. This is, this will, this carries the entire face. I thought that was a, okay.
No game audio. Fuck. Now there is. Yeah. Like from here, damn would I look good in a Batman mask.
You understand? Like with the, like with this, like covered, like I would be a great Batman.
Your chin's too pointy. I'm that person up for an hour. Not kidding. 10 minutes. All right. So
last thing we did, uh, do a Batman voice. Not going to embarrass myself in the first five
minutes of this one. All right. So last thing I did, let's take a look at the map in the menu.
I can go do this, which is the, how am I, how can I still do that?
If I already completed that whole area, right? I can, can I actually do this?
I want to explore. Okay. Let me, I gotta make, these are marked. Let's just do it. One, two,
I'm going to check this out. I want to, I want to look at this because I want to see from the
mountain and I think I'm ready to go. We're on the mountain. This is where we are. Why is this
marked? Oh, it's cause it's a, a map thing. All right. So here we go. Uh, we're going to go to
this. We're going to go to the left of us right now, which is, uh, how late are you going to
stream? I don't know. We're just going to, I'm just going to play. I've been really, really active
in the evening hours lately as the last couple of weeks. And I blame that on my sleep schedule,
kind of getting detonated after the streamer awards. Cause I had like a
politis slash proctitis flare up that kind of fucked me up for a little while. Uh,
so I'm kind of on a weird schedule at the moment, but I'm awake. I'm alert now. Can I level up?
I can shit. All right. What am I going to do? He's a vampire. No, I'm not a vampire.
I couldn't cut it. I wouldn't, I wouldn't be cut out to be a vampire. Uh, health.
You, okay. Like drinking other people's blood. No, no, I, I don't even want to be, I don't even
want to be near anybody else's blood ever. No one tell them. That's what a vampire would say.
I don't, that's part, that's a huge part of being a vampire is drinking somebody else's blood.
But it's not something I'm going to do. That's fucking, I don't like it. I don't like, no,
I don't like blood. Nope. Werewolf. I would rather be a werewolf a hundred times. Do I have to
actually answer that question? Like vampire, you got me to get to live forever, but you have to
drink other people's blood all the time. Werewolf. You get to like change into a werewolf. That's
kind of cool. Right? Like I could just be like, I could just hang out as me. And then there's a
full moon. I just like, and I'm looking strong and shit. And like, I'm really powerful and I'm
really smart too. And I'm handsome and I have a cool tail. And I, um, I can read it at least
11th grade level after I change. All right, let's kill this guy. You got a lot of help.
Oh, it's a lot for you. I get off the horse. These guys, I can fight these guys off the horse.
I did not say that. Wait, I have a question. Is a werewolf a furry? Yes. I don't think so.
No, I don't think so. I think that's wrong. How much health does he have?
Okay. For me, a furry is somebody that is an anthropomorphic animal person. Right? That's kind
of what it is. A werewolf is somebody that is like a person that changes into a wolf, like a
wolf person at night. Are there furries that say I'm not a furry unless it's like 11 o'clock at night?
That's, that's no. Like, oh, okay. If you asked me if I was like a furry, like at like four o'clock
in the afternoon, I said no. Then like at 10 o'clock at night, you said, are you a furry?
And I was like, yeah, dude, that doesn't make any sense. Am I going to use an entire fight to kill
this guy? I'm just saying what is that? What are the rules? I don't know what the rules are.
A lot of lock on. Oh, I don't, huh? What are the cat ears? Cat is not a werewolf. Sorry. I like,
do I, I'm sorry. I like a cat is not a werewolf. And I don't want to be, okay, let me, let me
clarify this too. When I say I turn into a werewolf, like if I was a werewolf, it's not like,
oh, I'm just, I kind of like get a little taller and I get some like scruff and I have ears now.
No, like I'm going to be like a gnarled like fucking monster. You know what I mean? Like we
get fucked up looking like terrifying, awful looking like we had hunched like spine like,
like I'm not, I don't, I'm not going to be handsome looking. Let me be really clear about that.
Is that, did he drop anything? No, like a bloodborne werewolf. Yes. That is exactly what
I'm talking about. They're terrifying. Like when you turn into a werewolf, it's not like, oh, I,
my like shoulders get a little more broad and my like chin gets more defined. And I get a little
snout and ears. And I like, oh, look at me though. I'm still, I'm looking at how handsome I am. No,
no, no. I want to be one of the werewolves from fucking bloodborne. Where am I going? I don't
want to be able to talk. Right. Cause to me, that's a werewolf. Like I don't want to change into this
werewolf at night. Like, no. Okay. Um, let me think. Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde, right? Like you,
Mr. Hyde, you didn't want Mr. Hyde. Like, but at like midnight, Mr. Hyde was going to come out if
he ate food after midnight. That's the gremlins. Um, who's the werewolf? What am I, what werewolf,
what werewolf am I talking about? I know it's the fucking gremlins. I'm not like other furries.
Okay. Well, I didn't want to look at this. So I'm here. I'm not like other, I'm not, I'm just
saying I would rather, this all stemmed because somebody said, would you rather be a werewolf
for a vampire? And I don't like the idea of drinking blood. So I would rather be a werewolf.
But wait, werewolves, do werewolves eat people? I would still have to consume blood because I
would be eating people. This whole thing got fucked up because I don't, I didn't think,
I didn't think this was really that bad. Greedy. Oh my God. These guys die in one hit. Oh fuck.
That guy needs to die right now. I don't know why I didn't think he was the same insane greedy.
Oh my goodness. Oh my God. Why can't I fucking dodge this guy? It's because this little dickhead
is right next to him and it's like fucking up my timings. You were dead already like an hour ago,
it seems. Why do I feel like this baby rattle lost 80% of its range overnight? What the fuck
is going on here? Yeah. I cannot step. You are the stupidest fucking enemy in the goddamn game.
Die already. I just used eight potions. His face is red. It's always red. Don't make the werewolf
come out. Yeah, don't feed me after midnight. When I get angry, I turn into a werewolf. It's
not about the moon. It's not about like howling at the moon. Can I just be like four fictional
characters combined? Yeah, that'd be a werewolf but like with like a green Sonic the Hedgehog stripe
of hair. A gamma radiated werewolf. Okay, fuck you. Hold on. Goku. Yeah, and I'm a Saiyan. Oh, die.
OC. God, all those cars. You know, like when I think of the Hulk, that would be so awful. Do
you know how many times I just get fucking angry? It would be so bad. I would never be able to
control it. You know how many times I've been in my car just like fucking furious?
Imagine like turning into the Hulk in like your car. That would be so fucked up.
When you cut somebody off and they're like, hey, and they go like, yeah, fuck you buddy. You give
him like the finger out the window and then this person speeds by you like 15 seconds later.
Their head is outside of the car and they're big and green and they're like coming after you.
What's that meltdown? Yeah, I would be, it would be bad. So many times that I just get so just I
turn on it like just Donald Duck. You know what I mean? Like I just get so just worked up.
I would never be a good Hulk. Who's shooting a bone arrow at me? That's an invisible ridge.
Just hold on. Oh yeah. Oh yeah. Invisible Andy. Okay. Yeah. 100% that's an invisible ridge. Oh,
invisible Andy. Yeah. Game crashed. You guys crashed my fucking computer. What the fuck?
What the fuck? It just actually crashed my whole computer. I'm stuck here. Um,
okay. Hold on a second. Oh Jesus. This is bad. All right. I'll be right back if the stream turns
off. This is actually really bad. I can't even like get rid of this. I can't, I can't alt F4
the game either. Fuck. Come on. It's doing that thing with my task manager is on the same screen
as the fucking game. So I can't go to the task manager. I cannot go to my task manager. How do
I get a tab? Windows key and tab. Yeah. Let me, well, I got it. No, I didn't. It keeps going
behind the game. Yeah. I, I pull it up. Okay. I think my whole computer is going down. The whole
computer is going down. I'll see you guys in a minute. My whole computer is going down.
The whole thing's coming down. I'll be back in a minute. Fuck. What? Dude, I can't get it.
Windows tab. And then like, I can't get it. No, this, I'm going to have to, I have to restart
the computer. I got to like turn, I got to hold the power button on. Use the arrow keys. I can't.
Go look at the fucking invisible bridge. You invisible bridge Andes. I would have been fine.
Windows key plus right. Oh, it's not doing anything. I can, I can get it on my screen,
but it immediately goes away. Real tough. There's an option to have task manager always on top.
Yeah. I mean, I just selected it. Oh my God. That person, unfucking believable. You just
saved the whole stream. Yeah. You just literally saved the stream. Okay. I'm coming back. We're
good. You just actually saved the stream. Thank you. Well, I don't know how much progress we just,
we didn't really progress that much, but that was weird. What the fuck? Kind of afraid to see
where we end up now. Yeah. For those of you that want to know what I did, if you right click in
the task manager, like that little icon, you can say always on top and it worked. What an absolute
genius. Did you mod that guy? No. You should VIP him. I mean, that was pretty, that was pretty
POG, but see if they have any other POG related things in the near future. Oh, I want to show
this too. Hold on. Somebody, somebody actually made this. I need to see this on. Remember,
do you remember yesterday when I did like the comedy routine joke? Let's do that right now,
actually, before I, because my Elden Ring is like freaking out. It's like, I need to download the
cloud. So hold on. I want to do this. Not that. I love that's the last thing that was saved.
These are really romantic candles. So I made a reference. Like the stupid candle routine was
just essentially a comedy routine. So let's see how this plays out. These are really romantic
candles. Oh, it probably stinks up here. I, gosh, I filled the room with the red candles like you
wanted. Gary, you fucking idiot. Did you have to get the red cinnamon apple candle from Yankee
Candle and put it in every room? We have to, we're gonna have to fucking open the windows and not
come back here for like a week. That's one of the most powerful, that's one of the most powerful of
all the candles and I hate them. I swear to God, I can tell, I can tell when a neighbor likes one
of those candles. Drives me crazy. Is that like cinnamon, it's like the fall cinnamon cider apple
one? It's just like, no, I like it for like a second but I don't want to fill my whole neighborhood
with that. The cough at the end. That was, Marie made that. Thank you, Marie. That was really funny.
You know what's weird? Old television shows and even current television shows, they just like make
you think that something was that funny. When it just, you almost, the laugh track was sort of like
I don't want to be left out kind of thing, right? Where it's like, you don't want to be left out
because people are laughing at something. So if you don't laugh, it's like, fuck, I'm the only
person not doing that. I guess I have to. I love knowing when to laugh. I have a video that plays a
laugh track sometimes randomly during your streams. Somebody's called me a dumbass. Why?
What the hell, man? Why? Don't, dumbass. What the heck? Brew. What? I didn't do anything.
Why do you think I'm a dumbass? All right, I'm coming back. Hopefully this isn't fucking,
I don't care if that's an invisible bridge. I'm not going over there. Okay, I'm already getting
like shot by an arrow. Wait, that's it. I don't want to look at that. I am terrified to actually
go look at that. Well, you got a shirt change. Yeah. All right. Hey, let me get my bearings for
a second. What the fuck is happening? All right. I don't want, if it's going to crash the game,
what am I, I don't, I'm scared to go over there. A game crash there too. It should be fine. Now
there should be a lean down button on the horse. Just get off. All right. What's going on?
Something. Look at how weird this looks. Something's wrong here already. There's
something weird with the shadows. I don't know. This is fucking up. Look at something's wrong
with this. I don't want to be here. Look at how fucked up like the triangle shadows and shit.
Something's wrong over here. Run, run dude. Is there actually an invisible bridge here? This
whole area feels like broken. I thought the game crashed. I thought the game crashed. Okay. All
right. All right. All right. All right. So it wasn't bullshit. Wait, I need rainbow stones.
I have a shit load. Don't I have nine? I can make way more than that. Okay. Here we go. What if it
ends? It's just gonna fucking end. Where does this go? Can I throw them? I'm so afraid that it's
going to end. I think I'm already falling off. Holy shit. I can't go that way either. What? All
right. We can go this way. Oh, fuck. I'm going to run out of these things. I think I'm going to run
out. What? People are laughing at me. You lost on a straight line. What? What do you mean? I couldn't
go that way. What do you mean? It gets... What? Did I get... Are you sure? Why was I going to fall
off over there? Am I stupid? Just go. Just go. What happened there? It goes straight. Stop.
You're fucking lying. You're a liar. Oh, why does this... Okay. I think I got it. So it's only...
Okay. It's... I get it. Okay. I understand. All right. No, I'm afraid. Does this turn left?
It probably turns left here. There's no way it leads right here. It's going to go that way.
Okay. Yeah. Just run forward. Just run forward and die. I don't think those things... I hope
these things are not used for anything else. Yeah. It's a straight line, Jerma. It's a straight line.
You don't know how to run in a straight line? What the fuck? What? I see... I know I have to
go there, but I'm afraid of just going there. What keeps happening? All right. This is an
invisible wall then? It's not. Shit. This is not an invisible wall? What the fuck am I
supposed to do about this? I can't make that jump from here. Hit it multiple times.
There's nothing here, man. Why is there an invisible bridge that leads into a wall?
I don't know. This has to be a reason. Really? What's the point? What? Look for the mist.
Oh, shit. Whoa. Do these stay permanently? It looks like a Christmas decoration. All right.
I'm gonna put one here just so I remember that I can actually do this. I'm gonna put one back
there because I want to make sure I know that I can actually do this. All right. Well, that was
fucking cool. The reticle... the seal on the rise opened. I need like a bonfire or something.
I can't believe you actually did an invisible bridge. I thought you guys were fucking with me.
All right. Let's go up. Hold on. I gotta move this. Oh. Up. I need a place to heal or something.
This is probably like a memory stone or something. He almost growled at us. Memory stone? All these
rises have sorcery stuff, so why would we ever fuck with you? I don't know. You crashed my...
crashed my computer like 20 minutes ago. I'm holding you responsible for everything else going
forward. Oh, memory stone, right? It has to be. That's a legendary memory stone.
Founding Reign of Stars. Releases a downpour of star rain for a while.
Sorcery of legendary status. Summons a dark cloud of stars overhead. Shortly after the cloud will
release a violent deluge of star rain. This sorcery can be cast while in motion. It's about to be the
founding glintstone sorcery. All right. I'll try it. It's a golden legendary. Yeah. That's cool.
I'll check it out. All right. I gotta mock this. Sword means I did it and like did the thing in
there. I started to try to do that before, but I gotta start doing that because I will look at
the map and go, what's this? Heretical rise? What's that thing? That's cool. All right. So let me...
I can just leave from here. Is there... are there gonna be a bonfire somewhere in this building?
All right. Yeah. When I... people are asking like what's with the Boston accent? Anytime...
I mean, if Starlight's in the inventory, then like it's gonna come out.
Like if I have... if I got Starlight in my pocket, like I can... it'll come out.
There's what? When this comes off, if I replace Starlight, then it'll probably go away. I apologize
so I can advance. I'm sorry. I can hit it. Oh yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I forgot about that.
I want to do that too. I want to go get the remembrance so I can do cold sorceresses.
That was part of the plan too. Wait, is that a painting? It's not. You know, uh, okay. I've got
a disappointment. I've got one disappointment for you. Falling snow marks something unseen.
Oh, I did this whole... I did this backwards. I just went completely in reverse. Okay. Well,
they're weird. Uh, I've got a Elden Ring complaint for you and it's not a complaint as much as it's
I wish there were more. I thought there were going to be way more of those hidden kind of
area painting things. There's some of my favorite parts of the entire game. I wish there was a ton
of them. Going to find that one little spot is so cool. It's so fun. It's so much more like reason
to kind of go explore. There's like six in the game that I've found so far and there's probably
like 10 to 12 in the game total. I wish there was like 30. I love that. I love trying to find that
one little spot. Okay, this my computer is not happy. My computer is not happy right now here.
This area is really just like my computer hates it. I need a bonfire. So bad. I caught
him. It's actually pretty good. No horse Andy. I'm just exploring. Oh shit. This is gonna take me
down here. I don't want to do that yet. Maybe I'll get the map fragment. Yeah, let me get the map.
Just let me get the map fragment. I'll come back. That looks suspicious over there. There are seven
paintings. I did. I've done like four or five. How many we've done? Like what? Four? That's pretty
sus over there. It is. Stop making me say that. All right, seriously need a bonfire because I want
to go get the remembrance from Ronella. Are you wearing red because you're the imposter? Yes.
All right. Worst noise. So clip it and put it in your inbox or something for later this year.
I'm not going to tell you what you can and cannot nominate. Yeah, I'll get the map fragment. I'm
very curious. What was that? I don't know. Oh, Evergold. Everjail. Lord Contenders Everjail.
Should we just go here? Is there a statue here? Because I don't want to do this unless there is.
Is there a statue? There is right here. Okay. Let's just go lose. Look under your HP bar.
Oh right, yeah. Okay, let me try it. This is a boss. Let's go. Round Table Knight Mike? I don't
know what that does. What's he doing? Hey, what? An actual named boss can drink a potion
with a bar at the bottom? I don't think I've seen that. Oh, fuck. Oh, he's trying to drink
another potion. Oh, don't be greedy. Oh, fuck. A clean finish. Mike's Dragon Bolt. Fingerprint
helm. That was a clean fight. Somebody just said, where is that? I'll show you right now.
It is in the mountaintop of giants. Looks like along this road that comes down here. I don't
know the map fragments. Sorry. It's this Everjail. Lord Contenders Everjail. What does that say?
Bolsters right hand, armament, and body with red lightning. Incantation of Vike,
Knight of the Round Table Hold. Summons red lightning to bolster both the caster's body
and their armament held in the right hand. So it enchants your weapon with red lightning.
Enchants armament with lightning affinity attacks and increases maximum equipment load.
That's weird. This is the From Software armor? What do you mean? Fingerprint armor.
Iron armor signed and blistered by fingers. Born by Vike, Knight of the Round Table Hold.
No other Tarnished was closer to the throne of the Elden Lord than Vike.
But without announcement, Vike traveled far below the capital and was scorched by the flame of
frenzy. Did he make his choice for his maiden or did some other force lure him with suggestion?
Oh, it's Box Art Andy. Really? Is it? Box Art Andy. Okay. This helm is potentially better than
what I have on, but it doesn't boost sorceries. Is this the Box Art? I thought the Box Art had
like kind of hair coming back. Old goat gauntlets? What the fuck are these? Fingerprint greaves.
All right, I'd like my setup right now. The raging wolf armor is the Box Art armor. Yeah,
I thought the Box Art had hair out there. Using the trailer armor. That was cool. That's a cool
spell too. I wonder if it's any good. But it's a From Software game, so no, it's not going to be.
That'll go on the list of like, okay, From Software like spell tier list. Let's say we have S, A,
B, and whatever. Literally B, A, B, C, and D don't matter. There's like five moves that are at S
and then 70 that are at do not equip, like at the very bottom, like under F.
So probably looks cool. You should equip a branch. I got 100,000 souls. This is gonna get ugly real
quick. I need a I need a bonfire. Min-max Andy. I mean, I'm obviously just, you know, taking a piss,
but not these. Yeah, but whenever I get a new spell, it seems I'll be like, oh, dude,
star shards from outer space. And the sea of chat is just like, oh, no, dude, they're worthless.
It's like fucking awful. It takes like 80% of your mana bar, and it does like 12 damage. It's like,
oh, okay. Oh, Glimblade of the Distressed Soldier. No, dude, don't even put it on.
It's way too slow, and just swinging your regular weapon will hurt for more.
Okay, I guess. All right, I'm gonna die from one of these. Get on the road.
Ooh, what's this? Thank you. Although it's fun to have like the sorceries and then some of the
incantations. They're cool. Founding stars is OP though. You should talk to, wait, can I talk?
I can. All right, shh. We're almost there. The Flame of Ruin lies just ahead. Just ahead. I'm glad
it was you I traveled with. I must tender my thanks to Torrent too. Thank you, Torrent.
Please continue to lend your aid till the end. There is something I'd like to say. My purpose
was given to me by my mother, but now I act of my own volition. I have set my heart upon the world
that I would have, regardless of my mother's designs. This is America's daughter. It's America's daughter.
Not even you. Man, it is, right?
Can you talk to her again? I don't think so. Oh, right. I want to try that new move. Let's see.
Come on, From Software. Give me a move that's not swift boring glint blade, swift pebble stone.
That was works and is good. Can't take that off. Where is it? Oh, it takes two slots. All right,
a hundred and how much FP does it cost to do this? That lasts a long time. Okay.
Let's test it out on this unsuspecting loser right here. Hey, just stand right there for me,
if you will. It's okay. It's all right. I mean, it's actually that would be really good if the
group is chasing you around. I did. I charged it. Let's just aggro everybody. Let's like see what
happens. All right, let's go like fucking run around. Somebody come and get me. It kind of
hurts my eyes. Probably good for stationary large bosses. That's true. I'll leave it on.
It hits large enemies a lot. Okay. It doesn't actually take that much mana as much as I thought
it was going to. I thought it was going to be a lot more. Let's go. It's a cool spell. I like it.
Charge it. I am. I've charged it every time. Do you want me to prove it to you? I've been doing
that every time. It's kind of like a dot. Okay. Here's why I'm going to keep it on. Its surface
area is actually huge and it lasts a very, very long time. It doesn't take that long to cast it
either. So I think it could be supplemental. She just said that like this is the end of the
game coming up here. She's like, oh, here it is. This is right ahead. Right. I'm kind of afraid
to do this right now. I'm right. Like I don't want to do this. I don't want to end the game.
Oh, okay. All right. I don't, I don't hate it. I actually think it's kind of good. Oh, it hurt.
Oh, I thought I fell off the cliff. Why did I just have an accent?
Why did I just have like a Italian accent? Oh, damn. I don't know why. I just had like a,
I had like a European accent for a second there. What was that?
Don't just run around. What's going on with my voice? It's because I have two headphones in.
I have two. I can't hear myself talk. So like, it's weird. Holy shit. What is that thing?
Walk over here. Huh? Why did it turn off? I can't cast it multiple times.
I want it to rain down on these motherfuckers. It was patched. Was it actually? Can't cast two of
them. Yeah, that's kind of annoying. I need to swap out some stuff because I'm doing too much like
click, click, click, click, click, click, click, click, click, click, click, click, click, click,
the herd tree chest. Uh, I still, I want the map fragment. I'll all right. Mark this right here.
Remember to remind me to come back to two because I want to go inside of there,
but I want the map fragment and we're going to go get it. I gotta go get the other staff too.
It's so good. All right. Somebody said fuck toad.
All right. Let's see if we can get a triple here. It's truly amazing. What do you say? What
moonlight spell? How did you get the moon blade? Uh, it was, I forget. Oh no, it's from the dragon.
It's from the glint stone dragon that's in front of, um, that hangs around the Ronnie's, um,
and the rises, right? It's from the magic dragon. Keep going. I want the map fragment.
These are weird. Is it a little, um, statue like things? Oh God damn it. Where is the
map fragment? It's not all the way down there, right? Oh, it's right there. Isn't it?
This is a no. Okay. It's probably right here. That's right there. Jesus. These guys alive
and not. Oh, I thought that was one of those ghost people to talk to. This is a rock.
I didn't skip the castle. No, no, no, no, no. I'm coming here to get the map fragment first.
I'm, I just want the map fragment. There we go. All right. Now I can see what the hell is going
on here. All right. So this is where this looks. What is that? I don't know, but I'm not skipping
this. I just wanted the map. I can see where the hell I was. There's also something really
interesting here, which is what we're going to look at. I'm going to go do the fort here.
Is there a random mog like enemy incoming? I'm going to go in there. No,
no, it's not what we're doing. Where is the, where's the bell place? It's like here somewhere,
right? I want that remembrance because I want that stuff. Where is it? Hurry up and tell me.
Where is it? Northeast Lake. Fucking hurry up. When I asked something, I expect there to be
something in the fucking chat immediately. None of this like talking, talking, like hanging out,
having fun. No, when I asked something, fucking answer it. Fucking unbelievable. Where was it?
Where? I didn't even see it. Stop spamming the chat. I'm quitting tomorrow. I quit. I quit tomorrow.
Wait, where is it? The Eastern part of the lake. Worst face. Werewolf face. I'm sorry, the moon,
the moon's up. Northeast. I'm just going to go here. Northeast next to the castle. Like right
over here around. I'll just go look around for it. Yeah. It's like, isn't it right here?
It was walking around here. You've changed. I know. I know. Just like, I just hate being here.
All right. Would you guys, let me ask you a question. Those are the viewers.
Right. Would that be, okay. If I was like that, would that be funny? Would you be watching to
watch me have like a meltdown? Is that like funny? Or like, would you like not, would you be like,
nah, I don't want to watch this guy. This guy like is a fucking dick. He's like always hates like
Hey, who did that? Oh, depends on if it's a joke. Yeah. I'd be sad. No, it's never going to get there.
Don't worry. You guys already know the minute that I'm not having a good time anymore. It's
like, all right, that's it. Right? Like that's it. That's not, don't worry. I would subscribe for
like meltdowns. Would you? Well, I think I already do that. North like up here. Did I,
I feel like it's not over here. Is it even further up here? East literally. You literally
looked at it. North east of regular area here. It's to the east. You're staring at it. Oh,
but like my view distance is low. I actually haven't made this one sit down. Did I? Yeah.
I made the other ones. There's a lot of fucking people here. Your IRL view distance. Yeah. This
one's not moving for like my head and the bell. Uh, there's nothing to brush off either. I have
to do something else. Yeah. Ring the bell. That's what I'm gonna try. I don't think I can hit it.
Um, there's a dungeon over there that I didn't do. Ah, me strong will do it. All right. Except
what about the people that are around the bell? Maybe if I aggro the people that are around the
bell, right? That makes sense. All right. So it's just like, okay, here it goes. I'm like whacking
the spirits over here and you can hear the screams of the spirits to jump on it. How the fuck am I
supposed to jump on it from here? I'm up there. Teleport to this grace above, like up here. You
mean bugged? It's supposed to be moving. Give me the item. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay.
So I have to jump from up here. We're going down together. How am I supposed to land on that?
I don't understand. How am I supposed to land on that? Okay. Is it like one of those is this soft?
Wait, I already have one of these right here. I get to use this one. Okay. Cool. Oh, oh,
I need the other one. How am I supposed to get onto that? I definitely, it's probably a jump from
here and you can, it's probably soft enough on top where it doesn't kill you. But if it does,
just know that this is an experiment. Somebody said it's bugged. It's supposed to be moving,
but I mean, would the game really be this bugged over and over again after loading like three
times? Kill that guy real quick. All right. It's a clear. It is moving. Fuck. It was bugged.
It was bugged. Come on. Is it only moving certain times of the day? I can't make it from here. So
we're going to have to go back to where I was. They sleep at night. Well, let me make sure it's
daytime, like right in the middle of noon or whatever. Well, you, your runes. I don't get out
of bed for less than 50 K. It was 45. Not what I said. I'll get them. Don't worry. Have you ever
played Ocarina of Time? Oh yeah. I played Ocarina of Time when it came out. I remember sitting there
playing in my bedroom. Game had just just released and it was like, holy shit, this is crazy.
Old. I mean, yeah, I was old. I mean, I mean, I am old. I don't know. How old was I? When did
it come out? Like 1996 or something. Okay. So how does this work? 1998. 24 years ago. 24, 25 years
ago. I was 14. 13. I don't know. All right. So how do I do this now? Does it have a gunk on it?
Oh, you piece of shit. It's going that way. I have to, I have to jump over here, right?
I, yes, I definitely have to jump from right here. It's going to keep walking just over there.
So it's like here. I, okay. All right. Get the runes too. Stop. What? What? I can't get it from
here? This kills me. I'm going to be pissed. All right. My runes are right here. Let's get those.
And then I have to jump from like over there. There. Right there.
Fuck you. So I just want to get there now. You know what I mean? Like I don't want to like,
I want to just fucking get there. I don't want to just do this. Get me there now. Right now.
God damn it. It's not from the cliff. What do you mean? It's not the cliff. What the fuck?
It is from the cliff. Minus 45k. I don't, at this point, I don't care.
I'll go get them in a minute. Should we have sprint spring on the lake? What is a sprint spring?
Is this Sonic the Hedgehog? What's a sprint spring? Sprint spring? Horse jump. That's,
you should just say horse jump. Sprint spring doesn't, no, it's a horse jump. Horse jump.
It's fucking midnight. I didn't think this was going to take this long to go get this stupid
remembrance. If I had known this was going to take this long, I would have just fucking
burnt the urn tree by now. What? Look, everybody's got all the, okay, there's like 17 endings in this
game, right? You're, you're bad. You're, they're all bad. You're all, there's no good. Oh, I'm a good
person. No, you burn the urn tree. You eat the fucking fire. You kill the fingers. You
kill the lady. Like, there's none, there's nothing good. There's no like, oh, you're a good guy.
No, there is no good person ending. There's like, kill this person or like eat this person, right?
We're going to end up eating someone or burning something. So I, look, I don't know what you want
to tell you. There, there is no like, oh, that's a good one. No. Okay. I'm ready to move on from
this or I freak out. Meat grinder ending. There's never been a good ending in a souls game. That,
yeah, that's, all right. So where's this, uh, spring pad? I don't see a spring pad. Don't
crush me. Spring pad. Oh, there it is. There's the sprint spring. All right. Now get over here.
What time is it? What time is it? What time is it? What time is it? What time is it? What time is it?
No, I thought it was stopping. Jump on him with the spring.
Wow. You are full of shit. You are full of shit.
Get over here. Just wait. Have you fought the fallen? Yeah, I killed it in one hit.
You can double jump. Can I? He's close. He's closer. He's closer. Okay. He's close.
Oh my God. I can't. Why are you not over here yet?
Why do you take so long to get over here? You're not going the other way, right?
All right. For everyone telling me to look at its feet. That's not how you do this one.
The fuck is right there. All right. This motherfucker is right there. You were lying
to me. It's not the jump. You were lying to me. It's over there. Okay. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
literally lying to my face. Got it.
What happened? Why did that happen? I have to wait again. I have to go from a lower one. Hey,
okay. I'm going to give this five more minutes before we're going to eat this controller.
So we just, okay. I, so I was right. Who needs the thing? I, I could go from here.
I actually could go from here. You guys, I had it right from the very beginning.
No, no, you got to go down. Let me explain what you guys told me to do. You got to go
down to the lake to jump up from the spirit jump to where you were already standing. I was
already there. I, like, I would get to this edge and there were those gravestones. Remember I died
from them and you guys were like, no, dude, you're fucking stupid. You're a fucking idiot. This is
wrong. And I'm like, it's wrong. What do you mean? No, you got to go down to go up to where you are.
Uh-huh. What? Okay. So it's over here. Wait, where am I? Why is there to be so foggy down there?
See, look at all this shit. I have to go right there. Okay. See, that's where I was going.
And everybody told me you go, don't fucking rush it. Don't rush it. I rushed it. I rushed it. I
rushed it. I put a quick game. Okay. I'm just, okay, I just fucking get a trainer and just get
the resemblance. I don't want to do this again. I don't want to do this at the 15th time. This
requires patience. I just need patience, man. I just need patience. I'm going to do it wherever,
okay, I'm going to go from here. I'm going to go up the thing. This is so fucking easy.
I just don't want to spend the five minutes to wait for his slow ass to go over to the edge.
Why can't I just fucking punch him? Why can't I just? This resemblance better be worth it.
Otherwise I'm going to be pissed. This dude can't even jump on a building. I did jump on a building
and it killed me. Now I'm being told, well, Jerva, you actually went off. You have to go
from a little bit lower. I'm like, okay. Dude, this is a kid's game. Relax. This game is not for kids.
I'm not sure what would be like. Okay. Those like Elsa Spider-Man videos and like Elden Ring.
I don't know what could be worse for a child's brain. So I, you know what I mean? Like this is
not a kid's game. Don't let a kid play this. My little sister plays this game. Don't let it. Don't
let a child play this. Time is it. It's moving. Okay. Simple. It's so simple. It's easy right there
all down to a level where I can jump on it and just jump onto it. It's going to be worth it.
I'm going to become a cold sorcerer. Simple. It's so easy. Here we are. We're right here.
It's so easy. My sister's 24. Well then. All right. But yeah, don't don't do. Okay. Get off the
horse. The horses make overcomplicates this. How low do I need to be? This is where I jumped from
before. So all right. If I go from, oh my god. Okay. If I go from here, there's no, there's nothing
else I can jump from. This is the only one I can jump from. There's no other one to jump from.
Now we just have to wait an hour. Shit. It's not over there, right? It's not over there. It's
definitely here. You need to fight Mog. When I eventually get to Mog, I'm gonna snap his neck.
I'm gonna sneak up behind Mog and just grab him. Just, just turn. Turn. Uncle W. It's Mog. It's a
Mog. What do you mean? Oh no. But sneaking up on sneaking up behind Mog with a fucking
sword this long and shoving it through his back. Oh fuck. But I say I'm going to snap Mog's neck.
Oh my god. Relax. Oh my goodness. Now? Nope. Nobody said if you, I bet a three day ban,
you don't make it. If I make this ban that person for three days. Hold, hold, hold, hold, hold.
I gotta get up there. You're about to be banned for three days. Turning around.
Ah! God damn it. I actually can't believe it. He's turning around. Was he not turning? I thought
he was turning around. What am I doing this for? Because there's an item in there that I really,
really need. Was he turning around though? It looked like he was turning and walking the other
way. Is it actually the jump from the horse? Go get a different one. I'm begging you. There's a
different one. Where's the other one? There are like eight. This island south of Limgrave.
One down here. But wouldn't, isn't this one, do you have to do the certain ones? I thought it like,
it didn't, it's not tied to the area? No. How come I couldn't get Ranales from the one I just went
to? It wasn't available. Behind the, next to the shack on the left side. Okay. Some are minor.
The ones with bells are the ones you need. Oh. Oh. Oh. So is this one weird or is this one just
clean as feet? This one's definitely just clean as feet. Okay. Sure. Let's go.
Why would this make walking harder? Wouldn't this make walking easier?
All right. Finally. So, fucking sick. Let's go. All right. We want Ranales.
Oh, that's so annoying. All right. I want Ranales remembrance. I want the staff from, you know,
because I want to do cold. Now, please confirm this. The full moon sorceries are cold sorceries.
Please. I'm asking you. This is, this is cold. Full moon sorcery is cold sorcery.
What's the point of me doing this? It's just the moon ones. But is, my sword counts.
But like, I think so. I hope so. It buffs all magic. It boosts moon sorcery. It doesn't boost
your sword. No, no, no. I'm talking about, I don't want to just waste this if this is wrong.
I need some lore masters to tell me. This moon blade is a moon sorcery. Right? It won't boost
the moon blade. Moon sorcery is different. No. Well, why am I doing this? It won't boost the
sword. Only moon spells. It does not boost the moon blade. Why am I doing this? Moon blade counts
as a carrion sword. Did one guy put up, put like an hour on this stream of us going and doing this?
Because the whole, the whole point was to get that new staff. It's a good staff regardless.
Carrion glintstone staff is the one that boosts this spell. Do I have that? I'm going to sorcerers
that might enact the role of knight enhances carrion sword sorceries. This is, that's a carrion,
but it's an OP staff. You're already here. Might as well just do it. I already told me to do this.
The best staff and upgrades the moon spell, which is the best spell in the game.
It's a snow witch sorcery. Well, then I'm going to have to get some more moon shit.
I mean, what do I need? I need 60 int to put this on. Moon does not matter. Only two moon spells.
It's the best. This is, is this the best? Whatever. I'm just, I'm buying it. I'm going to take it
because I'm going to use it eventually here, but a boost full moon sorceries.
It starts. This is also as scaling. That was a great, like 45 wasted minutes. Let's, let's,
let's continue the play through. Do you think so? Oh, duplicate it again to get the moon.
This was a filler episode. No, it's not. We're about to do real fucking content. You better get
ready. The moon is too slow. All right. Enough. Get, I'm going to get my fucking runes and we're
going to continue to play the game. And, uh, that was, you know, great content. It was, uh, about
30 to 40 minutes of just wasted time. Um, all right. Runes are long gone. What do I mean? Wait,
are they? Your runes are gone away. I didn't have 40,000 runes. It died, died like 10 times.
Oh yeah. Don't worry. You don't get out of bed for less than 50 K hypers.
So what's at this lake? Probably a monster. Let's explore the lake. Oh, I like the ice.
Something's going to come through the ice. I love this ice. Look at it's breaking. Yeah. I can see
the game. I can see the video game engine. I can see it. It's pieced together. Something's
breaking out of this ice. It's going to be an ice dragon. I'm going to come through the ground
and it's going to be insane. I was going to make sure I get a good view. Something here.
Where is it? Just heard it. What the fuck? That was quick. My fucking God. I'm awful.
Oh my God. I'm not good. Ash of war. Sepuku. Sepuku. Use one swords. Uh, Sepuku, a forbidden
technique used by swordsmen from the lands of reeds. Punch the blade into your stomach
to stain it with blood. Increases attack power and improves ability to inflict blood loss.
That's probably amazing. That sounds incredible. Get that on a fast weapon. It's OP. Yeah. It's
really OP. I imagine. All right. Where's the ice dragon? I want a good view. Right here. Here
it comes. Come on. Give me a good view. Yeah. Oh, here it comes. Here it comes. Where is it?
I didn't get a good view. It's an ice dragon, isn't it? It is an ice dragon. I told you.
I was certain we were getting an ice dragon right here. This motherfucker definitely drops
ice sorceress. You know it. Force force. I thought, okay, this is why I didn't move.
Why? I thought I didn't. I thought it was going up to do the thing where it hovers and then lands.
So I was going to dodge it and then get on the horse. Oh, you know what? That's not a bad idea.
I can cast this on the horse. Holy shit. What? Are you serious? I can actually do that? I'm in a
fucking weird mood. I'm sorry. Can you please do the me strong stream after you beat the game?
Everybody wants the me strong stream, but I don't know if I want. It's like, I don't want to like.
Oh, okay. Why did I do that back there? Holy shit. Actually kind of good. It's actually awful here.
Yeah, it's awful. He moves around. Stamina, please. Where are you going? What are you doing?
That was weird. Oh shit. What the fuck? Wait. Oh, my eye. It hit me in the eye. That felt
like it hit me in the eye in real life. I feel like my eye hurts. It hit me in the eye.
I can't see. It like scratched my eye. I like that scratched my eye. That was crazy.
What? There's no power. That was, I feel like it hit me in the face. Okay. Um, it was like,
was that 3D for anybody else here? That really felt like 3D. Like it came out of the screen and like.
Okay. Um, so there's no, that's unfortunate. I thought I was going to get like an ice power.
Well, that's cool though. There goes that dragon. That means we have completed that area.
Market. I didn't have any. Okay. Well, wait, hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. That's not it.
Let's take a look out around the edges. Oh, it's a faith. Right, right, right, right.
You have a hundred thousand runes. I'm not going to lose a hundred thousand runes right now.
I already lost 50k. I'm just checking in the area. There's nothing else here.
Exactly. That's why I came here. I want to take a look. I like this area. This area makes my teeth
hurt. It's kind of cool. So that's just a big dragon. So, uh, this is a good place to wrap around.
Wait a minute. No, no, no, no, no, no, no. Yeah. The edge of the, uh, lake is a thing over there.
I think probably like a church. This game is physically hurting you. Old era. Yeah. Like
it makes you turn purple too. Syn, synesthesia. What is that? It is a church. All right. I actually,
I'm pretty desperate for a better heal for this one in here. You need to replace your dentures.
Zomberstone miners bell bearing. Oh, thank God. Yes. Nice. Nice. Nice. Very nice.
250 vitality. I think I have like 42. There we are. A sacred tear. What do you have to say?
Spoken echoes linger here. Words of Queen Marika who vanished long ago. If you wish,
I will share them with you. I'm interested. It's you and this is America. America's own words.
Hark, brave warriors. Hark, my Lord Godfrey. We commend your deeds. Guidance hath delivered
you through each ordeal to the place you stand. Put the giants to the sword and confine the flame
atop the mountain. Let a new epoch begin an epoch glistening with life. Brandish the Elden Ring
for the age of the tree. Yeah. Um, and I'm using the bathroom right now. There are no baths. I,
I dig a hole and I go and this is kind of a weird time for you to be here. Appreciate the help though.
Classic fucking joke. Oh, oh, my mouth. What the fuck? Somebody this game's hurting me.
I just like bit a piece of skin off. This game hurts me. I like bit my skin on my lip
and it was like, ow. Oh, that's it. Wait, do you have any more to say?
Oh, that's cool. Pretty cool, dude. Uh, I definitely need to, how many, how much do I have?
I need 60 to put that staff on. So let's see what I have the talisman. 58. I need two more
int and I can put the staff on. I think I might be able to get close. Let's find out.
I think it's because you have a UTI. Thanks doc.
Secret tier. Oh, sorry. My ear was itchy. I could do that too. I had five. I thought I only had four.
Oh shit. All right. We'll do tenon, the tenants break. Very cool. So I did this. Let's market
just as completed. The sword means it has been complete. There is this bird tree. We're going
to do the urge tree. I'm gonna just head this way. What was over here? I'm not going to teleport
because it might be something on the way. There's also this volcano manor thing, which I thought I
couldn't do. Okay. That sounds like a plan to me. Keep going. What about the fort? Isn't that,
isn't that this here? Fort to the north. Do you not see a marker on it? There's a marker on it.
Fight Mog. I will fight Mog when I feel like it. And now I'm going to wait till the final stream.
I'm going to summon him. I'm going to, I'm going to use his item,
like on the edge of a cliff. I'm going to summon him in front of me and he's going to fall like
wily coyote style and die. Back over here. All right. That can go that way. What's this? Ooh,
there's a spring jump and there's a casket. This is uncovering.
Don't get me dogs. That's actually kind of good against dogs, even though I use like three potions.
Oh yeah. Yup. Yup. Yup. Yup. I can definitely level up now.
And then I'm going to have to commit to putting a bunch of stones into that thing.
I hope that's actually a good staff and it wasn't a huge mistake.
Best move in the game. I don't think it's the best move in the game.
You know what's really crazy about this? Like these caskets, they're kind of everywhere.
People are like coming out of these caskets and coming back to life.
Weird. Why are these like tarnished? It's interesting. These are because there's been
at least like two of these in every single zone and they always have the little runes on them.
Like that's the last little bits of their like souls or something. They all, yeah,
they like wake up and like get up and start walking around. Really weird, but let's do this.
Is that, is there anything else down there that I didn't, it might be a dungeon down here though.
It's probably a dungeon here. Just look. Is it gonna kill me? It's gonna, it's gonna kill me,
isn't it? Let me see if there's like dungeon right here. I feel like there would be. It's not. Stop
using the baby toy weapon. It's, it's really good. It's been great so far. Why, why would I stop
using it? It's been actually fantastic. It's been a great weapon. It's helped. It's been amazing.
It's been, it's actually been a really good weapon. It's a great weapon. Why would I check it up?
It's low to mid. Whatever. It's a great, it's a great weapon. It's a good weapon.
I like it. Guardian's Garrison. Oh my god, there's another fucking dog. Okay. Okay. Okay. We've got
him. Okay. What the fuck? I can't fucking do it. What's happening? Somebody get in there and die.
This is the most chaotic, sloppy piece of shit I've ever seen. This is, look at how sloppy this is.
What a sloppy piece of shit that was. That item, I feel like I'm like, oh wow, one, two, three,
four, five. There are five enemies there. Let me like, cast the cloud of raining crystals.
And I just aggro like eight people. I'm, I'm, okay. This is why I don't like using the sorceries that
often. Cause you just like stand still and like move one mile per hour to go like this. Cause you
really so badly want the move to look cool and to work. And then you just end up aggroing like
fucking 30 people. And then I, oh, I want to like, oh, it's going to kill like those four people.
I could have hit those guys three times and they would die. One, two, three, die. Like why do I need
to go like, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Oh dude, it did like 150 damage. Just kill them.
Kill them. Like this. Ready? Watch this. I'm gonna fucking stab it up.
Sucks too. All right. See, it happened to you too. You could have just swung the fucking sword at me
twice and killed me. Instead you have to show your chat, like the cool move you have.
And then it got you killed. When are you going to play the real Dark Souls? Like Dark Souls one?
He doesn't know how to dodge. Bro, I beat nobody in the game first try so far. So nevermind.
Time that person up for five minutes though. All right. So what do we got here?
Didn't go through that. Come on. I said, do something funny. I feel like the last five
minutes straight have been funny of me trying to like, I feel like that was funny.
Was that not funny? I feel like it could have been funny. I feel like that was funny.
I feel like the last like an hour has been kind of funny because I went on a wild goose chase for an
hour through a thing I didn't even need to do. And like a few people in chat were telling me
that I could have gone another way and I didn't listen to them. And I just literally jumped off
a cliff 13 to 14 times in a row. It was kind of funny. It was kind of funny. Oh, you want,
you want me to do something funny? Like you want me to like tell a joke? Okay, I get it. Um, sure.
Why did the flame guard, why does this person have a name? What the fuck was that? Uh, why did
the chicken cross the road? To get modded and ban that guy for a day. All right, I need to go up.
He's power hungry. Yes, I am. These late night streams, I swear to god, I'm fucking wrong with
me. I promise if you're like a new viewer, I promise I'm not this weird all the time.
Sometimes, but not all the fucking time. Not the whole time. I don't think I think I have to go
on the edge. Maybe like up that way. Is there a ladder here? Shit, I didn't see the ladder.
People keep calling you a psycho. What's your response? Um, I don't know. How do I respond to
that? First, I say I just, you know, it's me just hanging out fucking around. And I think I would
say I would, I don't think that's accurate. I would say eccentric. All right, let's check.
Oh, nice. Anybody that calls themselves eccentric is usually, is there anywhere else I can do over
there? Cool. I can get up. All right, go that way. I'm not, no, I'm kidding. I'm not like calling.
I'm just fucking around. Well, a good thing I, I did not know you're in here and you're a way
scarier dog. Jesus, chief guardian. What's this? What the fuck? What was that? All right. That was
kind of annoying. That was like one, two, three, but that was quick.
Dogs can't climb ladders, right? That'd be actually kind of funny. It's like somebody
mastered the art of becoming a human. Is that me? I have no idea what you're talking about.
These guys give a lot of, uh, souls. Keep going. I'm usually the joker. Yeah. All right. Where does
this guy even come from? Oh, he's here. The whole, all right. I get to go, go, go, go, go,
priority priority. Shit. Bad. Very bad. Very bad. Get the souls and just die. I'm alive. I'm
alive. Get me out of this room before he kills me. This is a stupid fire thing. God the fuck out
of here. Oh my God. This guy's got a, it's going to be hard. That shield protects tons of magic
damage. Jesus. That's awesome. Can I have that? It's free. Just spam it. Oh, I'm alive. One-eyed
shield. That guy was worth a lot of souls. That was fun. Okay. So what is that? 36 strength.
Great shield. Brick some shield made from white stone depicting a malformed one-eyed god.
Barrel of a firearm pokes through the open mouth. Once worshiped by the giants, this evil deity is
believed to have been slammed by Queen Merica. Evil deity. So you get the cannon. This doesn't
require anything besides strength. So that's actually really cool. I wonder how much damage
it does when you upgrade it. This one's cool too. This doesn't require faith. This is the big fire
one. This one needs way more strength though. The gun shield. That's cool. Very cool. All right. So
continue. I think that was a pretty good sorcery fight. It does about 2100 damage to adds. Wow.
That's actually pretty good. 2000 damage. I hear a cookie bug. You hear it? I heard it. I swear to
God. I heard it. It's not the rattle. Maybe it's up. Okay. It's probably up. Yeah. I love these
Elden Ring streams. I had a great time. I feel like something's going to get up.
Giants prayer book. What does that teach you? Giants flame take thee. Flame fall upon them.
I have a feeling that's faith. But that's cool though. Are there any mimic chests in Elden Ring?
Surprisingly no. I guess they didn't. Wait. Can I jump from here? I guess there was uh maybe lore
wise. There's no reason to have them but there's like trap chests. Not really. Yeah. I don't know.
I haven't really found one. I think I would have seen one by now. All right. Well that's cool.
Unless there's something else I can do over here which probably is. Can I do anything else this
way? I don't think so. After you beat it do you think you'll still stream it once in a while? These
streams are really fun. Okay. There's a nightmare. Uh the plan is to so after I beat it whenever that
is I want to do a couple of like kind of co-op like pvp sort of community nights where maybe
I'll do the me strong stream. It's possible. But I want to do where I just have a password and we
just do pvp. I also want to do just like invasion streams where I just kind of invade or if they
turn on invasions just kind of fuck around. I think I pretty much cleared it. Maybe there's
something else I didn't see but it's all good. This is like a back entrance. All right the next
marking is up here. You have a group password. Um I don't have online turned on right now but I will.
All right let me get out of here. So that is that. Decide on a password right now. Um
I don't have a password. I'm not going to give you a password. I did that. That was cool.
I got the prayer book and a couple of little things. Now we're going this way. I want to do
there's a marker that I have over here. Is this the volcano manor thing? This here. The urd tree
which is here. Let me put a marker on this because it is done. This is also done. I'm going to put a
marker there just because I there was an item behind that. All right I also need to go down
here at some point. So we'll do that after. Um I'm still looking up here. Go to this point here.
Go to the northern fort. I will. I'm just kind of making my way around. All right we need to go to
one. One is the urd tree like that over here. Like and maybe I can't get up here from here.
You look great for somebody with lego hair. Thanks. I hope it stays for another few years at least.
I got no gray hair is really either which is really surprising. I'm happy with the hair right
now. If it takes me into like 40 that'd be great. I've already been this way. It's probably better
to go from here. Unless let's go to this. Who asked? Somebody did. Are you on any hair medication?
No. I don't have any. I don't take any like medication for it or anything.
Just there. I am going to assure you though that it's it's not gonna it's gonna go. When it goes
it's gonna go. Ah there it is. All right. But it's all right. Whatever. I okay. I did not think
remotely that I was going to have hair for this long. I really didn't. Shack of the law.
Traveling maidenhood? Like a maiden outfit? Wood worn by traveling maidens.
Maidens traverse the lands between for different reasons. Some just seek audience with the fingers.
Others to find the tarnished who they were destined to guide. Stop! What's happening over here?
Finger maiden. Traveling maiden. What's the difference? Traveling maiden? Okay. Is there a
I do not see. I'm kind of afraid of this. Is there not a grace over here? Okay well I I I
there's no grace here. I don't think. What is there one over here? Day one of German not reading my
messages. Start the counter over again. Nothing here. Wait what's that? Okay there might be
something right there. I don't want to do this until I have I have too many souls to lose.
Let me see if this one right here. What are you doing here? All right let's check and see if
this one here. Is there a grace? All the way up. Did I go in those? Oh shit. I'm going in here.
Star gazers ruins. All right well there's definitely a dungeon here.
Maybe not but you know. I did have this marked anyways. I had it marked. Is there you held shut
by a seal? It is this. It's this. It is this. Can I talk? Summon a jellyfish here. Does that do
anything? Does it work? These things are like. Did I lose that? A seal was broken. Did I lose
that summon? Still here. Let's just get this shit out of me. Where is it? Oh that's a grovel for
mercy. Curt C? No it's like spin. Where is it? Okay I see it. Okay so now what's down here?
Oh fucking starlight. I'm annoying I think. Primal glintstone blade. Spells consume less
FP but maximum HP is reduced by a lot. Oh my god. This is almost. It's 300. It's not. It's worth it.
That's a lot of HP to lose. That's too much HP to lose. That's a lot of HP. Try it. Okay so what does
it do with it all? Is it like 30% or so? I mean it seems significant. Keep in mind the staff that I
have on is makes me. Everything cost more. It's definitely doing a little bit. That's two, three,
four, five, six. Okay so what about with it off? Is it maybe one extra spell? One. It's two extra
spells. It's. I can cast two more times. That's actually kind of good. That health reduction
though is really really bad. Where's my health right now? It's like right at the edge of the compass.
Oh yikes. That's bad. I'll try it for a little while but I can't promise I'm going to keep this on.
Although. Especially when I start using the other staff. Once the other staff goes on it's reduced
by even more because this staff makes me cast faster but everything costs more. Very cool.
Well that's probably worth it. We'll see. I'm open to trying it. It did replace the
FP from killing enemies though which hasn't really been that much of a factor.
I will be honest over the last stream or two. I need to level up because I have enough to put
the new staff on and we're going to commit to it. That was kind of that was kind of ridiculous.
All right cool. So now we need to go here. Is there a grace here somewhere though? Come on man.
Can't wait for the Elden Ring vids. Are you going to replace the baby rattle?
At this point I don't know if I can. I have enough probably somber stones or smithing stones
to get something like plus seven but I still have not found the final smithing stone yet.
At least for the somber variety. I don't know. I need to be down. Hey what the fuck is it this?
Is that is this a boss? Oh my god don't hurt him. He's shooting fucking laser beams at me.
Can I not target him? Come on go. This runs out. Whack him. He's get out of this like fucking
tombstone shit. Get out of there. He's stuck in like the fucking mountain thing. I don't get any
soul. Like nothing. Zero. Not even runes. Nothing. Absolute zero. And no item.
Unless it's hidden back here. Okay. So uh don't beast eye quivers. This fucking has so many of
these things. What the fuck? Um what? There's a hundred of them. There was so many of those.
Give me a break. Well I gotta go back there. Okay so that the plan is okay so this is what
happened. I um I uh this is far away. I didn't keep going and trigger the rest of them. That
would have been very a lot more surprising I think. God damn it I have to go all the way around.
There's summons. All right go around. I think I missed that. All the way. I need a race though.
Fuck. Is there one seriously like right here? I feel like down here. I'm looking down here.
Yeah. No no no I need my souls. Why is there so much random shit here? Death right bird? Um
I don't want to lose those souls. I have to run. Was there a grace? Oh my god. Okay grace.
Grace over here somewhere. Not gonna happen. You're not gonna fucking kick me off the edge.
Is there a grace here? It's close. Oh you piece of shit. I was I'm already gotta win.
What is this doing down here? I'm just trying to get away from the stupid giant skeleton people and
this is a giant bird down here with magical power. At least I'm right here. Are you fucking kidding
me? Oh I thought that was a grace. I'm killing this thing right fucking now. I'm pissed. Get off
Get off. Yeah get me off. I don't want to I don't want to be on the horse right now.
Fucking move is stupid. It's just like lingers. That move is stupid. It's just like he just grazes
it down and it's just like you can't hit recover from it. It just permanently just
That move is fucking stupid. The souls don't matter anymore. It's already over.
Oh my god. They don't explode right? You with that bullshit. Okay maybe I have to be on the horse.
Can you dodge through that? I feel like that lingers. Bring out the snake. See what you got.
Not bad. Does it hurt? He just got fucking staggered. All right well he's cool. The fire
is cool though. Oh well. Maybe I do have to stay on the horse. Although I'd rather fight it off the
horse. Maybe get on the horse when he does that move. I don't like fighting stuff on the horse.
Hmm that's bad. I don't like fighting on the horse.
It's like too awkward like the running around on the camera. It's like too hard to keep. I was
doing better with it off the horse. Let's try the boys. They're probably just gonna get scared and
run away. All right let's go boys. All right I gotta jump over that. This cameraman is gonna
drive me fucking crazy. Whoa he just started. What the fuck? He wasn't even looking at me.
This motherfucker wasn't even looking at me. He's like oh I'll attack you guys. Now you.
All right this guy sucks. Uh this is gonna be a lot harder than I thought. Strategies. You gotta
hit him in the head. He does that explosion. I gotta see that explosion move again. Otherwise
I don't know about this. I could get right up in his ass. Like it takes too long to get over there.
It's better. Where's he? Good job boys. Excellent work boys. Oh my god he's gonna explode.
Me. Who did that? One of the boys literally just stunned him. Holy shit. I don't know which one he
did that. Somebody like somebody staggered him. Did somebody actually stagger? Holy shit that was
so important. Wow he sucked. That boss was awful. What is that thing? Where is it? Is it like a staff?
Oh here it is. Ritual spirit used by priests of old who were permitted to come among the death
birds. Priests became guardians of the birds through the rite of death which also serves
an oath sworn to their distant resurrection. First the spear high bearing prayers into the sky to
summon a downpour of spectral spears. We need to see what that looks like. Okay. Damn. This does
not use. Oh that's used mana. Okay. I wonder how good that is. So that scales. It's d int d dex but
you need a more. I need strength. It's a little too slow though. That's cool. That's cool.
Makes your hat glow. That's really cool. Okay well now I have enough intelligence now. Now I can
get my I got my 70 000 souls back. It's time to get to 60 intelligence and it's time to get this
level the fuck up. That was an intense fight. It's a little like shit that he put on the ground but
boys really pulled through there. If you by the way if anyone's curious
um people like wait those that's a those summons are terrible like that's literally the like the
worst summon in the game and not when they're plus nine and soon to be plus 10 okay it's still
that to do but let me find a grace that's important i don't know if i seriously i don't
know if i did enough damage to do that or if somebody one of them actually did that
maybe with the with the fire the torch it was like tap tap tap tap tap don't maybe i wonder
i actually really don't know to be honest the summons obviously it's like oh yeah the summons
are cool it's the volume right i know it's like oh dude use this one this this person's awesome
we put the serpent out there and i got annihilated not plus nine but still having just five things
just walk around aimlessly just bump into walls is there another fucking boss oh my god don't die
here i need to get out of here now i gotta get the fuck out of here right now it's grace right
there okay get out get out get out give me the fuck out of here right now safe for me to jump
off this okay i see it i'm not losing those again not a chance i haven't done this oh this is the
next thing i want to see there is something okay get off just please get me out of here
oh i have like i just got like a wave of just fear right there okay
i think i have a crunchie i need the souls anyways to level up the other staff so we're
gonna just do it i'm gonna need to actually do a lot more than this so i'm at 60 int
i want some more um might take a break in a minute after this i want to get some more water
maybe some more tea let's see do you get a healthy amount of sleep yes i do stop doing this
i keep just biting my lip and just you know what i'm saying why do i keep doing that
yes i do i get i get a good amount of sleep i do get some chapstick i have it right here
what did you vote for in 2004 what it's like well what if it was the 2004 election
how long goes that that was i old enough to vote 18 years ago how old am i now i have some ball
bearings to give smithing miner and somber miner so these i'm gonna be able to buy pretty much all
of them i can buy up to somber six now which actually that's a huge deal 12 000 souls
up to all right so if those of you are ever concerned about um out there anymore i have
enough materials you were like probably in 19 i don't i don't know what was that was that
like bush was george bush running for president i don't know that's a very long time ago i needed
to look at a chart okay let's go to the smith it was bush and carrie that's when i started playing
runescape that's when that's when i started playing runescape in 2004 i gotta equip it
because i'm not looking through all that there it is what do you mean i don't have enough
intelligence to put it on 59 i thought i had 60 we're doing it anyways okay where is it
who the fuck is it where are the staffs oh where is i don't have the somber smithing stone one
uh you know what fuck it we're coming back like i can't i can't even use it yet anyways
let's just keep going i thought i had 60 that's my that's my bad that's my fault i thought i had 60
let's go whatever stop swearing i promise i will not say a swear word for the next 15 straight
minutes castle soul i think that was hurt that one getting up is that one getting up across breath
oh where is it where is it it's not where is it where is he oh my god he was up the
whole time how did i not get hit by one thing what kind of christmas miracle shit was that
i gotta get man up wrong fucking button there's not another one that's gonna drop down right
holy shit how long was he gone for that was so that was so scary i look over he's not there
have i would i was accidentally dodging his moves and somehow in that i my weapon got taken off
that was a lot of squares well starting now i did not expect that uh let's go this is a pretty big
place i'm gonna say i want to start left here starting now yeah maybe get over that was intense
i think being i don't like how the thing's right there it's just anxiety inducing
um i i need to start doing this because okay this is where i was in here i need to my brain
needs this i know a lot of people are gonna be like why are you doing that like i did this
section here you know what i mean like so i'm like where is it for flying i don't want to go up yet
i want to do the whole ground level first essentially at least most of it okay again
mark it because i so my brain just has so much trouble i'm gonna mark that to be like i didn't
go over here yet nope no not yet you're a completionist i'm not i just want to make
sure i don't okay i thought that was something else all right so i know what's over here
i want to shut that thing up so bad i actually might just go out there and do it
so just come here is it is it clean i don't see anything to clean so wait there's
shut this thing up you're not going to go into the building i don't think this is supposed to
be doing this i just want to shut this thing up it's not sure it's too tight coming off
so
go down go down already what the fuck was that all right now can the thing's not doing that anymore
that's good cool very nice excellent excellent excellent excellent excellent excellent excellent
uh i i know it's in here i'm just gonna open it so i don't do it again
you killed the turtle i did not kill the turtle i don't know who's like fucking slandering me
saying that i did that i absolutely have i did not kill the turtle at the full moon we'll see
dude dual wield the baby toy why are the lines back they dead yeah they're dead
dead dead okay let's continue the progress got it marked over there i know i gotta go that way but
we're gonna go this way first should i get the full moon one i feel like that's a meme spell that
no one uses and you guys are just gonna ruin the rest of my playthrough i'm gonna get to like
one of the hardest bosses in the game and i could have used a different spell but i can't
because i did all the dumb bullshit that everybody told me to do or maybe i can one hit kill one of
the bosses with that we kind of cool all right so we're up here it also needs 70 intelligence
jeez freezing grease we'll just float over here what was that
this looks it's ducks crossing the street okay i don't there's nothing to do with you too
i don't want to fight you but i'm gonna i think i'm gonna have to i'm sorry but there was nothing
i could do doesn't open from this side what's in there there's a painting in there definitely
want to get that is it almost time for a fucking green tea refill i'm gonna i actually might not
even have any left it's getting late too though all right no no i'm not done i'm not done i want to
keep going this i this i started this is a late night stream i said i was going to be a late
night stream so we're going to commit to a late night stream effective come on stick your head
over here and so that's that way let me go over here yeah it's only been three hours and i'm i'm
pretty i'm pretty alert still shit my goodness don't let this guy kill you you're all right dude come
on relax this is horse shit whatever good all right that's enough of this area can't mark it
but i i don't think i don't think i need to so i can go straight there's a grace over there let
me go back this way is there something i missed over here i don't think so i thought this is
family friendly it i will be in a minute wait till the after hours you know when cartoon network
goes to like 11 o'clock they say like swears and shit it's almost there we're there it's a
germa adult swim all right it's like my version of that imagine if somebody did that like from the
hours of i gotta pay attention here in the hours of like you know 12 o'clock noon to like 10 o'clock
at night they're incredibly family friendly they don't say swears they don't play any like mature
games but then like 10 o'clock rolls around and they just like saying oh fuck this shit piss
asshole that they talk a bunch of shit they play much immature games that'd be like a funny
it could be like a funny shtick i think that's literally you guys iced my streams of i've
what do you that it makes no sense to me keep going up the boss up there well i know where we're
going okay the legendary item over there it used to be family friendly maybe for like
seven months back in like 2011 he's open okay okay interesting oh great son frigid son of soul
surrender yourself to the eclipse grant life to the soul as bones
so that guy walks in here very okay cool so what what was the weapon that i just found
i lost it again there it is faith in decks storied sword and treasure of castle soul that depicts an
eclipsed sun drained of color one of the legendary armaments
so that guy walks in here very okay cool so that guy walks in here very okay cool so what what was
an eclipsed sun drained of color one of the legendary armaments and so the sight of an
eclipse inspires a dreadful awe preventing an onlooker from averting his gaze that the
lustrous sun ablaze with the prince of death's flames looking the death ailment on foes this is
a broken pvp weapon i can't use it but i'm curious interesting well i'm gonna set the bonfire though
because that unnecessary amount of damage to take legendary shuttle let's just sit at the bonfire
that spell this weapon used to instantly kill is this the thing people were talking about
this is the one that would instantly kill right it was like an unbearable um is he in the room
again it's show till wait nothing over here all right uh i'll go up a little bit it should be
definitely using sorcerers a lot more at the end of the end game here
oh wait a minute can i jump from here no shit around back okay end game he says i mean
and oh hold on quiet yeah sure whatever you say dude i would also like to swing
15 times in a row that would be i mean it'd be cool if i could do that if i would have the ability
to do that many swings in a row try that again did i go this way yet yeah this is where i went right
i am this annoying guy this is the worst enemy in the whole game well i need to be much more
prepared for that then maybe i should use a shield to prepare him oh you know what what am i talking
about i am a sorceress good luck the best part about being sorcery is you can just cheese the
fuck out of everybody i don't have to fight this guy somebody else can goodbye see you i don't have
to deal with that right this is why sorcery and faith is just so good they're just great
because i can just go run up the ladder and hide and i don't have to like be imagine being just
like a like a deck strength quality build you'd be up there throwing fire pots i think i already
i'm wearing this already except is this the work better version of it how is this one better i
found it like three zones ago okay that's all i can do up here hold on hold on a second just a
second on a second it's down here i mean that's a really suspicious place to put that if there's
nothing here all right oh it's just it's just the other side okay well i wanted to come down
anyways because actually let me now i'm not gonna set the bonfire why would i do that
i want to go this way and i'm gonna go up how come you're wearing mommy's beach hat
mommy's beach hat i wanted to go up from here so i don't get sunburned yeah so i don't get burnt
remember the dogs oh shit okay it's just one of these guys one behind me too of course there is
no why can i not lock on throwing those how can you throw that that far but i cannot
am i still too far away i killed the guy that was the distraction
holy shit oh my god oh my god i keep timing it so fucking wrong
what the fuck there's another one right there holy shit oh my god what the fuck why there's
so many of these fucking things okay what a pain in the ass whatever that's so annoying
uh should i maybe i should put a shield on just hold it out do a t-break all right if i
if i get past this area i'll do a t-break won't be long now i know no i know it's there
i could go that way too but i need the souls i could run by him what do i do there's nothing
down there where do i go i actually don't fucking know where i'm going what happened
what the fuck happened here what the fuck what did i go the wrong way is there a way
that guy's unfucking bearable that guy does did i go the wrong way i don't think that guy has i
don't think that guy has a stamina bar you just swing swing swing swing swing swing swing swing
swing swing swing swing swing swing swing swing swing swing swing swing swing it's like you don't
how do you fight that guy how are you supposed to fight that fucking thing how do you fight that
thing you don't even fight it you don't even play the game you just die how do you fight the
fucking guy how do you fight that guy you can't you can't fight him all right where where i don't
the souls are gone so fucking whatever who cares this ball this area is just like a middle finger
to the player it's just like yeah i just whatever you just every corner you turn there's gonna be
like fucking something that just spawns in front of your face i see the elevator which i believe
was down here i probably could go back to the front entrance if i step on that i'll go right
up there right i have to pull the lever you have to activate it all right well i'm just gonna run
over there well i don't i don't know i don't like this area fuck this area fuck the dual welding
fucking assholes that kill you in fucking three hits and don't stop swinging good look i don't
give a shit i don't think you can actually fight these guys i don't think you can physically fight
i think they're they're they're designed to be like obstacles there there are obstacles in the
arena it's like a spike trap you can't even pop you can't even hide okay well i got the
thing so i'm gonna go the other way you literally stagger them good luck getting a swing off and
if you miss you're dead try rolling no no quiet i'm not gonna hear this quiet okay so the elevator
was here right a little bit further down where's the elevator back here wasn't there an elevator
like right here is it further down oh it's this room with her yeah all right yeah fuck all that
i mean contraption does not move it just did it why is that not happening i have to stand on top
of it do i really have to do that bp yeah it's the wrong place i have to ride it once what i okay i'm
gonna have to do it can i summon here no you can't even summon here i was gonna say just get the
boys out here and i was fucking sacrificing and run okay here we go i have an idea there's like
the most physical defense this right this says okay here we go i was gonna hold the fucking shield
out and run but wait you are so annoying like holy shit get the fuck out of here like you just how
many of these do you get to have this endless goddamn supply of magical bombs all right get
over here oh wait wait where do we go where are we he's right behind me
i can see his shadow that's my shadow i hate these guys are the fucking worst okay
well it's activated now so i don't have to worry about this shit
i just want to see what the boss is what is the boss you didn't get in mandarin neal i have an
okay here's the play play is drink this going from here now the play is to drink that um
shit drink the thing to make infinite spells and then spam that moon blade and try to kill the guy
on the right first as fast as i can i do i also have access to the boys do i okay if i have access
to the boys then i'll do it i'm gonna drink this before going in the room right when i go in the
room some of the boys and then just spam the moon blade and hopefully i kill the guy on the
right before he even gets over to me well i think i'm safe right it's not do i have to run away
from anybody no thank god at least they have the decency to make it so you don't have to fight one
of those guys on the way here all right here we go all right boys get out of the way oh he's going
ahead all right it worked it worked to work good call good call we're good all right get him all
right holy shit what does that mean holy fuck oh no no no no no no no no way oh no okay it was a
good strategy that's how i'm gonna play that out that's a good strategy it is it was boys
flask i gotta wait to spam it though i was a little early i think i can drink the flask
after summoning the boys no no no no why would i do that because the boys will be free because i
i thought he summoned him instantly so he takes a minute he's like here i go i'm gonna summon so i
just get in there um drink the flask summon the boys and then by that point that should be good
it took a lot longer to summon those two than i thought that's why i did it instantly
okay here we go here we go oh okay did i get him only one got left all right we're fine good good
dude what the fuck man come on get him we're good all right he does a follow-up it's a follow-up
swing dude it's he does two follow-ups after that i might have to get rid of this spell now
shit hold on back it up all right you gotta get away you don't want to be near this guy for more
than a second okay all right all right all right you gotta jump no you don't i don't know oh my
goodness all right i gotta be quicker i gotta be much quicker timing's on that i got it wrong a
little bit no no not good not good i think you just need to get out oh okay all right all right
so here's what has to happen when he does that like dash in swing i don't think there's enough
time to do the carrying sword even if i get like a perfect dodge because it's like it takes a little
bit too long to be able to dodge that second like boom attack so i'm not going to use it i'm just
going to use my weapon use the mimic tier i mean the boys are doing great i got it i got it it's
just the timings i just i it's all about when he does that dash in i think it's just a single r2
or maybe just just just swing at him once and then get away i wonder if i can jump over it
can i jump over that attack when he goes like boom with the lightning can i jump i think i can
maybe even um winston i'll try it i definitely need to use this in the very beginning there's
no way i can do this about it just have to get away we'll try let's go i i felt like that was
pretty close although i feel like at least a few of these attempts are going to get really
fucked up by this part here just not killing these things fast enough
get the fuck away from me but hey what's he doing all right here we go does it two three times
hard to tell actually not that bad but once the boys are gone i'm gonna be in trouble here
fuck no again okay let's go that timing on that i gotta get it right it's a lot longer
no i don't think i could even do an r1 shit i'm in the fucking wall here maybe just one r1 and get
out okay that works damn once his friends are gone it's just about the timings damn that was
crazy that's fun but holy that beginning my god okay if you don't have if you don't have sorcery
do you just have to run around and just kite that around so you can kill those two i can't imagine
that as a strength user that must be unfucking that must be unbearable as like a melee only
character how are you supposed to do that that seems impossible strength is fine it seems so
hard that was cool all right we're good god damn oh someone's gonna carry that yeah he just sits
back and will buff until you attack him really all right now we can finally do the staff but
hold on this probably there's probably some lore shit in here that was a cool fight though i just
do not look forward to doing that as like a short sword character i feel like that would be really
difficult hold on wait don't just run around oh the weapon yeah let's see what it was what was it
what kind of weapon was it is it right here veterans prosthesis strength index
like a fist weapon yeah bladed prosthetic leg and wreath with the power of lightning
instead attached to the fist commander niel veteran of castle soul offered this prosthesis
in exchange for the lives of defeated knights held prisoner he went on to lead these men as an army
of no nation storm kick and use it like oh it's that thing he was doing oh that's actually kind
of cool that's pretty cool all right we can go pee in just a moment i promise i want to see what
else is here and then we might consider wrapping up soon not right this second but soon i would
say maybe like another hour we'll see after we get this lore dump whatever it is we'll uh we'll take
a break i'll come back maybe stream for like an hour or two maybe i don't want to go too too long
so what's up here halig tree secret medallion left lord nicola forgive me the sun has not been
swallowed our prayers were lacking the comrade remains soulless i will never set my eyes upon
it now your divine halig tree okay well i have half of the halig tree medallion
very interesting kind of curious what that is join medallions to operate grand lift of roles
branching the medallion with both halves can join will have activate the grand lift of
rolled granting access to a hidden path in other words the secret medallion will guide the bearer
to the land of michaela's halig tree what is a halig tree it's a special tree okay well very
interesting uh the game wants me to go down here so here's what we're gonna do i am going to take
a pee break we're gonna go here we're going to check out this area preferably maybe this right
here maybe take a little gander over here and then ultimately i want to end up in there so let's
mark that you have the other half i don't think so i have this one please have to pee right now
all right now i know we're doing it and when i come back i'm going to do the staff
yeah i'll be right back just go pee if it blows you that are going to bed we'll see you later
i don't think i'm streaming tomorrow although i've been wrong the last four or five days before so
let's just see where this goes i don't plan on streaming tomorrow i didn't plan on streaming
tonight either so just keep an eye on sus i i might show up and change it and we might not
stream for another day or two i don't know i'm kind of up in the air depends on how much of how
badly i want to play so we'll see we're back hey oh he's uninstalling elden ring right now thank
god somebody said all right first order of business the very first order of business
crush these back to the round table hold how many elden ring streams have you done um i
um i just fucking destroyed this person um i i isn't it illegal to fight here
what okay apparently not what was that you got invaded why did that just happen this late
is that why i fucking destroyed it that was just like one two three oh it's oh it's from the
medallion okay that makes sense all right what is it an arm it was like a bone arm where the
fuck is it oh there it is arcane and decks clinging bone horrific weapon made of a hardened
skeletal arm wielded by ensha of the royal remains fitted by placings one to hands with fists
until it digs in a clinging creature a king relinquishes not the hand doing this irl is cool
what is doing look at me that's cool this is our ass goes with arcane okay well that was weird
interesting it's the person that's been staring at me the entire video game what was that for
helm grace with gold human bones worn by the unspeaking adherent of sir gideon the all-knowing
slowly replenishes hp when hp is reduced bones belong to an ancient lord the soulless king the
lord of the lost and desperate who was known as ensha ancient lord term of twerk talk to gideon
you what is it about ensha what is for that nasty business and she got rather ahead of himself it
seems as his master liked to express my regret but now ensha is slain and gone finished forever
more ah yes by way of apology allow me to tender some advice in regard to the half of the secret
medallion you possess find the village of the albin oryx it lies to the southwest of leonia
below the alter clifflands and some of the old village folk have hidden the secret medallions
somewhere dude i i've already done it i did it already i said the southwest of leonia what the
fuck is happening in chat write that down i'm not writing down the pot dance all right so
there i this i could do that but the most important thing right at this very moment
is well isn't it i thought wait first of all let me ask this i thought you couldn't fight in here
you're not supposed to wait so that's up so they just broke the rules it's not that you
special thing it was bizarro world okay go get the medallion all right just wait wait listen
i need to do this first because this is important i need a somber smithing stone don't i i do okay
somber smithing stone l stream l gamer we could do all this other stuff the next stream don't i mean
look we're not rushing through the game how much is the somber smithing stone one three
doesn't the giant sell it giant sells them over here right nice sells one through four maybe i
should buy a bunch i don't think i have i have nine twos two threes i'm gonna need a few of these
right because i have up until eight to get to plus eight so i need some more fours and i need some
more threes as well right or is it is one per upgrade oh that's right it's not like the regular
smithing stones one two three four i'm gonna sneeze i had nowhere to go oh wait you have
something to say about this and think of myself a capable war counselor i'll catch up with you
soon enough did you pass up that talisman i didn't even look at it oh is fp consumed by skills what
holy shit that's pretty good all right okay i can do this now it vastly raises max fp raises
intelligence spells consume less fp raises potency of sorceries so why would i use this if i have this
one right i get my hp back because the skill is not a spell what a waste reload the area reload
the area okay good thing i bought the fucking one smithing stone instead of buying like a hundred
oh what's wrong with them can i talk to every little area again what is going on in this world
i don't get it easily broken and weak in striking attacks formed by those committed to high treason
it wards off the intervention of the greater will and its vessel fingers wards off the intervention
of the greater will well shit all right what was what's why these people what's wrong with
these people what's going on it's tinfoil hat okay very nice let's now go back to the
round table did you go to celavus's tower too let me do this first i'm not gonna be able to get
this up that high i don't think but i'll i'm gonna use all the stones that i have finally it only
took four hours only took four hours here we go finally that's the wrong one isn't it no it's not
okay here we go plus one two plus three plus four plus five plus six plus seven plus eight
this is now 274 262 this is better this thing scales on strength weirdly enough
new staff 262 yeah that is better scaling you're right how does it look pretty cool very cool all
right so now i got that i'm happy with this that's the wrong i mean the wrong one spinning weapon
it's annoying uh do i have any can i upgrade anybody else i'm not all right that was cool
i am now going to do what i set out to do before i know that i can go get the other half of that
medallion we're saving that i'm not doing that at the moment i want to go down here i want to
explore this part and then the stream is ending so let's just check this area down here go back
to okay all right all right all right all right just hold on i gotta go here you're saying
just don't forget i won't forget you got i'm sure you guys will remind me the next three days okay
here we go saying to go this way don't end i i mean it's it's like 12 30 pacific it's like so
late for so many people we'll be back we'll be back i don't know if it's gonna be tomorrow but
we'll be back you should be expecting to be there just be random elden ring streams like every other
day or something i i it really just depends on when i get the urge just just i want to play now
i'm in the wrong goddamn way all right just turn around it's early in germany right now yeah it's
probably like what eight o'clock in the morning nine o'clock in the morning that way so how many
full moon spells are in the game they're actually only like two there really are only two so you i
saw i'm gonna have to get the other resemblance then right you already have i already have one
okay so he's dead
everybody's just dying elvis is bell bearing his hat his gown era okay all this other stuff
okay finger wait these summons these are summons summons spirit of finger maiden theralina spirit
of finger maiden who never met the tarnished she was meant to guide uses healing incantations
and holy water pots she is not a fighter by nature and is ill suited for battle
maiden without a tarnish to tarnish without a maiden and yet no guy to bring them together
spirit of man who wished to become the innards of a living jar a jar hurling specialist who
throws all manner of pots and jars the warrior jar once told the nameless man this you are not
ready to join the warriors inside no you must apply yourself better yourself and one day i
will return for you wait by them they turn they cost starlight shards hopefully that wasn't a
stupid idea well i never came up didn't he sorry syllabus yeah it took me too long to find um the
person to give the potion to uh seems to have fucking died of old age where is it oops okay
does that does do you have any spells or like is it plus spells large hat with the movements
of the stars drawn on the inside of the brim worn by the magic perceptors who serve the carrion
royals increases mine to the detriment of stamina i don't want that although people die of old age
in this game uh i don't i don't know i don't think so upstairs haven't i already been up here
it wasn't there a memory still up here or something yeah i got whatever it is i got it
in the wall in the wall outside the outside wall where he's not doing it on purpose
dude oh my god the wall what i'm west side facing west west side facing west lay down here
i'm fucking dead is like a secret wall here is there actually some shit up here oh wait
was this here before black wolf mask mask fashioned after the head of a black wolf
relic of an assassin who assumed the guise of ranny the witch's loyal shadow the likeness is
striking so wait were we were we talking to an assassin the whole time it's like kind of awful
all right um i got his bell right i'm gonna this is you might have to turn the stream off sooner
than i thought i want to go do this i want to see the assassin in the underground that looked like
play was wearing a mask what's the problem that's the mask of the baleful shadow so
all right very cool karen phalanx karen retaliation ice crag and freezing mist
well i think we're gonna have to get these frag and mist i'll get them both i have enough souls
i need more i need more ruins try to sell some shit that i'm not gonna use
it's all right i'll be back let me at least put this on and replace it like knight comet
i took night comet up uh we're gonna replace a great glen stone shard with glen stone ice crag
and i have another cold thing too don't i i'll staff in the ground freezing tornado
yeah let's just let's put all like the cold shit on why not i'm that that's what i'm doing
this thing is this is a moon cold dark moon and it's oh all right and it's 68 and then starlight
still there was our ice storm ice crag granny's dark moon and then star lies gonna have to come
out eventually all right now i'm actually gonna go do the thing that i was doing before
we're only gonna i'm just want to take a look okay still got a lot to do but i do want to see
what's down here this is where we're going for the next the next like 20 30 minutes we're
going to go check this out a little bit and just check it out here we go my glen stone ice crag
we want to go straight over here stream is going to end it at it precisely one am
i'm gonna see if fire moves okay that moves that's just like a cool glen stone
i can't do anything else but that's fine this cannot be charged
oh watch out hey these guys are cool they're like yetis all right what's going on with all
these things they're all um hand over there they're all frozen statues on in a way with
all these like thorns all over them these hands are here too something going on with these hands
the fingers the fingers the fingers the hands these hands are gonna have something weird going
on some role that it played it's so much easier on horseback smithing stone seven
what do you got more shit down here oh shit what were you guarding down here a lot of nothing
they do have smithing stone seven which is really cool they make me think of zelda
yeah they do that's true they're fucking weird here far away zep let's check check around the
corner here there's gotta be something here right a dungeon probably yeah this dungeon here i
guarantee it and not that has to be right it's not never mind i want you to kill this one of
these is gonna start moving i think i wouldn't be surprised oh shit what's that let's check it out
i see your staves real quick yeah yes you can and i'm gonna call it up here whatever this is
this is the last thing we're gonna do tonight good thing i did that i freaked out i thought
that was the edge it was a little bit further what you looking at i will cry well i'll show
auto i told you i was let me just open this up whatever's in here this is gonna be a dungeon
and shit all right yeah yeah we'll start here we'll start here next stream will be today's
technically thursday let's get a game plan here because 29th me and my voice is just gone
me and ludwig are gonna do a stream together i'm gonna do i think bro versus bro
i'm gonna calendar all right here is the real plan are you ready we're gonna go
live on saturday the 26th and sunday the 27th that's the plan that is the next plan
stream now you might get something i might show up tomorrow but the sus i know i said thursday
you said thursday friday i know but i streamed today and i have to do i have to do my fucking
taxes so uh we gotta get on that because i've got like three weeks before they they did up the
deadline uh so so today is technically thursday no that's way too long isn't it thursday yeah i
don't know okay yeah that gets me a whole day to do it that's fine all right so i'll see you guys
saturday sunday and then we're gonna go i imagine that by sunday we're gonna conclude elden ring
temporarily i think i'm gonna get near the end of the game two streams from now maybe
it's very possible so let's just plan for saturday whatever depending what happens saturday maybe and
i don't know maybe i'll just fucking on friday maybe let's be like fucking who cares i'm going
live i've done to the last like two streams in a row so it's possible plan for saturday at least
and then we got the bro versus bro on the 29th which is tuesday yeah that should be good to go
let me just look and see what's outside here let me yeah it's a dungeon giant conquering hero's grave
okay cool the other half of the day yeah we'll we'll do a full cleanup i'll go get a bunch of
stuff that i didn't do i'm just very curious what's in here what is this i'm not gonna fight
anything it's just a free item flame protect me fire spell yeah it's a dungeon we'll start here
take a look what the spell is because you know everyone's gonna freak out about it faith greatly
increases fire damage negation during the war against the giants long ago there's so many
factions go to bed i know i know i'm i'm this is the end rest here at the grace i'll see you guys
on saturday i saturday stream is not going to be at like 9 pm okay we're going to go back to try
to go back to normal i've been really itching to continue to play this game so but i'm going to
put a lid on it because i want to start saturday at like four normal time not start at like 8 30
i'll go get auto i'll be right back we'll show auto for a minute for a second or two we'll have
yeah i'll be right back let's put this on at least until i come back thank you for watching everybody
really appreciate it we'll come back with auto and go grab him thanks for all the subs
there were a lot of community subs tonight thank you guys as always as you know though i
do not read subs really or bits anymore i do not on pretty rare occasions do i do that i used to
that's okay i missed the post stream hangouts yeah but they were they just they had to go they
really did i told you the two or three reasons why right it's you know you got i don't want
people to like pay me money for me to like read a message and talk to them
right it's like oh yeah it costs five dollars to get me to read your message guaranteed and
respond to it i don't i'm not into that i don't i don't want to do that anymore um as well as the
fact that we used to do the channel's gotten a lot larger too so it's just there might be so
many messages that might take hours and hours it already did a lot of times take an extra one to
two hours at the end of every stream so if i streamed for like four or five hours a lot of
times i would cut the streams shorter because i knew there was probably an hour or two left of
kind of reading uh messages and bits and stuff so now i i can just kind of go as long as i really
want to and there's not like a thing in the back of my mind that says dude you gotta be aware that
you gotta have enough energy to do like an hour or two at least of reading the bits that kind
of stuff combined together all the hell stuff like it was sitting down for more than seven to
eight hours was kind of too much for me at some point right i do appreciate it i do appreciate
anybody that gives this channel subs or gives any money to this you know as you know at this point
you the subs on this channel are there's a lot and i don't think i need to tell you guys to
continue to do that i don't think i need to tell you like oh yeah here's the incentive for giving
me money like i don't think i need to have that i don't think i don't really want that anymore
that's pretty much all there is to it if somebody wants to give me five dollars a month i'm not i'm
not going to stop them i'm not going to necessarily uh like encourage people to
oh yeah give me like 20 bucks and i'll read like two or three things that you said at the end of
the stream yeah just give me that money i'll i'll read it that's gonna be gone forever but uh let me
go get auto i'll be right back he knows there's a treat he's right here god he needs to lose some
weight hello i tell he's he needs to lose at least a pound or two he's very chunky but he's he has
lost one pound he has he's he's kind of a bean bag chair he's huge he's not huge he's not huge
he's just he's kind he's kind of a bean bag chair but he's not huge okay come here you want this oh
my god i'll see you guys on uh on saturday thanks for watching see you later it's a cookie it's one
little milk bone oh okay he got a little heavy but i've been actively making sure he loses weight
he's lost like a he's he's lost like 1.2 pounds in the last month i'm trying to get him down like a
pound a month a half a pound a month or so slowly and he he would be at ideal weight if he lost like
one or two more pounds he'd be fine his ideal weight is like 24 to like 25 somewhat between
like yeah like 24 to 25 is his ideal weight remember he's not 100% dachshund he's he's a
lot bigger than a typical dachshund but good night see you guys saturday 4 p.m pacific take care
of yourselves thanks for staying up late really hope i really hope tomorrow i don't like just
wake up and go oh no never mind it's gonna be a stream today at 9 30 at night i'm gonna try to
hold myself to this schedule because like i'm all over the place lately night goodbye see you later