Just one sec, hold on. Working on something real quick. Hello, how are you? Good to see
everybody again. Just got to make sure I get this settled to go here. Hi, welcome to the
stream everybody. I'm sure a lot of you are probably pretty curious as to the title of
the stream. And I've been gone for a few days, so let me sit down here. Am I in frame? Can you see me,
you know, everybody sit down here? So people are probably wondering what this stream is about. I've
been hyping it up for a couple months now. And of course, how do you describe your retirement? How
do you describe that? Because I've been doing this for about 10 to 12 years now. And as I've gone over
the last 10 years, I've never really had to think about this. And what I want to do, even if I decide
that I'm done, right? Like even if I'm done with Twitch, I'm done with streaming, I'm done with
YouTube, whatever it is. I ain't going anywhere because the brand needs to live on permanently.
And I tried to figure out what that meant. How do I do that? How do I, how do I let my legacy
continue? And oh, do you stream for like another five to 10 years? I don't fucking think so. I don't
think so, guys. So what I've decided to do is over the last few months, we've scoured the country
trying to find who I think could potentially be able to replace me. And this brand and this stream,
because I'm going, look, I'm going anywhere, okay? I might be stopping at some point in the future
here, but I ain't going anywhere. This brand is not going anywhere. I'm sticking around forever.
And I'm going to make sure of it today. So without further ado, what we have done is we've scoured
the country, various classified ads and newspapers, various boards of who would want to take the reign
of German at 85 because it's a very, very important reign, incredibly important reign. I've been here
for 12 years. It's got to go on and I need a 20% royalty, permanently. So we have scoured the
country. We have a group of people that I'm willing to at least assess if they can handle it or not.
So what we're going to do is we're going to have to go ahead and go and send in number one, please.
For who could be my replacement? Number one. How you doing number one? Very well. You've chosen
Dark Souls, I think is your game. Go ahead. Yes. Oh, all right.
Looks like we are playing some Dark Souls three here. That's right. Okay. Jumping around. I think
maybe I'm just going to roll the whole time. Oh, there's a guy right there. All right. I'm going
to try to roll past. Okay. Yep. I'm just going to roll here. Yep. I'm just going to keep roll. Oh,
there's another guy. Okay. Oh, I'm just going to roll. I'm just going to roll past here. Wait,
what was this thing? What did that say right there? Oh, okay. I'm just going to keep rolling.
I'm going to roll. I'm just going to roll. So I'm going to go around the curve here. What is up
here? I think aren't there supposed to be fights in this game? What is going on? I thought this
game was hard. Set the bonfire. Set the bonfire here. Do you know what that does? Yeah. I'm going
to light the bonfire, get some nice save point here. What's the bonfire do? It rests. I'm going
to rest here. What else does it do? It rests and it's a checkpoint. Yep. All right. He doesn't need
to be alive anymore here, I think. All right. Keep on going. There's a bonfire. Oh my god,
get out of the way. No, you guys. No, go, go, go, go, go. Okay. Okay. No, everything's fine.
Everything's fine. We're okay. We're okay. We're okay. Okay. We're okay. All right. What is this
guy? He doesn't look, this guy doesn't look very scary. No, I think I got this guy. He's like on a
knee. What's the big deal about that? Hey, what are you doing over here? You're just chilling.
It's a nice weapon. Oh, what was that? You can't shoot me from over there. That's not fair. What
do you think you're doing here? I would definitely do something like that. Maybe I'm going to back
step. Oh, nothing. You are, you are nothing. Oh, oh, here, here we go. Remove sword. All right. So
I'm going to remove the sword. What's the worst that could happen? Have you played Dark Souls
before? Great. I have played a little Dark Souls. This is what, what is, okay. All right. He's
moving now. That's all right. That's all right. I just, I'm going to go back to my strategy of
rolling here, I think maybe. And that's, well, I mean, I hear people just roll, right? You just,
you just roll and then you roll. Look, I'm, I'm doing, I'm doing all right. You know, I think,
that's all right. I got, I'm alive. I'm alive. I'm alive. It's okay. It's okay. It's all right.
It's all right. Okay. I'm going to take a Estus Flask here. There we're all right. I think I can
take at least two more hits, right? We're all right. We're all right. Yeah. It's okay. Oh,
it's all right. That's all right. I got this. I got this. He's all right. He was supposed to
roll. He didn't roll. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I don't, I don't, I, uh, thank you so much. So if you could
go ahead and that's, uh, I think I've seen enough. Yes. All right. Thank you. Thank you so much.
Thank you very much. Thank you. Can we send a number two, please? Hey, how are you doing?
I'm doing well. Take a seat. Yeah. All right. All right. What are we going to be playing today?
Uh, a little bit of Tetris. Oh, Tetris. Okay. Yes. All right. So I'll tab it there. Perfect.
Right there. Should do it for you. All right. Play button. I'm going to be,
I think it's the arrow keys, by the way. All right. Good. Good. Good. Number two, go ahead and
now I can start whenever you're comfortable. You got it. All right. Starting with a little,
a little squiggly shape, a little bit of the squiggle. All right. I'd like to see the squiggle.
Ooh, we got a little upside down tee. It can fit right there. All right. A little bit of
shpee. A little bit of shpee. What did you say? A little bit of, a little bit of shpee. A little
bit of shpee. You said shpee? Shpee. Oh, you said shpee. Hold on. A little bit of shpee.
All right. And a little bit of shpee. All right. Great. And another one here.
Shpee. All right. Then we got a little. Might be a little too much. Oh, a little bit,
a little bit too much. Pull back on the shpee. Pull back on the shpee. All right. You got it.
All right. You got it. All right. A little square. I'd like to see a square.
Okay. All right. I'm killing this. I, I would watch the middle there though. You gotta be careful.
I know. I know. Get built up and then you don't know what you're gonna do. All right. Good line
clear. Good line clear there. Thank you. Thank you very much. I appreciate that. Good line clear.
It was only one, but you know, sometimes it's all it takes. Sometimes it's all it takes. Another
line clear there. All right. So how long have you been a gamer for, number two? I've played since
1998 when I got my Nintendo 64. What was your favorite game ever made?
Favorite game ever made? Probably Legend of Zelda Ocarina of Time. My favorite. No?
That's a mean answer. Oh, that's a mean answer. Give me number two. Give me number two. Number two.
Oh boy. Trying to think of my number two favorite game. Second favorite game of all time. And then,
by the way, you're on the clock here. Oh, okay. On the clock. Of course. Of course. That's a mean
answer and you know it. All right. I would probably say this is going to be a little
controversial. I like Journey, underrated by that game company. That's a game where you played with
another person you didn't know who they were from across the world. Yes, exactly. Yeah.
You can work well with others. Yes. Oh, I love collab games for sure. Yes, exactly. Are you open
to collaborations with other YouTubers and streamers and stuff like that? You could get
comfortable in those spaces. Oh yeah, absolutely. I feel like I can get along with just about
anybody, really. Okay. If you clear this whole row, then I'm going to be very, very excited.
All right. Oh. We got two. We got two. I got to equip that one. Okay. Okay. You didn't get that
second row. I know. I know. I had a couple of missing blocks there. Oh, that was pretty good,
though, on the second theory. Good at deduction of mathematical intricacies. Absolutely.
The thing myself is something of a scientist. All right. Very, very nice. Very nice, number two.
Number two, very nice. Thank you. Thank you very much. I appreciate that. Right off the bat,
number two, very nice. Oh, thank you. I appreciate that. You know, number two,
that's all I think I need to see. That's all you need to see? That's all I need to see.
It's been an absolute pleasure. Absolutely. Yeah. All right. Phenomenal. Phenomenal job.
Appreciate it. Set it at number three, please. That was very good. Number three, how are you?
Okay. What are you going to play first? Oh, you know, like a true gamer,
you're going to flip some houses. Okay. All right. Should just be able to go like this.
All right. Right here. Controller disconnected, unfortunately. Let's see if we can get that
clicked in. Please connect the controller. It should be able to. There we go. Can you
play a continue game? Oh, you're going to have to use WASD. Oh, man. Right. Okay. Got some mouse
action here. Here we go. Let's see if number three is real. What is this garbage? Did you put this
here? No, House Clippers game where you clean. I'm not sure. Is that it? Is it just cleaning?
Yeah, I'm not going to say much. I have to stay back. I have to stay completely, completely out
of this. Oh, this is disgusting. Are there rats in this game? I bet there are. Why do you care
about that? Unless it's a large rat that makes all the rules. The fuck did he say? Nothing. Nothing.
Love it, bro. What is this? Can I take a sledgehammer to something? Doesn't like rats.
That's very important. Number three. I mean, Charlie Day and I, we go way back with rats.
What do I do with this? Set it places? Yeah. If you go to the, have you played House
Clipper before? I have never played this before. So if you go ahead and head to the laptop over in
the corner. I think there we go. There we go. There you go. Laptop will give you a job to do.
One of the jobs if you can. Sweet. Okay. Go ahead and do one of the jobs. Number three. I'm going to
just number three. You can do one of the jobs. Number three. Go to browser. I think. Fuck. Damn.
Yeah. Go to browser and then you can pick one of these. Oh, you can go to. How affordable.
Yeah. Pick one of the top left one. Number three, if you could please. All right. Can't afford
a number three. Okay. Go back. Oh, we got, can't afford any of these. Oh, is that the cheapest?
Wow. It's realistic. That's okay. That's pretty good. Go in the, maybe the mail.
All right. Okay. There you go. Yep. Okay. Except that job. Number three. Go ahead and get started.
All right. Let's see. He stole a radiator. He knows how to stall really well. That's pretty good.
He's got stalling in his record, but doesn't like rats. That's very important. Okay. Okay.
I wouldn't do that. No. I wouldn't do that. Number three. I wouldn't do that.
Hey, you around like that for no reason. That's weird. Go from Tetris.
His health just disappeared. I think you want to pivot number three. That's up to you. Go ahead.
I wouldn't let you know. I think it might've closed on itself.
You're playing Tetris. Wow. You're playing number twos. You're playing number twos. Game number
three. Number three. Can I get you to say just really quickly, can you say look at me? Look at
me. Look at me. Look at me right here. Uh, how do you, why does it rotate on its own? Who crafted
this? Okay. Number three. I think I've seen enough. Thank you so much. I appreciate it. Thank you so
much. Number three. Thank you. Thank you. Number four. I like the energy. I like the energy on
that one, but I don't know. Number four. How are you? Good. Nice to meet you. Good to meet you.
Do you want a hug? What do you want? Okay. You want a hug? I'll sit down. Now sit down. I'm
going to sit down. Yeah. Number four is weird. I'm going to sit down. Where is the weird fucking guy?
Yeah. Yeah. I'm a weird guy. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. What do you want to play number four?
House Flippin'. Okay. I think House Flippin' may have crashed. Number four. So we're going to
have to see if we can get House Flippin' back up. It's all right. Yeah. Play whatever. I play these
games all the time. You know, this is my, this is my thing. You know? Good. Very good. Yeah. Yeah.
Not House Flippin'. That's your name. Number four. What's your favorite game of all time?
I like Scrabble. Right? That's okay. Yeah. Sure. Scrabble is my favorite game. Yeah.
Online. Online Scrabble. Online Scrabble. So you play Wirtle? Yeah. Yeah. Other Wirtle. What do
you think about the New York Times buying Wirtle? It's a good buy. You know, it's a good move for
them. Probably. Yeah. That's a good idea. Yeah. Really actually good take on that. Yeah. Thank
you. I, you know. Good take on that. You know, make some, make some money. They're probably not
doing so well. No. I don't know. People's subscriptions don't be, you know, who reads
the newspaper anymore anyways. Right. Actually really good fucking mind on this one. Okay. Yeah.
You know, thinking. Yeah. Yeah. I'm a big thinker. Like, like you. Yeah, of course. Yeah. Yeah. So
when you get a lot, when you load in, there's a computer you can probably, they crashed out,
but it's okay. Well, we, we're not going to take this into your audition time, but. That's okay. I
mean, yeah, I'm waiting, we're hanging out, we're talking, you know. It's great. Now this is a good,
this is actually really good to see how you are in front of, because there's an audience here as
well. So make sure you don't, you're aware of that, right? Oh, you don't know you were on camera?
Oh yeah. I, I thought this was a, yeah, yeah, I knew that. Okay. Yeah. I'm ready. Are you actually
ready for this? Yeah, I'm ready. Yeah. We told everybody they were going to be doing, being on
stream, right? You didn't tell people they were going to be on camera. Okay. Well, I'm going to
have to knock that down for you, actually, Community Jay, because that's ridiculous.
Continue game. Maybe you can, you can load in, go to the laptop and then maybe play House Flipper
before. Yeah, yeah, yeah. I like the demeanor, by the way. Yeah, yeah, this is great. Yeah, yeah,
no, it's no big deal. I mean, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, it's great. It's great. I like the demeanor.
I think the accent is there. Yeah. I think it's good. Yeah. I actually do think it's good. Number
four, you're oppressing me so far. All right. Thank you. Go to the mail. Okay. Yeah, yeah,
I played it. Don't worry about it. Oh, you have? Yeah, no, I'm done. Yeah, I'm done. Yeah, I got
this. Are you done? Yeah, I'm done. Don't worry about it. I got this. Yeah, it's a big, big deal.
I've done this. Yeah. Ex-boyfriend celebrating. Yeah, except, yeah, easy. I've done this. Yeah,
it's nothing. Number four, you're perfect. Let me load. All right. Number four, you actually,
number four, don't even worry about it. We can send in number five. Oh, we're done. Oh, we're
done. You're done. You're good. You don't have to even play House Flipper. Go ahead. Go ahead.
All right. Send in number five. All right. High five him on the way out. You got it. You got it.
He was perfect. He was perfect. He had the exact demeanor. He had like the exact caveman kind of
demeanor. Number five, how are you? Hi. Good. Good. How are you? Number five, what are you going to be
playing? I'm going to be high. Yes, I'm going to be playing Dark Souls. Dark Souls. Okay. Yes. All
right. This is House Flipper. Number four, by the way, I just want to make sure you're aware
number four is phenomenal. Oh. I don't want to put any pressure on you. Okay. Yeah. So, all right.
Let's do this. This doesn't work. All right. Let's rock and fucking roll. Whoa. Left click should be
swing. Right click should be, yeah, block or whatever. Whoa. This is, all right, great. Number
five is I want to make sure a fall joke would be extra points. Oh, yes. Well, you know, because
the jokes, they're planned. What's this guy? Hey, buddy. What's up? Oh, okay. No, don't do that.
What's, what did I do to roll again? Oh, okay. There we go. Yeah. You know, your mom doesn't love
you. Your mom doesn't love you. Your mom doesn't love you. There we go. Okay. Cool. What were we
supposed to do? There he is. Well, you know, there's beggars can't be winners and choosers. So,
that's a great thing. Also true. Oh, hey, buddy. How you doing? Welcome to Starbucks. Nobody asked
you for the ice cream. Whoa. Whoa. Hey, buddy. What are you doing there? You got my money. You
got my money. That's something I would do. Yeah. It's, you know, fucking money. Got my money. What
is this? Number five favorite game of all time. Oh, it's definitely going to be, um, it was the one
where you beat the people up with the money and the cars. Grand Theft Auto. I love that game.
Which GTA? Oh, the one with the, the, the Roman numerals of, yeah, you're going to go in there.
You're going to actually, what are you supposed to do here? Press A. I'm pressing A. Which one?
I think number five, the one with the five. Yeah. Yeah. That's the one where you could fly around
and do the things where you like the cops are after you and stuff. Like you go to, oh, hey,
pull that edge. Oh, don't worry. Hi, buddy. What's up? Hey, you got my money. You got my money.
You got my fucking money. Watch out for that ledge. Number five. Watch out for that ledge.
Yeah. Don't fall off that ledge. I don't know if it would be funny or not. Oh, it would definitely,
would definitely be funny. I'm not sure. Yes. Oh, thank God. Oh, thank God. I won, right?
Oh, number five. I think, I don't think I need to see anymore. Okay. Well, it's been great. Um,
it's been fantastic. Thank you so much. What a pleasure. Thank you. Thank you. Go ahead and
send in number six, please. What a classic joke that was. Absolutely classic joke. Number
six, how are you? Good, sir. Good to see you. What are you going to be doing for us today?
Today will be dark souls. Well, good, because number five just left you out for exactly where
you need to be. Appear to be some sort of a knight. Should be an easy game. The controller
no longer functions. Number two broken. So if you use WASD on the keyboard there, you should be able
to make it. Oh, old school. Easy peasy. And the mouse too should work. Okay. I'll be careful of
that ledge. You don't want to fall off the ledge because number five, I'll be honest, number five
did the fall joke already. All right. Well, this is going to be too easy. I'm used to beating games
like broken trail. Oh shit. No, I'm fine. No, no, no, no. There you go. Actually can work under
pressure. Number six can work under pressure. I'm some sort of a paladin. This looks to be one of
my black robes friends. I don't know why the controller is vibrating. It doesn't work. It feels
good actually against my skin. Number six. There's some sort of a technical. Oh, number six. That was
actually a hilarious way to go. There was some sort of a technical glitch, I think. I don't think my
controller is working right. Your controller is broken. Is that what you say? Well, I mean, I am
a hardcore gamer. So what's your favorite game of all time? Oregon trail. Oh boy. That's bad.
Okay. Oh boy. Oh, this is easy. Click, click, click and slash. So number six, you like it when,
for instance, like people just get diarrhea through the whole game and you lose no matter what. Yeah,
I'm having some sort of a red diarrhea problem in this game. I don't know what that is, but it's
leaking out of my chest cavity. And I saw a wolf. To defeat my former friend. No one comes to the
boss door. Space is dodge by the way. Number six. Space is dodge. Oh, okay. Oh, you got a backstab.
Power punch. That was actually pretty good. Yeah, he's been working out. He's been to the gym a
couple times this week and. Number six. Destroy. Number six, I will consider this if you can get
through the boss door. A, A, A, A, A, jump. I will consider this if you get in the boss door.
What would A be? Meditate. A. A on the mouse and keyboard. Who knows? Does anybody know in chat?
Anybody know? Can anybody say it? Enter, save friend to enter. Lord of the Rings. No. Do you
like Lord of the Rings? Well, of course. Okay. Now what would you, what was the last time you
shit in your pants number six? Just about two minutes ago actually. Perfect. Right now actually.
E should be to go through the door. E. E to enter. I think you have to be standing in front of it.
So number six is shit in your pants right now. Is that what you're saying? It's a little bit
frightening here. There we go. This is easy. Number six, if you last more than 10 seconds
of this boss, I will consider it. Okay. I just. You're just supposed to click the left
button multiple times. Thank you number six. Thank you so much. That was a pleasure.
Well, we'll be in touch. Thank you so much number six. Thank you so much number six. Appreciate it.
We'll be in touch. He did get in the boss door though. Nobody else did. Nobody else has gotten
in the tutorial box zone. Set it number seven please. Number seven. How are you? Hello, I'm good.
What are you going to be doing for us number seven? Hoping for, you got destiny two on this?
I don't have destiny two at all. Were you playing house flipper? We'll do house flipper. Yeah.
Okay. I think you're going to probably have to use the keyboard and mouse. The controller is
Mad Cat's controller. No, it's a, I think it's something A. I don't know what it is. Okay.
House flipper. Okay. You know how you're going to play house flipper. I've played this game before
a good bit. What's going on chat today? We're going to be doing more house flipper again.
You guys have seen this one before a couple of times. Well, if I've actually played this
mission yet, I think you're in the tutorial, like in the house, uh, which by the way,
if you make it into the computer, that would be huge. Nobody else has done that.
Make it to the computer. Yeah. Like the laptop. Like this. Yeah. Just to do a job or something.
Oh, okay. Well, we're in a house right now. It seems. Turn around. Okay. Turn back around.
What's your, what was your name? Uh, Connor. Connor what? Uh, eat pants. That's your last name.
Well, middle and last. Yeah. You're going to eat pants. What is that? German French.
I'm not actually sure. I haven't actually done a DNA test yet. Okay. Connor eats pants. Wait,
wait, hold on a minute. Wait, wait, wait, wait. We, I was on a show with you. Yeah. I'm cleaning.
What is it? Do you want to continue? What the fuck are you doing here? No,
you're Connor eats pants. Yeah. You have your own channel. You want to be. Well, yeah. I mean,
you're getting a little older and like people always are like, you know, like
Connor wins German lives. I'm like, okay, well I'll apply. I saw the audition and here I am.
You have, you are a young, talented, you, you don't need to be here.
No. Yeah. Okay. Okay. Connor eats pants. I was going to beat it. Eat a level. No,
you're not going to beat you. Get out. Just go. You don't, you don't, you got to call.
Um, you don't get any call. You have a promising career in your own, you have your own channel.
I know you're not going to be there. Thank you. Thank you. What is he? What the fuck is he doing
here? Did you know that it was Connor Eats Pants? Number eight. Hi. How are you? I'm good. Did you
see Connor Eats Pants out there? No. You see his pants? No, I don't, I don't know why that's his
name. What was his name? That's weird. Number eight. How are you? That's me. I'm good. Oh,
that was weird. Why is he here? He has like a successful channel. What's he doing here?
You have booked all these people and I'm fucking furious. Don't worry about that. The audition is
Hey, how are you? I'm a normal guy. I'm not, you know, I was just like, that was fucked up and
annoying. Hey, he's a smart, fun guy, but you know, this is for the next gerbil, not for the next
goner. You know what I'm saying? Oh, go ahead and see. Okay. I got it. So what are you going to play
for us? Number eight. Uh, I think it's a game called Dark Souls. Okay. You don't know what the
game is, but that's what you're playing. Okay. I'm pretty sure. Should get you into here right here.
By the way, you're going to have to use keyboard and mouse. Keyboard and mouse. All right. W A S D
left click and right click. Nobody has been able to beat the tutorial boss. Number eight. True boss.
Okay. Left click, right click. Okay. That's like a, this is like a shield. Let's click space. Oh,
almost fell off the cliff. That's fun. Okay. Oh, you want me to go up the cliff? Oh, hello.
Uh-oh. Uh-oh. If you get a backstab here, that's huge to break. All right.
We're going to try. Oops. Where's my sword? Did I lose it? This is very interesting.
Okay. Oh, there we go. I can play now. Okay. Here we go. We got this. We got this. We got this.
We're in the game. We are in the game. This is the boss, right? Yes. Okay. I got this. This is
actually one of the bosses. So if you beat this boss, that's a big. Oh, I'm going to, I'm going
to do it. Oh wait. Oh no. Very close. I'm beating the boss. I was really close, right? That was very
close. Oh man. Do I get another try or? Yes, go for it. Oh, sweet. Awesome. Okay. I was like really
close. Okay. What's your favorite food? Favorite food. Oh, it's got to be like sushi or something.
Yep. Yeah. Gross. What's your second favorite food, number eight? Uh, pizza. I mean, why not, right?
Oh, pub. Pizza, pub. Okay. Yeah. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. I'm going to get this boss. Here we go.
Yeah. Just the first one. I got this. I got this. That was a good punch, right?
Oh, here we go. Oh, no, no, no. Block it. Block it. Block it. Block it. Okay. Okay. Okay. I got this.
I got this. What's your favorite phrase? Favorite phrase is, ah, golly gee willikers. It should have
been Hakuna Matata. That's a, that's a really good one. I mean, a Disney fan at heart. Minus five points.
I think I was like a little closer that time. It was okay. Yeah. It was all right. It was okay.
I gave you one more try. One more try. Oh my God. Okay. I got this. I got this. Some deep breathing.
Okay. Here we go. Here we go. I'm ready. You ready? Let's do it. Yeah. Yeah.
If you beat this one enemy, then, I mean, this boss, I mean. Okay. I got this. I got this.
Oh, he's up here now. Oh, this is a little confusing. Every time you set a bonfire,
enemies respawn. They respawn. Okay. Okay. I'm coming in for it. There's a punch.
Got it. Block the shield. Oh, no. I got cut up. Okay. We're coming back in. We're coming back in.
Here we go. Here we go. Here we go. Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh my gosh. Yes. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Come on. No, no, no, no, no, no. First boss of the game. First boss of the game. I can do it.
He got the first boss. Oh my gosh. I did it. Number eight, number eight. That's all I need to see.
He got the first boss of the game. You see, no one else got it. No one else is beating the first boss.
Oh my gosh. Wow. That was really exciting. Thank you so much, number eight. Hey, thank you. That's
it. We'll be in touch. Wow. Thank you. Remember, we call you, don't ever call me. Of course, yeah.
For literally any reason. I don't care if you're even in the hospital right now. Yeah, okay. Yeah,
thanks. Wow. Number nine, please send a number nine. All right. Holy shit. Okay. Yeah, we're
ready here. Yeah, we're ready here. Okay, here we are. Oh, is... Number nine, the controller does
not work. It doesn't work. Okay. You have to use keyboard and mouse. W A S D. If you're not familiar,
then I would choose Tetris. Okay. W A S D U P S. Okay. We also, you know what? Let's give you the
fucking sword for the love of God. Yeah, yeah. How do we give you the sword? Because somebody took
off the fucking sword. Yeah, plug the controller in. Because you can't just play Dark Souls without a
sword on. We're going to figure this out. I feel confident that we can figure this out. I think
we got it. Do we got it? No, we got this controller. It don't work. Hey, ask chat how to go to the
menu because there's no sword. And people just keep dying and nobody's gone to the tutorial yet.
Is it escape? It is. Let me help you out here, number nine. Thank you. So what the fuck? Where is
it? How do you take out the other hand? How do you like swap? How come it's not on there?
Sorry about this. No, this is... We are usually incredibly professional. No, this is all right.
It should be there. Long sword. Where is it? Somebody in chat want to help us? What's going
on here? T? E? Like how? Where is it? Right arrow key. Right arrow key. Hey, there we go. Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you. Okay. Okay. Okay. Read message. I'll read the message later. You know,
I got... Oh, no. Take the sword back out. Maybe I'm going to... Space is dodge by the way. Space is
very important in this game. Very, very important. Okay. Just going to... Okay. Hey,
hey there, buddy. Just going to... Okay. Space. Space. Yep. Can't touch me.
They hate him. Oh, yeah. This is the brutal one. Left click is swinging the weapon.
Can't get me. Can't get me when I'm going backwards. Can you? Nope.
Nope. Nope. Nope. Oh, God. Just... Wow. Two at once. Really? This is how the day is going.
Number nine, I've got to say, I would like to see you get through the tutorial anymore, please.
Thank you. Thank you for the... Thank you for the another chance. I appreciate it. Number nine,
what's your favorite pasta? Favorite pasta? Linguini. Is that the right answer? Is that the
right answer? Could be. Okay. Okay. What's your favorite game of all time, government?
Favorite game of all time? Of all time. Oh, Pokemon. Just Pokemon Red. Pokemon Red. I think
we're going OG. I really wish I could also switch up the camera angle here, but... Oh. Oh,
okay. Back to my old friend here. Hey, buddy. No, let's talk. Let's be civilized people here
and talk. Let's not use our weapons unless I'm using mine. Can I... Nope. Can't. I would use
Yeah. Yeah. No, I should use the weapon.
Oh, we're in business now. Yeah, that's right. Thank you.
Oh, I was like, this is very... This is an intense audition. Look at you. Play the game.
Also, if you could rub your belly and pat your head, that would be great.
If you could give me a look at me, if you could. Can you give me a look at me? Wait. Look at you?
Can you give me a look at me? Look at me. Look at me. Look at me. Look at me. Look at me. Look at
me. All right. I've seen it on number nine. Thank you so much. I appreciate it. Thank you.
That was fantastic. And when I said it on number 10, it was... Don't get your butt kicked from the
door. They can hurt you. Number 10, how are you? I'm number 10. I'm great. What are you going to
be doing for us on number 10? Oh, I'm doing some Dark Souls. Yeah. Everybody's... Let me ask you
do you... Can you get through the tutorial boss's door? Oh, yeah. I mean, listen. So long as I don't
have a sword, I'm going to be doing just fabulous workout here. Absolutely. Anyone know how I can
get the sword? Right on the right arrow key. Oh. On the keyboard right arrow key. Oh, let's go, baby.
Space is dodge, by the way. Make sure that... Oh, yeah. Space is very important. This game is all
about watching these. Oh, oh, okay. Yeah. All right. Everybody picked Dark Souls. Oh, let's go,
baby. Let's go. All right. Okay. I'm feeling pretty hot. Feeling pretty sexy right now. Number 10,
if you get the first boss right now, it would be $1,000. Oh my God. Let's go. I need that rent
money, baby. Let's go. Oh, shit. Oh, yeah. Let's... Nope. Yes. Number 10, if you actually go into
this door with E and get the first boss, that would be $1,000. All right. I'm in it. I'm in it
to win it. I'm in it for the thousand. Let's go, baby. Come here. Come here. Give it to me. Nope.
Absolutely not. Let's go. Give it to me. Press E. What is drink Estus? Can we get... Can somebody
chat? Oh, I do need that Estus. Cause he's really going to... That index thunder is actually the
first boss. It's very, very scary. Oh, yeah. It's a big boy. Whoa. Give it to him. Give it to him.
Okay. All right. Just... This is a war of attrition here. Come on, Gunder. Let's go, Grandle.
Press R. It's all right. It's all right. That was very good. Number 10, can I get a look at me,
please? Yeah. Oh, look at me. Look at me. Look at me. Look at me right here. Look at me. Perfect.
Perfect. Thank you. That's all we need to see. We'll be in touch really... Thank you very much.
Appreciate it. Thank you, number 10. Really appreciate that. Send in number 11. Oh, number 11?
Number 11? Can you come in for a second here? Hey. How are you, number 11? Good. How are you?
What are you going to do for us today, number 11? I'm going to try that Dark Souls.
Unless you'd rather something else. No, please play Dark Souls. Please play it. Okay. Number 11.
I need to be very clear. Number 11. Dark Souls. Nobody's gone through the tutorial door.
Can you make it through the tutorial boss's door and beat the tutorial boss in Dark Souls 3?
You know what? I'm definitely going to try. What's your favorite pasta?
Like the noodle or all of it combined? Everything. I like rigatoni marinara,
bolognese. Rigatoni bolognese. Okay. That's a good answer. Yeah. It's my favorite.
Number 11, did you ever shit your pants? Of course. When was the last time?
Just before I got in here. Sorry. I didn't want to admit it. Very good answer, actually.
Go ahead. It's keyboard and mouse. W-A-S-D is to move. Left click is to swim your sword,
and space is to dodge. If you could take up that controller there right now, if you could.
Just control it down here? Well, the controller's broken,
but the keyboard and mouse, you do W-A-S-D to move. W-A-S-D to move?
Number two broke the controller, and we're very upset about it.
Damn it. Number two. Oh my god. Fuck me.
So if you hit W-A-S-D. I get it. I get it. Yeah, it's move.
If you hold W-A-S-D, hold W will get you to where you need to be.
Oh, great. Okay, I'm going to just go down here, I suppose.
Yeah. Oh, you didn't tell me what the attacks are.
Left click is attack, and space is dodge. Did I kill him?
You did. Fuck yeah. Okay, I guess I'm going this way.
Number 11, say shpee for me, please. Shpee.
Again? Shpee.
What is happening? You guys want to kill?
That's good. Wow, maybe I will get through that door.
That's the door right there. When you get up to that door, you press E, you'll fight the boss.
R is drink potion to heal. Very important.
R is drink potion to heal? Oh, shit.
Make sure you get rid of that guy. Yeah, yeah, yeah. I just got to face him,
you know? Careful, careful. You got it.
You got it, you got it. You said R?
I'm healed. Where's my health? Oh, right there.
Cool. Top left corner.
You ever play Dark Souls before, number 11? No, but I used to play Crash Bandicoot,
and we would call that Dark Souls because that game is hard as hell too.
Good answer. You ever play Crash Bandicoot?
I have. That game is ridiculous.
All right, here's this bastard. Yeah, I'd definitely say so.
Number 11, thank you so much for your time. Yeah, thank you.
We appreciate it. Thank you so much. You can send it in the next one when you get out there.
Absolutely. Thank you so much, number 11.
Big Crash Bandicoot fan. Big Crash Bandicoot fan.
Love it. Hi.
Well, how are you? Good.
How are you? Good to see you.
Do you have ready to give us a little bit of a show here? I don't know if you want to play?
What can I play? You got it.
Do you want to play Dark Souls? No.
Okay. We've got Tetris. That sounds scary.
We've got Tetris, and we have also House Flipper.
Well, I will try Tetris. Tetris, all right.
We've got a Tetris player here. What is Tetris?
You're asking what Tetris is. Yeah.
I don't know what any of these games are, but Tetris sounded cool.
You don't even know what Tetris is?
Thanks a lot for coming, number 12. I appreciate it.
See, we'll be in touch. We'll be in touch. Thank you so much for your time.
You sure? Yeah, yeah, that's fine.
You don't even know. You don't even go home. You don't know what Tetris is.
No. Do you know who Super Mario is?
Yes. Have a nice night.
Thank you so much. I appreciate it. Number 12, that was really fantastic.
Thank you so much. Thank you.
Number 13 can come on in, please.
How do you know what Tetris is? Number 13, how are you?
Good, good, good. Thank you.
Good to see you. What are you going to do for us?
Good to be here. Well, I am going to do Tetris.
Do you know what it is? I do.
Okay, great. You press the okay button here.
You can put in whatever initials you want. It doesn't really matter.
It's just like a random website. That's fine.
I just hit the restart button right in the middle there.
So you got the arrow keys, it should be, to move the Tetris pieces around.
And then flip them around and down is to make it go down.
And number 13, I'd like to go right up to that.
What's your favorite sound is?
How do you flip it again?
It should be the right and left arrow keys.
The right and space. Space.
Oh, okay. That one's garbage, but the next one will be better.
All right. Let's see if I can hit this down and then slide it across right now.
Yeah, that's the ticket. We're hit to be square here.
So Tetris is really fun because it was invented in the 1600s in Russia
and people would play with nothing but sticks and vodka.
And here we are all these years later playing.
Interesting story. Is that the way?
That's history. That's history.
Yeah. Vladimir Tetrisnov invented it and they used to play with rocks and sticks
and they would try to fit it.
And apparently they would build whole villages this way.
And that's why Russia is such a messed up place now.
Number 13, can I get a hug of England?
There's other reasons too. Economics, pop, but mostly I blame Tetris.
So Tetris was invented, I did not know that. That's a lore conversation.
Oh, you remember the theme song, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding.
You know, you know that's vodka right there.
You gonna get a good clear here in number 13?
A good clear?
I gotta get a clear? Boy, clear.
Well, I think you're asking a lot for the first time, but I'll try to impress you.
Oh, it was one line though.
Well, we all gotta start somewhere. All gotta start somewhere.
Oh, you got actually. All right. Bingo, bingo, bingo, bingo. Very nice number 13.
I spent a lot of summers playing on my Game Boy. I didn't have a lot of friends.
Now I have two friends, but back then I didn't have any.
You always got to one up me, huh?
You're trying to be me. Don't forget that. Can I get a look at me, please?
Can I get a look? Can I get you to say, look at me?
Look at me. Again?
Look at me. Number 13, that's all I need to see. Thank you so much. Number 13.
Thank you. Next time.
Excellent. Excellent. Wait till the door closes and we talk about it.
Donnie, when you're out, we talk about you after the door closes.
Oh, I thought you wanted to talk about me now.
No, no. When the door closes, we talk about you.
You're gonna have my ear pressed to the door.
I hope you don't do that.
Number 14, please send in number 14.
That's no.
Hey, get in here.
No, you're 14. You're 14. Come on.
I know.
How are you 14?
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you 14. We have Tetris here for you.
We might have to restart it, but what were you going to play for us?
I mean, I love Tetris. I was going to do House Flipper.
Do you know how to play House Flipper? Or do you know how to play Tetris?
Which is better for you?
Looks like we're going with Tetris.
Can you salvage this?
Salvage this game right now?
If you salvage this game, number 14, that is a monumental deal.
Well, look at where they left me.
Just...
By the way, number 14, did you know that the Russians played this?
The Russians played this.
Apparently.
Really?
Yeah. If you can salvage this, that's a huge deal.
Number 14, what's your favorite ride at Disney World?
I'd have to say it's a small world.
Wrong.
Correct.
Try again.
Okay. The Pirate of the Caribbean ride.
Good.
Thank you. All right.
Ah!
Not bad.
A salvage.
Pretty good salvage actually. You can use the keys too if it helps you.
I can. Which keys?
Should be the left and right arrow keys.
Oh, yes.
Not bad.
Under pressure as well.
This is huge under pressure.
I was thrown into a game.
I feel like this is what happens to people.
14, what's your favorite emote on Switch?
My favorite emote?
I'd have to say...
MonkaS.
Okay.
Thank you.
Game over.
Game over. Did you lose?
Try one more. Try one more.
I'll give you one more attempt because you knew it was a game.
Okay.
If you were to use MonkaS in a sentence, how would you use it?
I would say...
I got put in the middle of a Tetris game of someone else and I failed.
So that makes me want to go...
MonkaS.
Thank you.
Very nice.
Here we go.
By the way, I never played Tetris on my screen one time.
I think the game sucks. I think it's a stupid fucking child's game.
Well, that's why I think I should have done House Flipper.
Yeah.
I think it's a stupid game for unintelligent people.
Intelligent people play...
That must have been number 13, Joyce, so...
Actually, you're doing actually a pretty good build up on number 14.
You think so?
Oh, shit.
Oh, shoot. Number 14.
Somebody help me.
Oh, number 14.
Okay. Thank you so much, Green.
I'm going to have to cancel you out there.
I'm sorry.
Close you out there, number 14.
Thank you so much for coming.
Thank you.
Please send in number 15.
15, how are you?
I'm great. How are you?
Good to see you, 15.
All right. What are we doing?
What do you want to play for us?
We got Dark Souls, House Flipper, and Tetris.
Let's play some Tetris.
All right. You want to go Tetris?
Yeah.
You got a game going right now.
All right. Oh, but who was this person?
They didn't... I didn't do this.
This is not me.
Under Pressure was even here.
Oh, that's a great song.
It is.
Yeah. I like these pieces because they're small and compact like me.
Oh, how do I... Oh, yeah, okay.
Where do I go?
Oh, and the colors.
Oh, all the colors.
Yeah.
Okay, there we go.
Look at that.
You see that?
I wonder if you're clear.
Oh, I'll clear the line.
I'll clear it all the way down the line.
Oh, they're cooking with the gas right now.
Oh, I am prepared.
I was up all night.
Just me and some jilt cola, baby.
Oh, look at this. Look at this.
I'm building a tower of love.
Let's see how the pressure's on now.
Careful here, number 15.
I know. I know.
You're getting close.
No, but I was creating sort of a mosaic.
You know, a mosaic.
You can restart it. I want to see one more.
Okay. All right.
How do I turn these things anyway?
So you should be using the left and right arrow keys you're doing.
The knobs might be a little bit trickier for you.
Oh, I see.
Oh, I see. I see. Okay.
And then I'm going to nestle this guy in here.
I'm just going to hug him gently.
You see that? You see that?
That was very nice.
Thank you.
Very impressed.
Yeah. See, the original Game Boy was loaded with this.
Did you have a Game Boy?
I did. I won.
The only game I ever beat was DuckTales.
That's a great game.
It is a great game.
You've played one now on NES.
No, I wasn't allowed to have that because my parents don't love me.
I had to play it over at friends' homes.
I had to play it over there.
That's also where I got sugared cereal.
Nothing but bran flakes and grape nuts at my place.
Very interesting backstory.
It's a little bit of a bio there.
Hold on. I got to do this.
It feels so good.
Oh, wait. I got to do this.
Get the other one too.
Yeah, I got to do this.
It feels so good.
15. That's all I need to see.
Okay. All right.
Absolutely phenomenal job, by the way.
Brought a change of pants.
Thank God. All right.
Everybody shook their pants before they got here?
Is that a requirement?
Number 16.
You didn't think we had more than 10 people?
16, how are you?
Hi, good. How are you?
Good. I'm doing fantastic.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
I'm very, very happy to meet you.
We already have Tetris going, but there's also other options
if you'd like to give us something.
Cool. Could I play Dark Souls?
You absolutely could.
We have all tablets.
The controller is broken.
Unfortunate.
So you have to keyboard and mouse.
WASD, left click, right click.
R is Estus and space is dodge.
What's Perry?
Perry, good fucking question.
What if number 16, you're the first person to ask that question.
So we're going to go ahead and write that down.
Okay.
First of all, number 16, 17, no, it's 16 people,
probably nine people picked Dark Souls for some reason.
Okay, that's a lot.
And none of them have, I think,
the computer is held by about 10 percent.
So just to know that.
Okay.
I'm just going to give you a different dark soul if you're worried about that.
Okay, okay.
Tab to Perry?
Okay.
It's tab is Perry, okay.
That's what Chad says.
Oh, okay, watch.
Shift, someone says shift.
Shift.
Is shift Perry?
Ah, control.
Okay, it's control.
Okay, we're good.
We're starting, okay.
Go for it.
All right, let's play some Dark Souls here.
Get ourselves some, excuse me, sir.
I'm trying to complete something here if you'll kindly back off of me.
Thank you.
Number 16, what's the accent you're doing?
Oh, well, I figured, you know, this is the new German, right?
Yeah.
Well, why would we want the same old cookie cutter German
when we could have a new German?
You know, I think maybe new German could like be like a cowboy and have like a beard.
So, you know, like we want to constantly be improving.
Right.
So, you know, that's why I think we should kind of keep it going
but constantly strive to do better.
Okay, I guess I follow you on that a little bit here.
Are you willing to shave the beard?
Well, that's a difficult question.
I guess it depends on if it's worth it, but I suppose I could part with it.
And you're okay with a 5% royalties on the screen
and 95% going through?
Yeah, I suppose, given the numbers.
They're huge, by the way.
Yeah, that's what I want to figure.
Just making sure we get that correct before we sign anything for anybody.
It should be E to go through.
Oh, I see, okay.
You could be champion Grunder and you're the first to do that.
Let's give it a big old college try.
Good try.
Let's see what you got.
So, not to give you anything to think about why you're doing this,
but number 16, what would you say is your favorite ride at Disney win?
That's a tough one.
I'd say Big Thunder Mountain if I had to give it the old guess.
Staying with the country person.
Well, that's me and the country person thing.
Dude, we're going to lean into that, okay?
What's your favorite food?
I'd say chicken fried steak.
Listen, I don't break character ever.
You better believe me.
Okay, I'm going to look at these books.
Yeah.
Number 16, can I just say, look at me loudly and put your hands in your mouth?
Look at me.
Oh, hold on.
I've got a good master's here.
Is it good for your health?
Holy shit.
Are you going to beat Gundyr?
I mean, it's Gundyr.
It's not that hard.
Wow.
Number 16.
All right, Gigi.
You just beat Gundyr.
You just did it.
No, it's even gone through the door.
I usually play on key on controller.
I don't know if that's a problem.
Number 16, that was phenomenal.
I just have to be very, I got to make sure you really wear this.
That beard though.
Is that just, that's, you just got to go.
That beard has to go.
Okay.
Well, sometimes we got to make sacrifices.
Thank you so much.
That was fantastic.
Number 16.
You can send it number 17.
I'm sure that was phenomenal.
Y'all come back now here.
I don't know why you keep doing this country thing.
It doesn't make sense to me.
Because I'm literally from the East Coast, from like Boston.
Like I could see like in New York.
Send number 17, please.
And that should round us out.
Number 17.
Do we not have 17?
17 is not here.
Number 17 is not here.
We have number 16 is there.
Okay.
That's the best we got.
That's what we got.
I mean, it was never classified in the country.
And all the newspapers in the country.
Okay.
I, this is going to take a little bit of deliberation here.
I have no fucking idea.
I'm, give me, I don't know if I'm addressing this camera here.
But like, give me a few minutes.
I need to think about what I'm going to do about this.
Because there are 16, there are 16 people here that I mean, I don't know.
I have no idea.
I'm going to need a few minutes.
Give us a few minutes.
Let me deliberate on this and think about what I want to do here.
And we'll be right back in just a few minutes.
Phone of friends.
So this is harder than I thought it was going to be, unfortunately.
I knew it was going to be hard.
But trying to eliminate people is not my, my forefront.
But I will do my best.
I'm going to have to say I've spent 10, 20 minutes sitting here trying to figure out
what I want to do here.
I'm going to have to cut.
I mean, number, I mean, number seven, Connor.
What are you doing here?
Connor Reid's pants.
You've got, you have a career going for yourself for the love of God.
You're a young guy.
You've got a great career in front of you.
You don't, you don't got to be me.
Be you.
And you, you're doing you very well.
Also, I mean, the number 12 didn't know how to play Tetris.
Just get out of here.
I mean, what, what are we going to do with you?
And then probably at the same time, I mean, number 16 as well.
We actually talked backstage.
He didn't want to shave his beard once and for all.
So I was like, I mean, if you're not going to shave how he, yeah.
Oh, country German.
That's not going to happen, man.
That's all I could come up with so far.
I sat for 10, 20 minutes.
Remember, this is me.
This is my shit.
This is my channel.
I have to be sure of this stuff.
So what's going to have to happen here over the next,
I don't know how long it's going to take,
but I've employed a few people to try to really narrow down
who I think could be the next German 985.
I need some help.
I need some more context.
So let's go ahead and start episode one,
season one, episode one, final pilot one,
end of the series one, final episode one
of Who Will Replace Me on German 985.
Hello. How are you?
Welcome to Who Will Replace Me on German 985.
I'm German 985.
Welcome. How are you?
I figured this would be probably hard to do.
So I have employed a few people,
at least a handful of people to help me do this.
And we'll go one by one to find out
who could help me decide who could replace me.
So we'll go back over here.
We have Ster here.
Nice to meet you, everyone.
I've known Germa a long time,
so I've been judging him my whole life,
and I feel like I'm especially qualified for this opportunity.
Camera's over there, honey.
I apologize. He's judging me.
I know. I'm just ready to figure out who the new Germa is.
I've been waiting for a new one for a long time,
and I hope we get, you know,
a better result than the first one.
Yeah.
By the way, when you talk about judges,
I had to bring people in
because there's no way I can do this by myself.
It was impossible to sit there and be like,
oh, who's better? Who can do it? Who can't do it?
I need experts.
And Ster has been around for a long time.
He's been around for about 12 years now
since the very, very, very beginning.
I'm 31. I've been around for 31 years.
We also have Ludwig here.
Ludwig is also part of the new school of Germa fans.
He's been around for like the last few years.
Ludwig, thanks so much for showing up here.
Yeah, it's a pleasure.
You know, I'm one of the few people
who actually took your role,
and your chat tried to kill me.
They did?
So I'm just trying to make sure
whoever we pick today is not at threat to die.
It's really, I couldn't do it.
When 16 people come in the room,
it's hard to base who I can do it on.
Why was that funny?
I don't know.
There's just a couple of words there.
Our third, our fourth judge
is somebody, a fan favorite of the channel.
He's my doctor.
He's been around since I can really remember.
To make sure blood pressure, blood type,
and all that is exact.
Dr. Schmikeson, thank you for coming out here.
Thank you.
Thank you so much for inviting me
to be on your panel, Jeremy.
And as you know, the others
might be interested in your talents,
but as a doctor, I know Germa Jeremy.
He knows me in and out.
In and out completely.
Wow.
Yeah, blood type.
We're talking blood pressure.
And he doesn't have very much time left, right?
For me?
I didn't think we were going to bring that up.
Am I dying?
I didn't know this.
I'd like to talk to you later
about some Germa fans.
Dr. Schmikeson, Ludwig and Ster
to judge these people.
Because I mean, we're talking about my replacement.
And I've been a content creator.
You've been a content creator, Ster,
for about 12 years now.
And trying to find the person
that can take the brand to the next level.
We're going to find that now.
By the way, let's explain
how this is going to work.
We have in front of us here, we have buttons.
People are going to come out on stage.
I've eliminated a few people off the bat
because I don't think they can handle it, by the way.
But we have a few buttons here.
When we press these buttons,
they are going to play.
Okay, we don't all have to do it.
We're demonstrating.
They don't believe us.
It makes this noise.
Three...
Three Xs means you are out.
Three Yeses means you are into the next round.
This is a talent portion of this stream here.
We got Dr. Schmikeson, Ster, Ludwig.
I think...
Me, I'm judging you too.
They're all backstage right now.
Who knows Jerma better than Jerma?
Exactly.
Who would know me...
Who would know me better than me?
Nobody does.
I know...
Actually, I don't know me at all.
That's why you were here.
You lose yourself sometimes.
I lose myself sometimes, but it's okay.
I would like to call to the stage now.
You got soda right here
because just like that show that we can't say,
it's delicious.
It's got soda in there.
Drink it up.
Can we get number one to come out on stage, please?
Three Xs means you are out.
Three Yeses means you are into the next round.
Number one, how are you?
I am very well.
How are you?
Thank you, number one.
Good.
Great.
Nobody's X-ed, right?
Okay.
I like the walk a lot.
That's how you walk around.
That's a good walker.
Look at me.
Somebody, somebody got it.
Finally, somebody got it right.
Number one, what are you going to do for us today?
I believe I'm going to juggle today for it.
Juggling, okay.
Maybe sing a few bars of my favorite song as well.
Okay.
Whenever you're ready, we'll go ahead and get that started.
Thank you.
No, pull it back.
Pull it back.
That's not fair.
Okay.
I just want the next hour to be this.
Could you make a German noise while doing it?
Higher.
Oh, he dropped one.
What do we do about that?
Higher.
Can you go higher?
Go higher.
No, don't take that back.
Does he think we're going to hire in notes?
What is that?
Fan, I'm not going to say anything.
Is that it?
Here, I'll try one more for you.
Hold on.
Great.
That might have got me.
That got me.
Wow.
Number one, number one.
Okay.
Chefs, I would say I'm going to have to be a yes on this one.
Uh, you know, I was almost a no and I was sitting there and I was thinking
he's not doing anything with the lower half of his body.
And then when you incorporated the leg...
I'm sorry.
You've been disqualified.
I get it.
I totally understand.
It's okay.
I enjoyed the performance.
Can you explain what the thought process between ah-ee-oo was?
Very good.
Very good idea.
It's the greatest song in the world.
It's my favorite song.
Could you give me just a five-second interpretation of what a Raid song is?
Okay.
A Raid song?
A Raid song.
Raid song.
Yeah.
Pull it back.
He goes first.
I don't know what my status is right now.
It's, uh...
Dr. Schmeichsen, what do you have to say?
Yes, yes.
Thank you, number one.
Number one, I just try to match things with this person at the other end of the table.
What is your basic metabolic rate?
Yeah.
So we got two X's here so far.
I think you pulled it back.
I don't...
Did you pull it back?
You pulled it back.
It's back up again.
No time left.
Sorry.
Okay, so two nos and two yeses.
I'm currently at a no.
I...
Whoa, whoa!
I don't know what...
You decided for me.
You hit my hand.
That was a joke.
Pull it back.
That's a yes from me.
I think the leg was fantastic.
Honestly, the leg was fantastic.
I think that's a good move.
We're split.
What do you want?
What do you want from our side, from our delegation?
He's got the look.
Uh-huh.
He's got the passion.
Schmeichsen, look, I would pull it back.
Can you do the thing one more time?
Which thing?
The leg, the leg.
With the leg.
Juggling leg.
Yeah, just one more.
One more time, please.
Okay.
Oh, shit.
I'm pulling it back.
That's classic.
No, no, no, no, no.
Good.
That's good.
Why did you say no?
I say no because he dropped it.
What about classic Jerma?
We're split.
We want a better Jerma.
No, no, he pulled it back.
I want the cowboy Jerma.
We want a better Jerma.
Only three yeses.
We both pulled.
That's three yeses.
Yeah, we're at three yeses.
That's three.
You're going through to the next round.
Thank you!
Yes!
Yeah!
Number one!
Okay.
You're not known for your clutch.
He's got one trick and two notes.
But he went under the leg.
That's a huge deal.
It is.
Number two.
If we get number two to come out.
Sir, you got your exit.
We got to clear it.
Dr. Shmoekson.
Yes, sir.
You have tested all the blood pressure,
all the blood types,
all the different height levels of all the patients here.
Can you reliably say that all these people could be
the next Jerma 95?
With some stipulation, I think that they're very close.
Okay, good.
I apologize.
We're calling them patients?
I mean someone, yeah.
We're calling them patients.
Okay.
Not for you!
That's not for you.
Tell us your name.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Number two.
My name is Austin.
Okay.
And I'm gonna play a little song for you guys.
Okay, don't buzz it.
What's the wrong name?
I'm sorry, I guess...
Your name's supposed to be Jerma now.
Austin doesn't make sense.
Can we?
Is it Austin 985?
No, clear the board.
Clear the board for the love of God.
All agree!
Oh, all right, all right!
There we are!
We have my attention.
Clear the board.
We all clear?
I think we're cleared.
Number two.
I think we're clear.
What are you gonna do for us today?
I'm gonna play a little song for you guys.
Okay.
All right.
Sounds good.
Now it's so sweet
Better Jerma!
Hey!
Yes!
I wouldn't say that.
The real Jerma would have got distracted by that.
Pause, time, pause, pause.
Pause right now.
It'd be nice having music in the background.
Don't you think it's like too much, though?
Music Mondays.
You think it's fun?
Yeah.
I'm actually, I'm rescinding.
Music Mondays, let's go.
All right, number two.
Number two, thank you so much.
Number two.
Very, very good job.
Oh, thanks so much.
We have, uh, we have a couple of, one no for instance here?
Um, you know, I'll take it back if you can answer this question well.
I mean, you already got three yeses, but you know, maybe you can make your case.
Really, why do you want to be Jerma?
Yeah.
Well, I just feel like, you know, teaching kids how to, how to farm properly
and, uh, and maintain their farms would be the best way to use my streaming services
and take it over for Jerma.
I mean, what a great audience.
He's got a good point.
Did he?
Oh, you said it was, you can't just keep going, sir.
Can I ask you a question?
Uh-huh.
How tall are you?
I'm five foot eight.
Perfect.
Dr. Schmuckson, do you have anything to add to that?
Yes, I actually, um, number two, I thought that was polymorphically awesome.
So, uh, I guess it's a go.
That's a go?
Yeah.
You know.
One X, but I'll take all three.
No, that's a yes.
That's a yes.
You're going on to the next round.
All right.
Great job.
I want to make sure that.
You can't just fucking press the button like over and over again.
I don't want him to be the new you.
That's annoying.
You're better than that, Jerma.
You're annoying.
I'm here for you.
Can you switch seats with him potentially?
Are we all clear?
I'll be good.
Can we send out number three, please, or whoever's in the next line here?
I'll just pick whichever person you pick.
Holy smokes!
We've got number three here.
Wow.
I'm here.
Look at me.
He's got to look at me.
Right, right.
You have nice arms, right, Jerma?
No, I've got arms, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Are you in the gym more than once a week?
I mean, home gym.
Okay.
Home gym.
He's got a home gym.
That's pretty good.
So number three, what are you going to do for us?
Seems like you already kind of have an idea here.
Well, I mean, still walking is pretty much an atmospheric talent.
So normally it's for creating an illusion of, you know, heightened magic.
Without the actual magic.
How tall are you right now?
Do you know?
Taller than you.
Okay.
I hear you're 5'8", but I can teach you.
That's fucked up.
In your retirement, you can be as tall as me.
Because I am also 5'8".
How tall do the stilts make you?
A little bit.
Seven foot?
About eight foot.
Okay, that's a lot of foot.
All right, so are you going to do a routine for us?
Are you going to walk around?
More or less, it's kind of, like I said, it's more of an atmospheric talent
where you can more or less do photo logs.
Do you do flips?
In a world that we all live in, me and you, I can reach taller things.
So I feel like I'm an improved germa.
And as you can see, I'm also firma.
Firma.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Don't clap yet.
Excuse me.
We're allowed to have our own thoughts.
What's your fursona?
My fursona is a wolf.
Okay, all right.
You know what?
I will actually, from earlier, I want to correct a mistake that I made.
I said I didn't like rats.
I want to make it clear that I do like rats,
as long as I am the large rat that makes all the rules.
Interesting.
Is that why you have a wolf tail on, sir?
You know what?
The internet is very limited on what you can buy in two-day shipping.
Okay.
It's a global pandemic.
True, true.
We've got two no's here, I think.
Oh, no.
What can I do?
Tell me.
Dr. Smikson, what do you got here?
Well, can you...
Let's see.
Turn to your left, please.
Raise your right arm.
Make a raspberry noise.
Hmm, uh, no, sorry.
I'm so sorry, number three.
That is unless we can come up with some kind of agreement.
I'm sorry, that's where your journey ends here.
I mean, I was gonna give you free lessons on still walking, but I mean...
Oh, I can still take them.
I can still take them.
I'll pay.
All right.
Very exorbitantly.
What was that?
I'd pay extra.
Number three, I'm so sorry.
There's nothing I could do.
Yeah, thank you, number three.
I appreciate your heightened performance.
Thank you so much for the chance.
Thank you so much, number three.
That's actually phenomenal.
A very good try.
It would have been fun to see him hold something out of reach from you,
and then you jump at it.
I'm gonna press your X.
Okay, sorry.
I'm sorry.
That was just an idea.
I was...
Let's go ahead and send it to the next one, please.
Who's up on tap here?
It should be number, I believe, number...
Doctor, if it's clear, your X, please.
Number four.
Hey.
Okay.
Hi, number four.
How are you?
I'm doing good, you?
I'm great, yeah.
You were kind of a weird guy in the first round.
Thanks for wanting to know one, huh?
Yeah, it does.
So true, so true.
Thank you, thank you.
So true.
Number four, what are you gonna do?
I like this guy.
Hey, how's it going?
Good, it's good.
What are you doing for us today?
I'm gonna do a little cat dog.
Cat dog?
Yeah, cat dog.
Like the show?
It's not like the show.
It's just cat dog.
Cat dog?
I'll take it at face value.
Take it at face value.
Just love it, enjoy it, yeah.
Great.
It'll be great.
Okay, number four, what are you doing?
I love cat dog.
You want me to...
He's doing cat dog.
I don't know what that means.
Can you give an artist the stage for once?
Well, what is cat dog?
You go live and you say we're playing Blumplkin 3 today
and no one questions that.
So, you know, just give him a shot.
That's true.
We're playing cat dog.
Number four, you have the floor.
Blumplkin 3, but cat dog.
Yeah, go ahead.
Don't clap.
He's a bad dog.
Absolutely fantastic performance.
I think the best we've seen all night.
We can all agree that was great.
I don't think so.
Well, I have the feeling that he suffers from dermatitis,
but having that said, I'm good.
Am I the only X here?
Do you get dermatitis from eating ass?
What's that?
Sorry, what was that?
No, just from eating X.
That's what he...
From eating ass?
Yeah, you're speaking about the posterior.
Do we have a two, V2 here?
You know, the ass talk pulled me out.
Can you make some more barking noises, please?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait a second, wait a second, wait a second.
Do we have a two, V2 here?
No, I pulled it back.
It's just you, I think, that do not enjoy this.
I'm not sure about that.
But an old, aging German wouldn't know the new one if it...
I mean, the cat and the dog thing, it was kind of weird.
Like, I don't know why you have cats and dogs and shit.
Like, he was weird in the first phase.
And you didn't like the other guy for the tail.
Well, he said he was a wolf.
Like, what about Otto?
Think about Otto, man.
Get your hands off me.
Can I ask you a question?
Sure.
What do you think about, like, a stream where you pretend to fight yourself?
Like a psychopath?
I'm not a psycho.
No, I'm just...
Cool.
Isn't that a cool stream idea?
I mean, it's a cool idea, but I don't know.
So then, like, this is like fighting yourself as an animal.
He's a little too weird for me.
I think that's why we like him.
Yeah.
We're all in agreement, gentlemen.
Am I getting vetoed out here?
It's three to one.
I'm sensing that in general, you're not ready to let go.
Times change, man.
Number four, congratulations.
You move on to the next round.
Congratulations.
Right on, man.
I love that guy.
On, on, my boys, unfortunately.
But we'll sit on the next contestant, please, if we get a chance.
Number five, how are you?
Good, good, good.
How are you?
I'm doing fantastic.
We're doing well.
Welcome to the stream, of course.
Welcome again for the second time.
I see a guitar.
What's that mean here?
Well, they handed it to me backstage and said that if I don't play it,
then I can't get any coffee, Cheetos, or chicken, which I was promised here.
Okay, that's a good callback, I think.
That's a pretty good callback.
What are you going to do for us?
Supposedly, I'm going to be playing a song that my mother wrote for me.
Your mother, okay.
Yeah, it was the hardest song I've ever had to learn in my entire life.
Let's go ahead and hear it.
All right, electric guitar, holy smokes.
I just want some coffee and Cheetos and chicken.
Number five.
Number five, before you get off stage, I just want to say,
it looks like every judge has said no, emphatically.
Absolutely rubbish.
Don't do this, stupid.
That's a different show.
Number five, we really think that eventually going forward here,
that you could probably do more with, you know, maybe eventually.
I think there's a reason she didn't love you.
Someone needs to tell him.
Well, I just have to say this, that I would like to see you improve your talent,
where I do appreciate that.
And we've all been through things where, you know,
your heart expands as much as it can.
Oh, excuse me.
Yeah, maybe next year.
Maybe next term.
I'm so sorry.
I mean, it's really emotional.
I can't do this.
Mark, I think you have talent.
You have what it takes, but maybe not with this exact setting,
but you are so smart.
You're so good.
You're so talented.
Well, everyone should cry during the segment.
I'm always upset.
Everybody needs to cry during the segment.
You shouldn't encourage him.
I would pick up a new hobby.
No, you have to really cry otherwise they won't believe it.
Really pick one up that's new.
Everybody needs to cry.
You can do it.
Thank you so much.
You were five.
You're so, you're such a fucking angel.
Thank you.
Cheetos.
He had one of three.
I don't know why.
Number six, please come out, please.
Oh, number six, we have a little bit of a thing for number six.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, so number six, we have a small package for number six.
I see.
Just to see.
Small package.
Already German.
Wow.
Talk to Dr. Swanson earlier, so.
God damn it.
Last 10 years, I've been listing this candy store in my town.
It's a small beach town that leads right into the Atlantic Ocean
and has the oldest boardwalk in all of America.
My father opened this candy shop in 1956 and he built it into the place that it is today.
Sadly, he passed away in 2012.
And since then, I took over the helm of the candy shop.
I'm actually such a large Germa fan that I named our specially chocolate fudge after him
to Jolly Germa.
Sadly, it's one of our least popular items.
The one major issue with running a shop in beach town is that
basically all of my business comes during the summer.
That means that nine months out of the year, I have almost nothing to do.
Hearing that Germa's retiring, I believe this would be the perfect job for me to spend
the rest of my time during.
Let's go.
Let's go ahead and bring them out.
What an interesting story that was.
You got a number six.
Number six.
What an interesting story.
Hello.
How are you?
How are you doing?
Number six.
How are you?
I'm excellent.
How are you doing today?
Fantastically.
How are you?
I'm wonderful.
I'm good.
How are you?
I guess we're going to go through this a few times.
Yes.
Can I chime in?
I'm wondering how you're doing today.
Beyond mediocre.
Great.
Okay.
What are you doing for us today?
Today, I will be doing a Yoda impersonation.
Oh.
Yoda.
I love that.
From the Star Wars.
All right.
Excellent.
What's your favorite Star Wars movie?
Sorry.
Has to be Empire Strikes Back.
Okay.
I only watch the prequels, but that's fun.
That's fun.
It is where Yoda showed up.
So you take a moment.
You're going to do Yoda?
To get into character.
Oh.
Okay.
Sure.
Huh.
German ass to you.
You called it.
It was so good.
I didn't expect that.
Which one did you have from?
Yoda speaks in backward sentences,
so I was like,
why would a disappointing start to a sentence?
Hold on.
Let him go.
Question pending is.
Question for me.
It ass to you.
They love it.
You're not answering.
You're going to have to tell the people.
Uh, uh, okay.
Follow-up question.
Do I have a follow-up?
Okay.
What's your follow-up pressure?
Your own ass.
Do you eat?
Can I press yours here?
I've had enough of this.
No, I'm enjoying this.
This is good.
Sure.
Do you hear the crowd?
The crowd loves him.
The crowd wants to see him.
Rule of threes.
Give him a third.
Give us another.
German.
Yeah.
What height claim you to be?
Five eight with shoes.
Five eight with dress shoes.
Just like everybody else here.
Because it gives you an extra oomph.
What are you without shoes?
Five seven.
You might not just say five seven.
Because that's.
Don't do that one.
Play that one back.
Oh man.
Five eight you claim to be?
Five eight with dress shoes.
Full of shit you are.
I want more.
I want more nos.
From the original Saga.
Right?
That line?
Yeah.
All right.
I'm just going to re-joke with that.
Can we please keep our hands to ourselves?
I'm going to press that one for Ludwig
because I don't think he should press yes.
German.
Familiar do you look?
Yeah.
C.I.U.
In a Spider-Man movie.
A villain would you?
In three one.
Wait Willem Dafoe.
It's a Willem Dafoe reference.
A Willem Dafoe reference.
Okay it's a Willem.
Okay.
I got it but C.I.U. in.
I'm a connoisseur of memes myself.
Yeah.
I mean what do we got here?
We got three.
Yeah.
Is anybody?
Schmoyxen.
Schmoyxen do you want to try to switch us or?
Let's see.
Perhaps a song we could sing.
I just I just want to know one thing.
Are the ears dry cleanable?
I regularly swab them.
That was forward.
It was forward.
Oh shit.
He didn't flip it.
Let me swab.
That was not Yoda.
That was not Yoda bra-
That was not Yoda based.
That was out of character for what Yoda's speech patterns are.
To the human was I speaking.
We got three.
Previously.
Number six.
I'm so sorry.
Good luck on the candy store.
I heard it.
I hope it goes well.
How dare you.
Again that's not.
Not too late for me to-
Oh I'm gone.
Is it time for me to stay please?
Number six.
Thank you so much.
That was unbelievable.
Goodbye.
Thank you.
It's about way too dank.
I guess maybe-
Are clapping?
Is it loud?
No I think it was a second before.
Oh a second before.
Unfortunately number six is-
Can you do your Yoda?
Do you have one?
I could probably do a Yoda.
Let me try.
Is that bad?
It really was one word elongated.
You sound like the sweetest chef.
I believe I heard a yodel.
Wait hold on.
Am I little-
I must-
We must go to the store.
What did he say?
Not that.
He doesn't say let's go to the store.
Maybe he was the next Jerma.
You both can't do it.
Wait hold on.
Yes we must learn you the force we will.
That was good.
Don't tell us it's good.
I feel like we are the judges.
Do you think it was good doctor?
We are-
Tony you can't X me.
You're over there.
One two three.
Judges.
Uh huh.
Okay who's-
I think it was all right.
All right we need to clear the X's.
Clear.
We were Xing you.
Oh are you?
Why do you have to go like this when you do Yoda?
You don't.
I think that's what you're doing that makes it bad.
Is that my fault?
You're doing a chicken that is walking.
I got a phone here and I'm ready to call somebody.
Okay.
Okay I-
Is that a threat?
Hello Mr. President.
I loved your Yoda.
That helps.
Your Yoda was fantastic.
Oh he's on the phone again guys.
Oh my god okay so we've got a-
I think there's a piano player coming up here.
If they take a second longer to get set up
which is not their responsibility I'm buzzing.
Okay I think we're ready to bring in the next person.
Number eight how are you?
I'm good how are you all?
Very good very good very good.
Awesome.
What are you doing here?
Well I'm a big musical theater fan.
Okay.
So I know you've all heard maybe like Cats the Musical
but you know I'm just really inspired by you in German if I'm being honest.
And I made a mini musical.
It's Rats the mini stage reading.
So I want to present it to you here hopefully so you can like pick it up
and you know like do something with it.
I really want to go to Broadway but like this is-
you're the first person to see this.
I put a lot of work into it so.
Okay.
Yeah.
This is- you wrote this?
Oh no it's totally Jerma's creation the Rats song.
You're bringing it to life.
I'm bringing it to life.
It's like he made Shrek and you're doing Shrek the musical theater adaption.
Absolutely I have a little choreographed dance to the song.
I have a dramatic stage reading and then yeah an improv jazz piano performance.
Okay.
I'm really hoping you'll enjoy it.
Kind of like you have before take with it and then we'll see how it goes.
Yeah.
Absolutely.
You gotta get away.
You have the floor.
Awesome.
All right then we'll put this here and we'll start with the dance.
Yeah go for it.
You wrote a musical?
No but I made a video with 3D move maker and it sucked.
People on TikTok thought it was funny.
That's all that really matters.
I'm huge on TikTok by the way.
Okay.
I checked it's not.
I mean I am.
That makes all of them fools.
Let's see what kind of troll we get ourselves into.
Oh yes.
It's gonna be great on TikTok.
That was amazing.
I don't believe it.
Part one!
Dramatic reading of The Rats.
Okay.
As done by Jerma.
Impersonating Wanda Bo.
Rats.
We're rats.
We're the rats.
We pray at night.
We stalk at night.
We're the rats.
I'm the giant rat that makes all of the room.
Let's see what kind of trouble.
Rats.
We're the rats.
Peter.
It's your birthday today.
Ice cream is on it's way.
Peter.
You've been such a good boy this year.
Chris is.
And then we'll cheer.
There's another part to this apparently.
The third act.
Buckle in.
He's gonna play something on the keyboard.
Check.
How are we looking?
Okay.
Test the tune out.
Make sure the tune is okay.
Yeah.
Check, check.
All right.
Okay.
That is...
Yeah.
I have no idea.
A connoisseur.
True connoisseur.
Mm-hmm.
Rats.
We're rats.
Damn.
We're the rats.
Stalk.
In the night.
We pray at night.
Yeah, yeah.
We're rats.
Not done yet.
Hold your applause.
Thank you.
I was about to clap.
I was getting there.
I'm the giant rat.
That makes all the rats.
What?
I'll explain after.
You would have buzzed him by now if he wasn't so good at it.
But this is painful for you.
That's good enough.
All right.
Ice cream is on its way.
Germa, Germa, Germa.
My goodness gracious.
Open up your presents and we'll have some cheese here.
Happy birthday.
It's nobody's birthday, but I'll take it.
It's all right.
It's your birthday.
Happy birthday.
I'm 37 this year.
37.
Wow.
All right.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
That was really exciting for me.
That was phenomenal.
Number eight.
We have one X from Ludwig and I'm very curious why.
Yeah, I want to talk to you directly.
Of course.
You're selling yourself short.
I'm thinking you Kanye West, Lady Gaga.
OK, Steve Jobs.
You're doing things that Germa dreams of at night.
Right.
He falls asleep wishing he could sing and dance like that.
You don't know how much that means to me.
Like it's been years.
You know, just like trying and trying and trying.
This might be my big break.
I want you to know this now is another door opening.
What about this now?
What's that?
What are you thinking?
I'm having a I'm having trouble.
Tell me what you're having trouble with.
Maybe we can work this out.
The keyboard is coming out.
It was a little too dragged out.
I was a little.
You're saying no to the voice of a generation.
Wait, wait.
I might be able to like work on that.
We have to take number eight.
I know.
But I'm having trouble.
I think I'm going to have to phone a friend.
Let's go ahead.
Let's go ahead and call.
Let's go out and get.
Can I phone a friend here?
Just get some advice here.
It's very tricky.
That keyboard was fantastic, but it was a little drowned.
It was a little drawn out.
Not like what's happening right now.
Can we can we?
You're great, darling.
I appreciate that.
Can we connect to Kit Boga, please?
I'm phoning a friend here.
Four, four, four.
I think we're a little split on this.
I don't know why you're flinging it.
Why would you be getting a ring if you're?
Hello?
Kit Boga, hi.
This is Jerma985 calling from through some cell service device.
I want to get your advice on something.
What?
Sorry, who is this?
It's Jerma985.
Jerma.
Oh, hey.
Are you watching the stream, Kit, right now?
Yeah, so I'm just trying to finish this 200 word essay.
So yeah.
OK, so I got a guy up here.
He's number eight.
He played the piano.
He's really funny.
He's really interesting.
I need some input on if you think that he could move on to the next round as the next Jerma.
Have you been paying attention to the stream at all?
I mean, it kind of depends.
You want my opinion or do you?
I need your opinion.
You're one of the two calls I can make.
There's one more person I can call, which you'll see very soon enough.
I'm not really that good under pressure.
Well, I need it now.
That guy clearly is, though.
Number eight, clearly.
Clearly is no.
So OK, OK.
I'll tell you what.
Whoever said money can't solve your problems must have not had enough money to solve them.
Right?
Ariana Grande.
What are you talking about?
Yeah, well, what is that?
Did you like number eight or not?
Like, what does that have to do with Ariana Grande?
The point is she says, I want it.
I got it.
I want it.
I feel like this is you.
Yeah.
What do you want?
I want my replacement kit and it's hard to do.
I love Ariana Grande.
OK, put him, pass him through.
Wait, what?
Yeah.
He loves Ariana Grande.
Put him through.
That's your criteria is if they like Ariana Grande, is pass him through.
He's really popular.
It's enough for me.
She's hot.
Hey, he's popping off.
Kit, thanks for absolutely nothing.
She's hot.
What a fucking crutch.
Don't spill that soda, sponsor.
I got some input.
Number eight.
Oh, yeah.
We have a yes from Dr. Schmikeson.
Is that what it is?
Yeah.
Well, all I have to say, you almost had me in tears, but I just have to say it's quite
uber-germaniac.
Definitely.
Thank you.
That means a lot.
Number eight.
I'm going to have to tell you.
Congratulations.
You've moved on to the next round.
You earned it.
Really good.
Really good stuff.
Thank you so much.
I really won't let you down.
This guy's the limit.
This is going places.
Thank you.
Number eight.
You've moved on to the next round.
I just like him one bit, honestly.
Why did you say yes?
He couldn't take it.
You're an idiot.
You can tell.
Why would you vote yes?
He would shatter at any negativity.
Why would you say yes?
He's just like a germa.
I don't shatter at negativity.
Oh, that's a good-
That's why you passed him through.
Look where he's going right now.
I do not shatter at negativity.
No, I don't.
I take a lot of shit.
I feel like you're not listening to what Kit said.
He said Ariana Grande's.
He said no, then he said yes.
It was hard to tell.
I take-
You want it.
I got it.
Clear your boards, please.
We have the next person coming up.
We're cleared.
Where's my chapstick?
I'm fucking freaked the fuck out.
Negativity.
I've got some on my lips.
I know.
Excuse me.
All right.
Number nine is out here now.
Number nine, how are you?
Welcome to the screen.
Number nine.
It works.
Don't tap it, please.
Audio issues.
That's a good German one.
There we go.
Very good.
Hi.
Hi, number nine.
How are you?
I am doing excellent.
Are you excited?
I am literally shaking right now.
You've moved this far, number nine.
We need a wow factor here.
Okay.
I'm going to bring it, you know,
I consider myself to be a dancer.
A dancer?
A dancer.
Something of a dancer myself.
It's a reference.
That's it.
That's it, Peter?
Yes.
That is it, Peter?
So you're going to do a dance routine or?
Yes.
I'm going to show you some break dancing here today.
I'm going to just use the entire area,
break it down for you guys a little bit,
show you my moves.
Are you aware the real German cannot break dance?
That's bullshit.
I can.
It's debatable.
I've been inspired by some of his work.
It looks like he's going to come up to stage
and he's actually going to preview it.
I don't know how I'm going to follow this up.
Get out of the way.
What did you, sir, sir, what did you say?
I said the real German cannot break dance.
Okay.
I think he can.
That wasn't me.
It was mostly the speed you went.
Wow.
I hope he didn't break something.
We all hope that you have better than that,
but I wish you luck.
I scraped, I scraped my fucking knee.
The next stream in three months.
Number nine.
Can you do better than that?
Let's find out.
Good luck.
Here we go.
Oh, yeah.
All right, all right.
This is a classic.
Okay.
Should we get up?
Should we stand up?
Let's stand up.
I'll half stand.
I'll do this.
All right, all right.
Warming up.
He's running at such rapid pace around.
The crab, the crab.
That's a crab.
That's very good.
Oh, fuck a bit of a stumble.
Okay, I thought he was gonna.
Wait, wait, he's got more.
Holy shit.
Well, that's the same thing but twice.
He gets a three.
What?
What's the problem?
Why did she say no?
We got two nodes.
I immediately node.
He fell.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
You stumbled.
That was fucking phenomenal.
Thank you.
We didn't have to.
Could I?
Go ahead.
As an avid German viewer, sometimes
German has through breakdancing
not been able to stream
for extended periods of time.
And when I saw you fall,
I had a that's a raven moment
where you were the German
and you hurt yourself.
Where's my streamer?
Right.
What do you think about that?
You have people depending on you.
You can't hurt yourself.
Totally.
First, safety is key.
Safety is number one.
Number two, I'm like a starfish
when it comes to like repairing
any sort of my body.
So just like quick recovery
like day or two in the hospital.
Just like Dr. Schmoyzen.
Can you?
What about starfish is Dr. Schmoyzen?
I think he's relating to something
that has to do with
you know, bones and tendons
and so on growing back.
But I don't think that that works
if you become paraplegic.
It's doctor.
Wait, Dr. Schmoyzen.
What's his blood type?
Is he is he a B?
I believe he's.
Oh, okay.
That's a big problem.
Okay, I believe he's old.
Oh, that's a big problem.
Have you donated before
your universal donor?
Yes.
Yes, I have donated blood before.
We are, unfortunately,
we're split again.
I'm gonna phone.
I'm gonna have to call
italics on this one.
He fell.
That's the rule.
I think he has what it takes.
He has what it takes.
Okay, call.
Make a call.
Can we call italics, please?
Of course.
Get him on the line.
Another phone, a friend.
Okay, we got a few of these.
I thought it was phenomenal.
I think you guys are out of your mind.
I still don't get why you get a ring
when you call someone.
Because it's calling them
and it's ringing in their house.
Okay.
Do we have italics?
Hello?
Are you there?
I think I have the wrong number.
Try it again.
We're at an impasse.
I need.
Oh, wait, it's ringing.
It's ringing.
I think he's dodging your calls.
He's got caller ID.
We need an outside opinion.
I don't think...
I think he's got what it takes.
It's Alex.
Hey, can you hear me now?
Can hear you now.
It's Alex.
You're on Derma's Not Got Talent.
That would be a copyright infringement.
You're on Who Will Replace...
That's another copyright infringement.
Who Will Replace Me?
Welcome, it's Alex.
Welcome to the show.
We have number nine here.
You guys can hear me.
Yes.
I'm number 17.
You guys already do the interviews?
Yes, we did.
You weren't here.
Shit.
Yeah.
You were not available.
So we just kind of caught you.
So sorry, dude.
Are you watching right now?
Do you see who's on stage right now?
Listen, I'll just be real.
Yeah.
It doesn't even fucking matter who you guys pick
because all the plus twos are chat memes nowadays.
Yeah.
So where's the test to see which of these contestants
can pick the correct one guy comment?
Interesting.
Okay.
Well, so you're asking if he can pick
one guy comment out of chat
and that should be able to fix if he can do it?
Yeah.
I mean, pretty simple, just breaking it out.
Number nine, I got a question for you.
Yes.
So there's three comments in chat.
One of them says, you're a loser.
The second one says, hey, like shit into a bedpan
and show it on stream.
And the third person says, hey, Jerma,
you should play Destiny 2 PVP.
Which one are you going to read?
I'm going to go with number three.
I'm going to take that advice
and let the haters build me up.
That's very, very good idea.
Very good idea.
Thank you.
It's Alex.
Thank you so much for the input.
But I think we have our decision here.
One last thing.
Okay.
Yeah.
I just want to say I've been watching
and I can't tell them apart
because I think the ultimate test should be
who looks the best wearing a chest brace
playing VR.
So if you could just get one of those on stage right now.
Hang up.
I hang up on him.
Hang up on him.
Call is breaking up.
I can't hear.
Hang up on him.
I couldn't hear anything.
I'm a size medium if that matters.
No one was talking to you.
Be clear.
With that input, I think he goes through.
You like the picking the Destiny 2 comment?
I think he's got what it takes.
I'm just asking questions.
Can you do a little word play with me?
Yes, of course.
I want you to finish.
I'm going to say a word and you say a second word.
Okay.
Doll.
House.
Cat.
Mouse.
One for two.
There it is.
Bingo.
You can go on.
Number nine, you're moving on to the next round.
Thank you so much.
I won't let you down.
Thank you.
Somebody, the audio sucks.
I don't know what happened.
Did the call break up?
I'm so sorry.
Call broke up.
FMV game audio.
Right?
You're reading that one guy comment.
That was literally one guy.
There was only one guy.
That was like a hundred guys.
I'm pretty sure in between all that I heard like
Jerma is great.
Jerma is doing fantastic.
And then you read the comment.
And then you read the one audio is messed up.
This guy wants us to play Destiny 2.
Destiny 2, I can't get a close up here.
I will never, ever, ever play Destiny 2 PVP ever.
It's never.
What are you doing?
He said he's like crawling over.
Okay.
Can we send the next person in please?
Number 10.
Double digits.
Oh, hey.
Yeah.
Okay.
That was cool.
I like that.
That was pretty cool.
Where are you from?
Oh, I'm from San Francisco.
You have a microphone.
Fuck me.
So I'm from San Francisco, born and raised.
Great.
So from San Francisco, from the town of Bay.
That's right.
So you're here to replace me, of course, ultimately, right?
Yes.
Only out of pure admiration though.
Okay.
Cool.
It's your time to retire.
I feel like I can ask you a few questions.
We all feel it.
Please.
Would you ever play VR games?
Yes.
Would you ever play Destiny 2 PVP?
No.
Okay.
Good.
Good answer.
One more question, sir.
Yes, doctor.
What is your blood pressure?
And I'm warning you, that's a trick question.
Uh, my blood pressure is absolutely excellent.
It's the healthiest blood pressure I think anyone has ever recorded.
It's a good Donald Trump.
Up until today.
My blood pressure is excellent.
The healthiest president I've seen in my life.
Okay.
So number 10, what are you going to do for us today?
Well, I have this talent that I developed into a skill over the last handful of years.
It all began one day.
I was in an absolute delirium and I demanded
for my friends to feed me coffee, Cheetos, and chicken.
And afterward, I completely lost my mind.
I went into a fugue state for the next couple of minutes.
Sure.
And I found out that this is what I did and I'd like to show you now.
Thank you.
Okay.
Just need a few minutes.
Sure.
Take as much time as you need.
So he's doing what he did in a fugue state.
In a fugue state.
But no longer in a fugue state.
Dr. Schmuckson, what's a fugue state?
Take it off.
What's a fugue state?
Let's go.
It's one of those states where it's kind of purposeful.
He's getting naked, actually.
What is he doing?
What?
What are you doing?
Can you take your shirt off?
His shirt's off.
What the fuck are you doing?
That's probably so loud.
This is your talent?
You're doing great.
It's a skill I made.
So what exactly are you doing?
It's obvious.
Well, if you pay close enough attention,
can I actually get a camera close up here?
If you pay close enough attention,
you can see the fat from my luscious love handles
actually sticking to the wood as I press down
and then as I come up from the mid-back.
Interesting.
It takes a lot of confidence to come on stage
and know the wood was correct for this.
It takes a lot of confidence to test your shirt off on stage.
Let's be honest.
And that's what I have for you today.
Wow.
That's it.
I'm floored.
Great job, number 10.
Thank you very much.
Very nice.
You can put your shirt back on.
Thank you.
Number 10, thank you so much for your time.
I'm going to know on this one
because I think that was just revolting and disgusting.
I would never do something like that in my life.
I don't want the next Jerma985 to be like lying on the ground
and farting in camera.
I think it was revolting.
I think with the hot tub meta coming up and rising,
we're going to need some more of this bravado.
Some more of like a more sexual comedy Jerma
I've been looking for for years.
More blue humor.
I feel like in the dollhouse, you publicly shit yourself.
But you're above that.
I mean, I don't take my clothes off like on stream.
It's fair.
Schmikeson, do we have any input from you?
I'm a little conflicted on this one, guys.
Physically, that was ridiculous enough that you could be Jerma.
However, I was a little, I mean,
watching things kind of squish, make squish noises on the floor.
I just have to say I'm conflicted.
Doctor, I'm with you here.
I'm not as set in stone as Ster seems to be.
I don't know.
I think that I wouldn't do something like that.
All right.
Don't you think there's like something maybe he could do
after the show to convince you to fart in front of him?
What are you talking about?
Fart in the parking lot?
There's a lot of that mean.
What is that supposed to mean?
Like he's going to fart in the parking lot in front of him?
Like fart in his face?
This is a final kind of test for me.
I want you to imagine you're a substitute teacher
and the kids are getting rowdy.
Make a noise to have them silence down.
The floor is yours.
You have a few seconds.
It's a good call, Ludwig.
I'm pulling mine back.
Whoa.
Jerma, don't you think that this would be an...
I don't have to convince you anymore.
The rest of you, this would be an important skill
for a Jerma to have if you were going to go to a water park.
I don't think you have to convince anyone.
There's only one X right now.
He pulled back as well.
Oh, oh, great job.
You're on.
Leave before they disagree.
You have made it through the next round.
Thank you, number 10.
Very, very nice farting sounds.
Appreciate it, gentlemen.
Back to the big time.
Have a great day.
No, wait, I'm out.
We're good?
We're good.
That was tough.
You're just a bit tall, I thought.
You think it's too tall?
Yeah.
I'm a smidge.
I mean, I'm 5'7", 5'8", with shoes.
You're 5'7".
I'm 5'8", with shoes.
But you can't say I'm 5'7", 5'8", and then throw it with shoes.
I feel like you can round up to 6'.
Gentlemen, we've been over this.
We've been over this.
Doctor, you've measured my height a dozen times.
Yes, I have.
How tall am I actually?
I don't know.
You will never take your shoes off.
So, you know, it doesn't make that easy.
When you're measuring someone's height and you have to submit it in the record.
You're my doctor.
Can you do it with shoes?
You can ordinarily do it with shoes,
but say there's something that is kind of hiding from us.
In the shoes.
Oh!
Okay, but how tall am I, doctor, with shoes?
What's in the shoes, Jerma?
Nothing, just shoes.
What's in the shoes?
What's in the damn shoes, Jerma?
Well, you guys, why is this such a weird, like, persecution bullshit?
I have shoes on.
I've dressed, I wear dress shoes to the doctor.
Is that weird?
Kind of, yeah.
To make sure I'm over 5'8", and a half.
I'm cringing.
No, you're not.
You would go like this.
I'm pogging.
There we go.
You're pogging about his feet?
5'8", with shoes.
You can say that whenever you want.
All right, anyways.
5'8", with shoes.
Another piano?
There's only been two pianos.
It's not like it's been, like, all day.
Not the second piano for the whole day.
This is going to have to be better than other piano.
Now, that's what I call music.
It's number 11, right?
This is 11, yeah.
Big one, one.
Number 11, if you're ready to come out, we're ready to see you.
Hello, number 11.
Hey.
How are you guys?
Very good.
I noticed your Dark Souls Play 3 didn't really know what you were doing.
Hopefully, you know what you're doing with the piano.
I sure hope so, too, yeah.
I hope so, too, yeah.
What are you going to do for us, number 11?
Well, I'm actually going to play you a ballad, a nice, pretty song.
Okay.
Thought I'd change it up a little bit.
Can I ask you a question?
Of course.
If you were hungry late at night, what would you order for McDonald's?
Oh, boy.
This is big.
I have a signature.
McChicken Plains, small fries, snack size, M&M McFlurry.
Wow.
M&M McFlurry, that's pretty good.
Just enough calories to pass.
Exactly, right?
Well, go ahead, please.
Yeah, we're really excited to see your piano work.
I love how it's calorie count, not like, okay.
So what song are you going to do for us, number 11?
He already-
It's a ballad.
What ballad?
We need to know.
It's a ballad.
A ballad?
The music speaks for itself.
Focus.
Can you look at a rash on my back a little?
It's called a strange room.
A strange room, okay.
No, wait, no, no!
What?
Did you just get the shit out of me?
No.
What are you doing?
It's nothing.
And he kept going.
That's really good.
That's big.
That actually-
You tried to fuck him up.
Didn't work.
Don't you press that button, I'll be pissed.
Not again, okay?
Church that plays the good.
That was a good finish.
No, pull it back.
Pull it back.
That was unfair.
Convince me.
Stop with the making me make my decisions, Danny.
Okay, listen.
Did everybody-
What the fuck?
We all buzzed.
Can I ask you a couple questions?
Where did you serve your mission?
You know, it's so funny you say that because I'm actually ex-Mormon.
Ah, yeah, I spotted it.
You spotted it?
I spotted it.
How do you spot something like that?
It's obvious, Jerma.
I'm white and I play piano.
I think that's a dead-game.
He said the word church, too.
It's not a church.
Ah, is it not?
No.
It's an original?
It's a cover by my favorite band.
When did you leave the church?
I thought that was really good.
When I turned 18.
Don't put 20 questions in the box.
It's just a couple.
It's not that big of a deal.
No more questions?
I do have a question.
That doesn't really relate to what the others have been talking about,
but could you do that standing on your head?
Actually, yeah, in Amadeus, how he does it turned over.
Can we get some of that?
I don't-
Listen, I'm the only one that didn't say no.
I thought that was phenomenal.
I thought you did a great job.
I don't listen to any of these jokers.
I thought that was great.
Well, thank you.
You know what my problem is?
He's absolutely delightful.
Yeah.
A pleasure to be around.
Want to know what my problem is?
That doesn't work, right?
Second piano guy.
Well, I think that's unfair.
You can't play a piano more than one-
The 16 people stir.
There's so many instruments.
I just feel like you're riding the coattails of the success you saw from the backstage.
Anybody changing their vote or is this it?
I think he's too sweet.
Number 11, you're apparently too nice of a person.
You're too good and nice of a person to take the moniker of Meade,
who is also a nice person, who tries to be nice to everybody
and be cool to his friends and his doctor and everything and have fun with him and stuff.
Don't listen to all of that, please.
Okay.
Number 11, I'm so sorry.
I wanted you.
Please go live a fantastic, healthy life.
That's right.
Number 11, thank you so much.
Sword to the stars.
That's unfortunate.
I thought he had what it took.
Apparently not.
I didn't want to ruin a young boy's life.
I thought he had what it took.
That's unfortunate.
I mean, look, because he was ex-Mormon, who cares?
I said it had nothing to do with the Mormon.
Oh, it definitely did.
It was because he was too sweet.
A year on Twitch, he'd be hitting the pipe.
I can't see him-
Wrong.
He's not unhinged enough.
Maybe he wasn't as unhinged, but maybe there's a new era of a nice-
That is not the new era.
You're way off.
We're going to play Animal Crossing today.
I played Animal Crossing when it came out.
That was the biggest mistake of your career.
No, it wasn't.
It's a fun, sweet, cute game with like animals and like the KK Slider goes like...
It's like, oh wow, what a fucking fun game.
That's exactly what you're doing right now.
What?
You think he's doing that?
He might.
No, he would be much more awesome at night.
Sorry, Professor.
Thank you.
He's a doctor, for God's sake.
Are they the same?
He could be both.
Can you be both?
Are you a professor as well?
Yeah, actually, I am a professor as well.
That's true, technically.
What does technically mean?
Technically means a lot of different things and I don't choose to name them.
Okay.
All right.
He's a doctor, he's a professor, he's everything.
Are we playing 20 questions now?
So...
Yeah, I mean, you were going off on Ludwig for asking that guy questions.
He said it's definitely Ludwig.
You said his name wrong, by the way.
That's a fucking X, by the way.
I'm positive.
I looked you up on Wiki before this.
It's Ludwig.
He doesn't even know his own name.
I know it, though.
That's his name.
Ludwig.
Well, go on YouTube and there's like the pronounce, how to pronounce.
Yeah.
It's Ludwig.
But I don't go by that.
Ludwig.
Okay, you know how...
Just call him Ludwig, it's easy.
Who do we got coming up next?
Number 13, I believe.
Number 13?
Lucky number 13.
Number 13.
What do you got for us coming out here?
All right.
Nunchuck.
He's ready to go.
By the way, let's make it really clear.
The nearest hospital, are we going to find that?
Because he might hurt somebody.
Medical kit is in the back.
We do have a doctor right here in case...
On the eye.
If I feel it slipping, I tend not to let it hit myself.
I'd rather it go out.
Okay, so we should duck.
Oh, so...
You guys look like you have quick reflexes, though.
Quick enough.
Yeah, yeah.
So are you going to do a routine with those nunchucks?
I'd like to.
Okay, so any back...
If it pleases the judges.
Any backstory?
You were the Russia guy.
You talked to us all about Russia and Tetris.
Oh, yes.
Well...
Did you forget...
Forget my Russian history?
What?
You had a...
It washed over you.
You forgot what you did in the previous segment.
No, he reminded me of my Russian history with Tetris.
My history with nunchucks is a lot more limited.
My grandma used to just call me the poor man's Bruce Lee when I was a kid.
She was off her meds a lot.
But I took it to heart.
And I decided to pick up the nunchucks in his honor.
Interesting.
Beautiful.
Yeah, so it's a thing that got to stay with me.
Have you ever hit yourself with the nuts with the nunchucks?
Yes.
Okay.
It's kind of a hazard.
It's gonna happen.
Was it comedic?
They tell you with motorcycles, if you ride long enough, you're gonna fall.
If you chuck long enough, you're gonna fall.
Were there more than three people in the room that thought it was funny?
Only alone, yeah.
I like to do really unsafe stuff when I'm alone.
Yeah, okay.
That sounds like...
So you don't get embarrassed.
The nuts went a little...
I'm just not sure.
Was it on purpose in that case?
Did you do it on purpose?
No, no.
Okay.
No.
What once.
So you're gonna do a routine with the nunchucks and...
Okay.
I'd like to.
Yeah, for sure.
Number 13, whenever you're ready, for sure.
Okay.
Thank you.
I do dangerous shit.
That's pretty cool.
You do, yeah.
I jump through a window and...
Wow.
That's true, actually.
That's true.
You have a history of that.
All right.
So close to his face.
Wow.
The danger.
Dr. Schwantz says you can cover.
Dr. Schwantz is scared.
Ooh.
Oh.
Whoa.
Wow.
That's what a flip looks like.
There's two.
Give us one more.
Whoa.
Oh my goodness gracious.
Oh, no way.
Oh, man.
No way.
Who wouldn't want to do that?
Four.
Okay.
This is what I wanted to do.
Oh, number 13.
That was a tease, but that was good.
That was very good.
Wow.
Very good.
Number 13.
Do we have any Xs at all on this table?
I'm afraid not.
Number 13.
That was phenomenal.
That was unbelievable.
Somebody would take my place
doing something.
I mean, that was...
If you would hit your nuts once in a while,
it'd be funny.
But be careful.
Oh.
Of course.
Oh, he's got jokes.
Jokes on you.
I don't have any.
You got no Xs, number 13.
That's a plus.
That is.
Welcome to the next round, number 13.
Thank you so much.
All right, sir.
Excellent luck, 13.
Thank you.
It's an obvious choice.
All about the next procedure operation.
How many have you passed through?
Four or five?
I think like two now.
It's like six.
Okay.
What do we got coming up next?
Oh, another chair sitter.
Don't call them chair sitters.
That's bullshit.
They're a musician.
I'm just going to sit on my chair.
Doesn't...
Don't streamers...
That's his...
I sit in a chair and I play like...
I was going to say Among Us,
but I didn't play that game.
I see you walking around on VR.
I saw you walking earlier.
I know that you can do more.
I don't know that they can.
They obviously can because they're dancing
and moving around playing.
Are you implying that you don't know
if they could walk around?
I feel like when you see them come on the stage,
that's the only time they do it.
Everywhere else, someone's carrying them.
You don't know if they're standing
when they're outside the camera.
That's completely inaccurate.
This is a talent that they are showing us.
It could be like an FDR.
You never know.
It could be.
It's a talent.
So there's a streaming world
and the other world.
There's a streaming world, yeah.
Doctor, you know very well.
Well, maybe this is the only world.
Well, according to the metaverse,
we'll be all on the same world soon.
Some of us.
If you get the Sims 2 level of graphics
and interaction with the goggles
that are out here, maybe Sims 1
level of graphical integrity.
You're hung up on the graphics,
but not the connectivity of all mankind.
And everybody has no legs.
It's very odd.
It's going to take off though.
I think so.
So in what year are we all floating heads?
2080.
We're like 50 years too early.
We're about 50 years too early, I would say.
So what do we got?
We got number...
Don't buzz unless somebody is actually here.
I fucking told you.
14, how are you?
Welcome to the show.
How are you?
Stop pressing buttons.
He's showing me what not to do.
Stop.
Clear them all.
14, how are you?
Welcome.
I'm going to punch you in the face as hard as I can.
Let's go.
You want to go?
Hi, 14.
How are you doing today?
What are you doing for us?
I'm going to play the piano.
Wow, piano.
Where did you learn that?
Don't say, wow, piano.
That's me.
It was genuine.
That was not genuine.
Can I redo it?
Can I take it again?
Cut this part.
Start.
Hmm, piano.
Wow.
I'm so sad that he didn't get through.
Wow, piano.
Everybody quiet.
Number 14, hi.
What are you going to do for us today?
I'm going to play the piano.
Wow.
Okay, let's see that one coming.
Don't listen to that.
You know, I'm actually named after a pianist myself.
What are you playing?
Oh, I get it.
Lude.
Number 14, the only person that matters on this stage is me.
Okay?
If I like what you're doing, I'm worth like a hundred votes.
These guys are just here for fucking fluff.
Don't listen to this bullshit.
You have a little bit of a thing that you,
a package presented to us, right?
He couldn't trust his own mind.
That's why we're here, to be clear.
We want to see the video first.
We'll watch the video first.
My name is Joseph Kostetsky.
I'm 29 and I've been running an arcade named Joseph's Palace for the past few years.
Ever since I was a young boy, I loved playing video games.
I remember I would play Marvel versus Capcom 2 with all my friends at my house
and we'd host tournaments.
I love doing this so much that I wanted to open my own arcade
and share my love of video games with the community.
However, with arcades becoming more and more obsolete,
I need a better way to promote my business.
And because Jerma's fan base is so large,
I think I can use this channel to really promote my arcade.
I found Jerma's just another guy who likes video games,
especially the older ones.
And I feel like that makes me a good candidate for this job.
Don't clap.
That was beautiful.
So you own an arcade?
Yes, I own an arcade.
And how's that going for you so far?
Not so good.
That's why I'm here.
So what do you think?
We think that you come onto the show and get the channel and then...
Yes, convert it to some arcade players, right?
Would you stream arcade gameplay?
Well, I view it one in the same.
I feel like this channel can really be a sponsor for my arcade.
Okay.
You said Marvel vs. Capcom.
Any other games?
You ever play any Super Smash Brothers?
Super Smash Brothers is my absolute favorite game.
Would you play Destiny 2 PVP?
Stop saying that because people will use it and start writing it in chat all the time.
Okay.
What are you going to play for us?
I'm going to play the piano.
Okay.
Let's go ahead and let you do it.
This is the least interesting part of you.
Let's get back, because look at how good that...
So I can do it again.
Number 14, thank you so much.
That was phenomenal.
We're at an impasse.
We have two nos and two yeses.
I mean, you are the third piano guy.
Yes.
I could be convinced with an overhand Amadeus.
Over the top.
Amadeus, like the song?
No, like the movie.
In the movie Amadeus, he plays like this.
While he's drunk.
Oh, okay.
To show his skills as a virtuoso.
Yes.
To convince these two idiots,
could you do something else?
Something a little bit more of a fast pace, too?
Well, actually, my problem was it was a bit too fast.
Fur Elise was written for Elise,
and it was actually really supposed to be a tender loving song
that picked up at times like the heights of relationships,
but also slowed down like the lows.
Right.
And I didn't feel the passion come through, although the notes did.
What a beautiful story.
Oh, okay.
He's got a point.
Number 14.
That was a phenomenal, phenomenal time on the piano.
But after hearing from some of the judges...
I only know what video game music is.
What do you got?
He's played like 6,000 hours of Path of a Devil.
My favorite genre is video game music.
I don't understand what you're doing up there.
I'm just trying my best.
I think you got a great future ahead of you.
I just got...
I just don't really listen to it.
I thought that was quite lovely.
Quite lovely.
But I have a question for you that might make my decision.
Do you have a bone spur on the left interior of your right mandible?
I don't even know.
He's a liar.
Number 14.
I'm so sorry.
You got a great look.
I think you got the great look.
You got the look of the part.
But apparently having a piano is an automatic no from like two people.
But I don't want you to quit.
Okay?
What is it?
Who is it?
Joseph's Arcade.
Joseph's Arcade can be a big thing one day.
It can be a big thing one day.
I want you to know that.
No, I'm going to say yes.
Can you hear me?
Joseph's Arcade one day.
It's going to be huge.
Thank you just for the opportunity to get a chance to get out there.
Wait, what do we have right now?
Joseph's Arcade and piano lines.
They're going to be talking about your arcade in the big times.
We lost our monitor.
It's in the big leagues.
Okay, listen.
What do we have?
Thank you.
That was very, very nice.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
All right, just stop fucking around.
Again, you were seriously such a great job.
You should have been the first player.
You just honestly.
Sorry.
It was the order.
Yeah.
It was a great job.
It really was.
It happened like that in Squid Game too.
But that was such a phenomenal piano player.
The order matters.
The order does matter, Jerma.
A good Jerma is lucky.
That's true.
What did you say?
What was my character?
You said I was like 10 luck and like five charisma.
Yeah.
15% power, 10% skill.
Okay, my D&D character was what?
Like if I were to make one.
I said you would put everything in charisma and everything else is a dump step.
Okay.
By the way, the Myriad is a great show going on.
It's Myriad.
Oh, fuck off.
You're not getting a plug.
Who's coming up next?
We got number 15, I think, coming up here.
Yeah.
15 should be running.
Getting down to it.
Number 15, go ahead and come on out.
We'll see what you got here.
You do hunch.
A little bit, yeah.
Hello, 15.
Hello.
I'll be clear.
Clear your exes, by the way.
How are you?
We're doing great.
How are you, 15?
15, what are you going to do for us today?
You got something?
No piano, by the way, so surfers can be happy.
It's difficult.
I like the fumbling.
The fumbling is like exactly what I was going to do.
I think it's just an introduction.
Can you hear me?
We can hear you, yeah.
Okay.
Hello.
Hey, 15, how are you?
Good afternoon.
My ability is doing slightly obscure impressions of people saying very specific things.
Okay.
Can you do any serial characters?
Serial characters?
Any serial mascots like...
Great!
That's a yes from me.
You don't need to impress me anymore.
That is Antonio the Tiger.
Yeah, that's very good.
Why do you have an accent now?
Before I was doing you, I've learned your voice, but I'm new here, so this is...
Oh, okay, so you have an accent.
It's more comfortable to speak.
Where are you from?
Um, from Stockton.
Stock...
Oh, Stockton.
Sweden.
California.
Oh, never mind.
Great.
You're from California, okay.
Stockton, California.
So what are you going to do exactly for us today?
The first one is a great Shakespearean actor, Peter O'Toole, doing...
Okay.
Nothing, darling, helps in my ride.
I used to know a bitch named Eric Wright.
We used to go around and fuck the hoes at night.
Take that, you motherfucking gangster bitch!
Why are there no other accents?
That is the...
Because it is his voice.
His voice, he doesn't speak with you.
Yeah, that's great.
That's great.
What else do you have?
Um, this is Harrison Ford going into store for Halloween candy.
Okay.
Bitter honey.
Blow pop!
Charleston shoe.
Just that one.
That was good, that was good, yeah.
Excellent.
Dateline Keith Morrison.
You watch Dateline?
Seldomly, yeah.
Seldom.
Oh, you are old.
This is Dateline.
He's 37 in this room.
Dateline host Keith Morrison describing genital warts syndrome.
Oh, god.
Somebody please spread that.
Genital warts.
Colored or whitish balls.
Show up on your vulva.
Vagina.
Servings.
Dr. Sports and Stiller, yes.
Scrooge or anus.
These are medical terms.
Sounds like Cave Johnson.
They kind of look a little like cauliflower.
That is from the actual website.
Okay.
Gary Busey.
You sort of look like the Gary Busey.
I've heard the Gary Busey.
Willem Dafoe, you know.
Oh, god.
I mean, my teeth.
I got big teeth.
Let's see.
I made that myself.
Wait, what is that?
Paper.
A piece of paper with Sharpie.
Oh, it's paper.
I thought it was actually fake teeth.
He looks like Jim Carrey from Donald Trump.
All right, all right.
The imposter is...
Shush!
I took it back.
I'm sorry.
You have to say no.
That was great.
Okay, this is a...
I'm close to a no.
Gary Busey is a Spanish instructor.
Okay.
I've been no for the whole time.
That was the bingo song.
I've been no the whole time.
I can't...
You know what?
Could I make a request?
Because, you know, at the end of the day,
impressions are great,
but Jerma really defaults to one always.
Yeah.
And it says Donald Trump.
Can you do a Donald?
Can you do a Donald Trump?
Could you do Donald Trump saying that
you're a better streamer than Jerma is?
What do we got?
One X?
You are, you are, or...
You...
Yeah, I'm a better...
Right, who are you?
You'd be Donald Trump.
You're a better streamer, better, better.
Okay, look it up.
It's true.
You're a better, better streamer.
It was on the...
Okay, okay.
It was on the spot.
Let me try and bring it to my side.
I'm a hundred percent yes.
Number one, a hundred percent yes.
To me, you're the next Jerma.
You had a serial mascot character.
That's a huge point.
That's like nine out of ten.
We're almost there.
All of your references are dated.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I have not a single clue,
and that's the extra point to get to ten.
Oh, that's good.
You don't...
How do you not know Harrison Ford?
He's like still...
He was in the last season.
How do you not know Harrison Ford?
Harrison Ford's still making movies.
Oh, sure.
Yeah.
For like old women.
Okay, so what...
You're a yes.
Yes, completely.
I have something else you were going to say.
Can you do...
You're fantastic.
That's okay.
Can you do...
Can you do Yoda?
Yoda, I can do.
Shit, he can do...
I will take all of your exes back.
Yes, yes.
No.
Doctor, doctor, what do you think about this?
Well...
Smelling his fingers, he is.
I'm not...
My fingers are like out.
I'm gonna keep them here.
I'm not smelling my fingers.
They're...
I'm gonna keep them at the table for now on.
Doctor, what do you think?
Number 15.
I'm afraid it's gonna have to be a no, but
I thank you for your accuracy.
Number 15.
It looks like we've got three nos.
Please, I'm begging you.
You're the only one who can turn this.
Give me a one sentence pitch on why I should switch.
I think I gave some pretty good reasons.
I'm defaulting back to serial character.
All of his references are dated.
Just because you know what...
I think Jerm is intimidated by him being good at the stuff he's not good at.
Hey.
No, no.
Just because you know what a serial character is
does not mean that you should take over my channel.
Start.
You know what?
It's Ludwig.
Oh.
Sorry.
I didn't mean to tease you like that.
Number 15.
I'm so sorry.
Thank you.
I loved Tony the Tiger.
But just because you know what a serial character...
That doesn't mean you...
Oh, you know what Tony the Tiger is?
I think that was the last one.
Do what Tony the Tiger right now.
I can't.
15 was the last one.
I can't do it.
It's like Tony Tiger.
What do you mean?
That was the last one.
Are we at the end?
I'm blocked.
That was all 16 that...
What are you...
Wait, no, no, no, no.
What are you doing here?
Connor!
Hey, I know everybody's had chances when they come back.
Okay.
Maybe...
I don't have talent or anything.
No, no, no.
Go, go, go.
Connor, go.
Well, I can like...
I can like...
You got a chat and I can't read your chat.
Hit the fucking button.
You know, I can read your chat, Ludwig.
No, for sure, man.
Oh, is it red?
Oh.
Connor, you have your own...
Listen.
Play the sad music.
I'm 5'8 with shoes, dog.
Hey, hey, wait, wait.
Connor, stay right there.
Play the sad music, please.
Connor, you're a young guy
and you've got, I think, a great future in front of you.
I'm 37.
I'm 45 years older than you.
I think that you have a lot of comedy.
You have a lot of really good shticks
and I think you're a really nice guy.
But you ain't me and you never will be.
Be you and be the best you that you can be.
Is that one X or three?
It's all...
Connor, if you start crying anymore...
I don't know where we're going.
I think you've got a great future.
You're a really young, smart man
and like security...
I mean, I'm pretending to cry right now,
but like he should never have gotten up here.
He should have been removed immediately.
And we all cry on these shows.
Security should have taken him out immediately.
Sorry, it's tough.
Thank you for the opportunity.
Yeah, there was no opportunity in the first place.
You have Connor's pants.
Read the room.
You're your own channel.
You don't need another channel.
Unless you want to try your Yoda.
Oh, he's got a Yoda.
All right, we've got some more deliberation to do.
Ladies and gentlemen, we'll be right back.
I think I'm looking at the right camera for part three of Who Will...
I can't...
Who is gonna be German next?
Shut up.
Who will replace me?
You should call it German 986.
No.
Who will replace me?
Coming back soon in a few minutes.
Okay.
All right.
Seeing a little bit of people talk about number 15.
Seeing 15.
Bring 15 back.
Where's 15?
We had a deliberation.
We have four judges.
15 was eliminated.
And that's how you have to handle that.
15.
Impressions are one thing.
But demeanor.
Way that you talk.
Way that you act.
You can't just say, oh, 15 should go through.
He was a great guy.
He was really funny.
Oh, you say that now.
What?
You voted no, too?
Well, to tack on.
Doc Dreamer memory.
You were talking about how he medically just doesn't even line up.
Medically, he has bone spurs, I heard.
Here's the thing.
Um, in order to play Jeremy, he has to have the physical as well as the-
Exactly.
Listen to the doctor, for God's sakes.
He's a doctor.
Well-
Well, they're probably Americans.
They don't do that.
Yeah.
And I mean, obviously, the thing to match Jeremy is just be a total maniac.
But, you know, on the other side, you have to survive him.
What do you mean?
You mean like I'm a funny guy, right?
Like surviving Jerma?
Yeah, I know.
I know that sounds difficult.
What do you mean maniac?
A total loony.
Yeah, total-
No, you mean like a wacko guy.
Wacko job.
Yeah.
Oh, okay.
All right.
Super mean.
15 is gone.
He was funny.
He was nice, but maybe didn't have what it took to be the next Jerboff.
985.
So what we're going to do now to narrow it down even more, we have to be certain.
The final round until you, yes, you, vote for who is the next Jerma 985.
We're going to bring out the contestants that we passed through,
and they are going to read a very important passage.
The JermaCraft copypasta passage.
However they do it, we are going to vote for it.
How well they do it, how smartly, how energetically,
we are going to vote for them as well.
This is the final round to the final.
Whoever goes through this round-
It's not the final round.
It's the final round for us.
And then you get to decide who wins.
We are going to narrow this down to three.
To be clear, you can't decide 15 wins.
The penultimate round is here.
Let's, let's see.
Guys, can we please bring out number one to read the JermaCraft copypasta
to see if they have what it takes.
Yeah, I just want to see you read the ancient text.
Hello.
Welcome back.
Why do you have like a, like a, like a water, like office water?
It's like a Dixie cup.
It's cider.
It's cider, okay.
Are you ready to read the JermaCraft copypasta?
Number one, you've made it this far, are you ready?
Is it an iPhone 12 Max or 11 Max?
Don't say that iPhone, who cares, Android, doesn't matter.
It's a private sponsorship I have.
Shut up.
Hello, ladies and gentlemen.
Welcome to episode one of JermaCraft, the series where I play Minecraft.
This is going to be a single player let's play.
And when I say let's play, I use that term pretty loosely because I am an idiot in this game.
You're going to see lots of fails.
You're going to see lots of triumphs, at least a moment.
So go grab yourself a nice hot cup of coffee, hot cup of cocoa.
I got apple cider right here, freshly brewed.
Let me take a sip.
That is some good cider.
You said that?
You said that's some good cider.
He nailed it.
You nailed it.
That was amazing.
Oh, you nailed it.
Man, I would not watch you play Minecraft.
Why would you play?
Why would you watch me play Minecraft?
It's a fucking horrible content.
I mean, either of you, based on what I just heard, I'm not watching either of you.
If you, okay, wait, wait, number one.
Yes.
If you took over.
What would be your number one video game to play on the first day?
Minecraft, maybe?
No, no, I don't want to press it.
I don't want to press it.
Say anything else.
Number one, please.
You get a redo.
It's a really good question.
Don't say Dark Souls either, because nobody got through them too early.
Call of Duty?
I'm just kidding.
Don't say that either.
It's a good gag.
But for real though, now.
If the brand were to live forever and you took it on.
Geez, you know.
First game you'd play.
Death's Door.
Holy shit, that's a pass for me.
I don't even know what that is.
You got to play Death's Door.
The bird?
Why?
The bird.
So good.
That's the bird, yeah.
You know what this is?
Yeah.
What's Death's Door?
You're a bird and it's like a roguelike and you got to go around and.
Made by the guys that made Titan Souls.
I don't know if you ever played that.
Yeah, you're kind of like a Reaper bird.
Chat.
It wasn't made 40 years ago so you might have missed it.
Or Nobody Saves the World.
That's another one maybe I would play.
Heard of this one?
Number one.
Jeremy's known for a lot of his bigger streams.
What big ideas would you bring to the table in 2022 and 2023?
Exactly.
Wow, that's really putting me on the spot.
Let's see, maybe how about while I would be playing I would also be getting a massage.
That's actually pretty funny.
Yeah, okay.
He goes through.
Okay, are we all getting a question?
I think if you have a question to ask him that's fine.
That's funny.
That's actually funny.
If you could approve upon one thing the current Jerma might not excel at,
where do you think you could do better?
I don't think I would stutter as much.
Oh, shit.
Okay, I am getting close to pressing the button.
Hey, they asked.
You know, I'm sorry.
I just did not ask much.
I was still, you know, stuttering like a little.
That was good.
I like that.
I want a look at me and I want it good and I want it now.
Look at me.
He goes on.
Welcome to the final round number one.
Fuck yeah.
Love that guy.
If number one goes on to the final.
So let the first guy go through but he just did so well.
It was so good.
It was actually very good.
I'm going to hit the next guy with harder questions.
Please do.
Tougher questions.
So number two we got coming out here.
We have a package for number two.
I guess some life story or something we have to hear.
Like all these shows do, you hear their fucking life story.
Great.
Can't wait to hear their life story and everybody cry.
Go ahead and play it.
I'm Austin S. Faulkner and I've been running a farm for the last 30 years
down in the heart of the country.
I come from a long lineage of farmers and we've owned this
plot of land for the last 200 years.
Running it with my wife Abby and my two sons Gregory and Johnny has been an
absolute joy.
Gregory, my youngest, absolutely loves this guy.
Shouting phrases like look at me and muck my ass at the dinner table.
I don't quite know what that means but my son keeps telling me that this guy's a
millionaire saying things like this on the internet every week.
Teaching today's youth how to properly run a farm through my streaming would be
a dream come true and I heard that German's retiring so I feel like I'm
right now in a good job.
Okay, so let's go ahead.
All right.
Let's bring our number two.
Number two, welcome to the stream.
How are you?
Welcome for the third time.
I'm doing well.
You got a farm.
We just heard about that.
Yeah, it's a beautiful farm.
You should come visit sometime.
I would love to.
You're retiring, right?
Hey, fresh milk?
We can trade spots.
You could run the farm.
I could run your channel.
Hey, that's easy.
25% goes to me.
Are you not concerned how the farm would end up
if Jerma were in control?
I think there'd be a lot of more muck-a-ass on the farm.
That's true.
He said muck-a-ass.
Everybody likes him.
Do the Pog face.
Well, no.
That's not even close.
Ew.
No, you didn't like that?
Okay.
I really didn't like that.
Did you say no?
Sorry.
Anyway, if you want to do your monologue.
Can we please hear JermaCraft copypasta, please?
And it better be fucking good.
Hello, ladies and gentlemen.
And welcome to the very first episode of JermaCraft,
the series where I play Minecraft.
Now, this is going to be a single player let's play.
And when I say let's play, I use that term pretty loosely.
I'll pull it back.
Because I'm an idiot in this game.
Now, you're going to see a lot of fails and a lot of triumphs,
I am hoping.
So grab yourself a nice hot cup of coffee, hot cup of cocoa.
I got a glass of apple cider right here, freshly brewed.
Let me take a sip.
That's a really good fake sip noise.
That was a good sip noise.
All right.
Thank you.
That was a very good sip noise.
I appreciate that.
I worked hard.
What do we got?
We got two and two here.
Can I field a question?
I would love to field a question.
I think a lot of Jerma's content revolves around creative ideas.
What would you do about the situation in Ukraine right now?
Jesus Christ.
It's kind of a touchy subject, but...
Just say, look at me, and it'll be fine.
Yeah, I'll just say, look at me.
No.
That's what you do?
You go to Ukraine, you go, look at me.
Look at me.
Distracted from all their problems now.
You know what?
Biden and Putin kiss in harmony.
Oh, boy.
Yeah.
I thought so, please.
Doctor, I think he's got what it takes.
Well, I'm sure that he's arrived farm fresh.
I do think that you have talent.
I just don't know if it's the kind of idiocy that we need.
Oh, no.
What the fuck?
Yeah, I'm going to remain a no based on your foreign policy.
No.
Well, I tried.
Number two, you were such a great presence.
You guys don't know anything.
What do you know about me?
We got to eliminate someone, all right?
And this guy's just walking around, look at me, like anyone can do it.
Am I the next Jerma?
Can I chime in?
This man's 36 with no kids.
Yeah.
You have a future ahead of you and it's your family.
There's a reason he's able to do this at 36 because he doesn't have one.
So we want someone who comes in to also not have a family that is more important.
I don't want to be tied down with real world issues.
You got to play video games all day.
What a loser would do.
You're a winner.
Thank you.
I appreciate that.
God bless.
Thanks for coming.
Have a good one.
Number two, thank you so much.
Here you go, keep that bill coming.
I feel great right now.
What a great feeling.
What happened to the kids?
I got 10 years on everybody at this table besides, of course, the wonderful doctor.
It depends on what you mean 10 years on.
It's true.
You're going to take 10 years from all of us.
All right.
I don't have kids, but you know, I'm thinking, I'm thinking about it.
I'm thinking.
I don't have kids, so I can spend a few in jail.
One day, you know, I'm 36, 37 this year.
You know, you think about kids, one day, one day.
One day.
Maybe we can have one soon.
Get your hands off of me before I switch seats with...
Turn your ex off before we get in trouble by production.
All right, number four.
Please come out, number four, for your German craft copybasta.
What's cat dog?
It's cat dog.
You, okay, before you go, everybody has put you through but me.
Yeah.
And you're doing like a really like caveman interpretation of my channel and me and...
It's so true.
I don't, I don't think that's like appropriate.
I don't think I'm that stupid.
But you made it all the way to the final.
I don't think you're stupid.
Do you think I'm stupid?
What do you think I am?
I think you're very smart.
Okay.
It's like Joaquin Phoenix in showbiz.
I like you.
Number four.
Oops.
Can you give us a German craft copybasta, please?
If I may, please.
Hello, ladies and gentlemen.
Welcome to episode one of German craft.
This is the series where I play Minecraft.
This is a single player let's play.
And when I say let's play, I use that term pretty loosely because I am an idiot in this game.
You're going to see lots of fails.
You're going to see lots of triumphs.
At least I'm hoping.
So go grab yourself a nice hot cup of coffee, hot cup of cocoa.
I got apple cider right here, freshly brewed.
Let me take a ship.
I thought he was pretty good.
Yeah, but he's got a mic.
He's got a microphone in his hand.
He's Sean Connery.
Was it take?
Nevermind.
Was it?
What?
No way.
You don't put this guy all the way through and then get him out in the last round.
There was no dog bark.
Where was the meow?
I thought it was a ship.
No, it's not a ship.
But you're actually pretty good.
You're actually really good.
I don't know if I agree with these three.
OK, so I'm sorry.
We wanted to get him through.
You whined and kvecht.
Now we want to eliminate him.
And you're whining and kvechting.
Do you want us to judge or do you want to tell us what to do?
That was a good German craft coffee pasta.
Hit it with some questions.
Tell me.
OK.
Convince me.
If you were...
OK, so you're in line at the Dunkin' Donuts drive-thru.
You're number four in line.
That's a good question.
Good question.
You're number four in line.
You're at Dunkin' Donuts.
You're at Donkeys.
You want a large iced blueberry with easy ice.
You're number four in line.
Do you, when you get to the counter, are you happy or are you sad?
How do you interact with the barista at Dunkin' Donuts?
Not what I thought the question would be.
I just spit everywhere.
Say it, don't spray it.
Sad.
You're sad.
Why?
Sad.
Because I'm number four.
All I've ever wanted to be is number one in Germany.
And I'm sad for the blueberries because the blueberries didn't have to die for me.
Why are they dying?
They deserve to live.
Why are you saying right?
OK.
And I'm sad that they would serve it to me.
That they would agree to serve it to me.
But wait, would you drink the whole thing in an hour?
Fuck yeah.
It takes me six hours to drink coffee.
I drink a full coffee in about six or seven hours.
That is true.
Also, what was the whole blueberry thing?
Are we going to just glaze over that?
Are you sad for the blueberries?
But I mean, you harvest them.
You take them.
You take their lives, you know?
No.
You take their lives.
I don't.
I mean, sir, you're a vegan.
Sorry, doctor, do blueberries have sentient lives?
I think they're plants.
And I have to tell you that, you know, I don't know if you are able to go through for me.
I'd love to send you through.
You know what I can do?
I can actually give you a referral for therapy.
Yeah.
If you need it.
I'll be right back here in the back of the stage after the show.
Okay.
That's great.
Okay, sir.
Yeah, sorry.
So that's one, two.
Doctor, is that a no?
There it is.
Okay, I was confused.
Number four.
Oh, okay, all four.
I don't know.
You're, I think you're out.
Number four, I think that's always need to see.
I got it.
I'm sorry.
Motherfucker.
Don't pray.
But don't be so mad.
By the way, my car is not in the parking lot.
So don't like, it's unhinged.
My car is not in the parking lot.
I think his car is in the parking lot.
If you want to key his, he's got a green sedan and it's got a vanity plate.
It says a path of exile.
Do you know like two things about me and one of them is not even true?
I don't, I don't have a driver's license.
Oh, you brought me on because I've known you for so long.
I know you better than anyone.
Those are the path of exile license plate.
Who am I?
Can we, can we bring out number eight, please?
Eight should be coming out right now.
You have the big suss guy license plate with your Jeep Wrangler.
Number eight.
Yeah.
All right, there it is.
All right.
Made it all the way to here.
Hi, number eight.
Welcome back.
Hello.
We are ready to hear your Germacraft copypasta interpretation.
Hello, ladies and gentlemen.
Welcome to episode one of Germacraft series where I play Minecraft.
He forgot his line.
So when I say let's play, I touch on very loosely because I'm an idiot at this game.
It's going to be a lot of triumphs, a lot of fails, or at least I'm hoping.
So go grab yourself a nice hot cup of coffee.
I pulled back.
I want to reiterate something he said.
Yeah.
It's going to be a lot of triumphs, a lot of fails.
I'm hoping he's hoping for a lot of fails.
Entertainment value.
That's entertainment value.
He's right.
I don't think that's.
All right.
What have we got?
I think he is tarnishing your legacy.
Why?
For what?
I would never.
By misspeaking, you mixed up a couple words.
You had to look.
But it's hard.
No one has had to look yet.
You had to look.
I got to call a challenge.
We probably can't get that back.
Yeah.
I'm just bringing a different new twist.
Everyone's looking for like what's the new about the new drama.
It's the new drama.
I like him.
I think he's got what it takes.
We're kind of bringing a new zass to it, making everyone, you know,
we're excited for something new.
Honestly, let me be honest with you.
Play the crying music if you can.
I think that's not crying music.
They can only cry to the song.
Crying music, crying music, please.
I think that honestly, you came up with the piano.
He had the rats.
Number one piano guy.
He had the rat song.
He knew the rat song.
Who knew the rat song out of anybody here?
He's the only one that knew the rat song.
And he did it by heart.
It's hard to cry.
I must admit I felt something for the rats.
I did.
That's why you were always a yes from me.
Me too.
Thank you, German.
I think you've convinced me.
His past failures make up for his current failures.
How do we get you two on board?
Do you want to do the rat song again?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
What color is your hair?
Your color.
Your hair looks kind of black.
I'm pretty sure it's your color.
It's just the lighting.
I didn't pick that up the first few minutes.
You didn't pick that up that he is obviously brown.
It's kind of black.
Come on, German.
You're on my side.
You got me.
Oh, your hair is black.
Your hair is black.
Get the fuck out of here.
German, come on.
Some hair dye.
You heard him.
Get the fuck out of here, man.
Don't do it like that.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
I got upset.
Your hair is black.
All right.
Behave yourself.
It was that four nos.
I'll take mine back just to be able to say to chat that I backtracked and I didn't give
you a no because I want to make sure people know that I'm on both sides and I never am
part of any argument that I always am on both sides of every argument.
So everyone agrees with me every time.
You know, so thank you for coming.
Appreciate it.
Always always correct on every argument.
You know, no, but I never on one side or the other when I'm on everybody's side.
You know, I love the song though.
It was a great song.
See you on Broadway.
Only person that knew the rat song.
Thank you so much.
Fuck you.
Fuck you for not knowing that.
I just didn't know he had black hair.
I thought it was one.
Yeah, that's the shame.
Hate those.
Can we bring out number nine, please?
Thanks for having me.
Welcome.
Welcome back.
Thank you.
How are you feeling?
Great.
Still shaking a little bit.
It might have been the three cups of coffee I've had today, but hey, yeah, we're here.
We're here and we're partying.
But not the crack that we all smoke before.
Never mind.
Just go ahead.
Go ahead.
If you want to do number nine, if you want to do German craft coffee pasta, I hope you're prepared.
I am.
I'm prepared.
Right there.
There's a camera here.
Cameras all over you.
Number nine.
Hello, ladies and gentlemen.
Welcome to episode one of German craft.
The series where I play Minecraft.
This is going to be a single player.
Let's play.
And when I say let's play, I use that term pretty loosely because I'm an idiot in this game.
You're going to see lots of fails.
You're going to see lots of triumphs.
At least I'm hoping.
So go grab yourself a nice hot cup of coffee.
A cup of cocoa.
I got an upside right here.
Freshly brewed.
Let me take a sip.
That's some good cider.
That was amazing.
Amazing.
Number nine.
I have one question.
Do you brew cider?
Is that like a thing?
You can, yeah.
I mean, like people brew tea.
Why would he know this?
Because he's going to be the next German.
You know, the answer to that question, I would brew my own cider.
And I would just figure it out.
You just got a pie in the face.
Clown got you.
You get your hands off me.
You've been touching me all day.
I can't put my hands on you.
That was sharp.
He backed you up.
Do you hear that?
What did he say?
Is that a clown or what?
He backed you up real quick.
Oh, excuse me.
Number nine.
You got no access.
Yeah, we had some safety concerns.
I take time back.
Don't you appreciate that?
He's a dick, don't you?
I'm concerned about another like, like you're a suck-up German.
That you're just going to take over where he left off and not improve at all.
Okay, I understand that.
Thank you for that.
Like, you're really like...
Yeah.
Doctor?
Uh, sir.
Could you just turn around in a circle for a minute, please?
Thank you.
There was no reason for that.
Oh, okay, great.
Oh, he just wanted to...
But, uh, happy to see you.
Did you like what you saw?
The real German has a dinosaur dumping.
Sorry.
Honestly, you're an inspiring performer.
And I'm excited to see you in the final round.
Thank you so much.
Number nine.
Congratulations.
Thank you guys.
Thank you.
Good luck, sir.
You're in Chad's hands.
I think we're up there.
Number 10.
Come on out.
Oh, what was that?
Sorry.
Hot.
Mic is hot.
How's it going?
It's good.
How are you guys doing?
Finals.
Who would have thought?
Number 10.
You're the, you're the, you're the lying in your back fart guy.
That's right.
I am the back part man.
Yeah.
I think that's on Brandon.
Sorry for keeping you here.
Oh, uh, what?
It's okay.
A lot of people got to go home by now, so...
Well, you know, I'm chilling.
I'm doing great.
Well, you know, back farting was one thing.
I'm excited to see you do this copy pasta.
If you want to...
Yep.
Let's do it.
You get the floor.
Hello, ladies and gentlemen.
Welcome to episode one of Germacraft.
The series where I played Minecraft.
This is going to be a single player.
Let's play.
And when I say let's play, I use that term pretty loosely because I am an idiot in this game.
You're going to see lots of fails, lots of triumphs.
At least I'm hoping.
So grab yourself a hot cup of cocoa, hot cup of coffee.
I have apple cider right here, freshly brewed.
Let me take a sip.
Ah, it's good cider.
He made sound effect.
I don't know.
He made a sound effect.
Sound effect.
I like the tea.
Very effective sound effect.
More like a...
It's even better.
We're going to know.
Okay, please mom.
Well, you know, to me, it was just more of like an NPR read, you know?
Like I'm listening to radio and they're about to introduce the next song more than a let's play.
Let's play, you know?
It's tough because you got the back farting, you got the look, you got the energy.
I just, I don't know if you got what it takes to be able to order
four sandwiches from McDonald's, eat it and shit your pants.
Really?
What makes you say that?
I just something about it.
I'm so sorry.
You missed Machito yesterday.
He was pretty fucking vicious.
What is your McDonald's order, if I could ask?
What's your McDonald's order?
Yeah.
That's four Big Macs and two Flurries.
That's it.
That's all I need.
That's not bad.
That's absurd.
No, I think the fries are actually pretty overrated there.
No lie.
Yeah.
I have a question for Jerma.
Sure.
I think this needs to be cleared up and should have been cleared up earlier.
How many takes did you do on the original Minecraft episode one
before you were like, that's the one?
How many takes?
I can tell, like the way it's written, I can tell like you were,
it was bubbling, you know?
Like you didn't do it first take.
I mean, it was probably 10 takes.
Look, let me be real to the entire audience watching.
Every YouTuber that you've ever heard in your whole life,
they spend two fucking hours doing their intro and they hate it.
They hate every single take they do.
Hello, ladies and gentlemen, welcome to episode one.
Of JermaCraft.
They fucking retake it 10 times.
What?
And you hated his first take.
Let's get a second take.
Second take.
Two take, Tyler.
I appreciate the opportunity.
Thank you.
Hello, ladies and gentlemen, welcome to episode one of JermaCraft.
It's the same.
No, it's not.
Let him go.
Let's get one more from the top, please.
From the top.
And really think about it.
I pull it back.
And you're underwater.
It's a let's play.
You're having fun.
Number 10, you're underwater.
You're underwater.
You're underwater and there's submarines everywhere.
Hello, ladies and gentlemen, welcome to episode one of JermaCraft.
How are you talking underwater?
How are you talking?
Shit, I didn't think that.
This is unrealistic.
I thought it was like Subnautica or something.
No, it's Minecraft.
You'd be drowning.
You wouldn't talk if you're...
You're giving him like unrealistic ways to like go about this.
This is like the fourth take.
This doesn't make sense.
If he's underwater, why would he talk so clearly?
Honestly, I think you have what it takes.
Unfortunately, these two knuckleheads...
Well, it's two-two, isn't it?
Yeah, these two.
Wait, what are you doing?
What are you...
Is that a no?
It's a no.
Number 10, I think you really have what it took.
Oh, thank you very much.
I thought you did too.
Give me notes for me, doctor.
Yeah.
Doctor, any notes?
Sir, I heard you wax poetic.
I heard you talk from the heart.
I heard intelligence of a new degree.
So no way.
Get your fucking hands off me.
That's fair.
Thank you.
I appreciate that, doctor.
Wait, number 10, you haven't cried yet.
You know, I came out here just a couple years ago to make a career at Twitch because I just love,
you know, I mean, you're such a young audience and they're really...
They'll give you tons of attention, you know, stroke the ego.
And I'm just looking for that.
That's how you win it now.
But you still are crying.
Cry though.
Yeah, I know.
It's fucking sad.
I feel your pain.
Cry and make sure you like put it on like the screen that he's crying so we get extra ratings
and stuff because people like when people cry on these shows.
Oh, God.
Hey, buddy, you have what it takes to be a shining star somewhere in your life.
Dr. Smoikson, please diagnose him.
Don't give up, sir.
WGBH is looking...
That's not even...
We're here.
That's Boston.
Thank you.
What are you trying?
Get out of here.
All right, I'm getting the fuck out of here.
Have a great night, Joe.
PBS is your...
PBS.
Can we please send out number 13 if you're still around?
Reset these buzzers.
Reset the buzzers if we could.
Hey.
So groovy, huh?
This is getting me in the mood.
Okay, 13.
I always thought you had a great smile.
Hi, 13.
How are you doing?
Well, how are you doing?
13.
You made it all the way to the end.
How do you feel?
Surprised.
Surprised?
But with the nunchucks and the nuts?
That was a great joke.
I didn't think it was gonna, you know, make the cut.
Don't think so.
No, no, but I'm pleasantly surprised.
It was a good pre-planned joke and I liked it a lot.
And sometimes you got to think fast on your feet.
Do the pog face.
Pog.
What's a pog?
No, no, no, he got it.
He's got it.
Don't even, are you serious?
Is that it?
That's a pog face.
He did it first try.
He's like, no, he's doing this.
That's literally it right there.
That's it.
Hold that.
You cannot buzz him.
He took him five seconds.
That was good.
He took him five seconds to do it.
All right, number 13.
If you could do the Germacraft copy pasta.
I would love to hear.
Hello.
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to the first episode of Germacraft, the series.
I play Minecraft.
Now, this is going to be a single player.
Let's play.
But when I use that term, let's play, I use that term loosely because I am an idiot in this game.
Now, you're going to see lots of triumphs, lots of fails, even more triumphs.
At least I'm hoping so.
So let's grab a nice hot cup of coffee.
Nice hot cup of cocoa.
I got a nice hot cup of cider right here.
It's invisible, but freshly brewed.
Oh, that's good cider.
I think coming in with a Christopher Walken is actually pretty brave.
He dropped it halfway through.
I mean, seriously, if you come in with a Walken, it's going to be good.
And that was a good Walken.
It sure was great.
Thank you, Germa.
If you do Germacraft copypasta with a Walken, wow, that's at least five or six extra points.
We're off to a good start.
Yes, we are.
Can you do like the cowbell routine, just to be sure?
I'm ready to know you.
Don't press the button.
I got a fever.
A new prescription is more Germa.
Okay, don't.
Got to have it.
He's got a Christopher Walken.
My pants on one leg at a time.
Nobody buzz this guy.
The only difference is after I've got my pants on, I replace Germa.
Okay, he's got an absolutely phenomenal Walken.
He's got a Walken.
That's better than my Trump.
That's better than my Bernie.
That's better than my Walken.
Is that J.R.R. Walken?
Oh, that's phenomenal.
Number 13, I don't.
Really?
He can't please everybody.
Can't please everyone.
He said himself.
Don't, no.
I'm kidding, I'm talking about.
I'm good, I'm happy.
I took it back, I took it back.
It was the moment.
Number 13, you've made it to the final three.
That is the final three we have.
That's a great celebration.
That's a good, I'm sorry, I take it back.
That's such a good celebration.
Jog in place.
Thank you very much.
We do have our final three, don't we?
I think we have our actual final three.
I love to hear that.
So we're going to take one final break.
And then guess what?
You decide on who replaces me on German 985.
Twitch.tv slash German 985.
We'll be right back in about two, three minutes.
For the real end.
Okay, we're back.
If you could please bring the three finalists out on stage,
please, if we could.
That would be one and nine and 13.
Hello, one, nine, and 13.
How are you?
You are the finalists for who will replace me,
German 985, on my Twitch channel.
How do you feel?
Very well, still shaking.
Good, good, shaking, shaking.
Well, unfortunately, the judges here now
no longer have a say because it's now your say.
They don't have a mic, but that's okay.
Everybody in the chat right now,
there will be a poll to decide of these three.
One, nine, and 13.
Who takes the German 985 moniker?
There will be a poll in chat.
It's for you to decide.
You get the final decision.
One, nine, or 13.
We look forward to the poll.
Maybe, maybe, maybe give some pizzazz at the end, you know?
Give a little, show them why you deserve it.
One, go ahead.
One, what do you got?
Right.
Nine, what do you got?
13, what are you doing?
Is it Batman?
Was that JoJo?
Oh, JoJo, I love JoJo.
We've got a very, this is ridiculous.
Okay, come on, what's the poll at right now?
It's between one percentage point, Jerm.
I'm looking at the stats right now.
It's one percentage point.
It's narrow.
One vote can take this.
One vote is deciding who wins.
Number nine, can you step forward one?
Move back now, thank you.
Number one, step forward two.
Step left three.
Step right three.
Cha cha, daddy-o.
Real smooth.
Step back and step back, okay?
What are we at right now for the poll?
Let's say it.
This is your Jerma985.
You are deciding right now.
One, nine, or 13.
Future one of the biggest channels on all of Twitch.
My goodness gracious.
I think it's going to double.
The projections are massive.
I don't know what to even do.
No matter what, all three of these guys
are a better pick for Jerma985 than Jerma985.
Absolutely, and I don't want you guys to forget us
when you ascend to godhood.
I would love to collab still
because I think I'll be even bigger.
You say totes collab?
That's great.
Ladies and gentlemen, we have the winner.
This is charming, totes.
The winner of the Who Will Replace Me
Jerma985 show is number one.
Step forward.
Now step back.
Number nine, step forward.
It's number 13.
Number 13 is the winner
for the Who Will Replace Me Jerma985.
Well earned.
Number 13 with 55% of the vote.
Unbelievable.
It was majority.
It was a majority.
New Jerma, new Jerma.
This is incredible.
Excellent.
A whole new era.
I love this guy.
Wait a second.
Wait, what?
Wait a minute.
What?
Kill the music.
Number 13.
You think you have what it takes to be me?
You think you do?
Well, that's interesting
because if you think that you have what it takes to be me
then you need to have what it takes to beat me
because you're going against the master now.
You got to go against 1v1 me.
Everybody understands this.
I'm not going to let this channel go very, very loosely.
We had like a process.
Oh, there's a process.
The process is I got to see if you have what it really takes.
Ladies and gentlemen,
if you think you've got what it takes,
we will find out right now.
You think you can beat me?
I know I can beat you.
I don't know what I'm going to beat you at.
You know you can beat me.
Go ahead and cue the music.
Good luck.
Weird monopoly, man.
Like a Swedish monopoly, man.
What is planned?
You guys secretized this?
Are you doing it so well?
Nobody beats me at my own game.
This is incredible.
These moves.
Whoa, whoa.
New Jerma.
He had moves the whole time.
One handed.
Something's happening.
Can you do this though?
Number 13.
There's no window.
Sure, there's no window.
Oh.
Perfectly executed.
I don't think so.
What's the vote say?
Chatters, you decide.
New Jerma or old Jerma?
Which one you pick it?
The old Jerma?
Yeah.
All right.
I win.
Nobody replaces me.
Nobody.
I'll be here forever.
This hardly seems fair.
No, that's not how it works.
What do you mean it's not how it works?
No, just get the fuck out of here.
Fuck off.
Cheater.
No, fuck off.
You lose.
Sweet, what was that?
Six hours.
Get the fuck out.
Just go fucking back.
Why are we all here if you were just going to walk on stage?
Just go.
Fuck off.
No, it's you.
You decided you come to the show
and you beat me for a little while and I win.
No, no, it's called being a sore loser.
No, it's not.
This needs to be fixed.
Judges, really?
Judges?
What can we do?
What power do we have, Woodward?
You don't have power.
Get the fuck off.
I spent weeks rehearsing for this.
Yeah, what the fuck?
I don't care.
Weeks?
It's my life, you whole thing.
Your life?
Listen.
What, do you want to fucking go?
Are you going to fight?
What, you think it's fucking funny?
Is he ready to throw?
He thinks, oh yeah, you can take me too.
Oh, you think you can take me, yeah.
Have fun.
Yeah, let's get this shit off.
Fuck off, idiot.
No, this is good.
This is good TV.
If it works for Jake Paul, it'll work for us.
Oh, I'm actually pissed up because this guy thinks he's fucking got what it takes.
Okay, you want to fucking go?
Okay, let's go, let's go.
Shit, give me that fucking number.
What is this?
I don't think we can show this.
This is so much.
Take the kids.
This is still a week when pants are too...
Wait a minute.
Why is he undressing?
He's like, what's going on?
These pants are too fucking tight.
Okay.
All right, get involved.
Let's go 13, I'm rooting for you, baby.
Shut up, Ludwig.
Oh.
As soon as you get those pants off.
13, baby, this is your show.
Yeah, yeah, fuck you, man.
Come on.
New Jerma.
Guys.
Wait, I'm getting confused.
No one's going to replace me.
Never.
What's going on?
Never replace me.
Wait a second.
Wait, all right, break it up.
Real Jerma, come forward.
Which one's which?
Real Jerma, come here.
What?
Who wants to sit beside him?
Hey, there you go.
That's real Jerma.
No, no, wait a minute.
Let's cut this shit.
He's impossible.
13, can you stop for a moment?
He's not fucking 13.
I'm not Jerma.
13, can you stop for a moment?
I'm not retiring.
He's got to be.
I'm Jeremy.
What are you talking about?
No.
Don't listen.
Come on, guys.
Can you say something?
This is the actor, I...
It's not a real deal.
Okay, do the thing, do the thing.
Like, prove it.
I think I do all the things.
Do the thing you do, Jerma.
Do the thing you do.
I've known you, Dr. Schmoox,
and I've known you for a long time.
Yes, it's him.
What?
Absolutely.
No, this guy, you can still see the...
Peter, six fucking hours.
We're going to pick this right now.
Okay?
No, it's me.
It's me.
It's not this idiot.
Well, we're going to figure out...
We hired this guy.
We're going to figure out who it is.
Okay?
All right.
Don't think we need violence.
That's stupid.
There is no reason for violence in this place.
Go out of the way, please.
All right.
Please, please, Dr. Schmoox, you know.
I've known Jerma for 12 years.
I've known him my whole life.
I know the real Jerma.
Stir, stir.
It's obvious which one's the real one.
Be cautious with the gun.
Guys, guys.
Guns hurt.
Look at me.
You know?
Guns hurt.
Stir, I've known him for 10 years.
We've...
TF2 and...
Look at me.
That's me.
Jerma, I just want you to know.
You can Google all that.
He knows nothing.
I could tell who it was the whole time.
What?
You shot...
You shot him.
You...
Fuck.
I'm going to haunt you for the rest of my life.
Don't listen to this fraud.
Somebody call an ambulance.
No, we don't need it.
No, you're a doctor.
Just go help us.
Hey, it's all right.
We shot the fake Jerma.
Real Jerma, you...
We can't...
You're back, baby.
I'm sorry he tried to mess with you.
I don't know.
He did a...
Okay, Jerma.
You can't do this.
Well, guys...
New Jerma.
Real Jerma.
Dead Jerma.
Let's get this imposter out of here.
Oh my god.
Do the thing.
Yeah.
That's my Jerma.
I guess so.
9.85.
All right, 9.85.
A hot cup of shite on you.
Yeah.
This guy.
Hit it.
We're looking forward to playing lots of Minecraft.
Epic fails.
Even more epic crimes.
What can I say?
Epic fails and fun.
German bag, baby.
I'm glad we got that imposter, though.
That was scary.
I think we're clear.