Hello. Hi everybody. I'm just realizing right now that this, for some reason, why is this not working?
My Monster Rancher 4 disc is for some reason not reading now. That's weird. Hold on.
Let's hope that doesn't cause a problem, otherwise we're gonna have to do something else. That's not good.
It was working before. Let's see.
Hello. Let's watch with me here. Let's see what happens.
But, hope you had a good couple of days. There it is. Okay.
But, here we are. Alright. Okay. That was weird.
Monster Rancher 4 tonight. We played Monster Rancher 3. It wasn't that good.
And there's apparently an animated intro to this game.
Don't ask me why this is here, but okay.
Didn't they make a TV show on this game? They made like a whole television franchise.
Is this just a giant ad for the show?
It started as a TV show. What? How come there's no audio?
Oh god, you're playing the bad one. The last one was the bad one.
I thought EVO was the bad one. Is there only one good one?
I was told that EVO was the bad one, 3 was the bad one, 4 is apparently the bad one.
Oh, that's Captain Hook Sonic! Am I gonna get flags for this?
I hope not. No, I'm not. This is just a simple introduction.
This is the intro of the stream.
Alright, but while you watch this, I'm gonna tweet this stream.
I can't even do that with this lingering cough.
I've made this noise before. I've made this song before, probably.
Hey, that's Monster Rancher 4. 2003.
Why does it look so JPGE? That's because it's old and it's being pulled through a device.
But, this is what we're gonna try to do today.
And I did say that if the game is terrible, I do have a solution.
Okay, that's tweeted.
I have a solution for if this game is very bad.
Am I emulating? No, I am not. This is real hardware. I'm a real hardware streamer.
New game versus mode option. Let's see what's in here.
Alright, come on. Can we listen to some of the sounds?
No.
75. Don't ever have background music the same.
If the game is bad, Google Feud. No, if the game is bad, we're going to Mr. Mosquito.
And that was hard to track down.
Monster Rancher 4. Here we go.
A long time ago, people and monsters lived in harmony.
But eventually, humans sealed the monsters inside tablets called saucer stones.
This is the intro to Undertale.
Those are discs, if you don't know. And I got plenty of them here.
The people are entertained by monster battles and the breeders who raise the monsters are heroes.
Weird.
The capital of the country is Toggle, a place far from Ruin.
That's the name of my town.
A boat from Age Island brought you here.
And that's how it all started.
And then she got snapped.
Get your butt out of here, you sneaky little rat.
This is TT.
Yowchoo, what are you doing? What did I do wrong?
Why, you have some nerve.
Sneaking in and sleeping in a stranger's bed.
Don't you play innocent with me.
Uh, what the fuck?
I didn't come into this stuffy room because I wanted to.
Huh? Boy, you really do have a lot of nerve.
What the fuck is happening here?
Excuse me, you two.
Huh? Well, what is it?
My name is Caesar and I'm from a nearby shrine.
If it's okay, I'd like to take care of that boy.
Huh, you're a big wig in this town. Well, good timing.
This brat broke into here.
He needs to be thrown into jail, I tell ya.
I trust you'll take care of this.
Oh, boy, and off she goes.
That young girl doesn't have a sharp tongue.
Yeah, I bet she scares all the boys away.
Well, good night, mister.
Zzz, I fell asleep immediately.
God, to have that power.
Sometimes I sit in bed and try to sleep for like four straight hours.
You know what superpowers people talk about they wish they had?
If you had a superpower, what would it be?
I would fly.
No, fuck that.
I think it would be fun to be invisible.
No, that's stupid.
I'd like to be able to fall asleep whenever I wanted to and go into REM sleep.
Now that's a good superpower.
Oh, boy, they're so already asleep, huh?
What's this? The boy's bag.
Looks rifled through it.
What an odd intro. Is this anime like this?
Are these characters from the TV show?
Hmm. Where am I?
What? My bag. The saucer stones.
Eek.
Sorry, have you seen my bag?
So he... I don't understand
what happened in the first five minutes of this game.
He broke into somebody's house,
fell asleep instantly,
and then an old person stole his bag.
I don't know what's going on.
Hmm, err, your bag.
Don't be alarmed, your bag and the saucer stones
are right here.
Did you know this girl worried about you
and stayed by your side this whole time?
Maybe a thanks is in order.
This girl, Rio, she's my daughter.
She did that for me? Thanks, Rio.
Oh, sure.
If I may ask, does this bag mean
that you're a student at Elvis School?
The elite school that trains top breeders?
To move their hips back and forth
real fast?
No, I used to be a student, but I was expelled.
I hate this.
This is fucking stupid.
What did you get expelled for?
No.
General lied about Minecraft VR thanks to the five community subs.
Thank you.
I see. You couldn't face your parents,
so you snuck onto the ship.
I can't say that I approve of that, lad.
No, I don't have any parents.
I had nowhere to go, and I just didn't know
what to do, so I came here.
What do you mean you don't have any?
What? Like, does he mean ever?
Kazzie, thanks for the five community subs.
Oh, yeah,
he's got his parents.
You have to watch
this show for one anime a year.
No, I don't think
I'm going to do that, but thank you Kazzie,
and thank you Peek-A-Banana for five community subs.
Fifteen community subs right off the bat here. Thank you, guys.
I can't help what happened.
To be honest, I hardly care about being
expelled anymore.
I see. Sorry if I mentioned
parents at all.
What is going on here? General lied about Minecraft VR.
Five more community subs.
Damn. Thank you, guys.
That's twenty now. Back to back.
Holy Jesus. Thank you, guys.
I'm sorry I mentioned parents at all.
I have an idea. Why don't you work here?
I'm looking for somebody to look after some
vacant land. You're not doing
any good just hanging around, so how about it?
You could even raise some monsters.
Raise monsters?
You mean you'd let me run a ranch?
You just met me and you'd let me do that?
Well, nothing big time,
but a ranch nonetheless.
Now I don't know what you did to get expelled,
but I'm sure you had your reasons.
This guy's messed up.
What do you know what he did?
You had your reasons to get expelled from school.
But there's no point in giving up your dream now.
So what it'll be.
Let's see. What's your name?
Fane.
That is too many
ways. That's too much.
Fane. I don't think I want to change that.
That seems pretty canon to me.
Fane? P-H-A-Y-N-E.
That's canon.
I can't change it. Yeah.
Fane. My name is Fane.
This is just like a live journal username.
Thank you Magellan for the
five community subs. Thank you guys.
Of course. I accept.
Thanks Mr. Caesar.
Now let's settle then. You can use this
saucer stone to regenerate monsters.
Okay, let's head to the shrine.
First monster. Here we go.
You can regenerate saucer stones in this
shrine. Is this your first visit to a
real shrine, Fane?
This time we'll regenerate from this saucer stone.
But if you find any others, bring them over.
As long as you have room to raise
more monsters, you can regenerate them
any time you like. Why do you have
red eyes? This is the adult
version of Annabelle.
This is like Annabelle grew up
to like a late teenager.
We're in the same clothes. Is this
the same character? Yeah.
It is. It's just
a little bit different color scheme.
As long as you have room to raise more monsters,
you can generate them. Yeah.
Now Fane, let the regeneration
begin. So I get one for free
or do I have to put a disk in? So those
of you that have no idea what's going on in the game, let me try
to explain.
This is a game where you battle monsters.
And you get the monsters by
putting in any disk you have in your
house. And it generates a random
seed for that disk.
And you get a monster. So this
is your first monster. Okay, let's have you give it a
name. That's the first
monster?
I don't want this like default
dickhead. I want my own.
It's just like, that's like
what a mouse design would look like
if it was a Disney Pixar movie.
Isn't there already like a Disney Pixar
like rat mouse?
It's like, I don't know. How about
Mawaz?
That's a wonderful
name. Give it all your love
to Mawaz. Now,
take Fane to that empty plot of land.
I want that thing. What do I get like
the baby King Dedede from?
We're here. Wow, it's huge and
so mysterious. This is just
awesome, huh Rio? Wait,
I hear a voice from over there. Who could it be?
Shoot, wait up, wait up, I tell ya.
Finally. I got
up. Are you the boy named Fane?
Yes, who are you?
My name is Yuri.
Caesar told me to come and help you.
I work at the item shop, but
I always wanted to try being a ranch assistant.
So I look forward to working with you,
Fane. Let's do some good work together.
Sure, Yuri, let's
uh, it's time
for me to go home. Hey Rio, she's
gone. Anyway, let's do some good
work. I might not look it, but I've done my
homework. You can count on me.
Okay, first, let's go over the ranch basics.
Clean out your ears
and listen up carefully. At the beginning
of the week, you create a schedule.
Oh no, I'm not very
good with those. Schedule training
to strengthen your monster. Can I have no schedule?
I work way better on no schedule.
And schedule breaks to let your monster
rest. You can schedule up to
eight weeks in advance. Use
this to create a long term plan.
I'm going on like a diet,
apparently. Okay, so then select
the training type and time,
then free time to play with your monster.
By playing with the monster here, the monsters
bond with you will strengthen.
We're playing like busy dad simulator.
I gotta ride in an hour
to throw the ball around with my son.
Praise monsters when they do a good job
to further strengthen your mutual bond.
And if a monster is not doing what it should,
then it's time for a discipline.
Lazy monsters must be brought into
line. Love is both carrot
and stick, and this also increases
bonding. Use your best judgment
and take advantage of free time as an
opportunity to raise the level of bonding.
Lastly, rest on weekends until you get used
to things. Later you can enter
competition and shop in town.
Well, that's a typical week on the ranch. The rest
you'll learn as you go. Well, what do you think?
Did you understand? Yeah, you schedule
out everything. You schedule rest,
schedule training, schedule playtime.
I think I get it. Kind of.
Maybe, probably not though. Good, you're a great partner.
Well, let's give it our best then.
Year one, month four,
week one, schedule.
Alright, so we got data, command,
training, schedule, shrine, system,
mows is very lively.
Let's go to schedule. So this is
year, this is one, this is the first
week. So week, we're gonna do
training. Uh, I need to see,
wait, what are you, the monster plans its own training
to raise strength. No, no, no, go back.
What, what does this guy even have his stats?
How do I see his stats? Data.
Monster, okay. So, power,
life, high power.
Uh, for one second, I don't know, my brain
just didn't understand. I thought that said
Oyoromo. I was like,
what's that, what name is that? I didn't
give him the name Oyoromo. Yeah,
pretty dumb, but it looks like,
what do you got for moves? Skills. Hmm.
So this is wild slash.
This is a power move. This is an
intelligence move for somebody with 85 intelligence.
Sounds pretty terrible. And then fire
charge. Okay. So
I think we're gonna work on power. And
what, this is also power, right?
Yeah, power. I can barely
read those numbers.
Yeah, they're a little crusty, aren't they?
Let's go to the shrine. Let's do the thing that we're supposed
to be doing, first of all. I don't know if I like
this guy. Well, hello, everything going well.
So what will it be? Okay.
Let's create. You already
have a monster you're, you already have a monster
you're raising. So what will it be?
Uh, do I have to, like, freeze him? Come again
anytime. I don't know if it was like the other games.
Put in, I got, oh, I got lots of stuff here,
don't worry. Uh, so,
how do I freeze him? Shrine system?
Holy shit, that actually is fireman.
Like, I could, I should have named it fireman.
It sort of is, with the big groucho
marks eyebrows. Alright, so how do I, um,
how do I do that?
Appraise? Maybe he can, like,
just a moment, feign. You don't have a saucer stone.
There's nothing to appraise without a saucer
stone. It's too late to kill
it. I'm not trying to kill it, I'm just
trying to store it.
Walmart brand
salamander.
Walmart brand charmander.
Alright, I don't, I don't think
I can fucking freeze him.
Schedule. Could I, like, schedule him to be put on
ice? System.
Save. Versus
data? Let's just save the game.
Schedule him to die.
Release him
into the wild. He's like a baby.
Alright, I think, I don't think I can do this
yet. I think we just have to play with, um, I don't even
know his name, mouse. Let's log,
okay, schedule. Training.
We're gonna do
power training, this is exercise,
and then let's
do a little bit of more
training the next day.
And then we're gonna rest, and then we're
gonna do rest, and then
what about, like, how do I do a play
date? No, not all training.
He's gonna die.
Automatic.
Maybe his exercise
high jump. Balance.
Let's do balance.
Okay.
So now, let's go back.
And just, let's go.
Let's, let's do it.
How do I, like, play out my
baseball season that I made?
Do I have to do it all?
Okay, submenu.
I guess we have to block this all out. Alright,
balance, that will rest, and we'll do
two weeks in a row. Of power.
And then rest again.
Okay. Let's go.
Command.
I command you to do something.
Begin the training. I guess.
Alright, so power.
Plus six.
What is he doing? He's just doing sit-ups
in front of the house. Free
time. I can actually walk
around?
Command.
Weekend. Book, belongings,
what do I do with them? Praise.
Okay. I'm assuming the, what's the
second button? I'm not gonna skull
them, he didn't do anything wrong.
Alright, let's see. Command. Schedule. What about
data? Breeder, belongings.
Okay, so circle is how you get to, like, your
inventory. Proceed to weekend
activities. Not yet. Hold on.
Schedule. Exercise.
Exercise. No. Alright, it just plays
out, no matter what you do. Cannot
do anymore. I cannot praise him again.
Alright, well how do I play with him?
There's no play? Does he do anything else
besides sit-ups? Alright, well let's just move
on. Proceed to the weekend activities.
Yes. Town.
Go to town next week. Do nothing
and proceed directly to the next week. What do you mean
go to town?
Hometown. The shrine overlooks the association
and other shops and port.
Let's go to town together.
Dude, that's like a triple
room right there.
These motherfuckers, I swear to God.
Alright, so let's try.
Well, hello, everything going well?
What'll it be?
I guess.
I don't think I got, I haven't unlocked
anything else besides the first town
in Chrono Trigger.
There's nothing I can do. Well, that was fun.
April, week two in spring.
Hello, I heard that you're going to start
a new monster ranch in this area.
My name is Cynthia. I do
registration for the Toggle Monster Association.
Nice to meet you. The association oversees
the various ranches. I'm in charge of Toggle.
First, register the
name of your ranch at the association.
Okay. Here's how you do it. First,
select a symbol for your ranch, then select
a name. The name of your ranch becomes
permanent, so make sure you think of a good one.
Wait,
it's predictive text.
Farm the...
Is it, wait.
Farm street? The...
No, no, no, no, no, no. What?
The park. Farm park.
Ranch school. I don't know what
this is trying to get me to do.
Club great.
Club new. Team
the.
Street cape.
How about club cape?
The club.
New team.
Ranch school.
I kind of like ranch school. How about
ranch yard?
Ranchdom?
Ranchdom.
Dom club.
Dom land.
Club
ranch.
I don't know. These are all too good.
Farm street is also really good too.
New
street. Oh, I'm gonna have to just close
my eyes.
Ranch club. Ranch town.
Ranch cape. Land school.
Land school.
What? No, no.
I want it to be land school.
It's permanent. I can't change this.
There is no going back.
Actually isn't.
This is such shit. This is the worst.
It has to be this.
School land.
Do your best.
I'm rooting for you.
That's fucking terrible.
Such a dumbass.
Look.
School land is good for me.
That would be a terrible Disney park.
I can't restart. She told me.
No restart.
He was expelled from school.
So he made his own school
land.
That's fucking funny.
Alright, let's go.
You guys are killing me.
Is that level 10?
I'm at 88% success rate.
88%. 9 power. That's pretty good.
I don't know
what these bars even mean.
The top bar is not even a bar.
It's a series of flags.
It's a series of
symbols that point to the left.
I don't know what that's supposed to mean.
The middle one is down arrow
with bar. And then the last one
I don't know. That's somebody making a
shadow on the wall with their hands.
With a light in front of it. Like a hand
puppet. I don't know what that means.
But good job.
You got almost 10 points.
If only there was a word for a symbol that
points in a direction.
Left. But why is that
what does left have to do with
this? Alright, let's fight.
No, not me and you, but like let's
let's see. How good are you doing now?
200 points? That's actually pretty good.
Okay, there it is.
Alright guys, if I didn't go to this menu
you can't tell me that you would think.
Focus, tired, and
fullness. That's focus
not left. Alright.
Let's just keep going.
Proceed to the weekend activities.
We can't do anything in town so let's just go.
Third week. When are we going to get a
tournament? Keeping up the good
work, Fane. I brought
some treats today. Here, give these snacks
to the monsters.
Plural, I don't have more than one.
On a ranch, you've got to train your monsters
but you've got to look after their health too.
Focus, fatigue, fullness,
status. You can check all these stats.
On the lower right gauge
during scheduling. During
free time, talk to your monsters plenty
and care for them as appropriate to their status.
And you know, breeder
rank and ranch status affect the number of
actions you can execute during free time.
You notice the small sphere
on the lower left during free time. That's the
number of actions you can do. Okay, good to know.
Now, there's one sphere
so I can do one
thing. Now, don't you forget
to feed your monsters. Well, do your best,
Fane. You received
two potatoes. Thanks
for the help. And two mangoes.
And a squid.
And a beef.
This week's HelloFresh came in.
Boy, man. Okay, so
it's raining. What do you got? Focus.
You're pretty focused. Tired.
Sorry.
This one was balance, right?
No, this is rest. Okay, this is rest.
Now, can I feed you from here?
Probably. Okay.
Food. What do you like?
Squid? I wonder what kind of
food you like.
Mango? Squid?
Most monsters eat it raw.
A big hunk of beef still on
the bone. It satisfies your monsters wild
side. Squid.
Disgusting. Pretty nice
triple Mario jump.
Yes, I'll make a Mario reference. I don't care.
Now he's dead.
Oh, don't ever eat undercooked squid.
Or you die.
Alright, let's go to the weekend.
How do I? I want another monster.
When am I going to get
to my stone?
I've got all kinds of weird shit to put in
here. I have a game that
I didn't get to play, that I was so
looking forward to, and I'm going to use it for today's.
Right? I bought a game
that I thought was going to be hilariously fun
for PC, and it just doesn't work.
Yawn. Up and at him.
Yeah. Hmm. A visitor.
Hee hee. Is that right?
I'm so glad you met such a
fun person, mouse.
Hey, Rio!
Oh, there you are. Whatcha up to?
Uh, oh, I
just dropped by.
Hey, she's gone!
Hey, Yuri! Do you think I said something wrong?
Don't worry, she's always like that.
She talks so kindly to monsters,
but doesn't say a word to the villagers.
She is a monster. Hmm, really?
Okay, what's the schedule look like
this week?
Balance, rest, exercise,
exercise, rest, exercise, exercise,
rest. Yeah.
That sounds pretty good. No, actually, don't fuck that.
I like that better.
Actually, hold on
a minute here. Hold on a minute.
I think I'd rather
put it on, like, you know, my streaming schedule.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, okay.
That looks good. Three days on,
two days off, two days on,
one day off. Go for it.
Let's get some more life.
Plus seven life, good.
Success rate at 90%.
I wonder, you know what I kinda miss?
I really do miss from the second game, when you get to see
like the fun little cartoon of them doing it or failing
it or not, you know what I mean?
This is dumb. Where's like the cool
where's like the them actually doing the technique
and try, you know what I mean?
You're just balancing on one foot and I see a meter
go up. Uh, how you doing?
Lively. The first,
Monster Hunter 2 really is the best game.
It's like really the only one you should play.
But, hold on, I'm gonna hold off
until we get some more monsters here.
Alright, he's not hungry, he's fine.
Just play two? Well, I need to see
what this has to offer.
I'm not gonna write it off yet.
The moon is so bright tonight, I can't sleep.
God, I wish I had that super power
that Gerber985 talked about at the beginning of the stream.
When I was
expelled from school, I thought I lost my shot
at my dreams. But now
here I am, standing in the middle of this ranch.
Under such a beautiful moon,
what a strange fate.
Is somebody there?
We don't get many chances to meet these days,
do we? Well, you know,
you're welcome to come any time
you like. He sure
seems like a nice boy.
I sure wish I could meet him too.
No.
If you did that, you'd be in trouble.
Just like I am now.
I'm sorry, please
don't cry, Rio.
Is this a tree? Don't worry, I won't
do anything rash, okay, Rio?
Rio?
No, I'm sorry. Well, I've gotta go.
Rio, who is she talking to?
I couldn't get a good look.
There's a tree.
It was sweet rind.
Hey, week one, mate.
We have a visitor. Okay, let's get this- ow.
Let's get the game going.
Hello, Yuri, and Fane.
This place is turning into a very
nice ranch. You bet it is.
I wouldn't settle for anything less.
So what brings you here?
Well, I figured it's about time for you to
start thinking about the competition.
Would you like to go and take a look
first? Wow, yeah, of course.
I'd love to go. You too, right?
Fane, I'm not doing that every time.
Yeah, sure, I'll bring Miles along.
Are we gonna get a heart tear
at the heartstrings here?
Are we gonna lose this monster?
This sure is exciting.
Next is the main event with the Ruin
and Breeders.
The rabbit class.
Ladies and gentlemen, finally presenting
the beautiful thorned rose of Thimba.
Miss Titi
and her Kalarino.
Why is she here?
If it isn't that kiddo, what the heck are you
doing here?
You even brought a monster? Wait a minute, don't tell me
you are a Breeder.
Well, well. Is that so?
Hmm.
Well, I can see you've got the perfect monster
for playing in a sandbox.
The whole crowd fucking
laughs. What did you say?
See, I just did that.
I just fucking did that laugh.
I think syllable for syllable.
I told you guys think I'm
fucking stupid. I know these things.
At least you'll get to see my wonderful fighting
style. Hmm. Well, I could give you
my signature. At least that would make your
trip here worthwhile.
And then I laughed. And then we fight
and we instantly beat this person.
Because this person actually sucks at what they do.
What? Oh, we're not playing.
Apparently we're not playing. My internet's
dying though. Are we good?
Come on, man. Come on.
I'm dropping a lot of frames.
Are you guys seeing the frames?
It looks like I'm dropping a shitload of frames.
I think we're okay.
RIP INT
for internet, probably.
Hmm. Well,
we'll just let it see if it passes. Usually it does.
I hope so.
Oh, what is wrong with that girl? I'm getting really impatient
with her. I'm getting impatient with cocks too.
Huh? It's real.
It looks like, is that like an emoji?
That looks like somebody doing an
elaborate emoji in chat.
That has to be something. I don't know
what that would mean, but
it might mean something.
Association.
Monster Association, yes.
Finally. Got a 45 minute
tutorial here.
Here we are.
Alright. So.
Combine, retire,
ranch. I don't, do I
really want to retire mouths?
Do I? Thank you very much.
No, shit.
Couldn't you freeze them? You can't freeze them in this game?
Once you retire, you
cannot unfreeze. You can only
combine. Oh, shit.
Oh, that's not good.
But, we need to put like
C-man in here. No.
See you later. I need to see
what comes out of C-man. It's important.
But don't, we can combine
retire
mouths.
This is going to end up being a mistake.
But, 200 power.
We'll get something better. You had
a good run of doing
30 fucking
push-ups. And like balancing
on your foot for 5 minutes.
Bye. This is like fucking
kind of...
That was really sad.
What'll it be?
Which method will you use to create
a monster? From the
saucer. Alright,
you ready?
Well, let's turn the camera on.
I did like a disappearing
act right there. Alright, first thing going
in. By the way, hi.
First thing going in, as you know,
is going to be C-man. C-man is the first
game going in. See you in a minute.
Your hair looks great.
Jimmy Newton Mustache.
Single left side mustache hair.
Alright, open the disc tray.
Opening disc tray, okay.
What are you talking about? Insert a CD
or DVD into the disc tray and push the X
button. Here we go.
We are going to see what we get from C-man.
And we'll try a few of these.
And then press X. Checking
disc. I'm going to laugh.
If it's a fish with a face, then we have to play with it.
Any CD will work.
No matter what it is, as long as it has data on the disc.
Alright, here we go.
Opening disc tray, if okay, press the X
button. I don't know what they keep saying that for.
Alright.
Hold your breath. What
classic monster are we going to get out of
here? Remember when you recorded
yourself screaming and it caused a blackout?
I do. Okay.
Thanks for waiting. Time to create a monster.
Pull the lever.
The planets have to align.
What the hell is that?
An odd monster, I'd say.
I see it's the first time
Fane has raised this monster. Let me
add a page to your book.
Take this monster home with you.
Um, yes.
So you're naming this monster?
Uh, it's like a
hippopotamus
rhinoceros triceratops on a wheel.
Yeah.
It was
Fane. It has to be Vroomer.
Is Vroomer okay?
Uh, can you praise
my monster? Oh.
Let's go back to the ranch and take a look at the stats.
Does what CD, what you put in
matter? Um,
I think you'll get the same thing from the same
disc. It's just a seed
that is created from whatever
is on the disc.
So, it's just, it could be
it is random, but whatever the seed
that comes from the data on the disc
I believe is the same seed.
Maybe. This could be wrong.
Alright, let's go. Uh, let's take a look.
Oh, you are
terrible. Look at how bad
this monster is.
133 is the highest stat.
What do you have from moves?
You've got backspin
and drifting.
Drifting.
Drifting does a
decent damage, but with a high crit.
It takes 23
guts to use.
It has no effect. This has no effect
either. Well,
so it's obviously a power-based
monster. Goddammit.
This thing sucks.
Looks like power and
accuracy. I don't know what you're gonna have to do.
Alright, let's do some training
here. Let's see if we can get this any better.
Schedule. We got no
rest. Power.
The next week. Power again.
You can rest and then
let's go with
shadow boxing.
Shadow boxing.
Rest. Power.
Rest. No.
Power.
Alright, let's go for it. Let's see if I can get
anything better.
It just picks up its wheel.
That's all it does. It just lifts up
its wheel over and over again.
I didn't see it fit. Okay, that's
why notifications don't go
through audio-wise because I'm plugged into
the PlayStation 2.
But Comedy Chatman gave 50
bucks. Thank you so much Comedy
Chatman. Five
thousand bits. I will not financially
support a man who plays Monster Hunter.
It's not about the money this time. It's about
the message. Well, this is Monster
Rancher, so I'm not playing Monster
Hunter, so that's fine.
He's doing CrossFit.
This is such a weird,
uncanny, strange person here.
But thank you so much Comedy Chatman
for the 50 fucking dollars.
How much does that
raise it by? Not by very much, but
I feel like we can take this thing
somewhere.
Somebody said, is the wheel part of
his flesh? It has to be.
Watching Who five community subs. Thank
you, Watching Who. So much better than
Mao's. Well, statistically, no.
But aesthetically, yes.
Yeah, this is part of his
body. This weird wheel is part of his
body. It's somehow detached.
Creepily enough. Alright, let's go.
You don't need to eat right now.
The moonlight is bright tonight, just like
the other night. Where is Vroomer
heading off to? Okay, for a second I thought
that was the car noise going by.
I was about to be like, you gotta be kidding me.
Well, Rio, I can see the monsters love
you, like they always do.
I have an idea. Why don't you run the ranch
along with that boy, Fane?
I'm sure it'll be a lot of fun. Don't you
believe Vroomer? I can't.
It'll just turn out the same as always.
They'll become scared of me and
eventually hate me. I don't want
to be hated again.
You mustn't assume things, Rio.
You've got to open your eyes. Be brave
and say what you want to say.
When you have too many sequels, you just start to make
like a dumb fucked up story when it's just
about like raising monsters and like battling them
Pokemon style. Why are we doing like talking to like a magic
tree in this game? Ai!
What? What, Fane?
No, don't look at me!
No, it's alright, Rio. You can't hide
it forever. I told you she was a monster.
It's a beautiful moon tonight anyway.
Why not talk it all out?
My name is
Mukruji. Trees
with unusual powers like myself
are called Spirit Trees.
Who's talking? Oh, he is.
I'm one of the- I was gonna say, you're not a tree.
Like, pretending to be a tree.
I'm one of the oldest
Spirit Trees. And at some point
in my life, I learned to speak human
a bit. At some point, I learned how to speak
human. Every language.
I didn't want to surprise them, so during
the day, I stay quiet. Wow, but
you know, isn't it kind of sad to
stay quiet even though you can speak?
What do you- You humans
have nothing but fear of any kind of power.
You don't understand. You attack it!
Rio, what are you doing? I'm
sorry about her. Rio, you see, is a very
unusual girl. She's a part
tree. She has the power to talk to
monsters. And from a young age,
that power was feared by others
and she was disliked for it.
I didn't know that. I'm sorry, Rio, but
you shouldn't keep your thoughts to yourself.
If you do, you'll never be able to share your feelings.
Rio, you just have more chances
to understand others than ordinary people do.
This is what happens when writers and developers get bored.
It just is. This is Monster Rancher 4.
You know what I mean? At some point,
you just, like, you don't want to make
Monster Rancher 2 again.
So now you're making-
It's like you got bored and you're gonna make something else.
Yeah, chances. To be able to speak
and understand monster language, that's an amazing
opportunity. I've never thought about
it that way. I was always just so scared.
I couldn't look at it that way. Does this happen in
the anime? Or is the anime like a different
universe? If you close your heart, you'll never
be able to rid yourself of your fears.
You might be right,
Sora. Oh, it's about time for me to go
home. Good night, Fane.
Yeah, good night, Rio. Okay.
Do nothing and proceed to the next week. Let's go.
May, week two. Spring.
Another day ahead of us, Vroomer.
Wait, Fane, first, take this. What is it?
It's my extra special battle practice,
Kitty Meowser. First, use this
to review monster battles, okay?
What's with you today, Yuri? Pretty early
to be bouncing off the walls.
You wanna know why? Cause I'm determined
to beat that nasty girl in the competition.
I'll kick her butt to Kingdom
Come. I'll send her to a one-way trip to
La La Land. Vroomer!
Imagine this is her and let her
have it. We're gonna get beat by the training
dummy. Vroomer versus Meowser.
Alright, do I get to see the
their stats? They usually have the screen.
I guess that is their stats. Ready.
Fight. Alright, here we go.
You ready, Fane? Here I go.
First, approach the opponent. Get into short
range.
Hey, don't back up. Get close. I'm trying.
You moving the camera around. There you go.
That's within short range.
Next is step back.
Press the D-pad or left stick away from the opponent
then push the triangle button.
Yep, that's just like the second one.
Yes, perfect. This is called a
step back. Don't forget.
Next is a step in. Push the D-pad
or left stick toward the opponent then push triangle.
Yep, you need like a little dash to get close.
Exactamundo.
All tens. This is called a step in.
Next is a slam. Get close to
your opponent and push. Yeah, you can break
it up, right? Nice
throw. Next, use panel rotation
to select a move. R1 and R2
buttons swivel it around.
R1, okay. You get multiple panels.
Panel rotation.
Try your skills. Give them hell. Move to the distance
set in the skill panel. Yep.
And push the O, X, or you can push any button.
Okay, so
drift. Guts
down. Very good. Now you're ready to
compete in the tournaments.
It's just like the second game.
The combat is very much
the second game. I don't know how it was in the
third game. I don't think we even saw combat in the third game.
I didn't like the third game at all.
Okay, so use the skills screen
under monster data to assign monster skills to the
panel, right?
After you learn a new skill, don't forget to assign it
to a panel. You can't use the
skill without it being assigned.
Also, if you learn knowledge of fire, et cetera,
you can assign elements to certain skills.
That's a whole nother layer.
Try to figure out the weak points of your
enemies. You got it? Yes.
Practice makes perfect. Do your best.
Alright.
So.
Let's go to the schedule here.
Yeah. We're gonna do power here.
Go for it.
No, no, no, no, no. This.
Are these games actually any good?
They are. There we go.
Plus nine. Level eight
power. New move, maybe?
How you doing? Eh, you're a little
not that tired. You're fine.
Good work. He looks like a
beanie baby. He does
look like a beanie baby.
Nice job, rumor.
Let's keep going to the weekend.
Which one is my favorite? Monster
Arranger 2 is probably the best.
So far, at least. Let's try entering
a competition. Sounds like a good idea.
But I don't really know how. Maybe
we should go talk to Cynthia about it.
Hehe, I thought you'd say that. So I brought
a competition calendar. Use this
to enter the competition.
First, use the cursor to mark the competition that
you want to enter on the calendar. Right, you just
go. I get it.
Then select the monster and add it to the schedule.
Next, find a weekend
that a competition is being held and
selected as your weekend activity.
Also, to enter official competitions,
you have to first earn star points
from normal competitions.
If you win an official competition, your monster's
rank rises. And you can enter
higher ranked competition.
But to enter the top ranked official competition, your breeder
rank has to rise, too.
Only the association can
It's hard to know when your rank
will, yeah. So I guess you just
have to hope for the best.
I guess that's about it. Well, did you get all that?
Yeah. You're all set.
Let's beat that annoying
TT girl. Welcome to Monster Rancher 4
calendar.
So we have
800 bucks.
And we get a potato. What a
shitty competition. So we're currently
E ranked. You climb
all the way up to S. I think the highest we've ever
been in Monster Rancher 2 was
like A or B, right? That's the farthest
we got before I stopped playing.
Alright, so this is the single raspberry
cup. This is today, right?
Potato, tournament,
tournament prize. It's all the same thing.
So this is May. This is week
four. Let's
wait. Let's get this one.
Week two, June.
Let's enter this one.
All set, right?
Yeah. Rumor's in there, right?
So now let's look at the schedule.
So June,
here it is. Let's
actually rest up. See if we
can do anything here.
Let's train
today. And then
train tomorrow
here.
And then rest the day before.
So we got shadow box,
exercise, rest.
And then rest the day at the tournament too.
Sounds pretty sick to me.
Here we go.
Any points? Plus seven points inaccuracy.
Should we like play or something?
Alright, let's
give you some food. What do you eat for food?
Is this a carnivore?
I don't think so. Mango?
Here, try one of these.
I think he liked it. I think that means I like
it. He's doing okay.
Let's just go to the weekend.
Competition. Enter
monster being raised in competition. No.
Not ready yet.
So this is week four.
Lift.
Nice. Still have a really high success rate.
During free time you can
feed and praise, scold.
You can give items too.
Praise. It's bouncing with
agony. You need to euthanize this thing.
What? No.
What are you talking about?
It's having like a bunch of fun.
Alright, here we go. Weekend.
How's this? Let's take a look at the stats now.
Not bad.
156, 134.
It'll be probably around like 160.
What's it carrying?
It's carrying its own body, which is a wheel.
Somehow. Alright, this is the last week
before the tournament.
This is a day of rest.
Be gentle to this kind creature. I am.
I don't think there's
anything else I can do, so I might as well just
begin the training.
Isn't the training just rest?
It is, right?
Yeah.
Alright, it's kind of...
Is this like... This looks like roadkill.
Is that like part of the thing
here? Steal the
wheel. Roll the wheel
off the cliff.
I'm not gonna do that.
Have another mango.
You killed him. Alright.
Very lively, not tired.
Focused. I think
it's time. Let's see if we can
win a tournament.
So, here we go.
Calendar of tournaments today.
There are four
rivals.
You're not really that
strong, but it's okay.
This is also... This is rest today.
Relax. Here we go.
Competition.
Single Battle
Hydrangia Cup.
Rumor is in it.
Take part in the scheduled competition.
Yes. Let's see if we can make something happen.
Ladies and gentlemen,
here it is, the Hydrangia Cup.
Who will arise victorious?
There can only be one.
Now let the tournament begin. That's a weird
device around his neck.
Is that what he's yelling into?
That's like a weird... That's a weird microphone.
Alright, so we've got
Rumor, Cypher, Charon, and
Ober. Let's take a look at the info.
Enemy. So,
Cypher is a chump.
Low... I got higher power.
Low into... Yeah.
Life is not that bad.
I think this will be easy.
Give commands. Let's go.
35 speed.
Alright, Rumor. Let's fucking run him over.
Rumor versus Cypher.
Cypher looks like it is
in complete and total agony.
That thing is fucked up.
It's got five... One,
two, three, four, five faces probably?
Are the faces on the feet?
Here we go.
I'm trying to back it up. Guts 59.
Let's actually...
Let's get in closer.
Bullish. Backspin.
Nice!
Oh, that's a good move.
It just almost killed me.
I'm almost dead.
Okay. I gotta get in closer,
I think. Yeah, stay in close.
Got him.
Look at me! That was almost pretty
bad. Okay, who's next?
This is Charon and Ober.
I think it just tells you who wins.
Alright.
Looks like Ober has the upper hand here.
Ober wins.
So it's Rumor versus Ober in the championship for this.
Let's take a look at the other one.
I need more defense. I almost got one shot.
Alright, so this is a chump.
What kind of...
I think I'm ready.
Rumor versus Uber.
That's not a bad looking monster though.
Alright, let's see what they got.
Right in the middle, let's go right up front.
Started off with a drift.
I fucking crushed him again.
Don't even let him do anything. Again.
He blocked it.
Again. See you later.
Champion.
The winner of this terrific battle is
Rumor. Congratulations.
I've got really weird hands.
The timing, yeah.
800G and a potato.
Plus five fame for Rumor.
He was so happy he just
drove by the house.
InvincedGerman has a key to play the vroom noise.
No.
Nice work.
Let's take a look at the schedule.
Yeah, when's the next...
Wait, wait. When's the next tournament?
So I got a star.
This is...
Let's do... What's this one?
This is a single official grade E tournament.
This is the real one.
I think I can enter this though.
Because I have a star.
Can I enter this?
And just prepare for it?
The monster does not have enough points
to enter the official league battle.
Ah, fuck off.
Let's do this one.
We just have to stomp on him.
Alright, let's take a look at the schedule.
Let's do exercise and then rest.
No, exercise,
exercise, exercise, rest.
No, no, no, no.
Hold on.
I'm getting into this here. Hold on.
No, no, no.
What does he need?
Defense is terrible. Speed is terrible.
Let's do defense, defense.
Defense, defense.
Defense, rest.
Defense.
Let him have day off in the middle.
And then that night is the tournament.
You can have up to four monsters?
I thought...
I don't know if I have that unlocked yet.
Okay, that looks good.
Do I have food?
I have like a potato.
I just got my first money.
Alright, go for it.
Not that great.
Plus three defense.
This is like a fucking goofball.
What a goofy motherfucker.
Alright, let's do an okay. Let's pray.
Skold?
Well, it's not his fault.
He's like big, dumb, and slow.
He's not like the fastest.
He can't sprint around.
He uses his wheel.
I can't be mad that he's like too slow.
I'm spoiling him. Skold him.
No, I don't want to eat. He's my friend.
I'm not going to skold him.
Alright, food.
Oh shit, I can only do...
That's not good.
I can only...
Why can't I feed him?
I can only do one action
and feeding them is an action.
That's not good. Okay, well...
The tournament is
tomorrow.
So let's feed him.
Make him fear you.
Hey, you want to run your monster
village the way you want, I'm going to run my
monster village the way I want. Plus, this is like kind of...
This is like a little
janky looking...
See what I'm talking about here? That looks weird.
There we go. Okay, that's better.
Now it's not a bunch of like
black bars.
Now you can see better, can't you?
He's not very focused.
All I have is a potato.
That focused lively.
I think he's good to go.
So then this is the...
Is this the right week?
No, okay, it's tomorrow.
Yeah, it's tomorrow.
Yeah, he's in that one. Alright, we're good.
He's not dead.
He's fine.
Free food, good.
You come with the same
grocery list.
Alright, you're not hungry, you're not tired,
you're pretty focused.
And today was what?
Today was
training.
This is for, I believe, defense, right?
That's good.
Good. Five points.
Are you tired?
No, not really. Very lively.
Very lively.
Alright, let's go.
I'm not gonna do anything.
He's ready to fight.
I think we have to win
two or three of these before we can do the official tournament.
Ladies and gentlemen,
representing the Bamboo Cup,
who will arise victorious?
They can only be won.
Let the tournament begin.
Rumor, Kylan, Gatti, and Yellow.
Oh, fuck, this is not good.
Okay, really high intelligence.
Low defense, though.
I think if I get two or three quick moves off,
like that, I'll probably bury him.
My intelligence is awful.
He's got Tail Whip,
Spit, and Kiss.
Kiss is the thing you want to look out for.
That's the only thing that does intelligence damage.
So wherever Kiss is on his slot...
Wait a minute.
I'm not even fighting this.
Alright, well, good luck, everybody.
No, what? No, no, no, no, no.
Shit, I wanted to give commands. I hate when it does that.
He's gonna always on his own.
I wanted to look at the other menu for a second.
Alright, good luck. Good luck, Rumor.
Don't get hit by anything.
Good job.
I'm so glad you're doing this.
I would have reacted five times faster than you.
Come on, do it again. Quick.
Don't let him do anything. Kill him.
Don't let him do his move. He's gonna do the Spit.
Do it. Do something.
Do it quick before you die. Do it.
Stop shifting.
Oh, thank god.
That almost was a disaster.
Okay. Don't yell at him.
Gatti just destroyed Kylon.
So Gatti's the one with the one win.
And it's the person we're about to face.
No, we're not.
Kylon versus Yellow.
Alright, so Yellow just sucks.
The high intelligence doesn't really matter at all.
Alright, here we go.
Info. Gatti.
Stats are very low.
Just fast.
But sometimes it's all it takes.
Is this the evolved version of the monster that I had
but without legs?
It looks like it. It looks like Snoopy's cousin.
But with no legs.
Spike. That just is Fireman.
No, if he had no arms it would be.
No, he does have legs.
No, not good. Break it up. Break it up. Break it up.
You missed.
That was a yo-yo.
No, don't let him.
Alright, getting close and hitting with drift.
Oh, fuck. Back it up. Back it up.
I need more guts.
I haven't hit anything.
That's not good.
Get it. Yes.
One hit kill. Do it again.
I just made him mad.
Again?
No.
I got plenty of guts still. It's okay.
Is it the speed of the defense?
He's blocking everything.
Holy shit, man.
I'm almost out of guts.
He's just gonna wear me down.
Oh, shit. Okay, I have to hit him here.
Hit it.
Yes. Hurry.
Alright, that's two and all.
That's pretty much tournament victory as long as
I pretty much win.
Gatti in yellow.
Gatti loses?
Yeah, that's it. That's game over. I win.
The only way it's possible is if I lose to Kylon.
Which, I mean,
that's not gonna happen.
Well, it might.
168 accuracy, 133 speed.
Terrible power, though.
Kylon's moves are awful.
It's just a question of
not being able to hit them.
53 power. Yeah.
But my defense is bad, too, though.
It'll still hurt.
It's Vrombor versus Umbrella Head Dog.
Alright, we wanna
stay away from the one in the back.
Got it.
Damn.
There it is. Dude, again, quick. Don't even let him do anything.
Again.
Fuck. Alright.
I gotta learn a new move.
Stupid drift.
That's a victory.
The winner of this terrific battle
is Vrombor.
Congratulations. On cue.
I'm not doing that.
I'm not pressing a button to have a loud
engine sound.
Got a banana this time.
Five more fame points?
Vrombor's better than Beanbag Sonic, and that's
debatable. Nice work.
So, I think...
Let me see. I have two stars now.
What does it take? Official Cup?
No.
I need three stars.
When's the next Official Cup?
Oh, Jesus.
Official Grade E. When's the next
Official Grade E?
Oh, no.
That's not till October.
He's gonna
die.
Um.
Yeah, I'm gonna have to wait.
Wait.
Oh, you mean this July? No. There's no end.
There's this one here.
But I don't have enough.
We have to wait till October.
Dammit. Alright. Well.
Freeze him?
I don't know. Do you think I should freeze him now?
He's doing so well.
We got plenty of time to make more.
Not in his prime. Yeah.
Let me see the...
What do we need to build on here?
Power's good.
Defense could... Level 6 defense
is probably important. Speed is pretty
terrible as well. Intelligence is terrible.
Although I might get another move if I level up
power again.
I think.
I'm gonna try to get power to level 9.
Maybe life? Life is bad too.
Speed. There's so many things he needs.
Schedule it out. Alright. Let's do...
We have like
two months to get him there.
Let's do
speed. Speed.
Then...
Do speed twice. And then power.
Rest.
Rest in the middle of that.
And then we'll see where we're at.
Put in the stupid
invader's disc.
I have that here. I have a bunch of stuff.
That's a good increase.
Alright. Let's feed you.
We're doing okay.
Banana.
Sweet, nutritious banana from the
Parry jungle. Popular with kids.
Squid, beef.
Let's just... potato.
Let's save the good food for when we need it.
I do have Floydgan Brothers as well. You're right.
Let's continue.
Floydgan Brothers disc or riot.
Yeah. I'm gonna turn the web game on.
Just break it.
What was the training today?
Speed.
Alright.
Plus 6.
Tired. Good thing tomorrow's rest, right?
Put the other
monster ranchers in.
Yeah, there's a lot of options.
Once we get a decent...
How this game really functions is
you build up a
monster. You make them good.
You make them win. You get
a good start. You freeze them.
You make more and then you combine them.
To make a better one.
In the freezer.
Is he gonna start to rebel?
He's okay.
I can't believe the bootleg space channel 5
bullshit.
Okay, so he's tired. Today he was resting, right?
So rest.
Then it was power.
Rest and then
let's do defense twice.
And then we'll see where we are. Alright.
Here's the thing about 4.
I like how 4 you can batch
out stuff to do.
But I do miss the minigames.
I miss the fun little animations.
It's very lively. Good.
You good on food?
No, you're good. Let's go.
So today we've got
power
and then
I don't think you need to rest after this.
Power and then defense.
Power, defense, defense.
Hopefully we learn a new move.
Did you learn new moves? You have to, right?
Level 9, there it is.
Alright. Something new.
Did you learn to move?
Go to the shrine and make more insults to
God.
I will, I will.
I promise.
Let me just see. Did you get any new moves?
You only have
these two moves.
Nothing else?
Is it pee time
yet? I wanna get a drink. Ah, it will be in a
second.
Is it defense day? Level 6. Yes.
It's almost time to pee.
You need to eat.
Have a potato.
Okay, you're good.
Well, you're just okay, but that's fine.
I need to do one more
tournament before I can do the...
Let's pick like a shitty tournament and just steamroll
everybody.
Scold him for daring to ask for food.
You are...
You are awful.
That's an awful thing to say.
That's just awful.
More defense.
You're good.
Let me see the schedule. Alright, so...
Calendar.
What do we got?
Okay, so we have
September.
October.
So we need to do...
Where are we? We're here.
We'll just do this one.
We'll go...
We'll go just make fools out of everybody
here. We'll go embarrass everyone here.
Probably get booed and shit, but whatever. Who cares?
Making money, right?
Okay, he's signed up for that one.
Let's get out of here.
Training!
What were you doing today?
Defense, right? Very good.
He's very tired.
You gotta get three stars?
Why would they boo?
Um...
Because I'm going in there with a very strong Pokemon.
The strongest, it's possible.
Alright, we need a day of rest.
Fail?
Oh, no. Fall.
It's like, how did I fail?
Rest.
Who cares if people like you
if you're making cheddar?
Well, that, I mean...
I need money. This is a game about money.
Let's feed you
a potato.
And then let's go kick some ass.
And then after I kick everybody's ass
in this tournament, I'm gonna go pee.
Competition.
Take part in the competition.
The Autumn Festival.
Welcome to the Autumn Festival. Who will arise victorious
that can only be won? Now let the tournament begin.
Clay,
Decker,
and Chara. Look at Chara's icon.
That looks fucking terrifying.
What an extreme emoji.
Alright, let's see.
This is Clay.
I'll kill it in two hits.
You know what? One hit, probably.
This is the equivalent.
You know when you played Little League?
And some of the coaches
and some of the parents?
The age range for Little League was
like 10 to 13 years old.
And there was the people that
wanted to have their like 15-year-old
pretend to be a 12-year-old and be on teams.
And just decimate. It was bullshit.
I don't know why people wanted to do that.
But that's what we're doing right now.
We're faking to be like a 10-year-old
as like a 14-year-old.
Like look, that didn't even hurt.
Come on.
He ain't got nothing on him.
Rumor. I want to end this with like
me killing this creature.
There we go.
No.
I wouldn't do such overkill.
Yeah, there we go. He's fighting infants.
I don't know. I don't understand.
He's batting 6.88.
He has 48
home runs.
He reaches base almost
8 out of 10 times he's at the plate.
He's like 5 feet tall
than everybody.
I wanted to see
that face though.
Chara looks really interesting.
This is Decker. Decker is actually pretty strong.
This is a scenario where whoever
gets the first two hits is going to win.
159 power.
Well, shit, that's not good.
We have the same build.
Both bad defense, no intelligence though.
Decker looks like
a child's drawing
of a ninja turtle.
This is Michelangelo.
Alright, no more fucking around. I actually have to focus here.
Whoever gets the first hit
is going to get it. Bingo.
Nice. Alright, again. Quick.
Go, go, go, go. No, no, no, no.
That's not good. Alright, I gotta kill
him here. He's gotta die here.
Oh, this is bad. Back it up.
Back it up. Do it.
No. No.
Please. I win.
We both have the philosophy of
try to kill people in one hit
or two hits or you lose.
Alright, we got three under our belt now.
Time for an official championship.
I thought we should go to town and buy some stuff.
Oh, Jesus. KDK.
KDKD.
945. 20 community subs.
20.
Thank you, KDK.
For the insane amount of subs.
Call me KD.
Alright, KD. Well, it's KDKD.
It's KDK.
But thank you, KD. I'll call you KD
from now on.
Really? Dermal lied about
Minecraft VR. 21
community subs. 21?
Not necessary, but thank you.
That's a
sub war. Alright.
That's a fucking shitload of money. Thank you, guys.
My god.
Alright, I gotta pee.
I'll be back in like a minute or two.
Gonna refill my cup here.
Take a piss.
See you in two minutes.
Hello. Ooh.
You guys have had this music on the whole time, huh?
Oh, yeah. I don't know what's going on with the internet.
I don't know.
Are we still good?
This is bad.
Hold on one second.
Give me a second.
Well, I don't know what's going on with the internet, but
apparently, I've got like a bright red bar right now.
Strangely enough.
More subs came in?
Goodness, thank you.
KD for the 20 more community subs.
Before that, too.
The ball of koala.
Was this 20?
Holy shit, guys.
This is like really fucked up right now.
I'm dropping like
so many frames at the moment.
Is it okay now?
I think it's alright now.
Might be one of those days, apparently.
For some reason.
That's like 200 fucking subs today.
150, something like that.
For community subs.
Ball of koala, KD.
Thank you both.
Let's keep going.
Our wheel skunk.
I don't even know what the hell this thing is.
Alright, so today's the day, right?
No, no, no. Today's not the day.
Today we have a calendar.
Here we go.
This is the one I'm signing up for.
Six battles.
Sign up for it. I want to be prepared for this.
So we got
a couple here.
We have one, two, three, four.
We've got about four or five weeks.
Let's rest up.
And get to D rank.
Hopefully we get there.
So let's start with
no, no, no. What's the schedule?
High jump, yeah.
High jump, high jump, rest.
And then we're going to do exercise.
That sounds good.
Tournament's here.
Let's rest
here.
Work your
ass off for a couple days.
And then rest on the day of the tournament.
Alright, I think that's a good schedule.
Begin.
Plus ten speed, that's really good.
Let me see here.
Have a potato.
Twenty more community subs
from KD.
KD, what on earth?
Twenty more.
A hundred and fifteen total.
Holy shit, dude.
That's a ton. Thank you so much
for the twenty more fucking community subs.
Holy shit.
I hate this
monster for no reason. Why?
Why do you hate this one?
I like this one.
I mean, it is kind of big on the screen,
but still.
You don't like
Smoochy from Death to Smoochy?
That's what it looks like.
Alright, looks good. Let's go.
Ten more speed.
He's very good with speed.
He's very, very
attentive to how fast he can go.
I mean, he does have a wheel, so that makes sense.
Alright, you can rest.
That's a boomer reference?
That's not a boomer reference.
How is that a boomer reference?
It's like
a Danny DeVito movie.
I love Danny DeVito. He's still relevant.
Alright, rest, right?
No, rest here.
Sounds pretty good.
I'm ready. Go to sleep.
You skitch.
You just did the sloppy joke thing.
I love that lady. That's my favorite
character probably ever.
I know you skitch. Like a
sloppy.
Hey lady, you're scaring us. Billy Madison?
Come on.
The lady. The lunch lady
from Billy Madison.
Wow, I
am old apparently.
Alright, what do you need? Nothing?
No, you don't need food. You're good.
Somebody just said it took me
twenty days to finish
the Seaman book.
Why? Is that because
you didn't like it?
Were you forcing yourself
to watch it?
Keeping up the good work.
This guy just brings food.
Last game you had to buy food. I have a
surplus of food. This guy just keeps
bringing the same recipes every day.
Or every month. Or every like couple months.
I don't even know. Every season?
Twenty days. Alright, we got two trains
and then a rest. Or should I try to get
power to level ten?
Just go absolute fucking hammer.
What do you think?
Hmm. I think we're going to do
power again.
Yeah, I want to get to
level ten.
Rest, and then that's the official
tournament. Come on, level ten power.
Give me a new move. Yes!
New move. Give me a new move.
How do you learn new moves in this game?
Yeah, no big deal. Just another
twenty community subs from Katie.
Again. Twenty more.
Holy shit, man.
Twenty more.
Let's give him some food.
I can't. I can do it tomorrow.
Katie must have robbed a bank.
This game looks like Sekiro, but
good.
This game looks like Sekiro.
Five more from Katie.
Five more community subs
to top it all off.
Holy shit. Thank you, Katie.
His bank is going to
block his card.
Bill Gates.
Some of you guys
have given
like extreme amounts
of money. How about some beef? Yeah!
Before the tournament,
let's carb up. He didn't like that.
It's because he's a vegan.
Well, he's focused now. He's just having a rest.
He's fine. Yeah, he's ready to go, right?
Let's make sure.
Yeah. No, he's ready.
Let's go. First official
tournament. Six rivals.
A thousand dollars
for an item.
Official Grady. Let's move out of Grady.
Ten more subs from Jeremiah
about Minecraft VR. You guys
are just playing like sub-asteroids
right now with each other.
Thank you, both of you. The official
grade rank E tournament. The winner of this
tournament will receive a voucher for rank D.
Let's give it our best.
Begin the official grade rank E.
There we go.
Vroomer, Harris, Schmolet,
Judith, Lefort,
and Sunny.
This is against Sunny.
Low intelligence, low accuracy.
Really high power and high
health. What about me?
I've got really high power,
really kind of low
health. That's going to be the downfall
for me, I think. I've got to start to level that up.
And intelligence.
Alright.
What do you go for moves? High
power, so that means you want to be getting in.
Alright, he's got
a lot of moves. This is
going to be tough. Let's see if I can get a couple
of hits on him.
Okay.
You're dead. Your spine
is going to shatter. Why did I come up with
a pirate ship? Oh no, it's a
Sonic. It's Sunny the
Sonic dog.
This is some rivalry here.
Here we go. Start it off
quick.
Nice. Let me see if I can finish it with the
backspin.
Try it again.
Not good. Get in close.
Yes.
Final Guts.
What the fuck does that mean? What?
Oh, not good.
Thank god, he revived and I still got him.
Final Guts.
That's some weird technique.
He's going to be hard. Come back with one
health. Harris versus Lefort.
Lefort just beat
Harris. 0-1.
These two. Judith and Smollett.
Pretty one-sided
fight there. Lefort and
Judith. Me, Lefort and Judith are the only
ones that have wins.
That just went to
time, I think. Sunny wins.
Here we go. So now
we get to see one of these weirdos.
Rumor versus Lefort.
Wrong thing.
That's a ton of intelligence.
I have to avoid all those int moves.
Jerma lied about Minecraft VR just gave
15 community subs. 10 and then 5.
More.
15 more subs.
Just dropping them everywhere.
You're just driving by in a blimp.
The two years, the three years
tonight. Or just slowly going by
in a blimp and throwing out like
ten dollar bills over like a crowd.
But then
I come in with a vacuum
and I
have a giant fucking Dr. Eggman
vacuum that I suck up all the money
and I stand at a podium and go
but here are emotes!
And everyone's like fucking screaming at me. That was
my fucking money!
Adventure Dan. Thank you Adventure MF Dan.
Stop taking
their money. This guy's
gonna kill us. I need to be
aware of this intelligent move.
The green moves try to stay away from me.
Thank you so much Adventure Dan.
Where's my fucking money, Dan?
Put on facecam?
Dude, I wish
we had one of these
like pumpkin ducks. What is this?
That's the weirdest thing
I've ever seen. Alright, intelligent
move is not on the list right now.
Let's see if we can get it.
Do it again. Not even a chance.
No, he blocked it with his
body. I'm gonna take a
hit here. Not just staying close.
He doesn't have a move close.
Goodbye.
Go back to Cuphead. Imagine
gifting subs in 2019.
Laughing my ass off. What?
I think Sunny's gonna be the one we have to fight
in the championship here.
It's all about the power. Alright, Judith.
What do you got?
An exceptionally
high intelligence.
To a point where I would probably get one shot
by any of the inf moves. What do you have
for intelligence moves though, that's the question.
Almost everything.
So,
all those green moves
are devastating to me. I have
to try to keep in the range of Windy Lance,
whatever it is.
Chunky Baloney, 50 bucks from
Chunky Baloney. Thank you for the 5,000
bits. Chunky Baloney.
I tried to donate this money to the local
animal shelter, but your vacuum sucked it up.
My, like, money vacuum.
Get in close.
Everything she has is an intelligence. I gotta just try to end this
quick. No, this is bad.
All the way in the back.
She's got nothing, she's got no long range moves.
I only have a 27%
chance to hit with this. Holy shit, I got it.
This is just a Hail Mary right here, I have to do it.
Stay far away,
stay still, let me build up some guts.
Do it.
No! Alright,
get back in close, back in close.
In close again. Back it up, back it up, back it up.
I will do a war here.
No!
Get in close.
All it takes is one move.
No, shit!
Oh, I'm 18 seconds.
Oh, please.
Stay back, stay back.
Get in close.
Five, four,
three, two,
whoa! I win.
Wait, it's percentage based, right?
Yes.
Don't waste guts? Yeah, I just,
I saw the, I saw the
opportunity. 20 more subs
from Katie.
Oh my god.
Jesus Christ.
That's so many. I'm trying to have
everybody be a sub on the whole channel.
But thanks
Katie, that's a fucking extreme
amount of money. These
are the two, what's going to happen
here? Let's see, Ford's going to win.
Six hundred dollars.
That's a fucking ton of money.
We've seen some huge
sub and bit drops
on this channel and I can't fucking believe it every
time. Thank you guys.
Harris versus Judith.
Now who's the, Sunny
Okay, let's see. If Sunny wins this fight
then
they're going to be the championship fighter.
And they just barely did.
Alright, so it's going to come down
to, I just can't lose. Smollett
has not won a single match.
This is going to be probably fairly easy.
I don't know why though,
look at this. These stats are actually
really good except for power.
Muahaha is one of their moves that's deadly.
Why would you lose every fight?
It's just the power?
That's not good at all.
Smollett. It's just a rabbit.
See if I can one shot.
Whoa.
Okay.
Guts down
and I'll just do it back to back here.
High speed.
So it would be really easy to
only have 35% chance to win here.
Oh yeah,
you're terrible.
You're awful.
23 damage.
My defense isn't even that good.
Alright, LeFort, beat him.
Let's see.
Smollett just
destroyed Harris. That means Harris
is, I guess they both
pretty bad so it doesn't matter.
Close.
Alright, Harris. This is a guaranteed
championship if I win.
No it's not. If Sonny wins his
next match. No, I mean it pretty much is.
Let's see what we got.
Nothing really spectacular.
Welcome to Germacraft.
Why Germacraft?
I like those little Loch Ness
monsters. I want one of these.
Okay, we got
50% chance to hit here.
Uh oh.
That was embarrassing.
Didn't even do anything.
I feel bad. Can I buy
Harris from this trainer?
I feel like I would take better care of Harris.
The winner is
the winner is Vroomer
moving on to Class D.
He's trying his best. Yeah.
Thousand gold. Prize carrot.
More fame. Vroomer is now
climbing the ranks. New monster?
You can train up to four in your
ranch. I think I might have to unlock
that though. You won the official
competition. Well, I guess
my work is done. Well you
done? What do you mean, Yuri?
Well, my father wants me to come back
and work at the store. I
decided I would quit if you won the competition.
That doesn't make any sense.
Sorry I didn't tell you before.
I wanted to beat TT before
I quit. It's been a lot of fun really.
I see. But wait, you mean I have to
take care of the ranch by myself?
Hee hee. Don't you worry, partner.
I've got my replacement lined up and she's
here. There you go.
Don't be shy. Come on out now.
Hi. Er. Hello.
Huh? Is that you, Rio?
Yup. Doesn't she
look different? I was amazed too.
What do you mean different? She has her hair in a ponytail.
Really?
I figured it would be easier to work with
this outfit. Does it look alright?
What's the difference? Of course
it looks great. So check this
out. When I told Caesar I'd be moving
on from my assistant position,
Rio said she wanted to take over.
Gosh. I was totally
surprised. Wow, really?
So it's okay then, right?
You be a good girl, Rio.
I always wanted to
raise monsters on a ranch.
When I heard about Yuri,
I thought this is my
chance. This is my chance?
Well, you said it. This is our chance.
Yup. Our chance.
What a good boy. Who's a good boy?
Who's a good boy?
Who's a good boy? Yes, you are.
Uh, let's save the
game before I have a panic
attack meltdown when it doesn't
happen and the game crashes or something.
Please end this stream forever. Why?
End it.
Okay, so how...
Let's go to the shrine. Can I...
I want to... Let's get a new monster.
Let's do it. Everything going well.
What will it be? Create.
You already have a
monster you are raising.
What will it be?
Yeah, how do... Somebody said I could...
One guy told me that
I could do four. Do I need to...
I might have to get to a certain rank?
I need to unlock the bigger ranch.
Alright, well then, rumor's going to take us to the top and then from there
we're going to get more.
This is the next, like, six to
ten weeks worth of streams, guys, so...
Alright, let me take a look at
what we need to work on here.
Power's good.
Accuracy could use some work.
Everything... Intelligence could use some work.
But I want 200
attack power. I want more accuracy. He's...
I don't like the 50% bullshit.
I don't know a lot about Minecraft VR.
Ten community...
more community subs.
Back to back they keep coming back and forth here.
Thank you.
I haven't trained any life at all either.
I know. It's true.
It's too much to think about.
Let's get a good schedule here then.
Alright, I want...
Let's do...
I'm going to do
accuracy and life.
Back and forth here.
Day of rest.
Let's see how we go from there.
Accuracy.
Not good, but not great.
I'm going to scold. I mean,
we've been very, very, very...
Focus is not that great either.
Yeah, I know.
Look, we've been very, very
nice.
We've praised every time.
Don't want the monster to get
to a point where they're, you know,
getting lazy or anything.
Hello there.
Hello Yuri. What brings you here?
Well, actually, there's somebody I want to introduce.
To you. He's right over here.
Hello.
My name is Todd. I'm a monster
venerarian.
I'm traveling around
checking the health of monsters.
Oh, nice to meet you.
Todd came all the way from the
faraway island of age.
He's traveling the world for the sake of
monsters everywhere.
All around the world, that's incredible.
Please, it's not that big of a deal.
Oops, I'm sorry. I interrupted your monster caretaking.
No, it's no problem at all.
But then I'll be heading to the other
ranches. Goodbye, bye.
If you're ever in the neighborhood, I can't help you.
If you're ever in the neighborhood, I can't
please feel free to stop by.
Okay, goodbye. What a nice person.
I can sense his love for monsters.
So there are other people in the world like
Fane, aren't there? I gotta get out of here.
I gotta go.
This ranch is just like I expected it would be.
Hello, anybody home?
Yeah, I'm the
breeder at this ranch. Who are you?
Excuse me, I'm Pollock. I'm a training
gadget peddler. Training
gadget? I saw your battle
in the competition the other day. I guess you're
not using training gadgets. I could tell.
Wait, just a minute here.
What the heck is a training gadget?
Oh, sorry. There's a fucking fifty
community subs just came in. Somebody
just blasted out like
a thousand dollars.
Hold on one minute.
KD just gave fifty community subs.
Fifty community
subs. Oh my god.
How many have you
given tonight? Let me see.
Quick math.
Holy shit, man. One guy
aims to gift all.
Thank you. For the
fucking, I don't even
that's a lot.
Vacuum is overloaded. I gotta, I have to like
empty the vacuum. Thank you
so much, man. Oh, sorry, Charlie.
I'll stop there.
Training gadgets? Oh, well
gadgets that you use for training.
In other words, they're machines that
boost effective training. Everybody
uses them. And you, my friend,
have great potential. Why don't you try
using the training gadget on your ranch?
You'll soon be seeing even better results.
Well, I'll come again later. Bye.
Hmm. Using machines
for training. What do you think, Rio?
I'm gonna change
it to this. Training gadgets
run off Geonite.
Geonite is an energy of the earth found in
spirit trees. Eddie?
It's found in spirit trees, Eddie.
So you mean gadgets
use energy from
Makroji, Eddie?
Don't worry, I'm old enough to have saved a plenty
of extra Geonite.
Makroji, don't over-exert yourself.
It's decided then.
Let's try using training gadgets
on our ranch.
Quick refund to all the gift subs.
Well,
hello. Wrong guy.
Well, hello.
They're doing well? Have you decided?
I can't, there's only so many anime fucking
dub voices I know. I don't know any others.
I know like four.
Have you decided to try using
training gadgets? I feel like I'm
stuck in a time portal.
Just give it to me.
You really ought to give them a try. Feel free to take a look at them.
What will you do?
I don't know what these are.
Pinman just gave ten community subs.
Thank you Pinman for ten community subs.
By training
effect?
You don't have any appraised training gadgets.
But thank you so much Pinman.
What will you do? By training.
What will you buy?
Oh, look at this.
Look at this.
Two thousand gold. Strength training.
Get level two. Space one by two.
Ooh.
Alright, alright.
Okay.
I'm thinking, uh, how much
do they cost?
They're like two thousand each. I got thirteen thousand?
Dude, Ruby the dog.
I'll try to do Ruby the dog.
No.
No Ruby.
It's me, Ruby.
Got it.
I'm gonna go, I want
this one.
Buy this. Yes.
Thank you very much.
Customize immediately. Uh, sure.
Oh, I have to place it.
Wait, what?
Poor house,
poor hut.
Oh, my God.
This is huge.
Um.
Poor streamer.
Not tonight.
Alright, then.
Alright, we're gonna use that.
Anything else to buy?
Um, yeah.
You guys are out of your minds.
Studley Do-Right gave twenty
community subs.
Holy shit, guys.
I'm spoiled rotten.
Uh, what about speed trampoline?
Is one by one?
I can do that, right?
No, it's not. I can't. Can I?
But thank you so much.
I'm buying the speed one.
I think I can fit this.
It's one by one, right?
Yeah. Trampoline?
Any more one by ones?
This is one by two.
One by two.
Two by three. One by one.
One by two. No.
Alright, what else you got?
Sell?
What will you sell? Can I sell my house?
Uh, Adventure MFDan
five more subs.
Five more subs.
From MFDan.
Money laundering stream.
Holy shit.
Alright, so now.
Let's see. That was speed and
accuracy.
Let's go to the schedule.
This is speed and accuracy, right?
Yeah. Shadow box is accuracy
and balance is speed.
I believe.
No. Oh, look at this!
Target.
Very cool.
Target and then
Trampoline.
Target, trampoline, rest, trampoline.
Got it.
I'm excited for this one.
We actually get to see them do a different animation.
Nice.
So you have to build up your ranch and they can
use... This is cool.
Nice work. Alright, you're very tired though
and very hungry.
Uh, food. Let's give you some...
Let's give you a mango.
I love mangoes.
Frustrated? Well, you'll be fine.
Vroomer is cute. Vroomer seems to be
a little worried about something.
Hmm, I wonder what's wrong. Oh,
Caesar!
In the hut, things might get exciting around here.
It should be fun.
But with more monsters,
you may have to expand the ranch itself.
How about this? I'll ask a carpenter
friend of mine. He should be able
to get working on something right away.
Carpenter?
But we don't...
We don't have any money.
Oh boy, could you stop acting like a stranger?
I know this will put a smile
on your face and to me that's worth more
than anything in the world.
Father, thank you.
Well, then it's settled. Leave the rest to me.
Ciao.
That's good.
So now we get to make more monsters.
Dude, what an
epic November fail.
Hello there, partner. Is Fane home?
Fane, it's me. But who are you?
Me? I don't know the name to you.
I'm the carpenter that Caesar hired.
You're the carpenter?
You betcha I am.
No, don't you worry about a thing. Leave it all to
you. To leave it to me?
No, you.
What?
Okay, we's got us a ranch, a hut
and a rickety house.
Okay, we'll have you a brand new ranch in one week.
What? Er, thanks.
In one week we have a new ranch.
Oh, I'm so fucking
excited now. Alright.
Frustrated.
Maybe you should jump on a trampoline.
Plus 10
every time you do that. 60% success rate.
Alright, what's your favorite food?
You don't have to do that with
the tire. You can do it
somewhere else. Alright,
let's give you...
What do I have? I have no items to give.
You're doing a great job.
Does the wheel feel pain?
I don't know.
I mean, the wheel is part of him.
Alright, good job,
Brumer. Take the week off.
Alrighty, boys, that'll do it.
Well, what do you think?
Gives you a lot of space, huh?
Wow, you, you're just
my age. But you direct all those
adults around like a true leader.
Yeah, so cool.
Oh, give me a break. I'm just doing
my job. Now three
monsters can live in the hut and you can
store more gadgets in the house.
So where would you like to
put the house and hut? I'll place it wherever you like.
Look at this real estate.
Just fucking so big.
Alright, this is what we need.
Normal house.
Up here.
And then a normal hut.
You can spin it around too.
Um...
I like it right here.
Okay, that means I got some more room
here. Yeah, I don't want the
house right next to the barn, you know what I mean? It'll smell.
You can range friends
for Brumer. No problem at all,
buddy. If you outgrow this hut, give me a
haul at any time. The next time I
charge the regular fucking raid dude.
See you later.
I don't know what I'm doing.
I'm being completely honest here. Alright, let's go.
So, let's go get some friends.
What's the next disk that's going in?
Well, hello, everything going well.
What will it be?
Which method would you use?
I'm going to use a saucer.
Generate a monster from a saucer.
Even more.
Even more community subs.
Alright, so I'm thinking
either Floydgan Brothers or Seventh Cross
Evolution. Cause Seventh Cross
Evolution was a game
about evolving monsters.
Wait, Floydgan? You want me to get Floydgan in there?
Alright, okay. Alright, alright.
I'll do it. Here it is.
Why is this hot?
This disk is hot. It wasn't even, I don't know why.
The window? Maybe, yeah. The sun is like
shining on it. It's going to like melt this thing.
Alright, here you go. I always have to
prove that it's actually happening, so.
Here. Let me look at my
hair too. People were talking about my hair.
Yeah, it is a little fucking weird, isn't it?
Here you go. Floydgan.
For the Dreamcast. Power Stone.
I'll do Power Stone. Just not right this second.
Your hair looks very nice.
Floydgan Brothers going in.
Give us something good.
Give us like a team, a duo.
What if you put in the other Monster Rancher disk?
They all kind of have something crazy come out, don't they?
We had more community subs
from Lunch Meat.
How many hundreds of community subs?
The ending credits are going to be crazy tonight.
Thank you guys. Alright, here comes Floydgan Brothers.
See what we get. I hope
it's a monster with two heads.
I hope it looks like me.
The count is three hundred and forty.
Three hundred and forty community subs.
Thanks for waiting. Time to create
a monster. Alright, does it get
put in the trash or does it come to the ranch?
This is a Cheeto
flavored vroomer. I see
it's the first time Fane has raised this
monster. Let me add a page to your book.
Take this monster. Alright, am I
putting like the Cheeto
vroomer? Am I throwing the Cheeto vroomer away?
I'm not having two
vroomers.
Destroy. They're brothers.
It's the Floydgan Brothers.
Trash. Trash. Trash. Trash. Garbage.
Garbage. I need a pole. I'm seeing too much
of this. It's just
vroomer without any skin.
I don't want
whatever. Alright.
Trash or no. Trash it.
Keep it. There you go.
New pole.
Wow, this is
80 percent.
Oh, nobody
wants this.
That's unbelievable. This might be the most skewed
pole I think I've ever done in here.
80 percent. I don't think I could
even let this go on. Yeah, that's
it. Take this monster home. No.
I'm sorry.
Try a different saucer stone.
Sorry Floydgan.
The one up next is, we're going to put in
Tony Hawk 2.
See what we get with Tony Hawk. So you see
let me show it off. Let me show off
the disc. Tony Hawk's
Pro Skater 2. There it is.
In all of its glory. Original Dreamcast
video game.
Third vroomer.
We'll see. Here we go. Somebody on
a skateboard.
Oh my goodness.
Did you buy CDs just for the game?
No, I have all original hardware.
One of my taglines as a streamer
is like, German95
what's that channel like?
He's an original hardware streamer.
It's a game for myself.
Real Dreamcast. Real PlayStation 1.
Real hardware.
I actually got Tony Hawk over here
to like skateboard in front of me.
Real hardware only. Tony Hawk Pro Skater 2
for the Dreamcast. Let's see what happens.
A lot of Dreamcast games, yeah. We just did a bunch of them.
Thanks for waiting. Time to create.
I have like the
Karilla's latest album here too.
Uh, what a cute
monster. I see it's the first
time Vayne has raised this monster.
Let me add a page to your book.
Uh, are we taking the little mushroom home?
It's
Vinesauce.
Alright, we'll keep it.
We'll keep it.
It looks like a magician. I'm gonna keep it.
You're naming this monster.
Name it Vinny.
I don't know
if I want to name it Vinny because eventually if I
freeze it and kill it, that's not
I don't know if I'm gonna like that.
Alright, what if we do
a, a, okay, how about
how about
hashtag V?
Shroom
hashtag V
is so bad.
Let's just go with Shroomer.
Because that's pretty good. Hashtag V is the worst
name I've ever made up.
Shroomer.
Look after it. Try a different saucer
stone. Uh, yeah.
So I have two more, right? Or one more.
Alright,
this next one cannot end in an oomer.
Alright, what am I gonna do here? Alright, here's what I'm gonna put in.
I'm gonna put in
I'm gonna put in this.
This game is called
for the PC
or I don't know, I couldn't get it. Yeah,
Windows 95. I couldn't get this to fucking work
no matter what I did. This is
Jurassic Park Scan
Command. It's got a, you know, T-Rex
on it and everything.
This, I was gonna do a whole stream on this.
You have like a barcode scanner
and you scan it, but
there's a, didn't, I couldn't,
you know, just didn't work.
Scan Command.
Let's see what we get for Scan Command
for Jurassic Park. Why is your hair doing that?
I don't know.
I have a naturally fucked up head. I'm serious.
If I shave my head and you like put your hand
over it, it's like a little bumpy and like rocky
and shit. Opening the tray.
Let's see what Jurassic Park Scan
Command has in store.
Oh no, that was, that's Tony Hawk.
I wish I'd put Tony Hawk back in.
Alright, bring it on.
Five more community subs from GermanLight
about Minecraft VR. Five more.
Five, five, five, five, five. Coming in
every, every five minutes
with five community subs or ten community subs.
So many. Thank you.
I hope it's a dinosaur. Alright,
no rumor.
Okay, I kind of like it.
It looks like,
it looks like something that you could eat
on the set of Willy Wonka.
I'm keeping it. No, I'm not.
Ugh.
I only have three slots.
Too many mushrooms.
Trash it.
Too many, I'm not, no too much. We got two
mushrooms in a wheel. No.
Alright, the next thing going in, let me ask you,
okay, I don't know why I have this.
I don't even know if I did this before.
Um, some people are going to know what
this is. This is from
MTV Liquid Television.
This is a DVD
set of the show
The Head. Does anybody remember
this show? It was the Liquid Television
MTV Audities.
I got all of them. I have the whole show.
I, I don't know like why I have this.
I think I bought this at like a
convention or something. And I was like,
oh, MTV, the Liquid Audities.
I haven't even opened this. I like took
the skin off of it for some reason.
Why, and I don't know why I brought this across
the country. I donated
a ton of my old games
and I gave a bunch of my old stuff away, but
The Head came with me
for some reason. I haven't even
watched it. For some reason I thought it was going to be
worth money. It was dumb.
I don't know. My parents didn't let me
watch MTV. MTV
was pretty fucked up back then.
The cartoons on MTV were
like Nickelodeon 4.0
with like the grossness. Puke, like
farts, throw up, acid.
You know what I mean? Like there was all kinds of weird shit
on MTV back like in the 90s.
Nickelodeon had like farts and
puke and throw up and stuff, but
not like that, like the
Beavis and Butthead era on MTV.
Alright. Wait, did I put the
I didn't put the same disc in, right?
Why? I swear
to God. No,
I put this in.
It's the same monster.
Did it glitch out and save it?
Alright, we're doing the Head disc 2.
How do these have the same seed?
Disc 2 of the Head is
I'm not accepting that.
Didn't bring his PS4, but brought
the Head. Alright, but a
PS4 is big and bulky and has to go
in a box and shit. The Head is just a
DVD case. Alright.
Insert the Monster Rancher 4 disc.
This is the Head disc 2.
What about your Bloodborne save?
It's okay. Alright, give me something
else that's not a shroom.
He threw away his PS4? Oh no, I gave it
away. I gave my PS4.
Alright.
That was the
Head disc 1 disc 2 and
what was the one before it?
Scan command?
No, I'm not going to name it another
Umer. I told you. I told you
that's the thing on like you could eat in Willy Wonka.
I'm not naming him Tumer.
Or Umer. Or like
Doomer.
No, we have Boomer, Shroomer,
and Wonka. Let me see the
stats. How do I get a different
another go? Okay, there's Shroomer,
Vroomer, and
Wonka.
This company doesn't even exist anymore.
They liquidated it. Look at that.
That's pretty awesome actually. Alright.
Shroomer.
High defense. Look at that.
He's doing the Peepo dance.
Wonka sucks.
Not really. That's a lot. That's really high health.
And the base intelligence
is really good.
What does he do?
Alright, we've got
pecking.
Slap. Accuracy
rate is pretty
high. This is the one right here. Pollen. This is a
poison. So unfortunately,
this is a dot. It's the only move
that doesn't do damage.
And even so,
it doesn't do very much damage. It's
D for damage. This is A for accuracy.
Yeah, he's terrible.
Ice him. Shroomer is
alright. High defense.
High base defense. Let's see what you
get from moves. Let's see if he's, you know,
So it's all about intelligence.
And power a little bit.
Let's see. This is
Pokorin.
It's a short range move. And then
aim hit.
Accuracy is an A.
Life damage is an E.
D.
He's kind of terrible.
The accuracy is alright.
But look at that life to E for life
damage.
We'll work on Shroomer. I feel like Shroomer will be
okay later.
He has lightning element
statuses.
Soft body.
Softens damage from punch or
stab attacks.
And is spoiled rotten already.
Doesn't like to fight.
Is already spoiled.
You are really on thin ice and I really mean
that literally because you're going to get fucking
frozen in about 10 seconds.
I hate this thing.
I think it might be, I think we're going to freeze.
Both.
Alright.
How do I, what does it do?
It's not a praise. No. How do I do it?
Association.
Fuse him. I'll fuse him. I'll fuse him. I'll fuse him.
I'll fuse him. I'll fuse him. I'll fuse him.
Wonka and Shroomer are going to get fused.
Don't you need a certain item?
Alright. Retire.
Or can I combine them right now?
They have to be frozen.
Look at Mao's power.
100 base power? Why did we throw that one in the trash?
Alright. Retire.
Shroomer.
Freeze Shroomer.
Sorry, but that's the end of you.
Retire.
Wonka.
This feels unfair because Rumer's stats are terrible
in comparison to all, whatever.
Now.
Combine. Let's combine.
We got Shroomer.
Combine.
Shroomer and...
What is...
Is that what they were
combined with in the first place?
Shroomer and Wonka.
Mao's and Shroomer.
We're going to get
a Shroomer dog.
Not even a day
old.
Not even one day
old. Both of them.
Shroomer and
Wonka.
Does it cost any money?
Petrin or Mushtan?
Unless you
actually select it now.
195...
145?
What the fuck?
What on
earth just happened?
An anonymous gifter
has just given a hundred community
subs. Anonymous gifter.
I don't know who you are,
but that's a lot.
That's a lot.
Whoever you are. Thank you
for the hundred subs.
Jesus. That's insane.
Thank you. Whoever you are.
Uh, I feel like both these
are terrible. Let me try...
That was so...
That was fucking crazy. Thank you.
What about Mao's and
Shroomer?
Kairotopia 5 community subs.
Oh my god.
That one sucks too.
Yeah, the subs are still rolling in.
My god.
What about Mao's and Wonka?
No, we're gonna get like
Mushtan.
195 health is kinda good though.
Magic Lore
and Pheromone.
Skills Pecking, Slap, and Pollen.
Nothing is the other one.
This character is terrible.
It's just another dumb shitty mushroom.
Let's go put some more CDs in.
Shroomer has good magic potential
to be combined here.
We, alright, the next few, we gotta
we gotta win some competitions here.
I'm gonna go with
we'll put in
I have humans here.
Oops. What is this? Something just fell out of this.
What CD is this? Whatever it is.
Alright, this is the thing that's going in next.
I don't even care.
The next thing going in is
MLB Show 17.
Okay. Boomers Sports.
Baseball is not a boomers sport.
Really?
Baseball is boomers sport?
Baseball has
been around for a
fucking hundred plus years.
They were playing baseball
back when K and Ben were throwing rocks at each other.
What do you mean exactly?
A baby boomer is
not from like
1880.
Do you guys think that they're still alive?
Yeah, fuck all those boomers
born in 1872.
Boomers are just old people.
A baby boomer didn't
invent baseball.
They did. No, they didn't.
What's after the boomers?
The pilgrims, I think, right?
I don't know.
What was, boomer was like the
30s and the 40s, right?
What was before boomer? Pilgrim?
Super boomers.
Nobody existed before
boomers. What the fuck
is this? Why do I keep getting this?
Something's wrong with my game.
I don't know what's going on.
I have to, I'm going to turn the game off.
And turn it back on. Wait, I have to save it.
Don't do that yet. Alright.
Insert a CD or DVD.
If this is the same thing, then come on.
Something's fucked up here. Alright, here it is.
Here's, here's, here's Gorilla's Humans.
ESPRoot5 Community
Subs. Thank you ESPRoot
Subs. All over the place tonight.
Everywhere. If this is a shroom,
I'm going to reset the game. I'm going to save it and restart.
Maybe it's because these DVDs are too
new? Well, I mean, was Dreamcast
Dreamcast was
they were CDs, right? Not DVDs.
Dreamcast wasn't DVD ROM, was it?
Alright, let's see if we get the same thing.
If it is a shroom, then I'm going to save
a reset. And then we might
somebody said we have to play, I think. More than 60%
of the monsters are held behind A rank
as always. Well, that sucks.
I have to get to A rank. Just get
to A rank. That's all we have to do.
Okay. No shroom.
No mushroom. Something else.
Clam.
This thing is so cool. It's a walnut
fucking. Oh, it's a walnut.
It's like the inside of a walnut.
First time Fane has raised this
monster. Let me add page to your book.
Yes, I'm taking it.
WALL-E?
A bell? No, it's a walnut.
WALL-E. I like
WALL-E.
Nut, nut. Nut, nut
man. Why would nut man?
WALL-E.
It's not nut
man. It's
WALL-E.
Okay, look. You can call
them nut man if you want.
It's not. It's a
WALL-E. WALL-E.
WALL-E the walnut.
WALL-NUT
WALL-BURG.
Let's get another one. Alright, so our game is not broken.
We just got unlucky.
Let's go with one more.
Uh oh. Oh shit. This is just
this is the Monster Rancher 4 disc.
It didn't get, I pressed the button too early.
Uh, no.
Okay. Hey, at least they knew.
So what's going on now?
What do I got right here? I could put
Mr. Mosquito. PlayStation 2.
Urban Chaos. PlayStation. Let's do
Mr. Mosquito. Maybe we'll get a
Mosquito monster. Please stop playing
this game. What are you talking about?
This game is so much fun. It's so much
fun just to like just hang out and make fucking
monsters from discs. Alright, Mr.
Mosquito going in. Put in Monster
Rancher 3. I don't own it anymore. That's one of the things
I didn't bring because I hated
that game. I thought it was terrible.
This is a little different
but it's still, it's still
I'm getting enjoyment from it. I didn't like 3 at all.
3 was weird. 3 did this thing where you had to
like walk around and do
select like shiny things on the
ground to train. I didn't like
it. This reminds me more of 2
than 3.
Does of 2. What? Whatever.
So this is Mr.
Mosquito. I think a bug just came out of
that. No. Just, just packing
peanut. You didn't show us.
Oh fuck. Oh well. Could have been anything.
I could be lying to you right now. I could be just
making that whole thing up. Here, look
I'll show you the disc. I'll show you. Just so you know
this thing was expensive too guys.
This was no, I gotta be careful
with this one. This was expensive.
Mr. Mosquito
from Eidos Interactive.
This was fucking, it was like 40
bucks. Let's go!
Break it in half. Okay fine, sure dude.
Fuck! Alright, yeah
excuse me. I'll take the fucking
Bear Swordsman. Holy
shit. I'll take the Power Ranger.
Yep. Robo Bear
Swordsman.
That's BB
This thing's cool. I'm gonna forget about
the other 2 characters. I don't care. Robo
BBs.
Robo Boomer. No.
This is not gonna be Robo Boomer.
Uh, how about
Robo Boomer.
Ugh, this is tough.
Slash. No. Uh
Bean Bag Boomer.
Oh that's a, that's a really good one.
I'll use that one. That's a good one. Dick Fart.
Yeah, sure.
That's a really good one. I'll do it.
This is a Dark Souls character?
Oh, you're getting invaded by, what's his name?
It's a bunch of asterisks.
Who's this? Invaded by Dick Fart
222222222223.
What's a, okay, what's like a
thrust or
the Hibernator.
Hibernator.
That's a little bit of Robo theme in a bear.
What, no it is a bear. Bear's Hibernator.
Why would I have to have bear in there?
Hibernator.
Hyperba, Hyperbator.
Master.
Hyper, Hyperbator.
I, okay.
Hyperbator.
Why would I do that? You guys, what's,
you guys usually are pretty good.
I can't fit that.
I can, I can only have like
seven letters, guys.
Uhhhhh.
I gotta get out of here.
Robare?
Roberto?
Roberto.
This thing's awesome.
What would it be? Back to the ranch, let's see.
This is gonna probably have, probably have
such ridiculous
stats. So I've got
Wally, Vroomer, and
Roberto.
Uhhhhh.
Actually not terrible base stats.
High defense, decent
power. It's all about power.
Okay, what do you got? You got
kick and charge.
Where's slash? You have a
sword in your hand.
Um, hold on a second, but guys
this is life damage B.
That's a lot of damage.
What's that? What is it? 22 guts?
That's not very much at all. This thing
actually could be pretty good.
Alright, what about your stats? Your uh,
golden foot.
Increases the power of moves that
use the feet. But you
have a sword in your hand.
You've got a golden foot.
That doesn't make any sense.
Alright, Wally, what about you?
Holy shit, look at that defense.
That's the best. Pure walnut
defense. And pretty high intelligence
too. This is probably the best character.
Look at the base defense.
Alright, we got some moves here. We got
life damage C.
That's not terrible. Pretty bad accuracy
rate though. What about this one?
This is called Cracker.
Not bad.
It adds addle to whatever that means.
What about you? Hard shell.
Reduces damage but harder to dodge
attacks. Okay.
And what's that element?
I don't know what element is.
Is it a teal? I don't know.
It's a wolf with a katana and you
didn't name him Sekiro. As a bear.
Maybe it is a wolf.
So it is a wolf.
But it's okay.
Just pretend it's a bear. That's a bear.
Alright.
So how do I... This is going to be interesting.
Oh fuck.
So.
Everybody has their own schedule.
Oh dear.
This is going to be micromanagement
of the video game.
So.
Let's see. Let's do
more defense. What do you need?
You need
your highest stat
is defense and intelligence.
Your moves...
The best move that you have
is
a power move.
But you have higher intelligence so this will probably do
more damage. So I'm going to say
increase intelligence. Intelligence
and defense. Intelligence, defense and
life. We'll start with here.
Give you a good schedule
here.
Three in a row.
Okay.
That looks alright.
We need one more here.
One more in
life.
Got two days of rest.
What about
you? So you have...
What's his moves?
He's kind of all over the place.
Power? Does he have any
intelligence moves? No.
It's all about power. So power.
Power, accuracy and life.
I would say. Or speed.
I'm going to do power, life and speed.
Because that defense is already high enough for now.
Power, life, speed.
Is it okay to clear the schedules
to other monsters using this gadget?
Oh, shit.
Okay. They can't do it
at the same time.
Oh, fuck. Okay. So
it's trampoline.
What was it?
Power, life and speed.
You can do the high jump.
We'll do trampoline on this day.
Rest.
Let's give you some life.
And we'll do
power again.
Rest.
And...
trampoline again.
Oh, you motherfucker. Who is doing it to this day?
You are.
You're using the speed.
You're doing fine.
No. What day are you not doing this?
I'm going to switch
these dates here.
Trampoline.
Target.
Okay. Now, you can do
trampoline.
There we go. I think we're ready.
Go for it.
So we had
rumors resting.
Wall-E plus six.
Roberto plus
six. Let's go take a look at what
they're doing. So we're just making a carnival
of monsters.
Good training.
You're doing great.
I don't even remember what the training was for this.
Where's Roberto?
He just took his arm off.
I think they're dumb.
Oh, no. Yay!
I'm having so much fun.
It's gold. No, I can't do that.
You're too cute.
I think this is going to be our
very special boy.
The other two. Who cares?
Well, actually, everybody loves the beanie baby.
I think this guy sucks.
Yeah, I might as well just throw
you into the freezer right now.
But we'll just leave. We'll see what happens.
I can only do one command,
right? Can I do anything else today?
Holy shit.
If that's going to hurt me.
I can do one command per
You are so cool,
but so dumb at the same time.
How are you doing? Are you doing okay?
Here, have some data.
Reason?
No, we're going to take him into tournaments.
Give him a chance, you know?
Alright. Not hungry, not hungry,
not hungry. Weekend activities.
I get three actions per week now. That's actually pretty good.
Uh oh.
Fane, wake up. Something's happened.
Oh, morning reel. What is it?
Somebody die.
Change those pants.
I don't even know what that's implying.
Sorry, just a second. I'll put something on.
Did I go to the bathroom with my pants?
Was I wearing pants?
This one,
this one found this this morning.
Was this giant cave here before?
No, I've never seen it before.
And I feel some strange power.
It seems like it's beckoning us.
Beckoning us? How cool.
Let's take the monsters and investigate.
What a cave doing here.
I'll have to investigate.
Excuse me, but who are you?
Me?
I'm in charge of the investigation of these parts.
Call me Mr. K.
And how about you kids?
Are you in charge of an investigation of this cave too?
Yes, that's why we're here.
Well, that's just splendid.
But you know, I'm a bit worried for you.
Let's take the monsters inside.
I have an idea.
Let the adventurer Mr. K.
tell you the ins and outs of exploring.
Is it going to be a tutorial?
Fuck the voice.
Finish all your preparations by the weekend.
Then meet me in front of the cave this weekend.
Until then.
Tata, he's gone. What a strange old man.
He seems like a nice guy.
And it might be fun to go exploring this weekend.
So this weekend, go exploring.
Who do I want to bring? Can I bring everybody?
What's the schedule?
Speed. Whoa.
Holy shit.
That was a lot.
Vroomer plus 16 speed.
Wally, 6 defense, 8 power for Roberto.
That was a lot.
That was like a critical hit.
Wow.
Good job.
Okay, how are you doing?
Okay, okay. He's kind of hungry.
What do robots eat?
That was pretty bad.
Actually pretty cool. That was awesome.
Yeah.
You get to stick around. That was awesome.
What about you?
Are you hungry?
Not yet.
Continue your training.
Alright, let's see the weekend activity.
Well, the weekend is here and I assume you're fully prepared.
Well then, we're off.
Mr. K., the adventurer, will be your guide on this fabulous expedition.
So is this just
adventure?
I've been raised exploring.
A toggle cave.
A mysterious cave found behind the
ranch one day.
Select monsters to explore with.
Wally? Who should go?
Who's like...
Roberto is the least.
Or maybe Vroomer.
Yeah.
Or if it's dangerous.
High defense maybe?
Let's throw Wally in there.
We can take everybody.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
What the hell is this?
This is turning into an iPad game.
713 energy.
Okay, I guess.
Let's go.
Go exploring with these monsters.
Yeah.
First floor of the toggle caves.
Let's start with the basics.
Left analog stick move.
You can move the camera with the right analog stick.
First try going to the treasure chest ahead of you.
The hell?
When in front of the chest push X to open it.
This is a different game.
What is it?
Received yarn ball.
Well, this yarn ball is yours now.
Keep it safe.
Sometimes chests are hidden when you get near a suspicious location.
The cursor appears.
Suspicious location.
Should I explore around?
I'm running out of time.
The top left is, I think, their total health pool or something.
That's how much energy they have.
Go close to a suspicious spot and look for the cursor.
This is not a suspicious spot.
Alright.
There's a mouse hole over here.
That's it. Now push the X right there.
Except you don't have a monster to search it right now.
How?
Let's move on. We'll search for stray monsters.
What are we talking about?
Can I select a different monster?
You can't fit in there or something? I don't get it.
Command.
Sword.
This is too big.
What about the walnut?
Whatever. Apparently I can't do it again anyways.
We're stray monsters.
Well, I think I just ran into...
Random encounters?
Alright, it's one of the flowers.
Here's the question.
So I have to...
Is this like Marvel vs. Capcom?
Can I pull in other people?
It's kill or be killed.
Experience plus 13.
Level 1.
Interesting.
Win battles to raise experience points.
As you level up, new skills, traits, and items can be obtained.
This is how you get new moves.
If you lose a battle, your experience, skills, and items remain, but you will return to your range fatigued.
Using Quit Exploring on the circle button, set square, is the same.
When you quit exploring, your monster becomes exhausted, and its lifespan is shortened.
What? You mean it won't live as long?
Nope. It's a cruel world.
What an explanation.
See the gauge on the lower left of the screen?
That's the energy gauge, and it lowers over time.
It's essential to exploration.
It lowers each time you move.
And when it reaches zero, your monster's life lowers.
Watch it carefully.
Does energy ever rise?
No, it does not rise.
But while you have energy, the life of the monsters that took damage during battle will gradually recover.
So run too much, and our exploring will be cut short.
Every floor has a staircase to the next floor.
If you make it there, you can return to your range without taking heavy damage, or go to the next floor.
Important choice, I suggest not getting too greedy in this respect.
I guess that's all. The rest is up to you.
Well, do your best.
I kind of don't want to do this.
I'm going to drain their life essence forever.
Something bats?
What about chests?
Nothing? Nothing to investigate? Nothing to look at?
I still have plenty of energy.
This is cool.
Alright, so we get a Mogie E.
R2...
Just...
Okay, L1 brings out another monster.
Alright, let's see what we got.
Timidity.
Alright, I don't want you to lose health, because you're my favorite.
What about the other move? Let's see it.
Team Up!
What does that mean?
Dodge. Dodge again.
Nice.
I want to do the other move, but he can't.
Let's bring in Beartow.
He's a little timid.
Kicks do more damage, right?
There we go.
Nobody did damage.
Fucking decimated.
Cool.
654.
Two paths that we can go down here.
Let's check the one on the left.
Okay, I kind of want a smaller monster out here.
Because you take up almost the whole screen.
Chest.
Obtain Junk Toy.
How are you that big?
Okay, well I got a toy.
Where do you corpse?
Oops.
Oh dear.
Meeklon E.
That's a cool little monster.
It's like a giant beetle.
E for easy, yeah.
They do have different ranks.
Obtained Rose Perfume.
You skipped the dance.
You've seen the dance a million times.
You don't have to see it every single time.
Chest. Good.
I definitely like this more than the last one.
Because this same idea was in the last one.
Because this same idea was in
Monster Rancher 3.
But this feels more fun to do.
Than the other one.
Don't ever skip.
I still have 600 points.
Should I get out of here?
That was like a little tutorial. I don't want to drain them.
Stay here forward.
Or ranch.
Let's go. Second floor.
We have to see the other command here.
We have to see how the other run.
How do you run, Roberto?
You all have a really loud,
annoying sound.
But that's okay.
Can I touch this?
What is it?
Roberto can't help you to investigate.
I know who might.
Not Wally.
Can the rumor jump up there? Like bounce up there?
Rumor can't help you investigate.
Wally can't help you investigate.
Why? Why are you all so stupid?
Whatever.
Maybe they have to be able to fly?
To get up there?
Chest! Playing cards!
That's cool.
Nobody can fit in here.
Can you fit in there? Are you big enough?
Wally can't help you.
Yu-Gi-Oh! Battle cards.
Ant Coro E.
What are they?
I think these are Sesame Street characters.
I want to do this move.
That's a cool move.
It's like a party blaster.
Stop being so timid. Stop!
That's the thorns.
You be in time. Bring in the drift.
It's one of those little party poppers.
As you buy the gas station.
Rumor almost level 2.
Isabel side smash?
Is that what Isabel does?
This is a green chest.
Obtained a life tablet.
What's this? Something strange is inside.
A stone tablet. It seems very old.
The writing seems to explain something.
A blueprint.
You're right. That's really interesting.
But why do I have the feeling that I've seen this before?
Really?
I suppose it's nothing.
Anyway, we found something really neat.
This is enough exploring for now.
Alright.
So the life tablet, I'm gonna assume when you combine it
you can add it and add extra life.
Or you can just consume it and put...
He left before I did.
Rio is just baked.
Hello. I invited myself in.
Guess you're out and about.
Yeah, I guess you could say that.
What's that stone you have there? Let me have a look.
This I found in the cave.
Do you know anything about it?
This design, these joints, looks like a blueprint
for a training gadget.
Wait a minute. Does that mean that people from ages
past use training gadgets too?
If that's the case, then this is a real discovery.
What?
Could I ask you a favor, Fane?
Could I borrow this from you?
I want to try recreating the ancient
training gadget described in these blueprints.
Sure, go right ahead.
Oh, I'll go exploring again and look for more.
Oh, actually, I'll give you the training
gadget as soon as it's done.
A chance to recreate a training gadget with my
very own hands.
Oh, it's just amazing.
I've got to get started right away by then.
Public looks so happy.
We've got to go exploring again.
How's everybody doing? Okay, we've got
more training sessions.
You're a little tired, but well...
Anybody scheduled to sleep right now?
Week one. Exercise,
rest, and trampoline.
Okay. Let's get to it.
Rumor's been
on point with the training recently.
Roberto, I'm going to scald you.
I mean, you didn't even try.
You just, you didn't even try.
Sorry.
He could have killed you.
You did really good, though. He thought about it.
And you're asleep. Good.
Anybody hungry?
Not really. Everything's all right.
Are you hungry?
So you can go
on an adventure. I can do this whenever I want.
That's cool.
Do I have to find a new place?
Probably have to find a new place to do it, right?
I like the snow.
It's nice.
What do we got on schedule now?
We've got exercise,
power, balance,
and you are going to rest.
Yeah, you're frustrated.
Might as well just rest.
Holy shit.
It's time to do some tournaments here.
Look at these stats.
205, 142,
149.
I think it's time.
Let's get some tournaments going here.
Here, have a mango.
Did you like it?
I don't want to be weird here, but
what is on the stomach?
What is that?
It's an ear.
Not yet. Hold on. You're not hungry.
You are very hungry and very tired.
Eat a potato.
Happy? Good.
Now you, on the other hand,
you're doing all right. You're just resting.
God, I can't wait to see you
in some fan fiction
OC somewhere.
Sorry, I meant to say every fan fiction OC.
I have to correct myself here.
All right, I think we can go.
Let me open up the schedule to see.
All right. Next week, let's plan out
some competitions for the three of them.
Calendar.
So, Rumor is able to
join this one. This is just a
snow cup. 1500 bucks.
Let's sign you up for this one.
Get your tip-top shape for it.
And then down here.
Can they fight each other?
Only one? Okay, Wally will do this one.
That's next week.
And then
Roberto
kind of can't do much.
There's already one
going on here.
He'll do the first one on this week,
Roberto. Another competition.
Oh no, that's the same one.
This is January, so February
you'll do this one.
All right.
This bed is so comfy right now.
I'm glad you're having a good comfy
rest.
Speaking of rest.
Let me take a look at the schedule here.
Tomorrow, Wally has a tournament.
How are you doing, Wally? You're doing fine.
Wally can do
whatever he wants to do here. Meditation.
And then Vroomer has
Vroomer, you need to rest.
Because you're very tired.
And you can do the trampoline tomorrow.
So rest.
And then you, it doesn't really matter.
All right, let's do it.
Vroomer looks really, yeah, Vroomer's
going to rest today.
There we go.
He's doing okay.
Get ready for your tournament tomorrow.
And no, you have the tournament tomorrow.
You're good. How are you doing over here?
You're always hungry.
Beef?
All right, will you like me if you do robot
animals eat beef?
Yeah, he liked it. Good. He loved it.
Now he's happy. Now he's lively. Good.
So now it's time
to proceed.
And it's a competition
tomorrow.
Right, yeah, tomorrow it is Wally.
Here we go.
Wally is lively.
He needs maybe a little bit of food.
Do you think you need food?
Do you need food?
Schedule for today.
Meditation for Wally.
Rest.
Yeah, you can have two days off.
And exercise for you.
And then it's your tournament tonight.
We'll feed you after this.
Not bad.
Hungry. Let's give you some food.
I'm kind of running
out of food.
He's like my uncle with the food bag.
Should be good, right?
Yeah, focused. Not hungry.
Not that tired.
What about you?
You okay?
You're doing a good job.
Bacon diaper? What do you mean a bacon diaper?
Oh, you mean
that. Like a bacon wrapped
skull.
I had no idea what the hell you're talking about.
Alright, let's see if
Wally can win a tournament.
The Christmas Cup. Merry Christmas.
Let's begin.
Chara, still
stuck in the shitty chicken league.
And then youth K.
Youth K.
So this is
me. Insanely high defense.
Good intelligence.
Not bad speed.
Really fast.
But terrible at almost every
single thing that matters.
It'll be hard to hit.
Shouldn't be a problem. Let's go.
What's my title? Oh, this is an awful title.
Another placeholder title that I forgot to change.
Creating life.
Whatever. Alright, Wally.
Let's go. Bring it on.
Ooh.
Right off the bat. Aggressive.
Party cracker.
Double party cracker.
Nope. Alright.
Dodged it all. I get really, really
good defense though, even if I get hit.
Still timid. Still timid.
Come on.
Come on. He can't do a
move either. We both make such a weird position.
Oh my god.
I have so many guts.
This is kind of bad right now, Wally.
What the fuck is going on here? Timid
like four times in a row?
I can't even do his basic attack.
He's blocking everything.
Hellvana? What is that?
12% hit chance.
32%.
Okay, that makes him even harder to hit.
Lucky, actually.
That was a bad display, Wally.
That's a great dance though.
Alright, Chara, Youth K.
Youth K is one of those dogs with the
one of those dogs with the hats on.
Alright, Youth K and Wally.
Let's see.
Oh my god.
What the
hell is this?
Did you forget to train other things?
482 intelligence.
No accuracy.
No speed. No defense.
No power. What does your money even move?
Scratch is the move to look out for.
Alright.
We're gonna give it a try.
RNG just needs one hit.
Alright. Let's go.
Let's do it again.
Oh god, is this it?
Let's headbang.
63% chance to hit this.
You're dead.
Back to the drawing board with these stats.
What a dumb character.
I guess that would work.
But your hit chance is probably at
8-9%.
Always.
Maybe even worse.
What's the point of having all that intelligence?
Can you enable Pog?
Pogchamp? It already is enabled.
It's a global emo.
Alright. First week of January.
I think it is. Vroomer has a competition
coming up here, right? Tonight?
Yes. Vroomer has a competition
today.
And you're not that tired.
So let's see what we got here. Trampoline
for Vroomer. Get that speed
increase.
Are you tired?
Are you resting today?
Yes, you should be.
You're also resting today.
No, that's...I'm sorry.
Get back in the training.
Enable Pog.
I don't even know what you're talking about.
Enable Pog?
Pog is a zoomed-in version
of Pogchamp.
Oh. Lively, how you doing?
Where...oh, you're on the trampoline.
Focus. Let's get some food in you.
Just a little potato. Just something easy
so you can crash
on the competition. First,
time in D rank for Vroomer.
D rank, $1,500.
Let's see who
the competition is now.
If you want a better Pogchamp, just use German Venus.
Yeah, I mean, come on.
Vroomer, Carl,
Farrell, and Bob.
This is against Carl.
High HP,
but not a threat anywhere
else besides an intelligence. What are your moves?
A lot of intelligence moves.
Shouldn't be a problem, though.
Just get the Woodlum down.
Farrell is just one of those plants.
No, not very much defense. Just go in there.
Polish.
Popped it.
Come down.
Really? I'm going to back it up a little bit.
No, no, no, no, don't. That's his intelligence move
back there. I don't want him to have
any...no, that's not good.
25% chance to hit.
I'm going to stay forward, though,
because all of his moves are terrible
besides the ones at range.
No, stay in.
Damn.
Carly, kill him here.
Oh, this is bad.
This is bad. I have to hit him with
something, otherwise he's going to die.
35% chance to hit.
He's got a 66% chance to hit. Back it up.
That Nirvana thing
is ridiculous.
No!
That was kind of a last-ditch effort there.
Thank God.
I'll stay in the middle.
Percentage-wise, where does that put me?
It's pretty close, actually.
Uh-oh. Blocked it.
Block it!
Yes!
Getting close.
Perfect. Again.
Quick, quick, quick.
Composed.
What does that mean, composed?
Thankfully, I blocked the two dots.
That would have been bad.
Faro and Bob.
Pretty close. Bob wins.
Alright, Bob.
Fairly balanced.
Head throw, head swing, boomerang,
fat belly, and nasty.
Fairly balanced character.
Decent power.
Decent life. You kind of just spread out
all over the place, don't you?
Oh, and he's also nasty.
It's another one of those weird ducks,
but this is not a pumpkin. This one is made out of stone.
Get in there right away.
He's got nothing close.
Back it up.
He has nothing far away here.
Oh, he just got destroyed.
Alright, now I'm gonna take it in close.
That was just...
Those two moves are really good.
Unfortunately, the one in the back doesn't have a high percentage,
but if it hits, it's good.
It's some easy money.
I gotta take him out
to learn new moves.
And six new fans.
When do you get to milk your monsters?
How did I read that one?
I don't know, because I looked over and it was there.
That's so fucking stupid.
Alright, trampoline.
Okay, let's do some more tournaments
scheduled out here.
Can't do this in official one.
The next one available for
Rumor is here.
And then...
Over here is Roberto.
And we'll do Wally on this one.
So this string here...
February is the
tournament week, or month.
We'll do some more
just resting and training
in January.
Alright, how tired is everybody?
Everyone's pretty good, actually.
Begin!
Ten accuracy.
I have to bring
at some point here.
I gotta bring him back to adventure.
D and E. What babies?
Not for long.
He's gonna hit me up at C after the next tournament if I win it.
Do my parents watch my stream?
Oh yeah, my mom and dad are both subbed.
I need to feed. You are always hungry.
No, not you.
You're always hungry. Here. No, you don't get that.
Yes, you do.
I think he's the only one that wants to eat it.
Rest up.
Everyone's kind of tired.
Good work.
What do we need to work on here?
155. He's across the board.
He's pretty good.
Accuracy is kind of lacking.
Accuracy and intelligence.
Or maybe accuracy and power.
Accuracy and life.
Accuracy
and life is what I want to do.
Rest here.
Life?
It's gonna be close to the tournament though.
Let's see what happens after that.
Now you, Rumer,
what can you do here?
Rest.
Yeah, rest and then trampoline.
Yeah, that's, yeah.
I'll take the power in trampoline.
That sounds good.
Proceed.
February week two is the first tournament.
Not that focused.
Can we throw Roberto into a meat grinder?
We have, hold on there.
Wait till he shows himself in battle.
And then we'll decide that.
Level nine intelligence for Wally.
Roberto, not so good.
Frustrated.
Hey, you can do better.
Just relax.
Roberto's not a waste of space.
He's just tired.
And he's gonna rest this week.
Food you need to eat.
Have a mango.
Would you throw a fork into your garbage disposal?
No.
I actually, I would not.
That's a good idea.
What about a carrot?
Yeah, have a carrot.
You're gonna like this.
You won a good tournament.
You deserve it.
I'm running out of food.
I have to buy food.
He's focused for his tournament.
Yeah.
Two more weeks.
The way we raise Vroomer from this point on
will determine the difference between victory and defeat.
What does that mean?
Does he look sadder than usual? He looks sad today.
I don't know why.
Anyone catching that?
He's gonna do the trampoline.
Trampoline and then rest.
And then you can do exercise.
The tournament is here.
Now trampoline.
Exercise.
Rest.
Yeah, that looks good.
You have the tournament here.
So we're gonna do, yep.
Now there you go.
Target.
Rest.
No, we need a resting now.
And then power.
And we'll have to see because you're really tired.
So you can rest.
Go for it.
Alright, pretty successful day.
Freeze him before he dies so he can live forever.
Yeah, I'm gonna use his body for another DNA.
Good work.
I don't have any food for you, but I'll say good job.
Yeah, Wally's doing a really good job training.
A lot of like plus eight, plus nine.
Very lively.
Okay, so now.
Very good job.
You too.
And you are just doing okay.
But you're also just really good at training.
And you're also just really good at training.
Okay.
But you're also just resting, so.
What about food?
I gotta give you something before the tournament.
You like squid?
Yeah, you do.
Glad the heavy dialogue is gone.
It makes the game much more enjoyable.
Yeah.
It kinda just had to get us here though.
That like first 45 minutes of just kind of
TV show talking.
And look at the sacred tree.
I don't even remember that thing's name.
Oh yeah, save the game.
Have to do it from like the other menu.
Alright.
February, week one.
Hello, how are things? Need anything today?
Go ahead, take a look around.
Alright.
What can I buy? Training.
Sandbag, better sandbag.
I got lots of money, so.
The life blade.
That's the thing.
One by one, let's get this.
Life blade.
Put it right here, perfect fit.
That's the thing he made, right?
Probably, sandbag is, yeah.
I'm gonna need this.
Sandbag is
perfect fit right here.
And I can do one more here.
Whatever it's gonna be.
This one is book, target,
trampoline, tub.
I feel like I want the tub.
Tub.
Anything else that's it?
So what is a praise?
I had a praise one, but you don't have
a stone tablet. Alright, okay.
Sell, buy, end.
What will you do? I will end.
Yes. So now today,
it is
Roberto's tournament.
He's gonna rest today, because he's already
still tired. Why are you still
tired? But here's the thing now,
so balance.
I can change this to
the life blade.
Exercise can
be changed
to the sandbag.
Exercise can be changed to sandbag.
I know, yeah, yeah.
You need it more than he does.
You know what?
Let's do like,
you do the life blade.
Let's see what happens.
Plus ten, nice.
I needed that actually pretty bad.
Roberto, plus seven.
This is shake weight.
Looks like he's stuck
in an animation or something. Like he's glitching through the wall.
And then there's the sandbag.
He's out of control.
Alright.
I need food.
I'm running out of food. Eat a banana.
I'm gonna have to go to town and buy some stuff.
You're fine.
Alright, that's it.
Which money do I have?
Hold on, let me just swallow this banana.
Shrine, association, item shop.
Oh, welcome.
Well, what will you do?
I will buy.
Which will you buy?
I will buy
mushroom. The common mushroom
is cheap but it's not very filling or tasty.
Cheap and filling
so it's a breeder standard.
Let's get a few of these.
This is the one you want to buy, right?
Can I increase the...
I will take five potatoes.
I will also
hit energy bar. Like a cookie, it
charges up your monster fast.
I feel like I want
like a couple of these.
Just in case.
And then maybe a couple of bananas.
Three bananas.
Yeah.
And then yarn ball
junk toy.
Pretty old. I found this, didn't I?
It's like great as a toy. How do I do this?
How do I use this?
It will be five hundred bucks
for beef.
That's too much. I'm going to have to eat potatoes.
I'll get like a couple of electric potatoes.
This four games, there's actually
five games.
There's one after this too. But apparently the one
after this is
awful.
Is what I've heard.
I've heard Evo is a
unbearable...wow.
That's fifteen hundred bucks.
That's wrong? I mean
everybody told me Evo was terrible.
I heard it was not good.
Doesn't it have like a forty five on Metacredit
or something? Wow.
Wow.
Battle cards? Should I just sell
this? The DS ones are good.
Maybe I'll try those eventually.
Can I use the perfume for any reason besides just to sell it?
I mean the cards, what am I going to
play? Cards together?
Just sell it.
The Game Boy ones are good.
Which one's the best?
I think Monster Rancher 2 is the best one.
But this one's not bad.
This one's actually growing on me here.
Most fans agree it's 2 or the second one for DS.
I could see it.
2 just was very straightforward but it was fun.
It was very basic but
that's why it was so good.
It seems like every other game they've tried to add
a bunch of weird shit that nobody really wanted.
They just want to breed monsters
and fight monsters.
But this one is
I don't hate this one.
This one's actually really fun.
I don't mind this one.
Are we talking about Sekiro?
Yeah I completed Sekiro
on the last stream.
If you didn't catch the last couple streams
it was Sekiro. Actually the last 5 streams
in a row were Sekiro.
So it's time for the tournament.
You're just doing okay. That's not good.
It was easy.
No it was not.
Not even the slightest.
You're going to rest right now anyway.
So that's fine.
And then we'll see what you can do in battle.
I'm looking forward to it.
So now you, Lifeblade and Sandbag.
And then it's time to bring
Roberto into a...
That's so cute. I can't wait to go look at that.
Look at this.
Is that in his mouth or in his hands?
He's jiggling the thing around.
Oh he's getting tired.
Too much work.
What should I do again? I'm trying.
You're fine.
Eat a potato. Feel better.
He's praying out of bonfire.
How you doing?
Mr. Cheese Wheel. Are you good?
Tired. Oh boy.
Did I overwork you?
You look like Cherry.
From Pee Wee's Playhouse.
Come on. You can do it.
You can do it.
See? That's all he needed.
Some encouragement.
So you're very lively and you're focused.
You on the other hand, you're using food.
You can just have a potato.
Let's see if I can steamroll this competition.
It makes it really hard
to juggle three monsters, four monsters at the same time.
Before it was you just had
one monster and you worked
the hell out of them.
Now you've got a whole family.
Remember Gaddy.
Has Gaddy improved at all?
Let's find out. Not at all.
Gaddy has not even
trained one step.
That's fine. You can go against my Smurf.
That's a lot of damage.
Followed up with a kick.
You may as well just have that be
somebody's dog now. You know what I mean?
Why are you fighting here?
That should be like a lap dog
just sitting on somebody's
stomach while they're lying down on the couch.
What is that dog doing here?
That should be somebody's just friend.
Why are they here?
You're fighting like a giant robot with a sword
in his hand. See?
Come on. Alias.
164 in accuracy. That's pretty good.
It's not going to be enough.
We come from a similar
breed.
Nice dodge.
Fine.
Do it again.
What's the defense on the bird dog?
That's good.
It can't be that good.
There we go. See what?
Demon doll.
Gaddy actually won a fight.
Shocking.
We fought Kylan before.
Just fast.
And has good accuracy.
Losing to Gaddy.
What an embarrassment.
Double charge. Do it again.
Or kick it.
That's it.
Final guts.
This doesn't feel right.
I think he's ready. Roberto.
That was BM.
800 bucks 7 fame.
You guys wanted to retire him.
I wonder how long they live in this one.
Actually, it's time to go pee.
It's probably going to be the final pee of the night.
I'll be right back.
Alright. So where are we now?
Vroomer has a tournament today.
Wally has tournament 2.
This is class D.
And then...
One more of these and we can move to C.
So I don't...
I want you to rest right now.
Rest.
And then when you...
Get in the tub.
And you...
What was he doing before?
Balance, right?
Lifeblade.
Use the new things we bought.
Bad.
Really bad.
6 only? Come on.
You're in the tub now.
I mean, it's absolutely adorable, but...
I'm going to get 6 points.
How is this improving defense?
I guess he's running out of the way.
We haven't seen him do this yet.
What a weird way to increase your defense.
What a weird way to increase your HP.
Alright. You... I'm sorry, but come on.
You can do better than that.
I know you can.
You too.
They can do better than that.
I know they can.
You're just resting.
So you have a tournament.
Let's give you the potato.
There's something with starch in it.
So you can get some carbs.
How do you increase your HP?
You don't.
It gradually reduces from the second that you're born.
It starts at 100.
I mean, you can slow the damage over time.
You know, if you eat carrots and shit.
But eventually it goes to zero.
How can I decrease my HP?
I'm not going to answer that question.
Okay, this is the next class D.
Carl, Mary, and Nat.
Rumer versus Nat.
None of the physical moves are dangerous.
Pretty slow, but has fairly decent IQ moves.
Thunder and attack.
Look out for thunder.
Their traits are super weapon.
What the hell does that mean?
Why can't we get one of these weirdos?
It's far away.
Get in close.
Any of the moves that they can do from far away.
Get in close. Any of the moves that they can do from far away.
Don't even let them do it.
It's two shot.
That was a lot of damage.
I might get this character to like C or B tonight.
Remember how long it took us to get from D to C,
C to B in Monster Ration 2?
It was hard.
There's a chance.
Mary sucks.
C to B is...
Watch out for the magic.
It's a pretty cool toad though.
We had a toad before.
That hurts so much.
Let's do another two shot.
Goodbye.
Aww.
Toothpaste toad?
Don't talk shit. It's really easy to lose.
I only have 150 health.
Oh god.
I talked shit and it's going to come back and haunt me.
I have to do this move.
I have to get a long shot here and end it.
Oh, he's bullish.
Oh no, this is it.
Oh no.
I talked a lot of shit there.
It's okay, I can still win. Carl has to lose.
I have to beat Carl right now.
200 health.
Nothing else though.
Just high HP.
Damn it.
Well, I had to lose once.
Eventually.
Alright, Carl.
What's the percentage here?
52?
Alright, good, good.
Just beat him.
Go back a little.
50%.
Stay back.
44%.
Accuracy is the big deal here.
Look at this. This is bad.
We are working on that.
Oh fuck you with this final bullshit.
We found the thing we need to work on.
Because that's not good.
My defense is good.
I'm blocking a lot of hits.
Accuracy.
I'm not doing so well.
49%.
Okay, good.
Still a chance to lose.
Do I have the accuracy upgrade?
Alright, Carl.
The winner of this terrific battle is Rumer.
That's because I beat Carl.
Nice. Just barely.
1500 bucks and a squid.
We have to get you into accuracy training.
Right now.
Good work, but still.
You gotta win one more of those.
Let me see you here.
Accuracy is really at 159.
It's really not anything that bad.
Needs to be higher.
Being at less than 50% sucks.
I guess it also depends on their speed too.
His health is terrible.
Accuracy and health. His defense is terrible too.
I'll do accuracy and health.
For now.
Rumer.
I need to win one more.
We'll do this one.
Because that gives us
one, two, yeah.
Okay.
Let's go to schedule.
You don't actually have to rest.
Good.
Okay.
Accuracy.
The life stick.
Rest here.
And then maybe
the life stick again.
The rest of you know who has
somebody has something today, right?
You Wally does.
Wally is frustrated so
just rest Wally.
And then you don't have anything for a while
but you're still tired so you may as well rest.
Let's go.
Much better.
Much better number.
Where is Wally?
Sleeping, right?
No, have a potato.
I love these potatoes.
It's just really easy to get them borrowed.
Enable Pog.
Well that means I have to get rid of something.
What am I going to get rid of?
I have five slots so I'm not going to get rid of anything.
I have to get rid of
FeelsBadMan.
I'm going to have to get rid of MonkaS.
I only get five.
Okay, very lively.
Yeah, you're good.
Okay, Wally's good for his tournament.
The February Cup.
Chavez, Agassiz,
and Yuki.
This is against Yuki.
Really low defense.
Not a threat.
Just do
just do physical attacks.
It's a little of these weird duck
dog hat combinations.
All right, Wally, show him.
Show him what you got.
Wally, what the fuck was that, Wally?
Wally!
And now I can't hit him.
I got to stay in the middle.
Stay in the middle, in the middle, in the middle, because he has no moves for the mid range.
Pull him forward.
And now he's composed.
This is bad.
Come on, again, right off the bat. Do it, quick, quick, quick, again, again, again.
Yes!
Chavez and Agassiz.
Chavez win.
Yuki versus Chavez.
Not doing so good. Chavez is
the one to beat here, all right.
So, Agassiz.
High intelligence, high speed,
low defense.
Stay away from the magic abilities.
That's pretty much it.
Some of these cats.
All right, stay out of mid range, and
start immediately with the thing I
blocked.
High intelligence.
See what I mean here?
This is going to be hard.
38%, fuck me.
Stay forward.
There we go.
I don't have very much power, right?
I'm really dumb. No!
I forgot if this defense is so high.
At least I have a 200 defense.
Let's end it with the pop.
Come on, let me be flashy.
You're not going to let me be flashy?
22%.
I still got it.
Is that Mewtwo?
It's just a regular Mew.
All right, Chavez.
You're the...
Why are you so good?
Because you have good defense
and good power.
I have to hit you with intelligence stuff.
Yeah, I'm going to...
I'm going to try to burn you quick.
Rock Bunny.
Gotta go for this. See if I can hit it.
He sprays a bleed to it.
No.
Again.
That does more, somehow.
Try again.
Stay in mid-range.
Because he doesn't have shit in mid-range.
I'm going to bounce back and shoot him.
3, 2, 1, go.
Not good.
35% chance.
I'm going to hold on to my guts and not use it.
Have to win this one.
He's trying to bridge...
No!
20% chance to hit him.
Might just have to win this one by
playing defensively.
Can't go back any further over the wall.
Fall back.
One second left.
Do not do a move at the last second.
Judges?
Who wins?
I do!
Full-on victory. I like it.
Stalling tactics. Sometimes you've got to just
wear them out.
Please clap.
Not yet.
This is the final
tournament before I
can go into Seacup.
So we've got Lifeblade.
We should probably do this in the other...
Yeah. Rest first.
Do Lifeblade.
Maybe Lifeblade again.
This is the day of the tournament.
So you rest.
Nobody else has a tournament, right?
Rest.
Actually, you don't even need it.
Just do balance.
No defense.
Get in the tub.
Then you rest here.
You, on the other hand,
do the sandbag.
Get on
the trampoline
for speed.
And then you can rest here.
You're tired. Go to bed.
Begin!
Molly, you're just really not that good
with training.
It's just the fact. You're on the level 2
shit. What is this?
You were doing so good in the beginning.
I know you did
just win a tournament, but still.
I know you can do better.
He's trying his best. Yeah, but he's
been eating
bananas and shit all day.
Every day. You're doing just fine.
I will praise you, because
you just got 11 points.
You're a cruel and hateful person.
No, I'm not. You can't just
praise him every day. They turn
to shit. I did that
to beanbag Sonic, and he went
all the way to the other side of the scale.
And eventually he wouldn't even listen to me.
Remember?
Here. Here's your favorite thing.
I just
talked about how all he does is eat bananas, and I
just gave him one. That's fine.
We got a tournament coming up here, right?
How you doing? You sleeping?
You need to eat.
Oh, shit. I can't. Wait a minute. I can't do anything.
Oh, no.
That's not good.
Oh, that's alright.
Alright, you're good.
Let's give you some food.
It's a life blade
again for you. Life blade again.
Maybe you should rest.
Tub, rest.
Trampoline,
rest.
They're all doing just fine.
Bigot.
Saved the game. Yeah, I haven't saved the game in about
four hours. That's actually
really bad, you're right. That's awful.
Something bad is gonna happen though.
How do I even save
the game? Look how hungry you are.
Come on, I got you.
Are you full?
You're still hungry.
Here. Did you not literally learn a new
move? No, not yet. I have to bring them
into the adventure mode thing.
For them to learn new moves. I have to
do that. Okay, after bringing
um, after getting to rank C,
I have to get rumors
of a new move.
For this one, they made it so you have to push
reset on the console to save.
That's really weird.
Wasn't it somewhere in like
weekend calendar? Where was it?
Reader? Book?
Isn't it like at the very beginning of each week?
Yeah, it's at the beginning of each week.
Hey Jerma, got your nose.
You don't, no you don't.
It's still on my face.
I'm not stupid.
There we go.
Saving game. Turn on the face cam.
What if I turn the face cam on and I
this whole time was having Voldemort
style makeup put on me.
And that was just a plant in chat to write that.
And I just had this flat fucking
no, nothing there.
I just start screaming.
Screaming as loud as I can.
And then I turn the stream off.
April fools.
Alright, here we go.
You have a tournament today.
You're kind of tired though.
Just rest.
You are, you need to rest.
You're frustrated that it's okay.
Everyone's resting today.
Or just go to bed.
That would be the greatest thing I've ever seen.
And have a potato.
Jerma, please read this. I want to be the one guy.
Your wish is my command.
Alright.
Final tournament.
Before I can do the
rank up. Let's hope I win.
And then
we're that much closer to C rank. We're in C rank
after that. Next one.
Rumor, Fate, Bernard,
and Garganny.
Versus Fate.
Tons of life.
Not really that much of anything else.
Just high health, that's all.
And then I'm gonna take them all
exploring for the next month.
Just gotta hit hard.
Good start.
Good start. You got nothing in the back.
54%. Let's give it a try.
Helicopter. Good luck.
Look at all my guts.
He can't even do any moves.
Did he use everything to try to do that?
Just kill him.
I had a nightmare about this thing.
Hey Jerma, tell a funny joke.
Nah, I got nothing, sorry.
Sorry. No jokes tonight.
Alright Bernard.
Not that special, just a lot of health.
The no joke joke.
That's the one.
Jerma lied about funny joke.
That is fucking terrifying.
It's just a giant mouth.
That's just Pac-Man.
That's Pac-Man with dentures in him.
In the back, that's a good backspin.
It's been good, but...
Try again.
There's two coin flips in a row.
He doesn't have very many guts.
Oh man, that's not good. What was his defense at?
This is gonna come down to the end.
I have to win this one.
26.
It's gonna be one hit for whoever.
I gotta go for one in the back.
I had to do it.
Fuck.
I can still do this.
He's trying to close the gap.
Oh no.
That's it.
I get to do this thing.
What? No.
Are you serious?
He's got nothing in the back.
Do it.
You are killing me with this bullshit.
This is bad, I'm gonna lose.
Get back, back, back, back, back.
In the middle, right in the middle, right in the middle.
How many guts do I have?
Come on, I need 15 guts.
11, 12, 13, 14.
That's how bad I lose.
Just missed half the attacks I did.
My stats are way better than that, guys.
I have like 200 attack.
I just had to throw my dice in the air and lose.
And his accuracy is almost as much as his attack power.
He has like 200 accuracy.
What the fuck?
Look at this.
You're at 170 accuracy and you still are at like 30-45%.
How much more points do I have to put into this?
Look at the speed, accuracy.
That's like one of his top three.
I gotta get him a new move.
Alright, no more tournaments.
You need a new move.
Something for the mid-range.
Yeah, you're all coming with me.
Let's go.
Trampoline at speed.
Let's do it again.
Target.
Target is fine.
This is the top right.
And then you don't need to rest.
Stand back.
And then we're going to explore a cave.
Plus 16.
That was actually really good.
Alright, everyone's kind of hungry.
Except for you, you're fine.
You're frustrated and hungry.
Nevermind.
Why don't you, the biggest monster, eat the others?
The brightness on your phone is low.
I was unaware.
Alright, adventure.
Take monster, being raised, exploring.
Caves.
I'm coming. All of you.
746 start adventure.
Hey Jermey, is your refrigerator running?
Yeah, it grew legs.
And sprinted out of my house.
And just sprint punched my roommate in the face.
And started pissing all over my couch.
And rolling around on the ground and shit.
And then it had been in a Kool-Aid band outside.
As hard as it could into my wall.
There was glass and stuff. It was fucked up.
I'm glad you noticed it.
Then you better go catch it!
Yeah, I really should, shouldn't I?
You can't keep doing this stuff and blaming your fridge.
Here we go. Random battle.
Somebody's asked me if he's the fountain of youth bullshit.
I don't probably.
I have no idea.
He's dead instantly.
He finally read it. What do you mean he finally read it?
Level 2, Vroomer.
Anything new? What did you get?
Vroomer obtained Hard Head.
Vroomer mastered Charge.
Obtained Nunchaku.
Nice. New move.
He's been saying that for like 2 hours.
Why?
I don't know. What is that?
Let me take a look at the data.
Okay, so we got Charge now.
This is Charge.
17 guts.
Life damage is C.
Critical hit rating. Accuracies.
Guts damage.
It's more accurate than anything I have.
Except for this.
It's pretty cheap to do.
It's cheaper to do than this.
A little bit less damage than this.
But, it is
fairly accurate. Move kind of terrible.
Alright, he got Hard Head too.
What the hell is Hard Head?
Wind Lore.
Ups wind and fire power and lets you
add a wind power to skill.
Does it.
Increases power of moves that use the head.
Okay.
All these streams are Jerva saying
dumb stuff and chat repeating it.
Wait, what?
What was the dumb thing that I said today?
I didn't say anything dumb.
What did I say now?
The refrigerator running
thing?
Did I hit this guy?
Most level 2 for the other ones.
I need to equip the skill.
It's not there.
Oh, I see.
Okay, so this is slot 1.
I can't have
these.
Okay, so that is a
move in the front, short range. Alright.
And backspin is going to be
in the back.
Okay, so I'll just go like this in case I want to use it.
Okay, makes sense.
It's not April Fools yet.
Well, it is April Fools on East Coast at the moment.
So watch out for people playing tricks.
So I'm going to do something funny.
And you're going to believe them.
Let's try the new move, Charge.
I'm a little too bullish.
Still a little too bullish.
You're going to die in here.
It's pretty good move.
It's got a high hit percentage too it seems.
I'm going to take you out.
Get out of here.
You died. Last hit, that's good.
All the gifted subs are April Fools jokes?
Well, that would be
pretty weird.
Ah, almost.
Another toy robot.
This thing is stupid.
Actually stupid.
Doesn't even do anything.
Why am I going that way? I'm wasting energy.
Alright, next floor.
They should level up the other two and maybe they'll get some new stuff.
There we go.
Just don't even let them get up.
Keep doing it.
70%.
Nice.
Alright, here comes the new skills.
For level two.
And?
Wally obtained a sniper.
Roberto obtained
heavy armor.
And got a junk toy.
Really, let's see what that is.
Nope.
Sniper.
Increases power of moves that throw
or shoot.
So that's going to be much better.
For this move here.
This cracker.
No new
ability though, unfortunately.
Alright, what about um, Roberto?
No move, it was something else. Heavy armor.
Reduces damage but harder to dodge.
Okay.
No new moves for either one of them.
Alright, so what do you guys think?
We've been playing for about
just over five hours.
Do you want to keep seeing this?
I think I'm going to continue playing.
This is branching like crazy.
Found the chest.
Got a new move and we found
document five.
What the hell is document five?
Found the
Fitz Lenderman page.
Is there any movies lately?
I've seen...
The last movie I saw was in the Spiderverse.
The last one I saw in theaters.
What is this?
Rumor can't help you investigate.
Anybody else?
One of you guys can do this.
Wally can't help you investigate.
Nobody can dig.
A sword is a shovel.
Why not Captain Marvel?
I just haven't had a chance to go
to the movies.
Do I dare go down?
Do I dare go down again?
542, that's not bad.
Let's see what's on third floor.
Roberto is way too loud.
Yeah, he kind of is.
They all are though.
They all have a really loud single audio file
that plays when they make a step.
A big money just came in.
And community size.
You guys are just
showering me with money.
You guys are just dropping money
into my vacuum clinic.
Let me pause this. Hold on.
General lied about Minecraft.
We have five community subs. First of all, thank you.
And then
Gopher yourself
gave sixty dollars.
Thank you Gopher.
It's sixty bucks
six thousand bits.
How did this streamer beat the demon of hatred on the first try?
But die to my
elderly neighbor Bernard.
I love this silly streamer. Ha ha.
There's so much misinformation in that.
Two sentences.
But thank you Gopher.
Thank you with sixty bucks.
Funny lad.
Rhino, Rhino Ryan.
That's kind of cool. It's like a squirtle Mewtwo.
When do you think he'll get a sword slash?
I think he's going to take it to level four or five to get it.
Jeremy, do you know if your earwax is brown
it means you're stressed out?
Well my earwax is
when I put like a little thing in my ear
The room is almost level three.
Silver coin.
When I do a little
earwax thing, you know
a q-tip or something. I know you're not supposed to.
But I do it anyways.
I can't help it.
That the entire q-tip industry
only survives
only because people do the
thing they're not supposed to do with a q-tip.
Put it in your ear.
But it's like
they never do anything.
It's always very clean.
What I typically like to do is in the shower
I do a little bit of washcloth
and I go in the ear and move it around
so I don't go deep in.
Always clean.
Just double tap that guy.
Jeremy only reads gross and rude comments.
That's not even true though.
How many things
have I said this stream
that were just responding to questions?
I'm just responding to
questions.
And comments people have.
I gotta get out of here soon.
I'm at 472.
That's a sword.
Goldal sword?
Can I put items on in this game?
What do I do with that?
Maybe I can just sell it?
How fast can I dab?
I don't know. I haven't tracked it.
I don't have a radar gun to track how fast
my dabs are.
If I'm gonna take a guess though, I would say
probably like 600
probably 60-50
miles per hour.
If I had a radar gun pointed at me.
Look at this guy.
Whoa.
I kinda want this praying mantis person.
He probably has a ton of speed.
Sit down.
Just measure it in DPS.
Dabs. DPM.
Dab for a minute.
Do you think that's ever gonna go away?
Do you think anyone's ever gonna stop dabbing?
Transition out.
It has to be soon, right?
Okay, level three.
Roberto obtains
super weapon.
Vroomer obtains sniper.
Roberto mastered swing.
Okay, finally we can swing the sword.
Yeah, I ain't gonna lie. Look at Roberto's stats.
They're actually getting pretty good.
Okay, let's go into this one here.
There it is. Swing.
Life damage C. Accuracy
rating S.
This thing will never miss.
Exactly what I need.
He just became the character we're gonna be playing with.
So that takes over
for kick.
Yeah, he's got something else too, right?
Super weapon.
Increases power of moves
that use the weapon.
Nice.
And then what did I get for...
I got something else.
Vroomer, right?
Sniper.
Throwing and shooting.
What counts as that for here?
Does the backdash count as a throw?
Charge, backspin,
with type far range.
This is a throw?
This is probably a throw, right?
I do assume.
Cool, alright. Well, now they're getting a lot better.
Just kinda had to do this.
Oh shit, what is this?
In the cutscene here.
What was my last toaster strudel I ate?
I don't eat toaster strudels.
So I go by the box
and you know how the icing is all kind of
attached, connected like a...
almost like they're on a string together?
Well, I take a pair of scissors and
at the very top of the icing
there's a little nub
that you're supposed to squeeze the icing out of.
So I take a pair of scissors and I cut across
every single part of the strand of icing
packets.
So they're all cut off at the top of the nub.
And then it's about, I think it's eight
packets that are connected.
They're all on top of each other.
Turn it upside down. Squeeze all eight
packets at the same time.
And just drain the icing.
All eight packages.
And then I throw the box in the trash.
What, that's not, is that not normal?
There's something about this, it's strange. My old friend
can you hear me?
Hello, old friend. Who is that?
Much time has passed since your
former adventure. But it seems the world
needs you once again.
What's happening? Who am I? Where are you?
Now I am a stone fragment formed
in the lands of Gaia.
A Gaia stone, if you will.
You will understand all
soon enough. What's up, Rio?
What a beautiful stone. Yes.
I'm gonna take it with me.
Eek. What the fuck was that?
Rio, what happened?
I'm okay, sorry.
Rio, let's go home. Yeah.
Let's go home.
That was really fucked up.
She's having a mental breakdown.
She touched the magic stone
and she started hearing voices.
It started to implant itself in her brain.
Hey, fain, fain.
I thought that actually was music, but it's not. I forgot.
Pollock, you look awfully excited.
What's going on? Are your
training gadgets working alright?
What? Why wouldn't they be?
There's a Geonite shortage in
these parts. Gadgets stopped working on
all the ranches. We seem
to be doing fine. Well, thank
goodness. But most of the
ranches can't train their monsters.
Official competition may be cancelled
for the time being.
What? Don't worry, I'm going to
look into this. Bye then. I can't do
any more competitions. Now that he
mentions it, I have noticed my body
feeling a bit strange lately.
But I'm no run-of-the-mill spirit
tree. I'm tough.
I think you're the only spirit tree,
to be honest. Will it be okay?
I wonder if the training gadgets used
too much Geonite. No,
it's not exactly that. It's like the
Geonite is being sucked down through
my roots. Your roots?
We can use the cave to
check underneath here. Let's do a little
exploration. Sounds good.
I just did that though. Don't they
need to rest? Wait, check
the fan art. What are you talking about? Fridge pissing.
What are you guys linking here?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I'm trying
to click it. A comic book?
Oh, intelligence
482. With my vast
intellect, I have analyzed all possible
futures. You have no chance of victory.
K.O.
A whole comic book?
Holy shit, that was fast.
You made a whole comic book.
That's true though. What the hell would you
buy? That was the weirdest monster.
See, I feel like the game broke.
Here, I'll show it. No, that's not
what I want. There you go. See?
482.
I want to try that with a monster.
You know what? Not today.
But on the next stream. On the next stream,
I want to completely design
a monster around only having
only speed and only
accuracy. So you could just
spam a shitty move
and hit it every time. Who cares?
But that was from Drosophilia.
Thank you, Drosophilia.
It's a new day on the East Coast.
Yeah, it is technically a new day.
Nah, I'm not done streaming now.
What are you talking about? We're still going.
I'll go for like another hour or two.
It's April 1st.
That means, I'm just kidding. Stream ends in like
10 minutes. Alright, what we got for a
second? We need to go into the...
There's no training allowed, right?
Everyone's tired. Rest.
Everybody go to bed. And then after
this, we're going to go into the
cave again, because we have scripted
cave content. And also,
by the way, for those of you that are
curious, I'm not streaming tomorrow.
I came back for one day
here, because
this has been
Kim's birthday weekend.
And there's some stuff
that I want to do. We went out
already, but tomorrow
I want to
take her somewhere else. It's not an
April Fool's joke, that's for real.
It's not April Fool's, I promise
you. Don't you guys know why
April Fool's jokes and joke
streams don't even happen on April 1st?
They happen on like April 11th.
Good luck.
April Fool's proposal.
No, this is Kim's birthday
weekend. And as you know,
you celebrate the whole
week when it's somebody's birthday, not just
a day. Stream the date.
I don't think so.
But, uh, I just want
to make that clear. And then I'll be
back. We'll go
April 2nd, April
3rd, and probably April 4th.
And then we'll see what we're doing.
We'll do another three days
in a row. After
tomorrow.
But now, where are we going now?
Everybody's all rested? Anybody hungry?
Because we have to go and do the scripted
thing. You are hungry, you have a potato.
Can't wait for the quick stream clip of Jerma throwing
a pine Kim's face for April Fool's.
No.
Like a 10 second stream?
That would be so bad.
Alright, adventure, let's go.
The owl is in energy this time.
So we have to go under the tree.
Every day is
my birthday. Every single day.
The bats are really annoying. Yeah, they
really are. They kind of just don't do anything.
Just fly around. Nobody can get in here.
Rumor cannot help you investigate.
No, you can't.
So, floor three? Floor four?
Everyone expects me to read
that. But I'm not going to.
Because I'm going to try to break
from the habit apparently if I look over and read
the weird gross thing that somebody wrote.
Not tonight.
I was about to read it out loud. I'm
starting to learn. I'm starting to figure out how to be
a streamer. Alright, let's try this new move.
Let's get uh,
let's get Roberto in here. So this is
swing. What's the chance on it?
76%.
That's a pretty great move.
Is it weird that I want to
turn this into the main character?
I feel like stat wise.
Alright, that's back to back.
Let's go. Nobody else got any moves,
right? There's something so timid.
89 damage.
Overkill.
Roberto is the protagonist.
Rumor is the funny sidekick.
That's true.
That's actually a really good point.
Document seven. Uh, let's actually
let's get Wally up here and
level up Wally to level three.
And Wally is the cute pet.
Wally is the cute pet that doesn't do anything
for the whole series, but like
two times over the course of
400 episodes will save everybody
for some reason.
Come on, I got extra damage on this, right?
Really? Not bad. Not very good
either. More damage on my
ranged attacks.
Team up.
I think I need more intelligence
that's why it's not doing any damage.
Alright, you have to get the
last hit, but you're really making this hard.
The baby, Walnut Baby
has to get last hit.
Or Walnut, or Wally might just die.
Wally's gonna die.
Alright, pull him out. Sometimes you gotta
know when to fold.
The Labo VR comes out on April 12th.
I can't wait.
Obtained a Nunchaku.
I cannot wait to do Labo VR.
I'm gonna lose
like 10,000 followers
and like 1,500 people on sub.
I have to do it though.
I have to. Not gonna be able to
stream it though, we can't see the screen.
I'll find a way. You guys
can just do it. I'll put the webcam
inside of the machine and let you guys do it.
Kermit's gonna go on a Labo
Cardboard VR date with
Kim.
Alright, level up.
Burn all your old Labo shit.
I don't even have it anymore.
Suiko E.
Alright, give me a last hit.
You only have 43 health.
Do it!
29%. This is not gonna hit.
35%.
I could have burnt it for content.
No, that's dangerous.
I may have gotten injured during that.
What a lame streamer.
10% chance to hit.
I may as well just stay back here forever.
But that would be some content.
Wally, you're really
kind of pissing me off here.
You guys don't wanna see that. That's not like, no.
I don't think it's time to freezer Wally yet.
Not yet.
He was so irritated. He was just like,
Jesus Christ, I'll take care of this.
Alright, fine. Level three.
Wally obtained King's Fist
and mastered Magic Hand
and obtained Reference.
Magic Hand.
Short range.
Finally a move that has
accuracy.
And it's short range. This is perfect.
Okay. I gotta start building intelligence.
What does Wally even have for
stats?
That's actually not that bad.
Pretty good, actually.
Alright, what else did you just learn?
King's Fist
versus power moves that use the fists.
Alright, Wally.
What smell do you think of when you picture the color
aquamarine?
A blue popsicle.
You know what I'm talking about.
Got an amethyst.
Cool. The smell of a blue popsicle.
I'm sorry, guys.
You have to do it.
The electric blue raspberry popsicle.
Smell it.
Oh, man. I can't get him with the comedy
move.
It's a double hit.
What's that? 60%?
Artificial blueberry. Yes.
Alright, let's get the guy that actually can hurt things
out here, please.
That's not good. Really?
82.
I'm taking this guy to the top.
Can I get Roberto level four before this is all done?
Can you throw Wally off a rooftop?
Even if I did, it wouldn't be a problem.
He would just close into his walnut shell.
And it would be fine.
Wally's gonna be a slow brain.
Why did you have to just write that?
I just made some salsa. Do you want some?
Why did you write that? Now I want some.
I actually do want that now.
87.
Aww. Ended with another one.
Actually, now I can bring out...
No, I'll just...
What kind of salsa, though?
This is a lot of different kinds.
Are we talking like a peach salsa?
A mango salsa? Raspberry salsa?
Black bean salsa?
Maybe a little bit of queso on the side?
I want this so bad.
I'll see you later. I'm leaving.
I'll see you guys in like a month.
What if I stopped streaming for a month?
You already did that.
Yeah, I know. Like before.
Yeah, just...
No, not just to eat salsa. This is kind of just...
We're just hanging out.
I'll see you guys in a month.
I'm gonna eat salsa.
I'm gonna be a salsa review channel on YouTube.
Well, to be fair, the reason why I stopped streaming for a month
is because I was traveling
across the whole country
in an inflated air car.
Alright, let's go, Roberto.
Mastered cut in two.
Yeah, I think Roberto's gonna be the one that takes us to the top here.
Short swing mid-range.
Cut in two.
Holy shit, look at that damage.
An A for damage.
Terrible accuracy.
But that's pretty amazing.
I wonder how much damage that actually does.
We'll find out.
Alright, let's pull it out. Let's see what happens.
Alright, cut in two.
The regular slash does like 90 damage.
I wonder how much this does.
Oh, he's gone.
He's right up on me, huh?
Alright, fine, I guess. Alright.
Alright, alright. It's time.
Let me just kill this motherfucker.
Bounce it back.
Cut in two.
Less damage than the other one.
Thoughts on recent politics? Yeah, sure, fuck.
Fuck.
This and that and that.
I think I have to make it to the fourth floor here.
Floor three, this is where we found the little tablet.
What did I have to eat today?
Two eggs.
Some orange juice.
And a bowl of Lucky Charms.
But I take out all the
actual cereal parts and I only eat
the marshmallow. It takes a long time
when I do it.
I just put them back in the box.
So it's like as if when I'm pouring it,
it's like its own cereal.
Troron.
You might as well just eat spoonfuls of sugar.
You actually...
Yeah, I'll be right back. I want to show you.
It's actually really hard to do this.
So,
Lucky Charms.
It's hard to put a lot of milk on these though.
No, it's good. Social eating.
I love Lucky Charms.
You guys thought I was making that up. I do this.
I've been doing it since I was like 11.
You have to put the milk at the bottom.
Because too much milk.
Too much milk will cause...
The sogginess of these marshmallows really gets bad
after about 30 seconds.
Why is everybody making fun of me?
You have weird shit that you do.
What weird shit do you do?
What fucked up shit do you do?
Tell me I don't fucking do that. Somebody called me a liar.
I put ketchup on my sandwiches.
That's fucking weird.
How long does it take to do?
Well, I buy like 15 boxes.
Because it really...
10 to 15 boxes makes one box of marshmallows.
And I throw the rest in the trash.
I don't know why this is so weird.
April Fool's...
It's 9.50pm
March 31st.
April Fool's. What are you talking about?
This is where your money goes, chat.
Rumor mastered bang drum.
It's not an April Fool's joke.
I just have this.
One sub is one box.
Somebody's really concerned.
Why would you waste money on brand name cereal and throw it away?
That's not...
It's alright.
What a monster.
How long does it take you to filter a whole box out?
A long time.
This is like burning my mouth.
Alright.
We got...
What happened?
It was Wally, right?
Rumor?
Yeah, okay.
Bang drum.
Life damage E. Accuracy rate D.
So addled.
Does your dentist know you do this?
He actually encourages it.
In his way, he said,
If you just eat sugary cereals every day,
you'll be more inclined to want to brush your teeth.
You're supposed to brush your teeth twice a day.
If you eat lucky charms only,
the marshmallow parts, he said,
for at least breakfast and dinner,
you'll have to brush your teeth.
Because last time I went to the dentist,
I hadn't brushed my teeth in about two years.
And these are all fake.
All these teeth are fake.
I hate this bit.
Do you though?
Are you sure?
Water. Can I go in there?
You're a bad influence on your child viewers.
Please take responsibility and brush your teeth on stream.
No, that's gross.
That's weird.
Child viewers.
How old do you think people are watching this channel?
How old do you think they are?
Four?
Speaking of four, we're going to the fourth floor.
By the way, have you ever had astronaut ice cream?
It is just
Lucky Charms marshmallows.
Gigantic ones.
Space ice cream?
If you're one of those people that loves to eat
freeze-dried marshmallow, like I do,
I've got a whole bowl of it over here.
Yeah, and it's fucking garbage.
Relax.
Freeze-dried stuff is way too chalky.
I mean, if you eat chalk.
Alright, I'm going to stop
because people are going to think this is like real.
I really don't want to end up
somewhere where people think that like, holy shit, he's like
fucking insane.
He's kind of good though.
This haha dentist and cereal joke.
Why can't I do anything?
I just dry heaved
because I heard him eating it.
It's not like dog poo.
It's marshmallow.
You act like I'm eating
a bowl of paint.
Or like somebody else's throw up.
What? It's freeze-dried
marshmallow.
What's wrong with it? What's the problem?
Like I'm not eating
blended up cold hot dogs
with a spoon.
Swing.
I would pay you to do that.
I'm not going to do that.
I would never do something like that.
Disgusting. Cereal, cereal
filter.
No, you want to actually, the best cereal I've ever had was
original cookie crisp.
I'm not talking about cookie crisp now.
Back when it was made with animal fat.
Whatever the hell it was.
It was great.
Stop it. Let me do something.
I can't even do anything.
He's just doing E over and over again.
Cookie crisp now is not very good.
I'm going to block. Alright, bring in the
real. Bring in the real
one here, please.
Is he dead?
I wasn't even paying attention. Did he get killed?
Can I please do something?
Oh my god.
If I die to this
I'm going to be so
angry.
Oh my god.
Finally. Alright, the big money came then.
Thank you Kairosobi for the
50 bucks.
5,000 bits. This is for the
Marshmallow Fund you 4-2 Leprechaun.
Boomerang.
I don't even want these.
I'm going to put them back in the box.
I don't want any more of this comedy cereal.
You're watching Boomerang.
It's all coming back to you.
What would your own cereal be? Something
light. You know Pops?
It would be something like Pops.
But with a lighter coating.
It's not as sugary.
Leave because of Roberto?
I'm not going to get the
cuts in here.
I have a fucking
stomach ache now.
Whose fault is that?
Jax mix.
There's like bacteria in these.
Somebody look it up.
Is that
bacteria in
freeze-dried marshmallows?
Bacteria in everything.
That's true.
You guys know that
according to doctors
humans should
not be taking in more than 32
grams of sugar or 36
grams of sugar a day
of added sugars.
That is like a whole day.
Do not consume more than
38 grams
of added sugar a day.
You know how much sugar is in a can of
Coke?
39 grams. You know how much is in Mountain Dew?
Throwback?
44.
I've said the same shit before. Yeah.
Well there's probably a bunch of new people here.
It's 42 grams of sugar buddy.
Oh I don't think so. Look it up.
Added sugar a day for a male
is like 38. For a female I believe
it's like 30.
That's what it says. Look it up.
Why do I know this? Because my dentist told me.
Alright.
I need to figure this out. How much sugar is in one
Lucky Charm Marshmallow?
Do we know how many grams of sugar is in one?
Level 5 for Vroomer.
What's going on? Nothing? Nothing new at level 5?
0.25
grams. I googled it.
There you go. Put this weight on a scale
because that's all it is.
My back hurts now.
What's with this fucking bacteria marshmallow
shit that I just ate?
Alright am I almost there?
Sugar is reverse salt.
Does it go underneath the tree?
How many marshmallows do we eat at a time?
Oh it's probably like 300 or 400 in here.
I can't believe you guys fell for the oldest April Fools joke
in the book. Guy eats
a bowl of marshmallows.
Somebody says we didn't.
Oh yeah the classic April
Fools joke. This thing looks
pretty dangerous.
Joke's on us. He just painted
wood chips to look like marshmallows.
Yeah. This is like
clay. You guys didn't even know.
Alright get me to the tree
before they all die.
Oh my god. What the hell?
Play-Doh unironically
tastes good. Well you should
unironically probably stop doing that.
That's really not good for you.
Play-Doh is vegan.
Yeah and
so is the plastic
on my keyboard but I'm not going to pop off
buttons and swallow them.
You know how much sugar is in Play-Doh?
Way too much.
Buy a keyboard made out of chocolate and eat it on the end of the screen.
That is actually kind of funny.
Whoa. This is a weird
looking monster. Let's shoot him.
Oh no. Let's just run into him.
But Play-Doh isn't gluten free.
Guys you're not supposed to be
eating Play-Doh. Who cares
what the nutritional content is.
It doesn't matter if Play-Doh is gluten free
or sugar free or
low sodium. Don't tell
me what to do. Yeah fine.
Don't tell me what to do. If I want to
eat my comedy cereal I'm going to eat it.
You're not our dad. You're not my dad.
Alright I got it. What
the hell?
Did I just stumble upon a boss?
Rawr. Whoa is he angry?
No no he's talking to us.
Please Fane leave this
to me. Are you the one using
the Geonite around here?
I've lived off Geonite for ages
rawr. But why
have you suddenly started using so much
Geonite?
The increased flow of Geonite woke
me up. Now I need lots of Geonite to stay
awake. But you're causing people
a lot of trouble. Please sleep once again. Go back to
bed. Rawr.
Never. Watch out.
Get back. Too much G
fuel. Um.
Okay.
That was a good hit.
King Shiden.
Shit.
Back it up. Do it again.
37%. Get it.
Good block. Come on.
You have 96 guts. Make this work.
Holy moly. Guts down.
Slow. Get killed.
137 damage.
Alright it's all up to you. You still
can't hit it. What? You alright?
Charge.
Get in there.
Alright. One more of those. That's it.
Come on Vroomer. 44% chance. Get it.
Yes. I win.
Only Vroomer gets the EXP unfortunately.
High speed ride.
And mastered 0
to 60. Nice.
You just killed an old
god. Alright.
I'm so sorry.
But please understand we need Geonite.
Therefore you have to die.
Humans use some Geonite.
Times have changed.
Young princess, it's been a long time.
I'll be good for your sake.
What? How do you know about me?
I guess we Raiden are your
friends. What do you mean?
Tell me.
Shoot he's asleep.
But at least now the flow of Geonite will return to normal.
Look near his feet.
Hmm. A huge pair of wings.
Are these his wings?
He said they are our friends.
Maybe these wings are to prove that.
The great Raiden are our
friends. Awesome. Let's go back to the
ranch. Who made
this game?
Who the fuck did it? Capcom, right?
Wally was injured. I'll send it to the
hospital. Uh oh.
Wally hasn't gotten better yet. I sure
hope it comes back soon.
Is anybody home? Yes.
Oh, Cynthia. Today I've come with a
delivery. A breeder
ranking card. We've earned rank
D. Yep.
Your efforts have earned an official ranking.
Congratulations. Thank you very much.
And also with the Geonite
shortage finally solved, official
battles will finally be starting again.
Well I'll be rooting for you.
Do your best. Yes, yes we will.
We'll do our very best.
Where's Wally?
Is he dead for real?
Okay.
Calendar?
Alright, rumor needs
another...
Unfortunately I had to miss
these because I can't join this yet.
And I have to sign up for this one.
Sign up for this one,
get ready for it, and then
also Roberto
needs to get ready for
one of these, this one, Banana.
Just let Wally die.
Let me take a look at
their data here. What do we need?
Roberto needs
um, accuracy.
Accuracy and life.
Rumor needs life
and either life, probably life
and defense.
Let's get you in the tub.
And then
get you with the blade in your
it's okay to click, oh no no no.
Do defense twice.
You...
What did I say for you?
It was defense, right?
No, it was life.
Do life twice.
Make another monster?
I could do that, yeah.
Wally sucks.
I'm gonna freeze Wally.
I mean, it's just the truth.
Here, have some food.
Have a banana.
Wally was good when he pierced shields.
Yeah, that's true.
But these two are way better.
Alright, hold on.
Silver coin.
I have so much of this stuff.
You want some cards?
I think Roberto hates battle cards.
It says I don't want it.
Yeah, right.
That's a nice cover.
You have every pack.
Alright, let's get back out here.
Check out Rumor's new...
I thought for some reason, I don't know why it said that.
I thought it said emote.
Check out Rumor's new emote.
What condiment would I choose
if I had to drink a liter of it in one sitting?
Probably like A1 steak sauce.
I feel like that wouldn't be that hard.
Let's go to the shrine.
Wally never came back.
Therefore, we're replacing him.
We can't.
I can't do anything.
Wally is in the hospital, but he still counts as a slut.
Freeze him in the hospital!
I don't think I can even do that.
Unplug him.
You guys are brutal.
Okay, training.
What's the schedule look like?
You have a tournament tomorrow,
so you're going to do light blade tonight,
and you're going to rest tomorrow.
You have a tournament later on in the week,
so you're going to do tub,
and then you're going to rest.
Get in.
Alright, you have to eat.
Oh fuck, I'm out of food.
I am out of food.
What happened to Wally?
Probably dead.
There's a possibility that Wally is dead.
He's been gone for a long time.
You don't have to eat right now.
I'm going to buy some stuff.
Crush Wally in a hydraulic press.
I swear,
some of you guys
have lost your minds.
What?
Why?
Let's get like five bananas.
Shitload of potatoes.
Okay.
I'm going to save my money.
Let's sell.
I have some new items here.
990 gold.
Yarn ball, battle cards,
silver coin, amethyst.
These are all worth...
I should just sell all this shit.
Bring Wally into a condiment and drink a gallon of it.
I'm going to tell your mother that you said that.
Slashman21's mom?
You see what your fucking son just wrote?
We all live in the same house.
Sleep.
Rest.
And you are also going to rest.
Look who's back.
You made it back. Welcome back.
Ship him off to the glue factory.
He has a terrible...
Alright, everyone's fine.
Let's get Roberto into the competition.
I want to get him up.
He's got to rank the fuck up, man.
And look, on the next stream, the next time we play this,
this is an audition.
Because whoever is the best
pretty much at the end of this stream
is the one that gets to move on.
What just happened?
Why did that... I couldn't... What?
He gave up.
He saw the wolf-gundam suit and he quit.
Why?
Alright, Decker.
117 damage. You ain't got shit.
I feel like this is the guy that would get to S-rank.
Super easily.
It was that easy.
Yeah, I bullied a bunch of rank-ees.
I did it.
800 bucks. And a banana.
You guys are fucking sadistic.
Somebody just said something fucking horrible.
Okay, what we got?
Begin training? Not yet.
So somebody else has a...
You have the final...
Is this right?
Hold on, let me see.
What's the calendar look like?
So you got...
This is the last...
No, where is it?
Okay.
So you got this one. If you beat this one,
then I can sign up for this one
and try to move on
to C-rank.
Good. So what do you need?
Life
and defense.
Let's do it.
Just do life twice.
Life, life, rest.
Sounds good.
You, on the other hand, you're gonna do...
You need like...
I don't have anything for intelligence, do I?
Just get your int up. Do it twice.
And you're gonna do...
Yeah, sandbag power is good.
And...
I also want...
Life. Get the tongue.
Pretty good session for everybody.
Probably should feed most people here.
All right.
Let's give everybody some potato.
What console is this on PlayStation 2?
PS2.
Are you hungry? Yes, you are.
You kind of had like a rough couple of days, so
I'll give you a banana. Are we all good to go?
Yes.
Oh, your whole schedule
is gone.
Okay, so you did meditation.
That's fine.
I'll change the schedule after this week.
So who else we got?
You're doing fine. You need to rest
anyways.
So you did life blade, rest.
Battle.
You are gonna do
hub, rest.
Yeah, let's go.
Pretty good increases all the way around,
except for maybe Roberto.
Jerma, I'm sorry I said you were
bad at Sekiro.
That's all right, as long as you apologized.
I accept your apology.
Lively. I just want you to
let you know that your mother loves you. Thanks, Mom.
All right, so you got something coming up here.
You're kind of all blue.
April Fools.
No!
Shit!
No, I had that queued up already.
All right.
Take a banana
or potato.
Let's do this last tournament, and then
bring you to rank C.
I think you have new stuff.
All right, so we got
this is 0 to 60.
Accuracy rate is B.
That's pretty decent.
Pretty decent crit damage, too.
I already have these on.
It's drifting.
All right, so 0 to 60.
What's the difference between this
and...
Let's see.
Life damage B, life damage C.
So this is better.
No, I have worse damage.
It's way more accurate, though.
Yeah, I would do this way more.
Holy shit, look at that.
It costs 40 guts to do this.
It's got a really good hit rate, but
that's a lot.
What do you do? You got something else to do.
High speed ride
lets you ride your monster at high speed
in order to avoid enemies.
How does that mean? Okay, anybody hungry?
All right, tournament time.
It's a passive or something,
somehow.
It's some kind of passive.
We're presenting the cup.
Who will rise?
It's the same dialogue every time.
All right, Pokey, Poke,
Jurl, and Cage.
Cage.
158 power, 147 defense.
You're a chump and will kill you
very easily to a point where
it is going to be...
Yeah, see you later.
I didn't even need to embarrass him.
Everybody's just afraid of me.
All right, this is Jurl.
Pretty good.
177, 172,
155, 151.
Not that strong with melee though.
All right, so you got a lot of...
Okay, I gotta be wary of your...
Why would I...
Why even...
Are they just going to give me the trophy for sitting on the bench?
Pokey, Pokey
is awful.
All right, at least Pokey Pokey is going to actually fight me.
He has the worst stats.
Pokey Pokey had the worst stats out of all of them.
The bravest, apparently.
Nasty!
All right, well, that was cute.
Back it up. Fine.
All right, don't get cocky here.
Okay, they were going to hand me the trophy and now I gotta be careful.
Just don't fucking let up.
Drift into the charge.
18 damage, that's it.
Pokey better not win.
Just do the drum again.
He's too unsusceptible to it, it's over.
All right, time to get out of this rank.
Almost died to Pokey Pokey.
That's the real question.
Only three fame, people are getting annoyed
at how easy this is for him, apparently.
Are you in a garbage
elo? Not for long.
Smurfing and almost losing.
Yeah, how many times have you guys been smurfing?
And you have to answer the phone or something
and you're playing with one hand.
Okay.
This is
who is in this one this week.
Let's get Roberto in here.
Because we gotta
start bringing people up.
Sandbag.
No, just, yeah, just do it.
Fuck it, do it, he's gonna win.
What are you gonna do this week?
Target, right, okay.
When are you gonna fuse, Wally?
I don't think I'm gonna.
So now you're ready to go to the
final tournament.
Hopefully I win that tournament.
Usually the official tournament's a no joke.
All right, you're okay, just eat. I'll give you something good.
You have a squid.
Proceed to the weekend activities, yes.
Let's pull
you out here.
Get him to D-rank.
I heard you're gonna propose to Kim tomorrow
and then pepper spray her for April Fool's Day.
Well, I don't know where
you heard that from. That's a
very odd thing to hear.
All right, Donna, a kubilik
inchara. Let's just, I don't even need to
see what they do. I'm gonna
insta-kill this person. Donna's the toothpaste.
I'm gonna go
level slash instant kill.
Well, would've been.
All right, well, if you would
not be so timid.
Good slice. Again.
These are, it's only
two matches, so it's easy. I like to do these.
For these low level ones, I should not
be doing the ones that have
four matches or three matches at least.
Just the ones with two. We already saw
you before. Didn't even get a chance.
Now we can pull him out of this
rank. And we're gonna do the same thing. I'm getting
right to see. I feel like he should be there.
Butter crunch ice cream is underrated. Butter crunch
ice cream is amazing. People say
butter pecan, but no. Get the pecans out of there.
Butter crunch is butter pecan ice cream,
but no pecans.
How are things? Need anything today?
Go ahead. Take a look around. What will
you do? All right. What do we got?
Effect.
Got any more training gadgets I can buy?
I already have this.
Tub, trampoline,
target, book.
That's the one thing I do not have.
Shit. It's one by two?
I have enough room, don't I?
How's that not enough room?
Trampoline. Which one's not gonna be used?
Oh, seven out of seven.
Oh.
This thing is so huge.
I wonder which one
I should get rid of.
Maybe the speed for now.
Just put it away.
I got everything.
I don't know.
No appraisal?
No.
Leveling intelligence.
Yeah. One of the
monsters I have is an int-based
Walle is an
intelligence-based monster.
Let's queue up some shit.
Calendar.
All right.
Here you go. Roberto.
Official tournament. Sign up for it.
And then the next
day official tournament for Vroomer.
And then Walle, who cares?
I guess Walle could do this one right here
just to get ready.
No, I want them to train.
Walle, you do this one.
Walle, go read the book.
Sorry, I wanted you to, yeah. Rest.
Tub. Tub.
Rest.
Lifeblade. Lifeblade.
Good.
Book.
Rest.
And then probably
Lifeblade.
You.
Rest. Lifeblade. Lifeblade.
Rest. Sandbag.
No.
Yeah. Sandbag. Tub. Rest.
Good to go.
You can actually read the book. You're so cute.
Hungry too. Here, come here.
He's learning.
His intelligence moves, the
green moves are the ones that are based on him.
The more intelligence you have, the more
damage those moves will do.
You understand?
Get in the tub.
You can rest. No, why?
You're fine. No, book.
Book. Double Lifeblade.
Sounds good to me.
Nice. After this,
we're gonna start to do, we're gonna hammer a tournament.
Frustrated. Oh, no.
Having trouble with the reading?
You're just doing okay.
Let's tell you you're doing a good job.
I have squid too.
Alright.
I gotta get one of these guys
to like ranks B or A.
Before they die.
He's gonna die soon.
Alright. Tub.
Frustrated. Have a rest.
Lifeblade. Rest. Good.
Just go.
That was a good amount.
Yeah, I'm gonna hammer tournaments here.
I should be able to jump up like two ranks
real quick. Just do three tournaments
and four tournaments in a row and win them all.
Summer. Week four.
Alright.
You guys are hungry now.
You can rest.
I'll feed you guys all in a minute here.
Feeding time.
Here you go.
No, no. Food.
Your favorite.
What a good boy.
You...
You're okay.
You gotta sleep?
Have a good night? Yeah, it's getting late.
We'll probably call it here in a little bit.
After another tournament or two.
It is getting late.
It's getting to be just about 2am eastern.
We will call it fairly soon here.
I at least want to rank up
two people. We're gonna start doing that now.
So this is the
tournament for Wally.
Hopefully we can bring Wally up.
A nice life increase for
Broomer. That's good.
I think everyone's good to go. Fight with Wally.
Yeah, you're good.
Good. Good.
Yeah, after
these tournaments, we'll call it a night.
And then I think I might...
I think I might get rid of Wally.
I'm not sure he's too...
He's great fusing.
I would fuse Wally with somebody else.
I'm gonna have to make somebody else.
Wally versus Yellow.
This is an intelligence-based
enemy. That's fine.
Wally's really cute, but
we'll see. If he won, he kills
this guy, maybe. Oh, Wally hasn't
moved, too.
Look at that damage.
It's like 48.
We used to see in numbers over 100.
Gatty's terrible.
This Gatty would probably give up. No.
This is really high defense. Maybe it's
good to keep him around. I wish you could unfreeze.
Because
he just has really high defense.
47.
How about the gun?
31%.
47.
I mean, this thing has the highest hit percentage.
It doesn't do very... 34
damage. Wally, come on. You're really starting to
get cold
here. And I do mean that
very, very literally.
This is the dog, right?
This dog is stuck
in, like,
wood. You know, they're like,
oh, bronze, silver. No, this isn't
your wood. How come they don't do that
shit? Why is it not wood
cloth? Cloth, wood,
stone, bronze.
That's what it should be.
Oh, god. Joel just came in with a raid.
What's going on, guys?
Thank you, Joel.
We are currently playing
Monster Rancher 4. Hope you had a
good stream. I don't know what we were doing earlier.
What was Joel just streaming?
Shitposts?
A microphone game.
Well, welcome or drop. Thanks a lot again,
Joel for the raid.
It's going to be hard for me to explain what the hell is going on on the screen here.
But, if you're
familiar with Monster Rancher,
you breed monsters and you fight them
and then you miss
five to ten times in a row of your moves, because they're only
at a 27%.
And then it gets even worse, because now I'm going to
be at about, yeah, 12%.
Eventually, I will kill this.
Or I won't.
We're actually about to turn this
monster into
into Gruul.
We're going to grind him down and use him as DNA.
Because he's really proving right now
just why he
shouldn't be on the roster.
He's very cute, though.
Yeah, they made five of these
games for console.
And they made like three for DS.
And like two for Game Boy Advance.
Can you do anything? Come on.
I was just pressing
L1 right there.
Because I was really hopeful that I could bring in
one of my other teammates.
This is E rank. This is fucking Wood League.
This is a bad indicator, guys.
I was killing enemies in one hit
with the other people.
And that dog didn't even do anything. Didn't even attack.
I still won.
Grind him up. He already has D. Good stats.
I don't know. What is it?
Accuracy is just terrible.
Eight fame's not bad. See, the game can hear
you guys talking.
He won all those fights, but he still sucks. Yeah, but he does
still suck. He's really cute
and he's really funny and really cool, but he
doesn't hold a candle to either one of these two.
Like, watch.
Take a look at this. Ready?
Well, not today, but tomorrow.
Meditation. I thought everyone's good to go.
I'm kind of tired, but you really need to keep...
You can rest tomorrow.
This is Roberto has his tournament.
This is a rank-up tournament, I think, isn't it?
These both are rank-up tournaments.
They gotta be both great.
Look at those terrible... those bad increases, too.
Your siblings are doing
way better than you.
I'm gonna go skull them. Only one way.
I've been spoiling them too much.
No. Alright. No.
Let me say... I'll be happy. I'll be nice.
Tenta, thanks for five community subs, Tenta.
Tenta coming in with five subs.
Thank you.
You need to eat.
Have a potato.
They won't learn
if you are kind.
I've been pretty harsh.
You've seen me be harsh.
Alright, here we go.
Weekends, activities.
Uh, it's tomorrow.
Yep.
No competitions are scheduled this week. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Wait, hold on.
Oh, alright.
It's here and then here, right? Okay.
Don't scold Wally yet
since he just won. That's true.
So now we have...
You were planning on resting today,
but I think I'll rest you tomorrow.
What do you need?
Lifeblade.
You...
You can rest.
You... it's your tournament, so you rest, too.
Yeah.
And then we'll give you...
We'll give you a good encouragement before you battle.
Nice.
German blocked Joel in fear of the message...
Wait, what?
Prostrated? That's not good.
Well, you can relax tomorrow. You don't have to do anything.
I didn't see it. I didn't see... What did he write?
Alright, you're good. Lively focused. You're good to go.
Let's go stomp the E-Ring.
This is an official grade E competition.
We should do this fairly easily.
Why am I playing Neopets?
You don't know what...
If you don't know what Monster Rancher is...
Neopets is like a...
A JPG game.
This is real animations on the screen.
You don't just...
Watch your character load as a picture on the screen.
My Neopet hasn't been fed in 10 years.
Well, that's on you.
Alright, we know all these people already.
Sunny is pretty strong.
But not as strong as Roberto.
I would assume half these people are going to give up.
I'm going to go with Double Slash.
Yeah, we've seen this before.
We've battled this before.
Watch this.
Goodbye.
You guys want to keep Roberto? No, no.
You guys want to keep...
Oh, what's that? Instantly death.
I don't have like a jokey fucking glove
come out of my clam.
And hit seven times in a row.
No. We just steamroll.
He loves you though.
Yeah, but we only have three slots.
And you can't unfreeze people.
In Monster Rancher IV
you cannot bring them back.
You can only retire them forever.
And then use them as DNA.
I don't have to look at these.
We do Double Slash into Side Slash.
And that's it.
Let the other two just carry him.
I mean, I could.
He's dead. One hit.
I don't even need to see their stats.
He's too good.
Oh, your opponent quit, by the way.
Oh, who knew?
Yeah, that the Transformer was a...
was going to be the best one.
You getting cocky? Cocky streamer?
Kind of. But I think it's worth being
cocky here, because...
I mean, seriously.
I just don't belong in this rank.
I gotta get up to D and C with
Roberto. This is way better than everybody here.
Is it Roberto of rank?
No. Rumor is rank D.
About to attempt to go to rank C.
I think I already win.
Yeah, there's no way anybody can come back.
I just have to win to beat Harris.
Alright, if I don't one hit kill
Harris, I will give 5,000 community subs.
I'm kidding.
I'm kidding. That's a joke, by the way.
Technically didn't hit him yet.
Technically didn't hit him.
I swung, but I missed one hit.
Didn't hit him.
I have to hit him. Alright, that's...
I told you it was a joke already.
I told you immediately it was a joke.
I can't do that.
I'll go to jail if I do that.
By the way, April Fools.
You believed it? Unbelievable.
April Fools.
You know those things that people say
on April Fools and it's like, whoa, what the fuck?
Is that real? Is that shit real?
Nope. Not today.
Not on this special day.
I can say whatever I want. I can tell you.
Hey, I'm like 6'2". April fucking Fools.
I can say whatever I want. Today is the day where you can say anything you want.
You already did a joke.
I ate a cereal I like.
Dude, you guys understand how much that is.
The comedy cereal was not April Fools.
It was just comedy cereal.
I just said as an April Fools joke,
I'm gonna give 5,000 community subs if I don't one hit this person.
It was an April Fools gag.
It's 25,000 dollars.
25,000 dollars.
Holy fuck.
Yeah, I get to have...
I get to have my April Fools joke.
That's what it was.
Thank god this is today.
Thank god it's like April Fools everywhere in the world right now.
Because that's my excuse.
And it's a good one.
If this was any other day.
It's the fucking liar day.
You need to press.
It's 11pm for me.
I'm speaking to you. It's midnight for you.
Why did I even say that?
I know it was like I was doing an April Fools thing but...
I'm not fucking doing that.
Are you kidding me?
That would like ruin me.
Constellation prize?
Alright, fine. I'll play Minecraft VR for like 30 minutes.
In like a week or two.
Alright, you're fed.
Uh, you're okay.
I'm gonna feed you.
Leave a carrot.
You already owe us Minecraft VR.
Five fucking thousand community subs.
Thank god it's April Fools.
What's the worst thing you've ever smelled?
One time there were eggs in the sink.
And they were wet.
And it ruined my whole afternoon.
The cooked eggs.
Yeah, wet eggs is the worst thing you could ever fucking smell in your life.
Alright, this is the one.
This is the one that actually really matters.
Because this is the go to rank C.
Only the winner will move on.
And we have rumor versus third.
Very balanced. High intelligence.
Decent speed.
But what about me?
216, 194.
Come on, I'm unstoppable here.
Never forget the five thousand subs.
It's April Fools.
I can say whatever the fuck I want.
Hey guys, my book will be done in like
two or three days.
It's like 1700 pages.
Whatever the fuck you want on April Fools.
All encompassing.
Any lie. You can say anything.
Tornado.
Not bad. Okay, let's go with a charge.
It's a good dodge.
Super claw.
I'm fine.
Let's head back. Let's get the guarantee here.
Zero to sixty. Sixty percent.
Get out of my life.
Colorado versus estate. I don't think we've even seen estate yet.
How do I feel about chat?
Well there's 3630 people here.
I think 3629 of them are amazing.
The one is one person. I don't know.
I'm not going to say who it is.
I hate them. There's one person here.
3602. I love
3601.
There's one person here. I don't like them.
That's the way it is.
Rumor versus estate. Estate lost the last match.
High intelligence.
Let's just burn you down with
power moves.
Joel, isn't it?
I don't want to say anything.
Thunder. Thank god.
It didn't hurt that much.
Zero to sixty. Sixty seven percent.
Get it.
That sucks to lose that. But I'm going to go for it again because
I max bet.
It was worth it. See?
I've got to chill the fuck out here.
I have no guts now.
Joel is... No, that's fine.
I told you I didn't want to say.
That doesn't mean who it is.
I'm not comfortable saying.
Holy shit.
That was a ton of damage. I've got to end this right now.
I've got to charge in right now.
Get it.
Come on. Yes. Thank god.
A huge bitch just came in.
Kristen, thanks for the fifty dollars.
Kristen with fifty bucks, five thousand bits.
They say, I hope one day you can stop
hating me.
Rewind to the riot.
Well, that implies that it's you.
Somebody else said it was ten fifty eight p.m. in Nevada.
April Fool's my butt time to pay up.
It doesn't matter.
I'm going off of... Hold on a second here.
I'm going off of
the general UTC time.
You know, the time zones like
UTC time
is just like regular time. GMT.
UTC.
What time is it UTC right now?
Six a.m.
It's six a.m. April Fool's on UTC.
That is like the general time
zone. That's the one
that everybody... UTC plus
six. UTC minus four.
I'm going by UTC.
I live in PDT.
But I make my
jokes in UTC.
I hope you're interested. High speed on
Kochi here. You live in a minus
two time zone. It's actually a minus three
time zone. You live in PST.
It's actually Pacific Daylight time now.
Read a book. I'm sorry.
Let's go.
Oh, it's another wheel.
This is like the bubblegum wheel.
Wow.
So cute. It really is.
Too bad it's going to die.
It's like a fish.
It's a bubblegum fish on a wheel.
Or like a grapefruit slice.
And if you have to rank C,
I can't wait. Who is it?
And do I even have any competition? Definitely not.
Oh, actually
Calabrino's not doing terrible.
Let's see what happens here. All right.
Calabrino is killing everybody.
Three and O.
I gotta be prepared for this.
The fish is insane to get. I have two CDs
out of like 200 that has
fish. Terrible intelligence.
Decent speed.
Really not that great.
Missed.
Sorry.
Blocked it, huh?
Can't block that.
I'm playing more of this?
I don't know. That could mean
there's a lot of meaning there.
As in, he's dead. He gave up.
So maybe you're talking about
you think this is Monster Rancher 2? This is actually
Monster Rancher 4.
If you'd like more of this, this is a
different game. Or more of this, maybe
you came here like seven hours ago.
We're still in this one. We're going to keep playing it.
I'm just making sure I cover all the bases there.
Answer all your questions.
All right. This is...
If Calabrino does this...
All right. This is bad.
I have to beat Calabrino or I don't...
Only one person wins.
None of these other scrubs matter.
All right. Here it is. This is for the championship.
For to rank up.
Why are you so good? That's why.
Okay. High intelligence.
Tons of life. Just watch out for the
intelligence moves. Defense is terrible though.
All right. Just watch out for the high
intelligence moves.
Wait! You two aren't planning on
entering the competition. You've got to be kidding me.
I think you're a little late.
But I'll beat you in a single punch. Wait, is this...
Because my Calabrino doesn't
have any more time to waste on you.
Oh, this is the...
This is the lady from the beginning. Right.
This is her Calabrino.
Well, I have to beat this.
Vroomer versus Calabrino.
Right off the bat.
What was that?
Mosquitoes out tonight?
Get the guarantee thing.
63%. 0-60. Kill it.
Yes!
That was a big crit too.
All right. We're gonna go with the charge.
And end it.
All right. Fine. I'm composed.
Okay. Slow down.
I only have 22.
That's not good. That's actually really bad.
No. What? Mosquitoes out
tonight?
17. Come on.
Goodbye.
You get to do final guts more than a
final time.
You're gonna make 15 of these?
Oh my god. Why?
Don't you dare.
Two fucking revives.
Oh, what we got? Fucking mosquitoes out tonight?
All right. Okay. That's not good. This is actually really fucking bad.
This is terrible.
I'm dead.
You got to revive twice.
What the fuck was that?
Why?
Nothing about that was fair.
He got to come back to life.
Final time.
Two final times.
That's fucking stupid.
All right. That's it. I'm going fed.
Now I have to do that all again.
That was not your fault.
That was bullshit.
Oh, yeah.
Roberto has a rank up, doesn't he?
Yeah, he does.
So annoyed by that.
The credits are gonna be long tonight, you know,
due to the 5,000 subs.
You know how fast that would go?
I'm gonna break my computer.
All right.
Let's at least get some good out of this.
And rank him up.
Everyone was such a joke.
And then you get the double final.
Wait.
What is this?
Doesn't even rank up?
What's going on?
Did I miss it?
No, this is yesterday.
What happened here?
Did I skip this?
Oh, fucking Jesus.
Look at this.
The next one's all the way in October.
Oh, no.
He did rank up. He did.
He did. He did. He did.
He did rank up. I remember.
He was so easy that he ranked up.
He's now in rank D.
Yeah, I'll save the game.
Guys, not tomorrow. The next day.
We're probably gonna play more of this.
I wanna beat this game.
So I will see you guys on
Tuesday.
We'll probably go Tuesday, Wednesday.
Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday.
I will see you guys on Tuesday.
And let's do the bits.
And there was a ton of community subs tonight.
You'll see them all in a minute here.
The guild? Oh, don't worry. I won't forget.
I won't forget about the guild. Don't worry.
We will determine what we're gonna do with Wally
in the stream on Tuesday.
Hope you enjoyed it. That was fun.
I had a blast. It's definitely better than
three. And we'll see how much
better it is than two once we get some more monsters
in the mix. But let's go back to
about seven and a half hours ago. Let's read
some of these bits. Combine
Wally. Yeah, we'll see what happens.
We'll see what happens to Wally.
Will he be used? Okay.
So now let me get this
high. Okay, there we go.
Oh, well this whole thing screwed up.
Did it? Yeah, it did.
Well, it looks like
we're gonna have to start from here.
Because my stream labs
decided to stop
showing anything.
Up until about
four hours ago.
So that's odd. But I'll just use
the other site. It's just a German
mustard site.
Where is that site?
I had a book...
I thought I had it bookmarked.
So I'm gonna link me real quick.
Why is this not in my bookmarks?
Stream labs, why do you have to do this?
It's like, it's like,
Ipokedex or something. What is it called?
I know, I know one of you guys got one.
Not the Ipokedex.
Why must you do
this to me, stream labs?
Let me see if I can pull it from here.
Yeah, because right now it's only showing me from the last like
two hours now. It's all
fucked up. Why?
What the hell?
Let's see if I can find the site.
Does anybody have a link to this site? Does anybody remember
what this site was? Because it's not in my
bookmarks. No, it's not.
That's not it. Yeah, I'm checking
my history for it. I don't know why it's not here.
We used it like, not even like a
month ago.
That is the site?
Is it? The URL changed.
Oh. That's probably why.
Oh shit, yeah.
We weren't memeing you.
I was wondering, I was like, why the hell can I not
see it? It's a .org.
The layout looks great. Yeah,
whoever put this together, with somebody in the
community, did a hell of a job.
This is beautiful.
I should just fucking use this only.
Yeah, lazy look, right?
Alright, so let's go
earlier.
So we had mostly
lost. Thank you for the 250.
I'm going to say, hey Jimmy,
any thoughts of jumping on the GTA
RP gravy train? I've been
enjoying watching it a ton and you'd probably be great at it.
We actually talked about it
not too long ago.
A few streams ago I think about how
I love RP.
I love doing routines and bits.
But
I don't really do, I don't do well with
strangers.
And when there's like more than 3, 4, 5, 6 people on
the screen, everyone's doing their own routine.
It's
almost like you kind of wait in line to tell your joke.
And I'm more comfortable
doing it with people that I know, people that I know that I know I can
bounce off of really easily.
It's not that I can't do it
or don't want to do it, but
it's just something I would rather not do.
There's nothing against
GTA RP at all. I think it's fucking fantastic
that people are able to jump on
and make these characters and have this awesome time.
It's awesome.
Don't do it with strangers.
Yeah, but then you kind of, you gotta get like in a group
of at least a few people.
I know there's a few people that
I know that do it.
Kiwo does it.
I think Kiwo's probably the only person
that I know that does
GTA RP that I could
like talk to and be like, hey, yeah,
let me join you. But don't you
also have to get like white listed?
And isn't that
the process of I would have to be on a list
and there's priority
and stuff?
It's not just something I can just do.
It's not like, hey, I'm gonna do GTA RP
tomorrow. I'd have to get like on a
like a queue, right?
On some servers?
Yeah, I mean, maybe. I feel like it's
hit its apex.
Is it still something people want to see?
I mean, maybe I would look into it and see if it was
something that was possible with a few friends or something.
Just grease your way in
with streamer charm. If I
could go in there with a few friends
and make something happen
and play off of people
that I know, then
I'm not against it.
Maybe it's worth a try.
But we did talk about it a while ago.
Like last week or so. But thank you.
Hey, Lazy Luke!
Speak of the devil. I drew a
German version of my favorite album cover. No offense
to your beautiful hair.
Let's see this. Does this look
infected? Does this look bald?
What the hell? Is this
actually a Sum 41 cover?
Sum 41?
That's fucked up.
That's not safe for fucking work.
Don't click that if you're at work.
That looks 4 a.m. Hey, don't click that
if you're at work at 2 or 3 a.m.
But thank you, Lazy Luke.
The website's fucking beautiful, by the way.
Soharv, thanks for the $2.95.
Soharv.
German, will you be reprising your role as alien engineer
frog actor in the 3D sequel to Crypt Dark?
Also, did you know that the Rat
Movie 1 and 2 are rated higher than The Godfather
1 and 2 on IMDB?
What a travesty. That should never be a thing.
I did not know that, but
yes, I think they're using
lines
from Crypt Dark
in the 3D version. I think they're
just porting lots of lines over. I haven't been asked
to record anything new
yet. Maybe
I think they're just kind of going to be using the old lines?
Because it is like a
reimagining 3D version of it, right?
We'll see. We will see.
Thank you, J
Zanye West for the $10.
Work put me in charge of monthly charity
donations, so any leftovers are going
to the Germ Research Foundation.
I'll take them.
Thanks for the $10. Appreciate it,
J Zanye West
for the $10.
Smelly Boy, thanks for the $2.50.
Remember how they got the
He Will Not Divide Us
flag one of those times by honking
a car horn near it and getting feedback
from chat? Someone's
eventually going to figure it out with
your vrooming car.
Where you are.
Uh, I think
you severely underestimate how many
busy fucking roads are
here. Derma lied about
5k subs, a new fucking user
name. God. That's just Vegas,
man. That's just the way it is.
You live near a NASCAR track.
I don't know. I have
no idea. But thank you,
Smelly Boy. Thank you, Superintendent Chalmers for the $4.
This is me
$104 I've given to you.
Took two years of being subbed and dropping
100 bits every so often to get there.
I'm not that one guy who gave
$600 in two hours,
but I at least got the boomer batch.
Take care of me, $604.
P.S.
Here's a new picture of Jupiter.
And it's a new NASA picture.
Look at that. Beautiful.
Look at that. Uh, thank you,
Superintendent Chalmers.
$600 in five seconds, $600 in
two years. It's still $600.
And it's... I'm
shocked that people
continue to pay money to me.
I just hope you still like the streams. I hope you're still
having a good time. Because
that's a lot of money to give anybody. It is.
Thank you.
And thank you so much to DubSkyDude
for the 250. Hey, Jerma, back in January
I gave bits and made a gotcha joke
saying my friend almost
died in a walk-in oven. Now
he's actually in the hospital. That's not good.
Uh, due to having
some blood clots. That's not, that's
not good at all.
Also, my dad had a heart attack on the same day.
Both are doing fine now, thankfully.
Just figured I'd share this bit of
dark irony. Stay healthy, everyone.
Well, that's... I'm glad they're doing
fine. But damn.
Thankfully they're
good. Thankfully they're good to go.
Stay healthy, everyone. That's true.
Thank you DubSky for the 250.
Glad everyone's okay.
ProcefProstar, thanks for the $5.
Play this visual novel,
but not Doki Doki Literature Club.
With a thumbs up guy.
Uh, this is not
a visual novel.
This is a monster breeding simulator.
Hey, AWildMaril, thanks
for the $25.
No message, just $25.
Thank you so much.
Cheer 10, cheer 10. 1, 2, 3,
4, 5. Thank you.
Thank you, Roguefort, for the
$11. I await his return.
And he does the beanbag
Sonic dab thing.
It's like an emote, but it's not an emote, it's like a
little... with the parentheses and stuff.
Virtual Monster Novel.
Yeah, there you go. There... I don't think
there is a beanbag Sonic in this game.
The beanbag monster, I don't think exists.
It might, maybe we'll unlock it.
We'll have to see.
Something or other, thanks for the 250.
If you fuse rumor with your dog,
would it be called the automobile?
Yeah, probably.
That's a good one.
Thank you, Freudian Weapon, for the 250.
Just $2.50, thank you
so much.
Felix, thank you, Felix Felis, for the $5.
Hey, Jeremy, I know how much you
liked the last Germacorn,
so I had a few people on the Discord make some
more variants. I just know one of these has to be
a new emote. Germacorn for life.
My god.
Okay,
the second one is Germamustard.
The first one is wild.
I like that first one.
They're all great.
They're all perfectly nightmare inducing.
That's a good Jeremy
got scared emote, isn't it?
The last one
is really good. Yeah, but the
last one is just Jerva Disgust
put on corn this time.
Thank you for those.
I need to have... I got more slots. I gotta do
a lot of artwork stuff for this
channel. We need more stuff.
Those are all great, though.
Thank you Manboy for the $2.50.
I wanted to share this image
that Kroskinael...
Kroskinael
made after discussion in the
sub-Discord. The
Fire family.
This is awesome. Fire grandpa.
Look at Babyfire.
This is great.
Fire dog. Fire dog
had better have that hair
on his tail.
You know, that's a perfect place for it.
That's wonderful.
Thank you Kroskinael.
Those are wonderful. All of those
are just so charming and wonderful. Thank you.
Feroidian Weapon. Another $2.50.
No message, just
$2.50. Thank you.
Easy Pants. Thank you for the $10
Easy Pants. Hey Jeremy Boy.
I hope you had a great time streaming today.
Quick question. Any tips on
getting fit and exercising? I want to start
living a healthier lifestyle.
Any advice would be appreciated.
Easiest advice is drink more water.
Cut out some of the bullshit that
you're eating. I know I had to make the jokes
about the fucking cereal bullshit.
But in all honesty,
cut out
all like the sugary fucking
Gatorade drinks you drink and all the
sodas. You wouldn't
believe with just like
removing like two shitty drinks
a day if you're drinking them.
Get rid of energy drinks.
Don't drink those fucking things.
Drink coffee. Just drink like black coffee
instead. Or even like a little bit
of cream, that's fine. Drink more
water. Cut out some of the bullshit.
Eat more fish.
That's, I'm serious.
That's a meme on this channel, but it's for real.
Coffee's bad for your sleeping
schedule. Well if you don't,
don't drink coffee after like 7 or like
6 p.m. If you drink coffee at like
you know, 8, 9, 10, 11
o'clock in the morning, that's fine.
I've been drinking coffee for years.
And my sleep is terrible. So don't
listen to me. Go for a walk?
Yeah. And move around too.
Don't let your body just be like complacent
and just sit. Sitting
is actually so bad for you. It just is.
You put more compression
on your spine when you sit down than when you
do anything else. Just move around.
Take a little walk. 20 minutes a day.
Not even. 20 minutes
every couple days. Take a walk.
7 and a half hours of sitting. Yeah.
And you know what I'm going to do tomorrow?
I'm going to take a walk.
I'm going to get up and I'm going to fucking do
two push-ups because that's all I can do.
But for real.
I do two miles a day and honestly I've never
felt better. There you go.
Just stay active. And staying active doesn't necessarily
even need to, you don't have to like go to the gym and lift
250 pounds in a bench press.
You don't got to go to the gym
five times a week.
Stuff as simple as just being
active is so good for
your health. Consistently
active helps.
But thank you EasyPants. Hopefully some of that
helps you. Thanks for the 10 bucks.
Garfield the Bunday Killer.
Hello Garfield. Thank you for the five dollars.
Five dollars.
Back to back here.
Another Monster Rancher sure does bring back memories
doesn't it Jerma? Remember when I began donating
all my Garphographs the day that Beam Bag
Sonic was born?
That is where you came from isn't it? It feels like
the only yesterday Garfield
started donating. Monster Rancher
4 is actually how I got familiar with this
series Jerma. I had a floating
rabbit with a mallet
as one of my monsters. It warms
it warms a cat's heart seeing
a Jerma and his pets. I'm getting all teary eyed
Jerma. All this emotion and I don't
even have a Jerma anniversary gift.
It's alright.
April Fool's Special.
Yeah it's called I'm going out with my
girlfriend. For
real. Not joke.
Garfield the Monday Killer again. Here's the rest of you five dollars.
Here I found the Garf-versary
present. That's right. Hope you like it.
Maybe even show it on stream. You don't have to
show it on stream. Okay.
Took me about a month to do.
Hope you like it. Hang it on
your wall. You must hang it on your wall.
I'm just Garfing with you mate.
Also want to thank Chat for being there and my
mother back
at the Italian restaurant.
Happy Garf-versary Jerma. Let's see here.
There's a lot of Garfields.
Why does Garfield have a Miss Piggy
Puppet? I don't understand that.
There's a penis?
Oh no there's not.
Fucking god damn it. Don't even say that.
Where?
You see how easy this is?
I can't fucking link shit anymore.
I know. Okay.
There is it. There is it. But like hey link
link. Hey hey there it is.
Oh link this place. Yeah sure.
I gotta fucking have a screening process.
But thank you Garfield.
That's wonderful. You can try.
I can trust Garfield. I can.
KXZ 501 10 bucks.
They say victory bits. Thank you.
Thank you KXZ. For the 10
dollars. Much love to you.
Garfield we trust the Flintstones.
We don't.
That was awful.
Oh I have nightmares about
that scenario.
That was so fucked up.
We don't even talk. We don't have to talk about it.
We're going to bury that. Tingy thanks for the 250.
Oh no I dropped some money.
Sherp. Oh fuck oh no. The vacuum
sucked up my bits. Sometimes.
Hey Silverflame. Thanks for the
two dollars and fifty cents. Hey Jerma Sally. I'm not
part of the mafia and can't donate
hundreds of dollars. But here's some money.
Thank you regardless.
Anywho. Today is my birthday. Getting drunk
and watching your streams is a great way to spend it.
You're my favorite entertainer in the world bro.
Keep doing what you're doing because both me and hundreds
of others love it. And you
smooches. Bye.
I hope you enjoyed yourself. Hope you enjoyed your night.
Happy birthday. Hope you didn't drink
too much. It's always
nice to kick back a few and hang
out and watch some streams. Or
stream. You know I drink on stream sometimes.
You've seen it.
There's dozens of us out here.
You got drunk on cooking wine.
Yeah. Cause I wanted to drink it.
Thank you masked hero
man for the three dollars. The other day
I sent you this video. I forgot to mention how long it
was. But I have the part
I actually wanted you to see here. Hopefully
you like it. It's a lot shorter since 21
minutes of 2D movie maker.
It's hard to stomach.
Let's see.
No this is not going to play is it?
Because I have this connected to my
Can you guys hear this? I can't.
I'm through
my Playstation 2 right now.
Let's see if I can hear this.
Can I hear this? What was it
Oh.
A slice of deep space. Moon fighting.
We all
want to see me turn into a
super saiyan.
Turn into a what?
Now it looks like
I'm a super saiyan again.
There's no visual.
Yeah well you guys have to figure out what's going on.
I have to bring out this power.
But you killed
Fleurgey. And I can't
be dealing with that.
Oh shut up.
I think that's pretty well done.
He's too strong.
But I have to beat him for Fleurgey.
Who's Fleurgey?
Time for you to taste my
final punch.
Big
Bastard
Oh hey that's kind of scary.
One punch.
Hey that was fucking crazy.
That was a fight on the moon.
Somebody said they were too high for this.
Relax don't worry.
The music's from One Punch Man. Yeah it is.
Well this makes much more sense.
Thank you Masterman
for your 3D
movie maker animation.
Sorry for making you watch that.
Why what? No it's fine.
Some of those animations are really
some of that shit takes a long fucking time in this program.
Which you guys don't understand.
Some of those like explosions and
hand beams.
That's a lot of processing power for
Windows 95 to handle.
But thank you Masterman.
And just the frame by frame that you have to do to make that
with like balls and sticks.
It's hard to do. Hey Jess you got it
thanks for the 250. Here's to fund your lucky charms.
I'd eat that too if I wasn't too lazy to put in the time
it takes to pick out all the marshmallows.
I got you.
Somebody in chat actually was like really upset.
And I kind of felt bad. They were just like why would you do
that? Like what the fuck is wrong
with you? What a waste of food.
Are you really that fucked up?
It was me.
Why would you do that?
I agree with that guy. Yeah I know.
But thank you Jess you got it.
VR Josh thanks for the 250. Jerma here's
some money to go toward your insulin
fund once you get diagnosed with diabetes after
eating balls of sugar for breakfast lunch
and dinner. Only breakfast and dinner.
But it makes me brush my teeth. I'm going to have real clean teeth.
Thank you for the 250.
Asbestos
Flask thanks for the four dollars
and two cents. Hope you have a six man
condiment battle
next rumble.
Why?
Because we talked about drinking condiments for
30 seconds. Hey
Sad Vega thanks for the 250. It was 10 58
p.m. Nevada time. We already talked
about it. We're going on UTC plus 8.
Thank you for the 250 though Sad Vega.
Pika Banana thanks for the 250.
Fun stream as always. Thanks for watching.
I'm going to get the credits rolling here.
They're probably going to go pretty fast.
Because there was a shitload of community subs
tonight. There were
I think like four or five
hundred almost community subs.
Which is insane.
Look at that.
Can't even see them go by.
That's high speed subs.
Thank you everybody that subbed and resubbed
all the community subs you guys.
You guys are too much. Thank you.
And while we see this extreme
amount of people that have subscribed to the channel tonight.
Remember when you used to read these?
Yeah I do.
Oh my god.
That's insane. Try and read them now?
Okay. Back on the agreement? No.
Impossible. Not possible.
Hey Zshpey thanks right
at the end. Thank you for the 10 dollars Zshpey.
Hello Jeremy. Just reminding
just a reminder to try
in and out since you're on the west coast.
I've had in and out a few times.
Also I'm craving some skate
from you in the future hopefully.
It's probably not going to happen. For your
fitness comments one way to get in good shape is to find a
really fun active hobby like rock climbing.
That's true. That is true.
Getting a hobby that makes you move around
is good for you if you can get
into something. Absolutely.
But yeah I've had in and out.
It is good. It is a good
little joint to get a quick berg.
I will say.
The subs are still going that fast.
How many subs is it total?
752 subs
this stream. Total.
Let me see what I have. Okay.
Oh my god. Yeah because
I was at 40
I was at like 4900 subs.
Like a 2 days ago or something.
Or 5100 or 4900 or something.
Holy shit. Yeah.
I'm
1 trillion emotes unlocked.
49? No.
4900.
Not 49000.
That's fucking crazy.
If you guys remember from
like 3 or 4 months ago
I think we crossed 7000 subs
from a bunch of gifted subs
and a bunch of like sub trains.
And I was at 4900
last week.
Yeah there was a point where
it came down but
I was up at fucking 7
damn thousand subs.
At least for a little while. It was there for a while.
Absolutely fucking insane.
Thank you everybody.
Still a couple more bits to do.
But that was
for the 10 bucks.
Talking about internet.
Hey Jermbo I've been super sick
for a while now on your VODs plus this stream
has been keeping me alive.
Anyway here's a quick interesting question for you.
What's the scariest oh shit this is
going to get my channel banned moment you've had on
the stream. Keep up the good work.
The Flintstones thing.
Definitely. Cause that was like actual
like weird fucked up
porn that like I linked to.
So it wasn't on the stream but
I like linked to a page
that had it on there. So
it definitely was that. When did this happen?
I don't know like a year or two ago?
When was that? That was like a year ago.
It was from some yeah it was from like a wiki page.
Like a McDonald's wiki character
page. When was this?
It was during Red Dead 1. That was a long time ago.
It was like more than a year ago.
But thank you Sergio. But we
were just talking about it.
Jermbo lied about 5k subs
thanks to the 250. I would have a sub if you didn't
lie. It was April Fools if I was just kidding.
It was just an extreme
crazy thing that I said that didn't mean anything.
Cause it was April Fools.
Why is it? Why does that LUL
look different?
This LUL there's two LULs
one looks like weird.
Oh that's okay.
That's the B. That's the BTTV one.
I was like did they change that right now
or something? That's the old one right? Okay.
I see.
I have better TwitchTV now so I can see it.
And hey Sweenex
thank you Sweenex for the 10 bucks. Hey Jerm
made an actual. I made an actual Jex
mix cereal box if you want to check it out. Feel free
to show it.
New
bald coin marshmallows.
That's funny.
There's a dick on there. I see a dick.
Right? But no thank you.
This is fucking awesome. Thank you so much
Sweenex. I did not put
I'm just referencing
what somebody else said earlier.
But that's going to be it guys.
I'll see you guys in
two days. I'll see you guys on Tuesday.
We will continue Monster Rancher 4.
And depending on how much we go there
we might just keep going. I don't know.
I'm into it though. I think it's fun. I think it's
interesting and I want to at least get to a point where we can
do some people together.
Special thanks to Joel.
Everybody that came over from
Joel's channel. Thanks for the raid.
See you guys real soon.
Be careful tonight
and tomorrow because people are going to be saying all kinds
of weird fucked up shit.
Like I wanted to give you guys an example before
to prepare you for it. I'm going to give
5,000 community subs.
You got to be prepared for that. I got you
with that one so you're ready for it.
But have a great night.
See you guys real soon. Take care of yourselves.
Have a good one.
Favorite species of sea creature?
Sea horse.
Do I have any pre-stream or post-stream rituals?
Pre-stream, coffee, pulse stream, bath.
Favorite album?
Demon Days by The Grylls.
Can you make some cat noises? Yeah, sure.
Least favorite food?
Uh...
I don't like soy sauce.
That thing's with soy sauce on it.
Is General Grieve going to be a German rumble? No.
What's the worst fruit?
Uh...
Like papaya or something. I don't eat it.
Fattest animal you can think of?
An elephant.
That's 8 hours. See you guys later.
Do you listen to Vinny's CDs?
Funny thing about Vinny's CDs,
it's going in.
We're going to get a monster out of Redbox.
It's literally sitting right here next to me.
So, yeah, that's
right here. That's it.
I will see you
on Tuesday.
Have a great one, guys.
Happy April Fool's.
See you soon.