Good afternoon. Welcome to class. I'm your teacher, Sternma. I'm Stern today.
I got bubblegum, get the fuck out of here. I can smell it. Hi guys. Uh-oh, internet. Uh-oh. Uh-oh.
Kind of going with the theme here. Starting streams and having them have cox problems.
But, Resident Evil 2 tonight. Looking forward to it a lot. I played the original a long time ago.
And fucking, are we going to turn off? Is this stream going to stay connected to the internet?
Well, I'm not even going to tweet this out yet. This is, they're just playing with me here. It's not actually going to happen.
I've been looking forward to it. Germa Pluto. Yeah, you moved to avoid this? Well, here's the problem. I live in North America.
It's a problem everywhere, unfortunately. I think it's going to be fine.
I'm going to do a prediction here in about five minutes. It's like it's not even, it's like it never happened.
Just take a balloon to Europe. You know, I might as well. All right, quick. What's the best state in Europe?
Somebody said Norway? Norway. I've seen a lot of Norways. London? But isn't that not even?
All right, give me a second. I'm going to go just, I'm not going anywhere. I'm actually, I'm just going to like sit here like this.
Let's turn the camera on just to as well. All right. But hold on. Let me make sure that this note like I'm not like naked in this one.
OK, I should be clothed. I am. OK, well, hi everybody. Welcome to the spring.
This is this is the portion of the stream where we sometimes just have to wait until I'm allowed to have my internet work.
And how was your Monday? I was pretty good. My hair slicked back with oil and I went like this.
I just stuck my hands into like jelly. I just went like this and I smeared it back over my fucking head.
I had to look OK today because the face cam might come on at random jump scare moments.
Two thousand drop frames. Don't do it to us again. Turn off the lights. It's the middle of the daytime, though.
I can't just turn the lights off. That's that's too much. It's too much for my brain.
I cannot sit in a dark room when it's light outside. Do it. No, I don't. It's it's daytime.
You're going to fuck with my cerebral. It's not going to do anything. There's light coming through the window over here.
My camera just auto adjusted because this this light coming. It didn't do anything. You think this is going to be scary?
No, boomer cerebral can't handle the dark. No, the boomers cerebral can't handle the red indicator that keeps popping up on my OBS.
The next time I get Internet, I'm going to ask a very specific question.
I'm going to ask, can I reach the moon in less than a tenth of a second?
And will it come back to me from the moon in less than a tenth of a second?
If the answer is no, I'm going to tell them to fuck off. Rude. I'll tell you what's rude.
You know what's rude? Charging fucking hundreds of dollars a month for a service that only wants to work like fucking 48 percent of the time.
That's pretty rude. That's real rude. Actually, it might even be goddamn illegal. It's not. That's rude. It's rude.
But it'll it'll fix itself. Don't worry.
They can't turn this back on. That looks so much worse. It looks terrible. I don't like how that looks.
In fact, let me move this where because I'm going to be like looking this way. Right.
So it needs to be like over here. That's way too far.
That's not that's good because I'm going to be like looking this way. Right.
You have to use the vlogger angle. I don't know what that means.
No, this is the one time like a year you're going to get a face cam. So let's do it. All right.
I might as well just go unless something really, really bad happens here, which I don't know if it will. It might.
What the fuck am I going to do? You know, what am I going to do?
Nothing. So let me just make sure. Let's hold on. Is this lined up correctly? Kind of is.
Let me just get it over here. Don't be mad already.
I don't know if mad is the right word. I think just disappointed is the right word.
I think the word is disappointed. But yeah.
What are we at? Ten percent of every frame drop. That's just fantastic.
What a great four hundred dollars a month service. Four hundred dollars a month.
Did you hear what I just said? That's a that's reality. Yeah.
You just heard me say that. That's Cox business. Works great, doesn't it?
No, not at all. Anyways, complain on Twitter.
No, here's what happens when you complain on Twitter, guys.
They have like people that automatically just watch.
Doesn't matter if it's Comcast, Cox, Disney Quest, whatever internet you have. It doesn't matter.
There are people that just scope through and try to find people put in hashtags of like hashtag Cox sucks.
Comcast sucks. And these support agents just go, hey, what happened? Are you OK?
And then you reply to them and they are they are like not even like the base level of technician.
They're like the they like get you in contact with like a base level technician.
They're just there to try to get you to shut up on Twitter.
It's it's stupid. And there are a lot of people that thought that I went.
I still have Comcast. No, I went from this is a completely different company.
This is a new ISP in a new state. It doesn't matter.
It's going to be fine. It will fix itself.
It will fix itself. It will. It just for it just for dumb, stupid, random reasons.
It'll just go to like 20 percent of what we pay for for like two hours, three hours in a row.
Stealing Wi-Fi from McDonald's. You know what? It would probably be better.
Why can't McDonald's make their own Internet? Think about this for real.
I want you to think about this because people are going to be like, what are you talking about?
McDonald's has some of the fastest service ever.
You pull up to the window. You order like a bunch of food and this shit is at the window 10 seconds later.
I bet you McDonald's could get a burger to the moon and back in less than fucking five seconds if they really wanted to.
I would I would love to pay for a McDonald's Internet.
Yeah, because they made it hours ago. So so what?
They could make the Internet hours ago.
They could just get the data package and like get it in a fucking box and get it ready and then send it out to customers.
Oh, you're over here now. Hi. Hi, everybody. My name is Jeremy and this is this is called. Let's wait out the Internet.
It's a fun game we play. I've been playing it since like 2016. It's very fun.
It's an interesting thing. Resident Evil 2 sounds like a fun game to play.
It will fix. It's going to it's going to fix itself.
I know it will. Fucking Internet.
Can I have to gonna have to fucking.
Are we going to just silently be angry here until this is like working?
I might have to sit here. We're going to have to go full screen then get this off.
Look, it's ready. It's right here.
The truck is there. I'm in the goddamn truck.
I'm ready to go. And it's stalled out. Look at that.
Oh, no. Oh, no. Sorry.
There's pedestrians crossing. Can't really go anywhere.
Sorry, Claire. I can't go anywhere. Yeah.
Oh, yeah. This is the Internet data is going across.
It's like a bunch of ducks. There's like seven thousand of we got to wait here for like four hours.
Well, let's let's go. Let's go ahead and just like do this.
Let's figure out what the hell I'm going to even do when I'm allowed to do anything.
So we got Leon or Claire. I was going to go Leon because Leon is from the original game.
Claire's from the original game, too.
But it don't use you start with Leon from the original game, right?
Do I have this is from my understanding, this is two completely different paths, right?
You got it's two completely different campaigns.
So that's OK. Do a smart click. I was going to play Leon of a huge fan of Resident Evil 4.
And this is the this is the sequel to Resident Evil 4 backwards.
So, you know, maybe if I just like go to the options menu for a while, you guys look, look, look, look.
You guys are going to make fun of my graphics settings for like 10 minutes and then we'll be able to do it.
This let me just hold on. I need to like just triple check something here.
I'm going to back out of this for a minute.
How do I exit the game? How do you exit Resident Evil 2? Is there no exit?
How do you exit? Because I need to exit to look at something, but I can't alt tab either.
How do I get out of here? Well, I was going to play Leon.
Assisted standard or hardcore assisted for players who are unfamiliar.
Aim assist recover a certain amount of health automatically and enemies are weaker.
I can't do that though. Normal. Hardcore.
Saving requires an ink ribbon, no autosave and I don't care about I don't care about the difficulty of the game.
It's the saving that I know we're not doing that.
That looks absolutely delicious. Holy shit.
Is that a triple? Is that a quadruple? One, two, how many patties are in there?
That's at least two or three patties. He's eating the he's eating the wrapper too, I think.
That's what you don't, you can't eat and drive.
You might accidentally eat the wrapper. It's happened to me a couple times.
And I'm in the passenger seat, by the way.
He's gonna crash into something. What? No, no, not good.
For a second I thought he just flew out of the car. I was like, hold on, what happened?
Truck driver with a truck driver hat on.
That's a truck on that hat, isn't there? Just in case you were wondering what he did for a living.
What's the thing with Leon? It's Leon's birthday today, right? It's like his 18th birthday.
It's his first day on the 18th birthday. There he is.
Turn up the game? I will. I just have no control over the game right now. Don't worry.
We are open. Let's go.
All right, so let me explore your surroundings. Not yet, because I need to turn this up.
How bad is it? Is the internet still fucking bad? Are we still having problems here?
Stop dropping frames. I wish I could stop it.
You know, I do have to turn the lights off. It doesn't make any sense like this.
It's a little better, right? No. I'm like so out of place here.
There we go. Let's bring this down.
Now it looks like I actually belong in here. It's like darker. It's a little scarier, right?
I can already see people making fun of my sideburn. I can see it.
I don't even have to look at it in chat. I already know you're doing it.
All right. Pray that we get our internet back, but I'm just going to go.
What can I do, right?
Okay, here we go. Explore surroundings.
Speaking of brightness, this monitor is too bright.
How do I turn the brightness down on this?
Oh, I can just turn it off. But then I can't see chat.
Hold on. I got it. Oh, you piece of shit.
There we go. All right. That's better.
And yeah, I'm going to do whatever I can to stall because like fuck this internet.
All right. Explore surroundings.
Now I can actually fucking breathe.
Now we got a fire extinguisher. We got a gas pump.
Explore. Let's go take a look at the highway.
I'm just going to walk home. Beautiful game though.
It says explore your surroundings. It didn't say how far.
Nothing out here.
Okay. See, I want to make sure I know exactly what's going on.
And we had an anonymous five gifted subs.
Thank you from anonymous.
I got to check the other way too. There could, there might be mutants out there.
Hold on. I see an item in the distance.
That is a twinkling item on the ground over there.
And half of you guys didn't even do that.
See it all the way down there. You see the red, the orange and red.
I'm going to pick it up. It's going to be an Easter egg.
And then I'm going to be on the front page of every fucking subreddit.
Nevermind. I have to find a way to stall.
Because this is 7,000 drop frames guys.
I've been looking forward to this game for like fucking 30 years.
And you want me to like do it with like 20% drop frames?
Okay. Here's the cop car.
I'm just, we're just going to go in.
There's hamburgers in here. This is where the guy got the hamburger.
Okay. Let's just open the door.
But wait, this is important. Is this the part?
Hello? Anybody there?
I didn't even get to say my piece. How infuriating.
Something's not right.
458. I just heard something.
Up in the ceiling.
There's a guy crawling around in like the vent right now.
All right. Let's take a look around.
Ketchup.
Now that's all right. That's Heinz 57 sauce.
It's gross.
But after you eat it for more than like a couple minutes,
like four or five french fries in, you forget how gross it is.
And you start thinking it's actually kind of good.
You all right?
Don't move. I'll be back for you.
They're going to bite in the neck.
He's going to get it from behind.
Officer, you need help?
Stay back, sir. I got this.
Never take your eyes.
Oh my God. That's fucking so horrible looking.
Jesus.
Freeze. I'll shoot.
What?
That was so ridiculous.
That was every tendon.
There's points in there.
Fluid. That was horrible.
Showing off their new engine, huh?
There's a key.
Key is the inventory. Put it in here.
So you hold items and weapons, right?
Okay. Fine.
Escape from the store.
I might have to adjust the sensitivity on the...
Okay, I thought the shadow was a person.
God damn it. Where is he?
Oh, fuck.
How?
Don't even shoot him, right?
Conserving ammo.
I've already used like 30 bullets.
Come on. There's got to be like 30 bullets in here.
The store...
The guy's going to get up.
And he's going to fucking burst through the door.
Hold on.
Let's just go through there.
When you need to use an item to unlock a door or solve a puzzle,
select the item and then use the use command.
Would make sense, wouldn't it?
He's going to die in the store.
Why would I die in the store?
Jesus.
Oh, shit. No, no, no, no. How do I...
What's the run command? What's the run command?
What's the run command?
I'm not...
That's clear.
The bullets from me, right?
Pretty good gamer reactions.
Hey, thanks.
You didn't kill those guys?
You're terrible.
I killed those guys in my place.
Hold on.
Alright, we made it out.
I win. I win. I win.
Huge bits from Great Canadian.
I'm Chris Redfield's daughter, right?
Whatever it is.
Thank you, Great Canadian, for the $50.
Twitch let me resub for free for some reason.
So this will cover it, I hope.
Cover it, like, 50 times.
Thank you so much, Great Canadian.
Capcom.
This is a Capcom game.
Capcom really just killing it lately.
What is this?
Just sitting on the desk.
Is it watchable? Are we alright?
Because I'm still looking over and I'm seeing, like,
the red indicator that's, like,
stop streaming Jeremy.
Resident Evil 2.
I was going to say earlier that I'm really excited for this game.
Not because of the game.
I'm trying to talk.
I mean, technically the zombies are survivors.
Right?
They're not completely dead.
Like, somehow.
They're not dead. They still have brain activity, guys.
You're not dead.
You're not completely dead.
Quick time. Are they quick time events?
That's a zombie driving a car.
Are you talking about...
Oh, no, it's not.
He's just speeding through.
Oh, he's dead.
Watch out.
Dripping oil.
Dripping gasoline.
Claire was probably in there, right?
That's what I'm thinking.
What is this?
This is loud.
We're going to have to turn the game down a little.
I remember this from the first one.
Oh, it's a guardian?
I gotta get out of here.
I gotta run.
Uh...
What's the run button?
How do you run?
I don't want to shoot. There's like 50 people there.
I just want to run.
Capcom, what's the run button?
Just tell me what the run button is.
Is there no run in this game?
Press in left stick.
That would have been great to know.
You know, just kill me.
Somebody kill me. Kill me.
Do it. Just bite my fucking neck open.
Kill me.
Just like every other game.
No, it's like B or A holding it.
No, it was actually X in the original one.
It was the face button here.
That's how Leon dies.
Let's check out Claire's side of the view.
Let's check out Claire's view.
No, wait. No, no, no.
Hold on. I wanted to...
No, that's fine.
I wanted to alt-tab before and I can't.
Just stop there for a second.
Do I really have to pull this out of borderless window
to alt-tab the game?
Because I can't move.
Hold on. Get out of the way for a second game.
Okay. Okay, okay, okay.
I'm just making sure I don't have anything open
that would be using any resources.
But I don't.
It was a long shot but it was worth a try.
Another huge amount of money just came in.
That was from
Miniclips.
Thank you, Miniclips, for the $50.
Off to a good start. Keep it up.
Thank you so much for the $50.
No, I tried to bait him.
You blame Cox for this.
Because I'm like, I'm like,
how many frames did you just drop today?
Blame this dog shit internet company.
Alright, let's go.
So which way should I go? This way?
Into the alley?
Oh, fuck.
Aging boomer can't
figure out internet.
No, it's called a bunch of fucking workers
just throw up a bunch of lines.
Bury a bunch of fucking lines.
Don't even care if it works.
They just build it. And then the company
that is responsible for it
just kind of goes, does it work?
Yeah, it technically works.
Alright, then fucking just turn it on for everybody. Who cares?
I don't know, there might be like a problem.
I think there's like water down there.
No, I fucking just turn it on for everybody. Who cares?
How much would it cost for us to like fix that?
Like 40 grand?
I don't know about that.
How much did we take in last month from subscriptions?
12 million.
No, I don't know about that.
I don't think that's worth it.
No, no, just keep it on. Turn it on.
No, hold on. I gotta pay attention. Hold on.
It's like seriously.
I bet you whatever this problem is
could be solved if just somebody
gave a shit.
You know what I mean? Like
if anybody, if anybody
from here to here just gave a shit
this wouldn't happen.
Oh, I remember this place. This is the police station.
Jerma is mad.
I am because it's fucking stupid.
Hello? Is anybody here?
And they go bolts. Alright, that's six.
You get six handgun ammo.
Takes up a spot in the inventory, right?
Okay, we got a
RPD. This is the storage box.
And a save point.
Thank god I don't have to do the
hardcore ribbon shit.
Sometimes there's stuff in the boxes
but I think a key, well-worn
key. I don't
think I'm gonna need this. This is the key to the
store. Uh, probably shouldn't
have this anymore. Right?
I mean is that, that's not like a
skeleton key, right?
Do I write for IGN?
What?
Watch out! There's Chickie over there on the bottom
right camera. Check camera, no, no
camera three. Freddy's on camera
three. Go check it.
You guys wouldn't believe it.
Doesn't matter. Like when I was
in, when I was in Massachusetts
and now I'm fucking in Las Vegas. Doesn't matter.
You know how many people you have to go through
before you find the guy that's like, yeah I guess
I'll take care of that. Like
this is just like super ultra
company bullshit. There's a
guy that you have to talk to to see if you
have a real problem. Then that guy has to talk
to another guy above him about how your problem's real.
That guy then has to be
currently caring about your current situation to talk
to the guy above him to say
we have to fix the problem that's going on with the guy. Guy
five below me said there was an issue but
Guy two said it might not be an issue. Guy
eleven, that's like the regional
manager. Jerma stop it's
getting annoying. Like
this? You're talking about like me dropping
a dickload of frames.
That is annoying, you're right.
Alright put gun in circle left.
Bullets in circle right.
Alright so
do I have a knife yet? I don't think I do.
Not yet. Can you please adjust
your internet? Alright so I need
to go. Let's
So here's the map.
The map is very useful
for more than just your current location and surroundings.
It will also show you points of interest in items you have found
and haven't picked up yet.
Oh that's cool. Taped box.
Goddess statue. So it will tell you pretty much
everything in the room. That's really cool.
The door over here, I wonder
if I can open it. Let's find out.
You probably have a bunch of
torrents seating. I would
be very surprised. I need
the spade key to open this door which I do not have.
So let's go take a look upstairs.
Let me see. Two doors
up here. How is this one?
This one opens. Alright isn't there like
a police chief in here?
From what I remember.
Somebody above? Alright I got the herb.
Uh
combining herbs. I'm going to have to remember
this shit. This safe.
Anybody know? No don't tell me the combination.
I don't want to know. Shit. Alright we got
a photograph here. Guide
pamphlet. Welcome to Raccoon City.
Did you know? Well we are the home
of pharmaceutical giant umbrella corporation.
Raccoon City is a vibrant and dynamic
city with a long rich history of its own.
In this guide we'll introduce you to a few more
unusual points of interest.
The police station.
Inside the police station
there are
the skipping makes my webcam look
pre-recorded. Look. Ready? It's not
one, two, three. See?
Various features like the unusual clock
tower. Yeah, yeah. This is an orphanage.
It's pretty cool.
Any more points of interest?
There is the safe. That's it.
This door needs a spade key. I don't have it.
So let's keep going.
What do we got here for Coca-Cola?
We got Campa, Arta,
food,
food.
Crack open a food soda.
It's also across the hall.
And then I could leave and
check the other parts of the town.
But let's just see what's up here first.
Another puzzle with some
dials on it.
All information that will be presented
in some way or another.
I'm going to have to get my notebook.
Spade key as well.
I cannot go in any of these rooms.
There are bullets up here, which is good.
And that leaves us with
going back downstairs.
Pre-recorded? Confirmed?
Oh, you want me to dab?
Well, that's not going to happen. Just use the emote
and pretend I did it. Just pretend
I did it with the emote.
So let's go back out.
This is the interrogation room.
Let's save first, just so I have a clean slate.
Can't get in there, can't get in there, can't get in there.
You dabbed?
Well, I did just wipe my nose.
You're not completely wrong here.
First aid spray.
Pick it up.
Did I miss? I didn't miss anything down here.
I better not have.
Did I crawl under here?
Alright.
It says keep out, but that's alright.
I'll go in. So you got company yet?
You got guy like number 11.
Alright, I need to fuse.
Nothing back there. Let's just go.
East office. Let's check the office.
If I can. I can't.
I'm going to be so meticulous here, guys.
I'm sorry, I have to.
What's this? Don't talk.
Why would you talk?
My press room is right here to the left.
God damn it. Okay.
Press room. Turn the lights on.
Ooh, bullets. Nice.
Only three? How did you only have three bullets?
You didn't come prepared.
Alright, finally. Good.
I can actually see what the hell I'm doing.
I can think of a pretty good joke here where I give a fake speech
like I'm talking to the press.
But it would just devolve into me talking about cocks.
So, I'm not going to do that.
No!
It's the
name of the terrible
company.
Did I miss?
All typewriter shaped objects, save points?
I guess not.
Do the speech. No, I'm not.
No speeches.
No speeches, just
sunny beaches.
No speeches, sunny beaches.
Okay, I'm good. Cleaning in progress.
Hydrate.
Yep. It's over here.
Got a bathroom.
And, alright, what's in the bathroom?
It's not really going to be in the stall.
But there was the door closing behind me.
There's going to be a person in one of these stalls.
This is a horror game.
Nope. Just the wet bandits
that's all.
No bullets or anything in here? Why even let me come in here?
What was that?
Lantern? Can I like pick up the
lantern? No, I don't think so.
Blind. He's blind. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. What do you mean he's blind?
Did I miss something?
What did I miss?
I thought it was like hairspray. I didn't think it was like
a healing item.
I thought that was like shhh for your
head. I'm going to sneeze.
Okay.
What's in here? Coffee.
I could use some right now.
Jesus.
This is something wrong here.
This is something
wrong here. I'm just going to leave
it. Maybe I can shoot it off.
It's possible. Although that's a waste
of a bullet, isn't it? We just had
five community subs come in from Herbert.
Thank you, Herbert, for the five community subs.
Congratulations to all of you that got a community
sub.
Where?
No, wrong one. Sorry.
Are you still alive?
I can't open the door, dude. I'm sorry. The door
is locked. Just he's blocking
it with his body.
Oh, he's talking about here.
I've got cash.
I'll take that cash.
Quick. Put him back under the rug.
Put him back under. My God.
That's disgusting. It's ridiculous.
Officers notebook.
OK, hold on. Goddess statue.
And then we get three. Three medallions.
This guy was just playing the game.
He was almost done with
figuring it out. So
the statue that goes down underneath.
So after you put the three medallions
in, you can go through underneath
the statue and then get out.
OK, so we got
some symbols here.
Which now will allow us to go to the
symbol machine and spin it around until we get
out of here. OK.
Do you have anything out here?
Whoa!
Oh, fuck. OK.
Take a left up here.
Left and then left.
No, let's get to the fuse box.
Yeah, no, that'll work. Let's go.
Jesus! They're everywhere.
Ah! Point precision. Sometimes
you have to be good at it, you know.
You've got to be prepared sometimes.
Quick time.
Brush his head.
Nice work.
There, there's the chief.
Stock sound effects.
Alright, so now I have the...
I'm not going to mention his stomach.
Hey, dude, I got some spray paint
for that wound.
Just open your mouth.
Stop.
I can't take your lightsaber.
Take it. Fine.
A Jedi never can give up his lightsaber.
Knife.
What? OK.
How do I repair it?
Do I only get one knife with one
bar of damage I'm allowed to do?
OK. Left bumper
and rod. Is it not equipped?
Interestingly enough, I'm looking at the same thing over here.
I'm looking at my...
I'm going to give you a Cox internet dog shit
reference, right?
The green is fine. I've been yellow this whole time
and then sometimes it drops to danger
for an hour straight.
What a great reference. He's still angry and he won't get over it.
I can't get over it. It's not going to happen.
Alright, so it's equipped.
OK, so you have to hit them both
to...
I guess not, OK.
I'm not using durability.
Thanks for the jump scare.
For whoever just called me.
Alright, let's go.
I've got to go back up here.
So let's see the symbols.
We can go...
Looks like I have a notebook.
Should I go lion?
Lion, witch, or wardrobe? Which one?
I'm going to go...
Lion's just right here.
So we need lion,
herb, and then dove.
This is going to take us to...
There we go.
Thank you, lion medallion.
I've got to put something in the box.
Next one is...
Lady arrow snake.
I can't do it again.
Oh, OK.
Well, might as well just put it in.
Cool.
Alright.
I need two more.
What are you playing over there?
Alright, now let's see.
I had...
East office. Let's save it.
I could use the
heal, but
I don't think I need to yet.
I could use the herb, but you can combine
herbs and shit in this game.
I'm not going to do it yet.
Why am I being selfish? Give him the first aid spray.
OK.
So, we've got...
OK, go back over here.
I don't think I can even leave this way.
Oh, no, the taped boxes right here.
That's right. Let's go check it out.
Why are my graphics so bad?
I don't think they are.
What's wrong with my graphics?
Image quality, 100%.
Anti-aliasing.
Texture quality, high.
Texture filter, high.
Mesh quality, medium.
High, on, on, on.
Medium.
High.
What's wrong?
Turned off the bloom? Turned off the motion blur?
Yeah, I'm an old Counter-Strike pro, guys.
I don't put on graphics.
I can see better when there's not a bunch of bloom and shit.
Alright.
I was about to potentially just waste.
Film grain is not on?
What do you mean?
Film grain?
The film grain is off.
At least I thought I turned it off.
Film noise is off? What?
Put it on!
Alright, now let's go. Let's do this.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm such a hoarder.
Because there's yellow and red herbs too, right?
Dude on the lowest graphics.
I would never.
Alright, let's just leave.
Nothing else in here.
Okay, what do we got?
I'm not gonna, no.
I'm not doing the 3DS port joke again.
Here, I'll do,
here's what I'll do for you.
Because one guy told me to do this.
So, one guy is gonna get it.
We'll do TAA, okay?
That actually looks worse for me.
That looks worse.
It looks like somebody blew, like, cold air
in my eyes.
Honestly, gelatin.
You got anything else you got?
What do you want to do with the window?
Okay, I need the
club key.
Something's gonna happen here.
Somebody's gonna attack me.
I'm trying to remember.
Look at how long this hallway is.
This hallway's too long for there not to be
something that comes up.
What do you want me to do with the window here?
Yep.
Okay, I was ready for it.
Open the, open the blinds.
Did you get in? Did you get in?
I think you got in. But wait, is there anything over here?
Any items? Did you get, you got in.
Okay, let's go, go, go, go, go.
They're not smart enough to follow me in here, right?
Okay, there's a way to go that way. Hold on.
What's this? Record of events.
Uh, we're turning the station into a temporary shelter
due to the massive sudden outbreak.
All police personnel have been instructed to make
the safety of the citizens their top priority.
Uh, and then all,
all hell broke loose and it went to shit.
Yeah, it is a lag stream today, unfortunately.
This is wild.
I don't think there was one drop frame at all
two days ago. It's, it's ridiculous
that like, not even two days later,
it's like barely a streamable day.
I wish there was something I could do.
Alright, I got a police station first floor
map, which is good.
Okay, open that up a lot. Good.
So, going over here, this is the safety
deposit room. Or towards
the safety deposit room.
See if I can, can I open this door?
Yep. I need like
wire cutters or something.
Okay, so can I bang a
left up here into the safety deposit
room or is that, no that was locked, wasn't it?
Can I turn the flashlight off?
Ah, what is this?
More handgun ammo?
Alright, I got a lot of ammo, so I
should be okay to at least shoot somebody once.
One bullet should be
used as a gunpowder.
Two, gunpowder times two is
handgun ammo. Gunpowder plus high grade gunpowder.
So gunpowder plus yellow is shotgun.
And then gunpowder plus
two yellows is mag
ammo. There's not a lot of ammo left
around the station to make you just spend a gunpowder you find.
Different guns require different ammo.
So pay attention when you're combining things or you won't get
what you need. Gunpowder.
Okay, I have to shoot this guy
in the head. I gotta kill this guy I think.
I have to shoot him. I have to kill him.
God damn it, really?
Okay, get me out.
Before he gets up, he might get up.
Alright, no more. Don't shoot anybody else.
Let's see what we got. We got a spade key. We got
something over here. That's a safe.
What the hell?
What the hell was that? What the fuck?
What the fuck, man? Okay.
Your mission is to unlock
your desk. The key to your success
is in the initials
of our first names.
Input the letters in order of our
desks. There are two
locks, one on each side of your desk.
Make sure you get them both.
Basically, your first task is to remember
your fellow officer's names, but you figured
that much out, right? Good luck, Leon.
By the way, it might take a little
work to get Scott to give you a straight
answer. Be glad you're not
here, rookie.
They're just fucking with me on my first
day.
In the initials of our first names,
input the letters in order of our desks.
So we got Scott.
Right? What does it say? Scott?
So, S.
So who else? Who wrote this?
S and B?
S, B?
Okay, well let's put it away.
What? Hold on.
The initials of our first names?
Does this have an S?
I'm going to have to look at everybody's
name tags. Cops are
known for their love of puzzles.
Okay, so let me
look at that one more time. Cause
we gotta go look at the desks.
Okay, this is David.
David, David Ford.
Alright, this guy's gotta die. Maybe not.
Alright, we got M.
Where are you coming from? I knew you were
gonna get up. M?
M? Oh
God damn it.
Okay, name tag.
We got N.
It's down to just me and three others.
No weapons, no ammo, and too many skirmishes.
Who are you? I don't care about any of this.
E. So, N, E.
N, E, D.
It is this one. Ned.
Okay.
And then this one is
M. I don't need to kill
you.
What is your name? What is your name?
Cool.
Give me the knife back.
God. Give me the knife.
It's almost broken.
Okay, that was George.
So that's G, R,
M.
George, George RR
Martin.
Open the desk. High capacity
mag. And
I have to take one of these.
I gotta take one of those herbs.
I have to. I hate that I have to do it.
I hate it. I'm gonna
No, but I can combine these.
Just do it. Fuck it.
I'm not taking any heals.
What did I do wrong?
Isn't that for a machine gun?
Alright, I'm getting out of here.
Where the fuck am I gonna go now?
Open this door. I can apparently.
It's for the pistol?
I saw the
mag and I thought it was
the gunpowder said that like
pistol and then shotgun
mag and I was like oh a mag for
fuck me.
I've only been on fucking Comcast. Not even
that's the wrong company. Okay.
It's alright though. I was gonna combine them anyways
eventually. So I can hold 24
rounds. Cool. Oh my god.
Oh my fucking
Jesus. The Olaf
just gave 50 community subs.
50. 50.
50. Gifting a moron.
I'm not a moron.
It's very dark in here.
Do you see how dark it is? You think you can read
a screen when it's this dark? Thank you
so much for the 50 community
subs. That's a shit load.
You are an idiot.
I'm like juggling so much stuff right now.
I'm juggling. I'm juggling with the fact
not only do I have my plane this game. I got a dark room.
I got an internet that's not working.
I had diarrhea this morning. Still have it.
It's coming up right now. I've been going
like this to try to keep it quiet.
Anyways. That's a huge amount of money. Thank you
so much. 209
109. I don't know what that means.
I think it's mo-
Thank you very much
first try. Got it?
Fucking Jesus man.
This 23,000 drop frames.
Should I even stop?
Should I just stop and do something else
because I don't want this to be like a lag
dog shit stream.
This is something I've been looking forward to doing for a long time.
Alright. What do we got? We got
prizes. Okay. This is 203.
I think it's missing.
208 is shotgun.
That one's already open.
109. 108.
106. Where is he?
103. 102.
I swear to God. Is there another
guy over here?
Let's do 108.
107. Which
is the one right there? 102.
102 and 103. Oh there is no
two. Okay. I need to find the two.
Can any of these other ones be
opened? 103? No. Two and three both gone.
So now these can be
opened until I get the
number off of the keyboard
or whatever the hell I have to do. What about this?
This is a weapons locker. I need a key
card. I don't have it.
There's a shotgun in there.
That's pretty amazing.
I don't think I can do much in here right now so
let's go back to...
Let me...
Give me one second.
Let me go take a piss. Let me figure
out what the hell I want to do about this because
it has not gotten better and I really
was going to give it like an hour or so. So we need to do
something else I think. Unfortunately
I'm sorry. Let me see
what else we can do. I was like praying
that this wasn't going to happen for this
long but it has so. I'll be right back. We'll figure
it out. Yeah it seems to have gotten
worse since I just left.
So I really don't know
what to do about it. All I can do
is continue to try to get
every ISP I've ever had
to fix their fucking internet.
So it's
stupid.
So I do apologize. I'm sorry.
I really was looking forward to doing Resident Evil 2
tonight. I was planning
on going for a long time.
But I don't know. Kind of at the
mercy of this
shit. So I'm really sorry guys.
I'm going to give it like another
20 to 30 minutes.
And if it's still doing it
if we still have problems
then we'll just go IRL and I'll just
hang out. We'll just chill and maybe play like
GeoGuessr or something.
Or something else. Maybe we'll just hang out for a little while.
We'll try again tomorrow.
I'm
going to also get in touch with
Cox as well. So let's see what
happens. So
so many subs came in too.
Thanks a lot guys.
Appreciate the patience.
So let me look what's over here.
Storage locker terminal memo.
It appears that the keypad to the
lockers terminal was missing a few keys. I suggested
the person responsible for this mess.
Find some spare keys and fix this
right now. Spare keys.
Interesting.
Spare keys. Wherever that would
be.
So locker terminal dark room.
How do I get to the dark room?
Jesus.
Somebody's going to come from the right side.
I just know it. What's this?
A heal.
I can take that. Let's open this.
Ooh what's that?
Wooden boards? Oh I thought there was a gun
taped to this.
Oh shit.
Is there a reason why that can be used to board up windows
keeping the rip-rap out?
Let's just eat the herb.
So should I board up this window?
I could board that window up.
I mean the board in that one. No.
I'm just going to save. Well he ain't getting it.
What is in here?
There's a save point right there.
Might as well do it.
It was that simple.
We saved.
Medicinal benefits of herbs.
Humans have used herbs to treat sickness and disease since the dawn
of time. In this book, we will
explore. No that's a plane.
That's just a plane.
I don't know why I thought that was like a bee or a
dog enemy in the game or something.
Green herbs have the ability to
heal basic injuries while blue herbs have
been used to treat poisoning.
As for red, they're very visually
appealing. They offer no
medicinal benefits or so it was thought
until recently.
It's well known that combining herbs
produces blends that heighten the herb's effects
but it's been discovered that red herbs can play a big
role when mixed properly.
Blue and red
produces a blend that will strengthen one's constitution.
Truly, we have just begun to realize
the full potential of these herbs and their ability to
heal the human body. Further research is sure to
yield even more fascinating results.
Red and blue is constitution.
Very cool.
And then you can do a triple herb, right?
Okay.
Well there's the gunpowder.
So do I hold on to...
I have such trouble playing these games
because I always want to hold on to everything.
In fact, I'm going to.
I'm going to store the herb.
No, I'm not. Store a heal.
Should have kept the damn key.
Alright, save it one more time.
Yeah, the red check mark. So wait, you got...
Yeah, everyone was...
Everybody was telling me that I could have used that key.
No, I couldn't have, but it has a red check mark on it.
See?
You can just discard it.
Okay. How do I discard it from...
Do I have to do it from here?
I'm not getting fucked with, right?
Okay, cool. Anything else in here that I need to do?
This is... This game's fucking good.
That it is...
It just is. Okay.
So we got some... I need a photo.
Photo.
We got some... Oh, this is a red herb.
Shit.
Okay.
Film contains evidence. Do not leave out.
So I need a photo to put in here.
And wash it so I can see what it looks like.
I'm going to store that herb.
Guarantee you. I bet you a thousand dollars.
That. An hour, two, three hours
into this playthrough, that box is going to be full of shit
that I haven't used yet.
And I'm going to be like, no, no, no. I need that for later.
I'm going to need that for later.
Later's going to come on. Dude, are you going to combine the red herbs and the blue herbs?
No, no. I might need them.
I think I'm going to need them later.
They're going to see the credits.
The credits are going to roll.
And you're going to say, dude, you never used
those blue and red herbs.
Yeah, but I knew game plus, man. It's going to be important when I need those.
I'll never use them.
So let's take a look at the map.
Item box, dark room, sink.
All right. There's so much to explore.
I can't go into
these rooms yet.
So we're going to have to take a...
Let's see. Where do I go from here?
Fuse box, entrance. How the fuck?
Upstairs, maybe?
Because they're going to bang a left and then maybe...
Oh, up the stairs. There's a stair.
I remember these stairs from the
original game. He can't open
the door, right? Gas. Dion.
Nothing. Shotgun shells.
Store room.
Portable safe.
A small portable safe. What the fuck am I going to do with that?
Portable safe instructions.
Press a button to
light up its corresponding lamp.
Yes, I'm like itching my ear. Sometimes when I have to think hard,
I go like this and itch in my
ear. Press a button to light up its
corresponding lamp. Then light them
all to open the safe.
The buttons must be pressed in a certain order. Pressing a single
button out of order will cause all
the lights to go out and you will need to start the
sequence over again.
Okay.
Press them in an order.
Examining items from different angles.
You can examine and spin it around.
Okay. So.
Let's go. Certain order.
Okay, okay, okay. Top right, bottom right.
Top right, top right, bottom right,
top left.
Yeah!
Ooh. Spare key.
What number is it? One?
Oh, it doesn't matter what it is. Okay.
One way to turn off that gas, right?
D.
D, D, D, D, D, D!
No, that was, I didn't even need to do that.
Shit. It's all right.
Oh.
I just shot for no reason. Okay.
Turn the gas off.
I don't have anything to do that with, but I do have the key
now. I can probably get something.
Let me go store. No.
No, don't even walk through it. You can't.
Let's go back to
the main room.
Ooh, what's this? Handgun ammo?
Really?
Come on. Don't like
bait me here. Just cut, just,
just get in here. I don't need to fight
this guy. I don't need to fight anybody.
Oh my god. Another fifty dollars just
came in. Let me go back to the
fifty dollars
from, from
Apocalyptic Cheeseburger.
Thank you so much for fifty bucks.
Uh, going off my last
update. My friend says he's getting more calls,
but they're already calling back telling him that they're
fixed. He was also hoping to play
Resident Evil 2, uh,
the remake tonight. And apologies to you
for working with people who don't know what
they're working with. Love you,
man. Thank you for the fifty
dollars. Thank you so much. It's a lot
of money. It's so much
money. You guys have given so much.
But, no, and the thing with
uh, Cox is fixed.
Yeah, but like it should, I shouldn't have to
be like this. It
shouldn't be like this. It shouldn't be
seriously like every other stream be throwing dice
in the air to see if I'm gonna be able to turn a stream on.
You know what I mean? I think it just shouldn't be like that.
And now I, I mentioned it by name
and I just dropped a frame. Turn the
lights on in my room. Oh, here.
It is getting too dark now.
There, see? That's like
fine. That's like still okay.
It doesn't have to be like this.
No, it really doesn't. It's
just companies
loading on as
many subscriptions as they can.
And not caring about anything
but a bottom line. When you
just dump as many
possible customers as you possibly
can, you don't, it doesn't matter.
Now we need to go to the dark room.
No, no, no, no, no. The uh, safety deposit room.
Uh, so I got a new key.
Let me.
Fucking God, I forgot this guy. You know, I'm
using some bullets. I can.
Like, I'm gonna use a couple of bullets here. I don't wanna
deal with this guy anymore. Okay.
So I have a spare key.
I could do 202, which looks
like some kind of fanny pack.
208,
which is shotgun bullets.
And then I need a key card for this.
So, should I do fanny pack or what's the
109, 106?
Uh, so something I didn't do.
Okay, we'll get that.
102, 103 is another knife.
No, we didn't do two.
How can you still be alive
after that? No way.
Just stay down.
Holy shit. Okay.
Put on, put it on two.
Uh, on two.
And then we need to do 20,
203. Oh fuck,
I can't open that. 20,
208.
208, 106.
106. Except that looks like a battery.
And then I think,
I don't know what the other ones are.
Let's just get these.
208, open it up.
More shotgun ammo, good.
And then 206,
which is, what the hell is this?
Ooh.
It's a roll of film.
Back to the dark room.
Can I open this one? 103, no.
102 can be opened. Let's get it.
Which is gunpowder.
Alright, back to the dark room.
And the storage box, I'm gonna burp.
Okay.
Uh, so, wrap around
the left.
Right. Okay.
Dark room, and the storage box, good.
Bah, bah, bah.
What happened? What happened?
Why is everybody saying bah?
Got three gunpowders, gonna hold on
to them. Store the shotgun shells
because I don't have a shotgun yet, and maybe eventually
I will, but not right now.
And then we get the film. Bunch of sheep.
Bah, bah, bah.
Film canister, let's give it a try.
Use.
Okay, it's a king. Commemorative photo.
I don't get it. Is the king
with a book in his hand?
Move the camera so we can see the bullets. Oh, that's a good idea.
You're right. You are absolutely
right. See, there we go.
Okay, uh.
Back up, back up, back up, back up.
Uh, that looks okay. Alright.
So, uh, I got
a picture of the king.
Whatever that means. Let me look at
that again. So, it's
a picture of a king with a crown
and a scepter and a book.
I can't move it around. I can't flip it.
That's just what it looks like. Alright.
Oh, that's good to know. Where was
that? Was there a
guy with a book that I
missed? Not the statue.
It's the Burger King.
The Burger King.
Alright, so it looks like
there's some windows down here. Operations room
maybe, but I can't go through there.
Now I can't see health. Re.
Uh,
I don't know if there's anywhere I can go.
Let me go back.
Uh, any new keys or anything?
Let me see. Maybe back upstairs?
Just keep your face
always over Leon's.
No, no, no, no, no.
That's not right. There's a safe
in there. There's a couple of saves.
Fuse box. I don't have a fuse box. Maybe
up here, no. Bathroom?
Break room? Watchman's
room, maybe? This is
maybe over here.
Put the cam in the corner.
Oh, we have...
...
Oh, olive oil!
Handgun bullets. Nobody knows what that is.
I'm just too old.
That's Popeye the Sailor Man.
That's just showing my age. I really am getting too
old, I think.
I don't know what the fuck that is.
Ooh! The key, the spade key.
Now we have so many more doors to open.
Nothing I can do with the, uh,
mannequin thing? Okay. What's this?
Dial lock? I can't do anything about it.
I need to find a map of this area.
What in the...
Persephire Lung? No.
To any survivors, consider this a gift
to anyone still unfortunate enough to be alive.
Keep your eyes peeled for those
creepy fucks that look like they
were skinned alive. Liquors, we call
them. They're blind as bats, but they're hearing
more than makes up for that. I forgot about the other
enemies in this game. There are, like, spiders.
There are liquors. There are...
So as long as you don't run around like a total idiot
guns blazing, you should be able to slip right by
them, probably. Either way, make
like my grandma and creep around
as slow as possible.
Anyway, not that I want to go, but duty calls
that, and I got a friend to avenge. David.
I gotta be quiet
and they're blind.
Now I'm gonna turn around, there's gonna be one behind
me. What's the sneak
button? There is no sneak button.
Yes, I apologize for the E3
demo, but I just got the
word that they're here, so...
I need you back here ASAP. Are you okay,
Martin? Back to the main hall?
I've got something to show you. It's important.
Copy that. I'll be right there. I like like a dirty
version of the original Leon.
Hey, thanks. Can I do
a Dark Souls free jump?
I guess not. Alright.
So much to look at. So much to explore.
Alright, so far I'm gonna give my first
impressions.
Kind of bad game.
I was gonna make...
It's a great game. Never mind.
Never mind. I go back
on everything I just said.
Where am I? The library? What's this?
There's a jack.
Red book! Hold on, I...
So at some point I gotta start fighting.
You know what I mean? This can't just be like a passive
playthrough.
Is he ever gonna not land a headshot?
What do you think, guys?
I mean, headshots only we're talking about. Okay,
jack this up. Fuck.
Where can I go with this? Over? Left? Right?
Can I not say I can move this one? Why can I not move
the other one?
Hey!
What do you do?
Only headshots we're talking about, guys.
I'm sorry.
So this shit in the way. I can't do it. I gotta jack that
up first. Okay.
I need that book! What can I do
here? The boards? The window
boards? Just get rid of them?
Maybe I can just get rid of the boards.
I could come back. Yeah, come back for it.
I got the key right. Yeah, that's right. That's right.
You got the right. I think it's fine.
The door's right here.
Back to the main hall.
That's so cool.
Just one giant puzzle.
I got the storage boxes right here.
Who is that?
I have no idea who that is.
Claire?
Claire.
I don't know. It doesn't ring a bell.
Dude, make a new meme
or riot. That's not how it works.
You don't just create a
meme because you feel like having a new meme.
That's not how it works.
That would not be a true new meme.
It wouldn't at all.
Alright. Gunpowder.
Keep the key.
Keep a couple of heals.
The boards. I mean
I don't
For now, I guess I don't know what to do with them.
Make a new meme or I'm unsubbing.
Nobody is ever required
to be subscribed to the channel.
I'm sorry. If you don't deem this channel
necessary to subscribe to and pay for
that's on you.
I can't tell you otherwise.
But if you're looking for a fresh new meme in
2019, you're going to miss it if you unsubscribe.
Okay. Let's go back here and get the book.
Claire's alive.
That's good to know.
Give me the book.
Streamer doesn't care about his fans.
Wait, this is the wrong, wait, wrong.
But also
different. This is the offices.
I don't know the safe combination.
So
anything else in here? Yeah, this is the safe
spring. Okay, yeah.
This is just a quicker way to get through here.
My meme stocks are dropping.
No, they're not. They're doing just fine.
Look,
it's alright. We're supposed to go through
a meme correction.
Our memes went parabolic in 2018.
There needs to be a correction.
Okay, so this is the book.
So who?
Who needs this book?
Is somebody in the main hall? Let me go look.
A handgun ammo
is in there somewhere.
Alright, waiting room, safe.
And then here's a spade door
on the other side of the waiting room. Let's go look at it.
But first, let's go
find there. Okay, is that the
Liberty that needs a book?
Where's the Burger King guy?
That's not the Burger King.
Where is the Burger King guy?
And here? No, this is like the
press room. No.
Alright, well let's just go open the
there's so much over here. Let's go open
the spade door that's over there.
So we can go back up. Save the game.
I'm back. Did you make a new meme yet?
Yeah, you missed it.
Nobody should repeat it either
because, I mean, come on.
We've got to keep that one secret for now.
Here's the spade door over
this way. Let's go check it out.
You missed it. I'm sorry.
Okay, new place.
Is somebody on the other side
of this door? I think.
Organize items.
You can discard items that have served
their purpose or any other key items with a check mark
by selecting discard. So that's it.
That's all the spade doors.
I can't do that though.
I'm just so attached to it already.
If I get rid of this, then
I can't have my, like, three key
collection. Okay.
I had to. Alright, we got two ways to go here.
Let's just try up here.
Do I have any boards? No.
Are there windows?
They might be a window, so just take it.
What's this do?
Okay, I need a crank.
I don't have a crank.
Art room. There's the king.
Nope, there's the king.
An article, the red stone.
The ruby that captivated Edward, the black
prince, the pearl that the queen of the Nile
milked dry. The diamond that led
a queen to the guillotine. There is
no end to the numbers of tales related to the
appeal of jewels.
The mysterious red stone is the latest to sparkle
among them. Like those other jewels,
this one's origin is unknown.
It's sad that it
once adorned a noble man,
noble woman's jeweled box, and was even dedicated
to a wise king. This
fall, this stone that's long been
shrouded in legacy will be on display
during auction. There are sure to
be many eager enthusiasts
there, but dear reader, one would do well to
approach with care and to
read this on another rainy day.
Shotgun.
Shotgun, shotgun, shotgun.
Alright, we've been going for like another 20
or 30 minutes. We good?
Internet fucking normal, kind
of? How are we doing?
Okay? Okay.
We'll just move on. We're not
going to talk about it, but thank you
for your patience. I really appreciate it.
There are like 3600 people here.
I'm fucking grateful and thankful for your
patience. Thank you.
Alright, so let's go. Now
I can give the Burger King his
Burger King late night menu.
What's that? King's hand.
A piece of plastic shaped
like a book. It looks like it was being held by
a hand. So this is bullshit.
This is just a replica.
This is a perfect copy.
Okay. Why can I
combine with hand?
Oh. Statue's left arm.
Fucking
wood. Can I just go find a window
to pour it up? Raid?
We got a raid? Combine
it with the book. Can you do it from the menu?
Who just came in with a raid?
Oh, I did.
No, it was all shit. It was
sham. Shamwow.
Thanks a lot, dude.
We haven't talked in a while. We got to like fix that.
We got to fix that. That's something we got to fix.
But thank you so much for the raid. Hope you
had a good stream. I thought
that they lived. Wait, you thought me and all
sham? No, we didn't live together.
What? Alright, but
thanks a lot, man. Welcome everybody.
I'm in the process of like, did you
play in Resident Evil? I can't believe
Mark's moving in with Jermo.
Oh, Diablo II
Paladin Shepter.
How's that for a reference
to a 2018 parabolic meme?
I'm getting minus two for that one. That's
a reference to 2016, which was then
revitalized in 2018.
No, sorry, 2014, which was revitalized
in 2016. And I'm referencing
a revitalized meme. That's how you know
our memes are parabolic and we've got to fucking change something
about that. Don't
sell those anymore. Don't buy those. Don't buy
any more fucking 700,000 games memes.
They're not going to be worth anything in like six months.
Alright, so now I got
the Scepter.
Now what the hell is you supposed to do with the Scepter?
Nothing else in here. No secrets.
Okay, let's go.
A jewel for your Scepter. I got a
jewel. Can I put that in the
gun? Can I like add that to
my gun to make it look cool?
Sell it. Alright, what's over here?
We have the crank that's over
here. Wait, is that a gem? Do you put a gem
in there? No, it's a crank. I don't have it.
I have a laser red dot sight.
We've gone to the art
room. There's the waiting room here.
The safe is in here. Let's just
keep moving down here. I got
full bullets.
Wait, you're fucking driving.
That guy, I don't even know how you got there.
Somebody just GTA'd over a stunt
jump and landed into the wall. I don't have
enough room for this. Alright, I got a super
herb. Hey, I got a superb
helicopter.
Claire?
You've
been standing at that door for a
long time. Alright, in the Claire playthrough
do you stand there for 40 minutes?
Claire, it's so nice to see you.
How are you doing? That helicopter
just came out of nowhere.
One piece. I'm guessing
you don't have a key in one of those fancy
pockets? Unfortunately,
no. Come on, am I gonna
do a joke here?
Grab the gate and go,
pretend you're a zombie. They had an opportunity
to make that joke. Any luck with your brother?
No, not yet. Claire,
don't lose hope. I'm sure
we're gonna find him. You know what
that means. Yeah,
our time. Claire, I think we should go. Don't worry about me,
Leon. You take care
of yourself.
You need to go, now.
Okay, let's get through
this, both of us.
Marvin, I've got a situation here.
I can't really climb that. I'm surrounded by zombies.
Marvin, do you
copy? Marvin? Marvin!
I don't think Marvin's alive.
Alright, cutting tool. Ah!
God damn it!
The stupid wooden boards!
I agree. Can I just
board this up?
This ammo, too. More
boards!
I don't need the boards. This is a boardless
playthrough. This is a real
board playthrough. I know, yeah.
Lots of action going on.
Headshots only! Got it.
No!
Give me the knife. What the fuck? I thought he was...
Honest to God, how many times do I have to shoot you in the head?
Fucking bozo.
Alright, uh, so that is...
That's good.
Back to...
There's a place where I couldn't cut before.
I gotta go back to the main room because I gotta see
if that guy's okay.
So we gotta go...
straight right, left.
Fuck! I screwed it up!
I need to heal.
Do I care about the knife?
Give me the knife. Where'd the knife go?
Why's the knife gone?
The knife just disappeared. Why?
Okay, leave.
I'm just gonna... No more killing people.
Just gotta go. All the way down.
Straight.
Ha! Ha! Ha!
It's okay. Shit!
This is blocked!
Oh, god damn it. Okay, I don't have the fuse.
Oh, I gotta go back through the press
room? Back up the stairs?
Can I... Hold on.
Uh... I haven't gone through there
yet. I don't want any
swords! Just... Fine, I'll take it.
Okay, this way.
And then I can bang a left...
No, back up the... I'll turn the light back
on. Why did I turn it off?
Change door. Oh, ooh! Okay.
Okay, out here.
Take a left.
I was supposed to take a left.
It doesn't matter. I can go in either one of these doors.
Change door.
No, the chained one is on the other side
of this door. Oh,
Jeremy.
Sometimes I wish
that you didn't have an eighth grade
fucking brain.
No, get him off! Okay.
So that takes us to take a right
and then cut the door down.
This is the east office. Let's take a look around.
Let's explore.
What the fuck is that noise?
Flash grenade.
Equip on the inventory screen to use guaranteed to daze
and stun enemies within its effective radius.
Can be used to counter attack when you
are caught by an enemy. It's great.
Left bumper and then right trigger is
throw it. WINDOW!
Alright, we're good.
And herb. I got room for it.
What else is in here? Let's take a quick look.
Got a boarded window now.
If you can't get through it, watch out for the glass.
There's probably, what's over here?
More gunpowder.
Can't take it.
Electrical part.
Mushroom. There's so many important items in here
that I can't take.
High grade gunpowder. Shit!
I have to come back here and just pick
everything up. All these are incredibly
important items. I need the fuse
to open the door to unlock here.
So what am I gonna replace or get rid of?
I love this game.
Alright. I'm fine.
I can't combine this.
I can't, I just have to throw the flashbang
at somebody. Consume the herb?
I know I gotta take the fuse, but
what am I gonna replace the fuse with? Just like fucking
put the herb up my nose?
I could throw the flashbang, but that's
not worth it.
Or I could go to storage. Where's the storage box here?
Watchman's room?
Yeah, just hold on. Hold tight, everybody.
Cause then I can,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I think so. Yeah?
Is there a storage box in here?
No? Yeah? No.
Okay, I'll take these.
Hold on.
Where's that storage box?
Yeah?
Press room? Bathroom?
I know there's one on the floor, isn't there?
Where's that storage box?
No, it's not in here.
Is it in here? Yeah?
Is it not marked?
Oh, I don't think, are all of them marked?
Oh, fuck it isn't. No, yeah, you're right.
There's one here.
That's what I'm thinking of. We're not there.
I could try to go back upstairs.
Or I'm just gonna, you know what?
Fuck it.
Oh, this is a lot. This is a lot I have to think about.
Because I need to, I have to just eat the herb.
Look, I've been doing, I've been playing so well.
The game has given me enough healing to heal.
And I'm just like throwing it right back in their face.
With such lines as, I don't need this shit.
And it's clear that I've already eaten.
So I'm not hungry.
Let's go.
I don't care. Let's go.
Don't eat it.
Just get hit one less time.
Don't you guys understand?
Just don't get hit one extra time.
And that doesn't matter.
Alright, where are you at? How are you doing?
I can hear him. He's a zombie now, isn't he?
Is somebody in here?
No, still alive. Alright, okay.
Alright, that's fine.
Storage box.
Streamer wets himself on stream.
Oh, you would know if that were the case.
Alright, I'm gonna store the ruby.
Bring the key card.
Store the...
Look at all these things I have in here.
I could just use the gunpowder or...
I could store the flash grenade.
Let me go get...
I just burp so fucking loud.
That's why I don't do face cam.
That's why I don't have mic ever.
Alright.
I want another water.
I'll be right back.
It's so dark in here.
I don't like how dark it is in here.
Can I turn the lights back on?
What's going on?
All the hearts?
Why is everybody doing hearts?
Is there any particular reason?
Show my pants.
What's wrong with my pants?
They're just regular pants.
Because you peed yourself and we feel bad.
Alright, I don't need this.
I wanna get the shotgun.
But then I'm gonna have a permanent shotgun.
What am I supposed to do?
I have to think about this stuff because then
what am I supposed to do?
Shotgun is gonna go here.
Shotgun bullets.
When do I get the inventory upgraded?
Alright, this is a very...
I like this a lot.
So we got press room.
Bathroom.
Where are the wire cutters?
Locked door.
Chained door. So I can go back here.
Let me see the...
Let me see the other floors.
Okay, so I got one more chained door
to cut.
And then that will be done.
So let me go open this chained door.
Well, Herbert
gives five community subs. Thanks a lot, Herbert.
Thank you, all of you.
You guys are fucking incredible. Thank you.
You guys are fucking unbelievable to me.
Thank you so much.
Chained door.
Because then I can get rid of that.
Let me go get rid of the pliers.
Because I'm not gonna need them more after this.
Let me set a waypoint right here.
So straight through the reception, bang a right.
Straight through the reception,
straight through the door, bang a right.
Operations room, chained door.
Okay, straight through.
Then that brings us to here.
Let me go straight all the way down to the right.
Do I have any boards? I don't have any boards.
Operations room, straight all the way down.
The windows are now open.
Now I understand why I should have boarded those windows.
Damn it!
Spin? Do I spin?
Okay.
This is why there's so many of them.
There's like 300
enemies against me right now.
Chained, this will be it. I'm gonna use it.
That's the last door that's locked up.
Yup, okay. Goodbye.
Thank you. It was very nice of you to be here
and give me the check box, but now you're gone.
What's in here?
Electr- jag- electronic
gadget. I said I was gonna
get a water and I just got another cup of coffee.
I think he might be deranged.
Alright, uh, a medium-sized
electronic gadget. Let's examine it.
Some sort of electronic gadget.
Uh, needs
a battery. A detonator for
C4 explosive. It's missing a battery.
Okay, so I'm gonna store
this until I find a battery for it.
Lobster room.
How am I doing on health? Fine.
I'm fine.
Fuck is that?
What was that? Oh, I unlocked it?
There's a flashbang in there.
Okay, locker terminal.
I got the electronic gadget.
It's a flash grenade.
All headshots. I'm
sorry, but when I went downstairs
to get some water and a coffee,
I was immediately backseated.
Like, it was- Atalix was waiting
at the bottom of the stairs for me. He was sitting there
going like this way. He knew I was gonna take a break.
And when I opened up the door and looked over, he said
it's bad if you just shoot
heads. He said, shoot up the limbs and stuff.
It'll help you. And I'm like, oh,
okay. How long have you been standing there for?
He's like, the whole time. I've just been watching on my phone
waiting for you to come down. I'm like,
alright, thanks, man.
Alright, we got the records room here. Let's go in.
I don't have that key.
Damn it, I fucking missed him.
Heart door.
Sync. Locker terminal.
Weapons locker. Ah, the weapons locker. But
I don't have enough room for that.
What's on the table? Nothing else in here
that I need. I got the electronic equipment.
I have just screwed myself
so much.
Why did you-
Ah, okay.
Weapons locker. We're gonna jump through here.
And I know I'm
a compulsive
map viewer. I know I am. But I have
to. Straight left left.
What?
Was it a dud?
Alright, I got the key card. I can finally get
rid of this now. I'll put it
in the locker. Give me the shotgun. Give me the shotgun
shells. Nice.
W870.
Let's go ahead and load it. Change weapons.
So it's down. Let's go ahead and load it.
Fucking asshole. What are you doing in here?
What is going on?
I got the shotgun. I'm fucking
like itchy and stuff. That's how you know
shit's getting all actually wild.
Okay. I need
to go
back here
to the east office to get myself
the handle and
some gunpowder. And then the valve
goes into the valve unit which was over- okay
so we gotta turn around
through west office. So through the door
turn around through door
out the other door into the main hall.
Save game.
You're not gonna get up, are you?
How you doing? You good?
Hey dude, I found a shotgun.
We're gonna be just fine. Okay.
So there- I got shotgun shells
in here. Get them out.
Wooden board. Electronic device
store it. Wooden board store it.
Gunpowder. Um,
first aid spray maybe. No. Red herb
no. Red jewel
maybe is what I'll need in here soon. I don't know.
Yo, shave tonight.
I'm not shaving ever again.
Save it. This will take us out there.
I got- I can get the valve now
which is just straight through. Go in, grab valve.
Is there a minute- enemy in
here? No. You can only hold
six bullets in a shotgun. That's fine.
This thing is broken.
No, nevermind. Let's bring this in
here. Give me the valve
which is in this office. Is somebody in the office?
I think there might be somebody lying on the ground.
No. Okay. Round
handle. Take it.
Super gunpowder. Take it.
Now, where
was that valve?
Valve was
Jack valve.
Second floor. So we gotta go
main hall. Is there a way
I can get up from here? A fire escape maybe?
No, that's too far away. We gotta go
main hall. So just go back to where I
was. Save game.
Am I doing a joke or am I just acting
weird? What do you mean?
The way he's narrating everything is
very YouTube streamer.
Am I acting weird?
Am I?
I can't even
tell.
Let's go back to the main hall. It's because I'm saying
everything I'm doing?
Is that the issue?
It's very tuber-like what you're doing.
Okay, so we get to main hall and then
I'm gonna activate this device. That's the
problem. I guess.
Okay. I need to use all this
but I'm gonna store the gunpowder. I have a lot of
gunpowder. I'm doing it again.
But I would be... How do I get over
there? Hey, you're doing great. Hey, thanks.
Is there a way I gotta go up?
Can I climb up?
I don't know. Who has any
damn idea?
I'm on the third floor now. Wrong floor.
I'm gonna go up and around here and then
down, which will take me. Okay, so I gotta go around
through the...
Yeah.
Bullets. I didn't miss anything though.
Like that. Some guys
scribblings.
Damn, those corporate assholes. They cut me off.
After all I've done for them but that's...
If that's how it's gonna be, so be it.
I'm gonna have a little fun of my own as the world
goes to shit. I boarded all those
filthy pigs up in a steel pen
and set some C4.
All I gotta do is detonate it.
Okay. It's no fun
if it's over too soon so maybe I'll give that
one raving loon something to really
squeal about. Yeah, maybe I'll
give him a little toy and tell him kill the guy
next to you and I'll spare the others.
I wonder what he'll do.
You yell about justice and pride but how
many times did you go against me, your own
superior? Okay, you're such a
good cop so good you had to die.
This is fun. I need some music
for this. Okay. So
there's people locked up somewhere?
What the hell is this? Hip
pouch. Oh.
That's exactly what I wanted. Thank god.
So that's how you increase
your size. Got it.
Grandfather clock.
Nothing else over here.
I don't want to miss anything.
So what is this going to lead to? This will lead
out to where I want to go.
Do I have any boards? No.
Unnecessary though.
Then I could be able to take
the stairs down and
there's the valve.
Interesting. I still
don't know the combination of this shit.
Dick. I have to shoot this
guy because there's nowhere for me to get out of here.
What the? I'm stooping into the
heads. I'm only shooting in heads.
Okay.
So I could heal full.
I'm not supposed
to have these. I'm not supposed to take this right now.
Metallix, I shot him in the
leg and the stomach and the groin
and I went against my own rule of headshots
only and I got bit. This is
your fault. You told me to
do this. Shoot him in the leg more
than one time. That's not what you said. You said
shoot him in the leg. And I said, okay.
Alright. Valve is back here.
Alright. There's bullets over here though.
Only a Sith. Only a Sith is
an absolute, right? That's what you would say in that accent.
Let's turn it off.
I feel like I'm missing
some things with the locker combinations.
But it's all good. Alright.
Anything I can do in here.
Hot water tank. Cool.
Dead or alive?
Yeah. Dead.
That's fine.
What is this? Gunpowder.
I'm gonna, just, I'm gonna combine it.
I have so much handgun bullets.
Might as well do it. Just on one of them, right?
Giving me
a lot of ammunition here.
So this is bringing me back here. There's a
door here and a door there.
It's one of those, shh, don't
walk silently.
Ah! What?
He just did like a street fighter move to me.
Oh my god.
I have no health now. Oh
shit. Whatever. I don't think there's anybody in here.
Keeping the shotgun out though.
I'm not gonna let that happen again.
Flashbang.
Dart. Throwing dart.
First aid spray. Alright. There's an office
in here. I'm not gonna activate that computer just yet.
What's in the office?
Internal memo.
Oh, office supply, internal relocation
notice. Heat resistant
three number combination safe.
Moved from Star's office
to West office first floor.
Right? So West office.
The combo is left
nine, right fifteen, left seven.
Nine, fifteen, seven.
Nine, fifteen, okay.
Please change the combo as soon as possible.
There's a combination of the safe downstairs.
Very cool. You guys need to
and there's the battery. That goes into
that unit. Alright, nice.
I'm making progress here.
Plenty of bullets. Some red
herb. Out of space.
No I'm not. I have so many
of those. It's worth doing at least once maybe.
Throw away
the gunpowder.
Now that's not correct.
Matilda. Wait, wait.
Do I have a CD or a thumb drive or something I need?
What about the battery?
Failed to authenticate account.
I need a USB dongle
to unlock this door.
Looks like a different gun.
Back out to where the liquor is.
Lightning Hawk times three.
So, I got a battery
and I got the safe combination to the door
to the safe down here. So, we need to go
down, which is
West Office. Safe is back
here. It's for that. So, I'm gonna get out
here and back downstairs.
Make our way to the West Office.
Let me just keep going. No, I need to get
to the save point.
Behind you. Stop doing
that. You know how fucking neurotic
I am? Don't do that. Don't
do that to me. I'll come back here after
I go back.
Right in the fucking brain!
What the fuck? He's still alive?
No!
Die, die, die, die, die, die!
What the fuck?
What was that?
What was that clown
move? He just
fucking threw himself into the corner.
Does he come through the door?
Okay, wait, wait, I'll...
He can't go through there, right?
Does the door eventually explode?
So, this is... I need the horse.
It's this right here, right here. No.
Where is it? This one.
So, it's Pisces,
fish, crab,
vase, I guess.
Give me the disc. It fits.
I really thought three
shotgun blasts point blank would do it.
Apparently not, and there's a police station
up the floor map. Nice.
I can't go in the linen room.
This is going to take me back to the library and then back down to the
main hall. Okay,
so I did everything I could do there.
Fish, crab? No, fish, then crab,
then vase.
I'm going to put this back in there and then
we'll go from there. He's not going to be
behind this door, right?
They are, though. Take a right.
Here we are. Beautiful.
Safe point. Stick it
in there. You're in Castle
Cainhurst. That's a pretty great reference,
actually. So,
gunpowder, gunpowder,
the jewels. Let me
put the battery in the detonator.
Detonator.
It looks like it's just
for C4.
Red herb. No blue
herbs. Alright, so I got
gunpowder and then I got high grade gunpowder.
Should I do one
and two? What was it? What are you doing?
What are you guys doing?
I have to increase the visibility in my room. Hold on.
Okay, that's better.
Every hour I have to increase the visibility because the sun's
going down.
BB pistol, BY
shotgun. Let's do
a BY.
Let's make some shotgun shells. Why not?
Might as well use them.
I could do it again. I'm going to do it again.
I'm one of those people that will never use
these. I just won't.
I'm so obsessed
with them. No, don't use them.
You're going to need them later. Alright.
That's a hundred dollars
from La Cranda.
Hundred bucks.
Thank you, La Cranda.
What's going on, Jerma? I hope to see you playing Fortnite
tonight with Thanos. I know I'd want
to be there. Much love.
That's not going to happen.
I'm not going to play Fortnite ever.
For any reason.
Thanos is in
Fortnite. Sometimes I forget about that.
Why?
Thank you so much
for your hundred fucking dollars. I really appreciate
it. But unfortunately
you're not ever going to see me play Fortnite.
Sorry to say.
Why is he in Fortnite?
Why is John Wick
in Fortnite? Just wait.
Mickey Mouse will be in Fortnite
in six months.
I'm going to hold on to these because
at least, yeah, because I want to save for the
machine gun. But
should I carry the detonator around
with me? That's something I don't think I want to
do. Take the first aid spray.
The jewel, maybe?
I don't know. Maybe I'll need it eventually here.
Nah, it'll be in Fortnite. Or
like Donald Duck or somebody
will be in Fortnite.
Default skin.
So now let me take a little bit of inventory
and figure out what the hell I want to do here
because now I have some options. So
I got the West office
is number one
because I have the key, the code
to the save. So let's do that right now.
What was it? 915?
Something else? 915
Somebody's in the office.
I'm going to have to blow this guy's head up with a shotgun, aren't I?
No, I'm not.
Shit!
Are you watching? I hope you're watching.
I got two on me! Am I dead?
Nah, I just saved it. Kill me.
Load game. What?
Is this one right here? Use the shotgun?
No, I can't. I need to only use that
for scary enemies. And save
scum. Oh, if I have the opportunity to, I have to,
man!
Don't get me angry
in a video game like this. Alright, nine.
It was left nine, right fifteen.
Left what?
Left...
Don't be fake numbers.
Four, five, six, seven.
Guys, it didn't tell me to go to those numbers.
It told me to turn the dials
that amount of times.
Big brain up here.
Got a big brain up here.
Nice. Alright, I got that.
Let's head back to the other room.
Excuse me.
It's open now. I'm not sure what else to do
for after that. Maybe I'll explore
a place that I haven't gone before.
Who puts a pouch in a safe?
Some fucking dummy.
Okay.
Open and locks and talking about
cocks. That's a great...
Actually, that is a great title for this stream.
Now, got an extra pouch.
Sink.
I do have the detonator.
Hmm. The detonator was up.
What room was that in?
Safe.
Jack.
A hundred.
A hundred dollars.
Again.
First, La Cranda.
Now, G-Bot. H-D-H-F-E.
Thank you for the hundred dollars.
Thank you.
It says, Hey, Jerma, if you got genderbent into a female version of you,
would you mess with the tallux and seduce him?
What? What?
I don't think
I would do that.
I wouldn't do that to tallux.
But thank you so much for the hundred dollars.
I really appreciate it.
Imagine giving money to this
evil man.
What are you talking about?
But anyways, I really appreciate the hundred fucking dollars.
You know what?
You know what would happen if I...
I'll give you an answer. If that would have happened,
I would just be the same person I am right now.
What would change?
Not much. Alright, save it.
Alright, so.
We're gonna go back to the detonator room.
Which is up here. Right?
Combat knife in there. We got
pirate room.
Crank handle slot.
I have not been in this area.
But I don't know if I can. I need the crank to get up here.
So I can't really go over here.
Um.
I feel like I have to do something with this.
Or maybe up another floor?
Dial lock?
What do I bring the detonator?
What was that message where the guy was like, I've done it!
I dropped them away! And I need a battery!
I don't know. I'm gonna go upstairs.
That's where I feel like I need to be.
Shower. Let's go up.
How we doing on ammo? Good?
Yes, sir. I have
lots of ammo. So,
we gotta go up, up, up, up, up.
Shut up.
You're not even fucking funny. You're stupid.
Nice.
I deserve it for fucking just trying to make a joke for no reason.
Just gotta get
no fucking reason. I don't know what the hell
that was. Somebody was, I was trying to make a new 2019
meme.
I don't know what I was doing. I can't tell you why
I did that. You gotta be very
careful in this game. And you can't just do that.
I don't know what the hell I was doing.
Alright.
Where do I put this detonator? It was this room.
It's dead.
Right here?
Right here. Alright, detonator.
Use. Confirm.
That's got ten seconds.
Does the whole room explode? Or just
That angered somebody.
Got it. Final medallion.
Wait, what's on the other side?
Okay. I just need to look at
the thing. It is
face, arrow, snake.
Face, a
arrow, snake.
It's the blind ones. Be quiet.
That doesn't make any sense.
Alright, I got them all. Nothing
else in here. I gotta go right down
into the main hall. Just one.
Don't have to worry about it. Don't have to freak out about it.
Just go straight.
I can't believe
that there's
one of those things in here.
When I say exit.
Oh, shotgun. Give me the shotgun.
Will you fucking die?
Oh.
Is it dead? Does it get up?
It doesn't get up, does it?
Fuck out of my way. I don't even care.
I just started the
I just sang that song from Sia.
The chandelier one.
We're not gonna go that way.
I need this.
No. Why would you have anything like that in the game?
Of all the things to have in the game.
Come on. That's horse shit.
So we gotta go down
and then back to the main hall.
Just go this way, right?
Main hall is just around the corner and back.
But where's this combat knife?
I don't care.
Save it first
because something's gonna happen. The boss is gonna drop down
in the middle of the thing.
Nemesis is gonna show up and I'm gonna
scream. You're gonna get a YouTuber scream.
You already have like five of them.
And I sang like a YouTuber. Oh my god.
Something's attacking him. YouTuber sound.
Alright. Let's put it in.
He's still alive? He'll get up after this
and I'll have to shoot him.
Alright. Put a three in.
One, two, three. One, two, three.
I can't get it out of my head.
Is he gonna get up?
I don't think so. He probably will.
It's gonna be a cutscene right here.
So it goes underground.
That's it. That's our way out.
Lieutenant Branagh!
Marvin!
It's time to go.
We need to get you
to a hospital right now.
Hospital? I think that's gonna help.
Save yourself.
You need to shoot me.
Look, we can still make it out of here together.
It's too late.
I tried, Leon.
But I couldn't stop it.
We can't let this thing spread.
It's on you now.
Just go!
I understand.
Jerm is crying.
It won't let you down, Marvin.
What a fucking actor!
Gunpowder. Got it.
This is the new little save point here.
I need help. Heartless streamer
tries to make himself cry.
What you meant to say was
incredibly talented actor shows his skill
and craft on stream.
Nowhere I were in the secret room and there's a T-bar
handle slot over here.
I don't have a T-bar. I don't have a bell.
What about the gem?
I'm just carrying the gem around still for some reason.
Let's go.
Bringing the bell.
Take out the gun.
Two ways to go. Let's go down.
Floor. Hand grenade.
This is going to kill me.
This is going to bounce back and hit me in the face.
Equip on the inventory screen to use.
Guaranteed to kill enemies within its blast radius.
Guaranteed to kill its enemies in its blast radius.
I got a guarantee.
I can't open that at all.
I need some type of key or device.
Nothing else in here.
Am I still hurt?
That's my health. Fuck, I am hurt.
Is this open? No.
Locked. Back up the stairs.
Sure.
Which takes us to...
This is the only way I can go.
Somebody up there?
Somebody's walking up top.
Boiler room.
Probably an item somewhere, right?
Machinery room.
Only one way to go.
Me?
That's me!
They took me and this is my DNA.
Where the fuck are we going?
Oh well, now it wants to go.
It wants me to go.
You gotta...
Where the fuck?
Boss? I'm finding a boss.
Are you going to give me a red herb right now?
I need healing.
What is this? Box?
Oh shit, what do I do about this?
What do I do? What do I do?
Steam? I have to blast him with steam in the face.
Guaranteed grenade.
Blast him with steam.
There's got to be something I can do to blast him, right?
Nothing to blast him.
I'll give you a blast.
You have a gun. I know, but I just want to see if there's an environmental blast.
Should I just combine these two? I'm not going to use the heal.
Just do it. Fuck it. Do it.
Don't heal. Not going to use it. Don't need it.
Where is he?
I see. I see. Right there.
Oh shit, I didn't see it.
No, he's got an eye. He's got an eye right there.
Oh fuck!
What? Show me the eye.
Where's the fucking eye?
Where's the eye?
Do you even eye up your ass or something? I don't get it.
Oh shit, where am I going?
I turned around twice.
I'm dead. See you later.
Goodbye.
Now I play as him. That was scripted.
Okay, so eye opens up.
Shoot eye and run away.
And then just kill guy.
Shoot eye.
Okay.
I probably should get the first aid, but we'll see.
Use grenade. Yeah, I understand.
Can't go through there.
Just unlocking it.
I'm going to save again.
Should I just go back up?
Let me see.
Oh shit.
Should I just go back up?
Let me see. Did I not bring the other...
I thought I had one more first aid spray.
Apparently not.
I gotta go now.
Just beat him. It's not going to be a problem.
Just fucking beat him.
I'm good.
Fuck, now I get some other way.
Left eye, middle eye, right eye, fire.
At least now I know what to do.
Alright, area, walk along.
It really is nemesis.
Just don't waste shots on him for no reason.
I don't even have an opportunity to shoot.
Alright, here we go.
FurtBernanda has 20 community subs.
Thank you so much Furt.
That's a shitload.
That is an absolute shitload of subs.
Thank you.
Always shoot in her mouth.
Not in this game.
Alright, let's do it.
Thank you so much Furt.
Congratulations to all the community subs.
I tell you.
Alright, shoot eye.
Not yet.
There's a heal right behind me.
Let's go get the heal.
Right here.
This is not a heal, but...
Which way are you going?
Alright, which way is he? I don't know which way he is.
And go, take it, use it.
Where you at?
I know how to combine, yes.
Alright, where the hell did you go?
Is he up top? Where the fuck is he?
That eye ain't opened yet.
What's it going to take?
Open your eye.
Open that eye.
Don't crush my head again.
You gotta wait for the second swing.
He swings twice.
Get the heal.
Come on.
I'm dead.
Am I dead here?
Steam. I didn't do that.
Blast him right here, right?
What's going on?
Is he getting steamed?
Wow.
Where's the eye?
Oh shit, that's a wall behind me.
Oh my god, why is he doing this to me?
He's running so fast.
Open your eye.
Goodbye.
Which way did he go?
Is he smart? Is he going to like,
wrap around this way?
He's going...
Don't go that way.
Don't get stuck here.
Are we getting even more steam in here?
Oh fuck.
Jeremy!
We're going to transform.
That was pretty cool.
That was fun. Phase two.
Somebody's watching me.
Wait, hold on. Let me make sure I didn't
leave anything here. I did.
In the corner there is a grenade.
But it didn't pick up.
Right there.
Let's reload the guns.
I got plenty of ammo left.
That's good.
Very cool.
Gunpowder.
Looks like a whole lot of nothing.
What's my health at right now?
Fine. Jeremy smells like Minecraft Steve.
I don't know what that means.
Like a piece of plastic?
Like a brick?
Minecraft Steve's not going to prison.
All the people in Minecraft that made out of blocks and shit, right?
Is he going to make a bridge to go across?
Minecraft Steve is more real than you.
What?
Minecraft Steve is made out of clay.
He's made out of dirt blocks.
So are you.
Yeah?
Have you ever seen somebody with this much like stretchy neck skin before?
When I'm like 60 I'm going to have to get that
taken care of.
Okay. Let's see. I have a lot of red herbs.
I feel like I'm going to need them for poison later.
Keep this in the inventory.
That looks good.
What about, take the boards.
I feel like I'm going to need them.
He doesn't know what red herbs do.
Yes I do. It's poison.
Red and green is anti-poison.
Red and blue is constitution.
Which I have no idea what that does.
That's not what it does.
That's incorrect.
Are you sure?
Do you have the game manual in front of you?
Because I don't.
Blue is poison.
Nice. Another pouch.
This just makes the game so much better.
Streamer admits he was wrong.
I will admit when I'm wrong.
Of course I will.
Can somebody with this much neck skin tell you
be right all the time?
No.
That means I can take, I'll take the jewel.
Okay.
You know that I'm a reptilian.
I watched his eyes during the stream
and they were going like this.
And they turned green for a second.
See Leon's eyes there?
They went like...
Parking garage.
So three and a half hours ago
I was going to save this.
And we had internet problems
and we seem to be okay now.
So the thing I was going to say back when I was like
I want to make this, I've got something I've got to say.
So in the original game there was an NPC
who was the gun store owner.
And I was really...
Did they omit that from the game?
Because he was my favorite NPC of the game.
The guy that goes, who are you?
And what are you doing here?
It better be the same voice actor.
They better have just taken that same audio file and put it over him.
That's in Claire's campaign?
Oh, that's too bad.
I think I'm going to restart the game in place Claire.
Alright, big open space.
There's probably going to be something that jumps out here.
This door looks locked.
And it is.
Don't go too fast.
Probably a liquor or something.
The guy in the trash? No.
Item in the trash? No.
There's two more doors. That door's locked.
They're all locked.
Okay. Hmm.
All of them are locked.
Fuse box? No.
Parking garage ticket? I don't have one.
Cut scene.
Boom!
Bob's face is going to get blown up right here.
From the trailer. Thank you very much.
Hey! Who is that?
Stay sharp.
Who is it? Ada!
Yep. Oh yeah.
FBI. Sorry.
Thank you. For your help.
I'm surprised you made it this far.
FBI, huh? What's going on here?
Sorry. That information's classified.
Where you going?
Do yourself a favor.
Stop asking questions and get the hell out of here.
I'm too appreciated to emotes.
Saturn?
Oh, by the way.
Just wanted to let everybody know because
there's people here, right?
The
t-shirts that I've been talking about. Remember I told you that
before January was over
the shirts are going up tomorrow.
So the shirts will be launching
if not tomorrow then Wednesday. I'm going to try to get it to work.
Try to launch the t-shirts.
Two of them. Glue Man's
coming back. And the solar system.
Because somebody brought up the solar system.
So that's going to happen tomorrow or Wednesday.
I've not figured it out yet. Make sure I get it
ready to go. But yeah.
And they will be there permanently.
So no more
three week campaigns.
And the Glue Man shirt is going to be in like
three colors. Get it if you
feel like it whenever you want. How much money
for a shirt? 20 bucks.
Or like, yeah.
Probably 20 bucks. Because I think
there's like different... I was
trying to talk to somebody at Teespring because
three years
ago when I made the shirt the first time.
It was... There's different like t-shirt
material. You can do like premium shirts
that cost more. I don't know. I
have to like look into that. But it probably
will not be more than 20 dollars.
For sure. So. There you go.
Do I accept what
coins? I don't know what that means.
Nah. A shirt on this channel
would never be more than like 22 to 25
dollars. But I'm not going to need to do that.
It'll be 20 bucks. For sure.
So where am I going?
Well, hold on. This door opened. Both doors
just opened. I could follow...
I'll follow her out. See where...
Whatever. Let's go this way. He's already
raising the prices! I just said
20 bucks. Okay. This opens that.
Which brings me to the
jail. Okay. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on.
Police station B1 map.
Nice. A lot of bullets.
Oh. Minimum bit... Oh, I see what you're saying.
No.
We talked about it why. We talked about
why before. Don't just...
Wait. Go save the game. Can I get
like a save point in the jail somewhere?
You're going to break this open.
I know you are. Should I just
take care of it? They're all
going to open. Just watch.
All these damn things are going to open.
That's going to open
them. So I need to have an escape
route here. Doesn't look like
there's any items in any of these cells.
NPC.
Hello, human. You've been here long?
Long enough. Are we
the last ones alive? No. No.
There's a few of us. That's good news
I guess. Yeah. That's of course Irons
sent you. Irons. You mean Chief Irons.
Is he still around? Who cares?
Hopefully he's somebody's dinner by now.
What do you mean by that? He's the bastard
that locked me in here. I'm sure
he had a good reason. He did.
I was about to blow
the whistle on his dirty ass. He has a full cigarette.
I added the same thing to him I guess.
Just took one hall and threw it in the trash?
On the ground? I'll make you a
deal. I'll lock this cell and I'll
give you this. Okay. There's no other way out of that parking
garage. Believe me. Sorry.
I can't do that. I have to talk
to the Chief first.
Look. We're both prisoners in this station.
I'll do it. So we can play nice
and help each other out.
Shit. It's coming.
What's coming? What's coming?
Come on. Come on. Don't be an asshole.
You need this.
Just get me the fuck out of here!
Oh, what is that? I just did a
boss. I just did
a boss. Who is that?
It was Ada!
Sorry. She's got the same
glove.
Ada, you got superpowers, huh?
Yeah, sometimes I get literally fucking mad and I
turn green. I get huge.
Just don't make me pissed off.
I don't have breakfast this morning.
Hey, you can't keep walking away from me.
I don't even know your name.
I'm Leon Kennedy.
No.
Find a way out, Leon,
before it's too late.
You're really gonna give me your full hand there.
Just say my name is L.
Name's Ada.
Okay, that's a start.
You give him one letter first and then you say I'll give you the
next letter when I see you again if you give me your first
letter. Well, I guess the deal's on.
All right, that's the
world. Pull the lever and
I'm home. Before I do that, let me make sure I don't miss
any items because they're all gonna open and I gotta
find out. I gotta get a perfect escape route.
So
that's the key
card to the parking garage,
which means I just gotta go right out the door
after pulling this.
So I gotta be prepared. I'm ready.
I'm ready. I'm ready. There's a
tool. It's like a crank.
I know where that goes.
Jail power panel.
I assume everyone knows, but since
the jail's power panel is old as hell,
we're gonna need those custom power panel parts
no one makes anymore.
There should be a few in the generator room.
There's only one of those power panel parts in the
generator room. The guy that's here to fix
the bell in the clock tower should have another.
So someone swipe, I mean ask nicely
for it please. So I have an unfortunate
thing to say. And it's actually
kind of, this really like sucks actually.
Remember a couple
days ago when I thought I was getting like a migraine?
And it's
happening again.
Wait, why is
this not open? I just did the power.
Does that not do anything?
Oh, okay.
Sometimes the
unfortunate truth about this is
sometimes I get like a string of headaches
and a string of like migraines
and then I'm fine. For like
another, like after a few days.
I have seen a doctor about it,
don't worry. But it's
kind of happening again.
Unfortunately. I get like a string
of like five, four or five days in a row where I'm
just really fucked up. But
I'm alright right now. But the
stream may have to do another one of those
ending before I want to.
But what can
you do, right? Electronic door
panel, it's that thing right there.
I can't use it. Let me look at that thing again.
Alright.
I'm gonna need those custom power panel parts.
Yeah, I've been sleeping fine.
Just taking aspirin.
Nah, I'll be good. Don't worry.
There should be a few in the, I gotta go to the generator room.
I got word that there's only one of those
power panel parts in the generator room. The guy that
the bell, the guy that's here to
fix the bell in the clock tower should have another.
So clock tower and then generator
room. Let's see what that is.
Generator room.
So we have to go out this way.
So back to the garage.
Get some, I've been drinking water.
I mean, I made the joke how I wouldn't get coffee again, but when I was downstairs
I had a full glass of water. So that's,
I don't think it's that.
But, yeah.
If I do end up stopping
prematurely, then
we will try it again tomorrow. We'll do it again tomorrow.
Okay, so
what other door, this door opened over here.
Make sure you have good posture.
Nah, I'm good. I'm good.
You're supposed to drink four gallons of water
a day.
That is not sound medical advice.
I will tell you.
It's a stray generator room. We can go up
here. Oh, no.
It gets down through the kennel.
Let me check over here first.
Shooting range.
Lunch box. I'm going to
examine that right now.
There's something inside.
And a well-worn key.
Equipment disposal notice.
Bent key no longer usable, but
can still open the car's doors and trunks
with its keyless entry buttons.
So it can open car doors and trunks.
That's excellent to know.
A message from Mr. Raccoon.
Howdy, boys and girls.
This is your pal from the Raccoon City Zoo. It's always great
to see you. Today I want to talk about
something really important. You know, my popular Mr.
Raccoon toys.
Well, I heard some bad kids have been using them for
target practice.
Bobbleheads, right? Good little
kids wouldn't be that mean, right?
Plus, it's super dangerous.
Bobbleheads. That sounds
like a Garfagraph.
It really does. But I'm going to assume
that's the bobbleheads of this game.
I'd probably be correct, right?
There's one right there. After you
shoot ten of them, eight of them, whatever,
you get probably a gun, right?
I'm going to get the bad ending if you shoot them. Kind of like a waste
of bullets, unless I really care, right?
Uh, can I go this way?
Yeah.
I need a diamond key.
This guy's going to get up.
Is there a reason to come in here?
Yeah, shotgun bullets. When I pick these up,
they're going to stand up. Like every
video game ever made. No, maybe not.
Nothing on either one of you?
But I was going to get my first
impressions before I got jump scared.
This is, uh,
this is very, very good. It's very, very
sound, fun gameplay.
How everything's connected and everything
you can see everything, the doors, everything makes sense.
It's very, I would,
I would, this is great. This is a very good
game so far. It's been
fantastic. This door's locked.
You're going to fall through the floor again.
Imagine, that would be ridiculous.
At that point, I knew what was going to happen.
And I'm just pretending
for the video. You know what I mean?
This is also blocked off.
So we can go on.
Got the key and the crank.
Let's go around. Just check around the other side.
Is it a shotgun?
I thought it's just an umbrella.
I was like, new shotgun just sitting on a
bench. Alright, slow down.
Okay, finally a blue
herb. We can use that.
Focus in here. Loaded, right
loaded. There's the,
gonna be dogs here.
Watch out for space. I'm running out of space.
Mmm, the dogs are gonna be so
fast too and it's gonna...
No, oh god. Oh god, just end it.
Do it!
Go, go, get out, out, out, out, out before they break out.
They're gonna break out. They're gonna, just go, go, go, go, go, go, run, run.
Just run through. Vent?
Is it a dog door? Watch out for the dog door.
Where am I?
It's actually a doggy door.
Well, here's a crank.
That'll bring it back out here.
What is out here?
There's the generator room
over there. Let me go to the morgue first.
That fucking doggy
door. Autopsy record
number 53,477.
Found
dead in jail cell, bed by
staff. Clenched due to
a rig of mortis.
Seized to his known kleptomaniac.
He would steal
even while in jail, though that was
consistent with his clinical diagnosis.
Why do I hear shit right now?
Someone's gonna break out of one of these
fucking doors. Here we go.
Somebody's gonna be on one of these dinner
plates. Ah,
fuck. Yep, he's gonna
jump out. What are you holding?
Diamond key.
Wait! I knew it, I knew it, I
knew it, I knew it.
Where did you come from?
No, I didn't,
I didn't want to do that. I keep thinking it's
knife. He's gonna, whatever.
Come on, where's the jackpot? There's gotta be something here.
Come on, give me a jackpot.
That's not a jackpot.
That's just a flash grenade.
Really? No jackpot?
What the hell
are these bugs?
Their faces? I don't know.
Red herb, I'll take it.
I can do three, though. Red,
blue, green.
Is a full superheal, right?
And that will
come out of all three of them.
That's a superheal and it's poison.
So we need to hold onto this until
we really, really need it.
It's a defense bonus poison heal superheal.
Good.
That wasn't really a jackpot, but I'll take it.
Nothing else in here.
Bullets are doing fine.
Alright, let's get to the generator
room. RGB
healing? Yeah.
Now, there's supposed to be a piece in here.
Right? Somewhere.
Box electronic part is one of
two. And then I gotta go to the clock
tower. Wherever that is.
Doggy door, you're not gonna
fucking fool me. I'm so paranoid
right now. Okay, so this is
on, on, on, on.
They're all on.
That didn't do anything. Maybe
on, off, on, on?
So they'll probably all have to be both
Okay, I see. So I think both need to be
in the red. So we got it on.
That's it, right? No, not quite.
There it is. Gotta hit that
sweet spot.
Where? I see the shadow!
One climbed over.
Hey!
There's a heal right there. Just give me the heal.
I got enough room for it. Why do I have
the boards? The boards are so useless
right now. I don't even need them.
Alright, bingo.
Where the fuck is the dog? Where is the dog?
He's sticking his head through the dog door.
Shit!
Oh, I hate it.
Where was it? Where was it?
I'm gonna shot it again.
Okay, so I gotta get out of here, then go all the way around
and up.
Oh, my fucking face!
Son of a bitch.
I know, really. Jesus!
Okay, we're good.
We're safe. That's all the dogs. No more dogs.
No more dog doors.
Is there another dog? That's what opened over here
and then bang it left.
Okay, I made it. Nothing else, right?
I think we're good.
There they go. That brings us all the way
up here. Oh, wow. We're back at
the main halls out here.
Very cool.
Combine. Key for the range.
Mission key for a car. Blade is bent.
I need to get to...
Let me get to a save point first and then I can go back.
There's like a break room here.
There we go.
This is...
Is there a storage unit in here?
Shit, there's no unit in here.
Electrical part. Shit.
Okay, I need a box.
Oh, I need a box.
Hey, look, there's a box.
Okay, so...
I store this for a second.
I just need... I gotta see what I got here.
Another key.
Still don't need the jewel yet.
I'm probably gonna need this.
Yeah, I have
the red herbs to combine with.
Yes, yes, yes.
Okay. Gunpowder. I got a gunpowder.
I can make some shotgun ammo, right?
Because I have one more. Do I have any yellow?
Yeah, I do. Shotgun ammo.
I can make some more pistol ammo.
Yeah, I'll do it. Why not?
Because then I can keep this one gunpowder.
This window is here to board. That's a good idea.
Don't need the flash.
There was another place down where I could
use this. Wasn't there
somewhere down on like the actual
floor here? I'm glad to be here.
Thank you.
Glad to have you. Thanks for sticking around.
If you don't organize it,
then I'm gonna be very mad.
See?
Got two boards,
45, car key,
and
I have to stop. I have to.
I'm sorry.
Sorry that we have to stop so early.
But, like, I can feel it now.
So. Kind of
annoying that this has kind of happened twice, two streams in a row.
But,
uh, I got another doctor's
appointment coming up. So I'm gonna
bring it up again. But,
uh, I'm fine. Don't worry.
I just kind of have like another weird
headache again. That like won't
really go away. So,
uh, I hate to
stop after four hours.
But I have to.
I don't want to just like do it.
I'd rather enjoy this and like be able to have
fun and hang out with you guys and actually
not have to think about like this.
So, uh, we're gonna try tomorrow.
We're gonna do it again tomorrow.
Uh, take care of yourselves if you're gonna take off.
I can still do the bits.
We've only been streaming for about four hours, so.
Uh, sorry
again that we have to stop.
Trust me, I want to
stream. But it's kind of annoying.
Really annoying, actually. But whatever.
You do what you gotta do, right?
Uh, thank you for watching. We're gonna just, we're gonna pick up
exactly right here tomorrow. Exactly
where we left off. And
we'll try again. Thank you
so much for your patience and understanding, everybody.
Uh, there's a lot of support
tonight, like there always is.
Much love to you. Thank you so much for coming out.
And I even had a day off yesterday, too.
I sure just streamed yesterday. I felt
fine. Whatever.
Uh, take care, guys.
Did I even feel fine? I don't remember.
I probably did.
Yesterday you said tomorrow. So
I'll see you again tomorrow. I want
I'm gonna complete this on stream because it's a great
game. I'm having a bunch of fun so far.
But let's do the bits.
This, uh, we don't have very much to go through, I don't think.
So, no, not really.
So it shouldn't take us too long.
We had, uh, Dala from
Timmy Tim Tam. Thank you, Timmy Tim Tam.
No bits. Go to bed.
No, we're okay.
We're okay. I can, I can do this.
I'll be good. There's only about
maybe 10 to 15 to go through
anyways. But let's, uh,
Timmy Tim Tam, thanks for the Dala.
Uh, it's a YouTube link.
Another daily conversation in
English. See what it is.
How about a drink?
How about a drink tonight?
I'd love to. Where can we
meet? How about the Relax Bar?
Alright. What time?
Is eight o'clock okay? Yes.
That's fine. I will meet you there.
I'm really looking forward to it.
Me too.
That was like a pretty normal
conversation. But thank you.
Thank you Sad Vega for the one Dala. Oh boy,
Resident Evil 2. Hope you do this hardcore.
You're robbing yourself for great experience if you don't
do hardcore first time through.
Uh, let me tell you hardcore
mode first time. Woo, will you be the
on the edge of your seat?
No, we're gonna do normal. I just wanna play through.
I don't wanna panic.
Thank you Alec for the one Dala.
Can't wait to see you scream at Mr. X.
I don't know what that is.
But, I'm, I'm sure
whatever, whoever that is.
Dork Cube, thanks for the one Dala. My brother and I
were watching back through your subscriber milestone
videos. And when I told him that
Burger Boy was married, he was amazed
that even the egg could find love.
Yeah.
Look at everybody. There's somebody out there for everybody guys.
Don't worry.
Uh, thank you Crusade for the four Dala's.
Thank you Divus for the two Dala's.
Thank you guys.
Uh, thank you Frick Nut
for the one Dala. Pause the game, I need to pee.
You can pee right now?
You get time to pee right now?
Flug Boy, thanks for the one Dala. So I honestly have been
trying to stay away from watching Resident Evil 2 gameplay.
But I couldn't stay away from watching yours.
I just wanna say after Resident Evil 7
this will be my first Resident Evil game.
And I wanna go back and play the other.
Do you think it's worth to buy the
previous consoles for it?
Uh, I don't think you need to.
At least
three or four of them have been ported, right?
Aren't there at least
a few of them that have been ported to the PC?
I don't think you have to go back to like
the old old consoles.
But they're great games.
Some of them are a little old and dated.
But
I think they're still all great experiences.
As long as you can stomach a lot of
kind of old school type of
gameplay.
Resident Evil 3 Remake is coming up for sure after this.
I would be surprised if they didn't
just do them all. Up until 4.
I mean they already kind of did one.
But not like this.
But thank you Flugboy for the two dollars.
Also sorry for the lack of bits. I hope you're doing well Jeremy.
Much love to you, Kim, and Italics, and the rest of the family.
Uh, don't worry about
a lack of money. You don't have to
you don't have to pay me.
Don't worry about that. Thank you for
sticking around. Thanks for watching. Thanks for the support as always.
Uh, robot mentality
thanks for the one dollar.
Andy's mountain thanks for the five dollars.
Hey Jeremy, are you still planning on releasing
shirts? Tomorrow or
Wednesday.
It'll be a storefront. It'll be there forever.
Because I can do other stuff besides shirts.
Uh, thank you Jeremiah
for the five dollars. I love you
Jerma, but your incompetence dishonored a great
game with Toy Commander.
Uh, that's alright.
Toy Commander was fun.
I don't need to watch Speedrun.
Appreciate the five dollars though. Thank you.
Uh, Anonilus thanks for the
one dollar. Anonilus, hey Jerma, it's the Animal Rescue
guy. Just wanted to say thanks for having people go to my
baby duck stream.
I truly didn't expect that.
Hoping a few people got cheered up by watching them. Thanks again.
For sure, yeah.
They're very cute ducks.
Everybody loves ducks. But thank you.
Uh, we had some big bits just coming
right now from
uh, Gornhole. Fifty dollars from Gornhole.
Thank you.
Here have some bits for the Bitcoin operated
doctor on the Vegas Strip. I hear he's
great at telling the future for 25 cents
a pop. What?
Thank you so much for the fifty dollars Gornhole
Adder. Is that even real?
That's not a real thing, is it?
Thank you so much.
And then the Olaf gave us
a million subs. Thank you so
much. That's so much.
So much, so much. I just said so much so many times.
But thank you.
Uh, Apocalyptic Cheeseburger.
Thank you again for fifteen dollars
and fifty on top of that.
Cox seems to have gotten the message
from my friend from Nevada.
Who works with them said there
was a surge a few
minutes ago when I asked him about it.
Really?
So that was, there was a surge?
So should I not have been
talking all that shit? Of course I should have.
Was there more money?
Lakronda, fifty dollars.
My goodness, thank you. Fifty more dollars.
You guys are showing me so much
love and so much support. I gotta get like
a full stream in here.
Four hours, four and a half, five hours. I usually
like to go for like six to eight.
Where's my goddamn stamina lately?
With these fucking migraine
things.
Thank you. They say, hey Jeremy, I love
donating to you. I plan on donating even more in the future.
I love the rush of being
noticed by somebody I idolize.
Well let me tell you one very
important thing. You don't
have to pay me to do that.
I hope you know that it doesn't matter if
you give me fifty dollars, a hundred dollars,
two dollars, five dollars. Thank you.
Like you're
allowing me to do this
and do it for a living.
You don't have to worry about paying me that much
money. I just hope you all know that.
There's no
requirement to have to give
me money so I'll
be thanking you. You know what I mean?
You being here by yourself
one out of
doesn't matter how many people.
I appreciate you nonetheless. But thank you
so much for even thinking about doing it in the first place.
That goes for everybody.
Back earlier after some
of these huge community subs.
But thank you Apocalyptic
Cheeseburger. Hopefully that
was just a problem.
And it's fine now because that would be
very annoying if it didn't go away, which it's been weird
the last week.
Thank you Meow for the one dollar. Have fun
getting spooked Jerma. I know
I did on my first playthrough. It's been pretty scary.
It's been pretty good.
There's been some decent scares.
Thank you Ike Turtle for the one dollar. The game's graphics
were very impressive. That sweaty zombie in the corner
looked very realistic
and frightening.
Also this. I look like Leon Kennedy.
Yeah, good.
From the Christmas stream. Yeah, he's a handsome guy.
Hey Solid Milk
thanks for the dollar. Cox controls
compact consumers crappy connection.
The six C's
is true.
Hey 99Trader thanks for the 10 bucks.
Hey Jerma, just hoping you're having a good time playing the game as we
are watching you get scared to shit.
Thank you for 10 dollars and yeah
I wish I could keep going.
But I need to know my own
limitations. And I've told you guys this
a lot of times. I don't, if I
know that I'm not going to be able to put forth something
that's, I don't
want to force myself to do something.
And if I know in my
brain and in my heart that I know that
I'm going to have to like force myself to
do this and kind of power through
an issue, I'd
I'd rather do it again. Just do it again.
We can just go again and
have fun. Not like, not like I wasn't
having any fun but I could, I could
just tell. I could feel it. And it's starting to happen now
too.
But that's just kind of a mentality I've always had.
But thank you so much for the 10 bucks.
Thank you Sosredo for the three
dollars. It's a clip. Let's see what it is.
He wasn't, no no I was having, I was having a
lot of fun. This game's fucking awesome.
It's just, why is this
black screen? Alright back to the dark room.
And the storage box, I'm going to confirm.
That's why I don't like the face cam.
Really.
Joel, thank, not Joel, thank you
iammonk for the one dollar. Joel has your
back.
Short people got
no
short people got
no short people got
no reason to
live.
We just had Jerma host us.
We're not going to have this.
He's got my back.
That's enough.
I can't
laugh that hard right now.
Joel, all I gotta say is one thing.
Just play it to the fucking gamer
challenge.
He's so bad at games.
Just while I'm going to turn it on, I'm going to destroy you
in the video gamer challenge.
What happened to
Jerma? He sounds sad. I'm not sad.
I'm perfectly fucking happy. Everything's great.
Except for I've developed
another headache here.
In the middle of the stream and I'm doing just alright.
I'm doing fine.
But thank you iammonk for the clip.
Mouse8, thanks for ten bucks. A jewel for your scepter.
Also examine the scepter with a winky face.
Thank you mouse8 for the
tips.
And the ten bucks. I'm not sad.
I'm not sad.
Oh my god another fifty dollars.
Holy shit.
Ace Mclase fifty bucks.
Head pain is the bane of my existence.
Thanks for the stream Jerma.
Jerma heart, Jerma heart.
Yeah, there's one
thing I really can't
handle. And it's
like head pain, like headache.
It makes anything I do impossible.
So those of you guys that get
cluster headaches and migraines and
headaches a couple times a week.
I completely feel your pain here.
I completely understand exactly.
It sucks.
Yeah, I know.
I don't want to play getting over it.
He's already getting practice. That's not fair.
How would that be fair at all?
I don't get the practice in getting over it.
He's streamed it like twice in a row now.
We gotta do something that we both have never done.
Two thanks or worse.
Yeah, those are really bad too.
There's a lot, but I don't know.
It's tough.
But thank you so much
to mouse8.
Thank you smelly boy for the one dollar. I shoveled snow.
Congratulations on the snow shoveling.
I haven't seen snow in a while.
Part of me misses it.
Thank you
yelewa.
Thank you for the one dollar.
Robot mentality, thanks for the one dollar.
Slop shop, thanks for the
ten bucks. Slop shop.
Hey Jerma, been a fan of the channel for a while.
When is the live action Jerma Rumble 2 happening?
I want it to.
I don't have a set date.
I don't have a set date for really anything.
But it's definitely something I want to do.
And that would be something that I would want to be actually
live broadcasted on Twitch
as an event.
And really go all out.
Even more so than I did last time.
Definitely something I want to do.
What about the school play?
That would be a nice precursor, wouldn't it?
But Slop shop, thank you for the twenty dollars.
You gave me another ten bucks as well.
Thank you. Right after that.
Thank you so much for the twenty dollars.
Egg Johnson, thanks for the one dollar. Please stop playing.
I want to go play the game and I can't if you're streaming.
Also, would you play Fortnite
if they added you as a playable character? No.
Hey, well I stopped streaming.
So you can go play it.
Hey, you got Egg. Egg Johnson.
You got your wish. Wish granted.
But no, I wouldn't play Fortnite
if I was a playable character.
I'd be like, oh, that's kind of cool.
And then I'd say,
where's my lawyer?
Then I would just start calling and suing everybody.
You know how quickly they'd get sued?
Sue Fortnite.
Peaceful Haley, thanks for the one dollar.
Hey Jeremy, just stopped by to say hi.
And recently, I don't know, I've been so confused
on what I want to do with my life.
I mean, I know what to do, I guess,
but starting is the hardest part.
I've been streaming, which is fun.
I'm just trying to go through more creative routes in my life.
Because all I want in life is to make myself another happy.
And yeah, I don't want to ramble,
but thanks for the inspiration.
I don't want to get creative stuff
and challenging yourself creatively.
Creatively? Creatively?
What the fuck am I saying?
There's...
There really is no right answer.
If you're stuck
creatively,
or if you want to go through more creative stuff in your life,
you kind of have to make it happen.
You know?
And he said starting is the hardest part.
Starting is probably the hardest part,
but an equally difficult part is
continuing to do things that you want to do.
And not letting
roadblocks get in the way.
Because they will, it'll happen.
But you also have to remember that
you don't have to do something
just because you think you do.
You know, there's plenty of things that I
wanted to do in my life that I didn't do.
That I wanted to do.
And you just, you have to make sure
that you have a few different interests
so that when at least one of them
works out, then you're happy.
Roadblocks in the way.
But you just want to make sure that you have
like I said, we've kind of gone over it
a couple times, and that's my opinion on it is,
make sure that you have a few interests
that you would be happy with.
And pursue them.
If one sticks, great. Awesome.
If the others don't, you have
more than one interest. Right?
I'm not saying that streaming is one of those things,
but it could be anything.
Just become the number one
roadblocks streamer.
You can do that.
But I wish you the best in life,
I wish you the best luck in whatever you're doing.
Just try. As long as you try,
and as long as you have a few things that you like,
give them all a try.
You never know. But thank you for the
$1 Haley. Thank you for the $1 to
robot mentality. Thank you.
No message or anything, but
just a dollar, thank you.
Getting close to the end here, we've got King of Acorns
for $5. Hey German, my name is Austin.
I'm a long time viewer of the streams.
Thanks for all the laughs. You are awesome.
Never stop doing what you're doing. Also, can I get
a birthday shout out? Yeah.
Happy birthday, King of Acorns.
Happy 23rd birthday.
23?
And then say LOL thanks.
You're welcome. Hope you have a great one.
Thank you Smelly Boy for the $1.
Please explain
this.
Breeze frame of
I don't know what that is. Those are green eyes?
You doctored that photo.
Thank you for the $1 though.
$2 actually.
Emooch, thanks for the $1. Hey German, much love
and I'm always happy to support the channel.
I really appreciate it. Thank you.
Mail Vallo, thanks for the $4.
Hey German, recently changed my alias.
Used to be FGWGWF.
Not sure if you remember me, I do.
Figure it was time for an actual username
and not one
that I got from slapping
my keyboard. While on the
subject, I remember you talking briefly in a TF2
video like 4 years ago
how you got your alias. Cause your name
is Jeremy. Is it inspired
by anything though?
No. Just kind of
easy nickname.
I was called and
kind of just stuck. But thank you for the
$4.
Great name change. Hey Tingy,
thanks for $2. Hey, here's $2 for express
shipping on those shirts. If you
can give Teespring a call and let them know I paid
extra. That would be nice.
I'm not in control of the shipping.
That will be on Teespring.
Freudian weapon, thanks for the $3. Not sure if this was
brought up, but your headaches might be caused by straining your
eyes on the screen. Have you considered getting
your eyes checked? Feel better, man.
Ah, but first of all, thanks for the $3.
Second of all, I've had my eyes checked. I had an eye
exam last year. Everything
is good to go. It's...
I've had headaches my whole life.
I actually got
diagnosed with migraines. I had to take
Imitrex for a little while.
I had an Imitrex nasal spray.
But I didn't like taking it anymore.
I didn't like what it did.
So... last year?
Well, I mean, it's 2019. I'm talking
like 2018, probably like
four or five months ago.
But, yeah,
it's just something that happens sometimes.
And I've had...
I've had like CT scans of my head to make sure
there's nothing really going on.
But it might be worth another conversation because
it's really annoying.
Spray gets you high.
No, it just like shuts you off. It's weird.
And when I would do...
When I would get a bad migraine and I would
do Imitrex, you're supposed to do it right when the headache comes on.
Right at the onset of a real migraine,
you're supposed to do it.
But, man, it would shut me off for like four days.
I would be just
turned the fuck off.
Groggy, messed up, sloppy,
slippery. I would be for like at least
three or four days. I hated it.
But, do not
be concerned. I know that sometimes
when I talk about medical stuff, people go
oh, fuck, are you alright?
I'm just like, no, I'm fine, I'm fine. Don't worry.
Don't worry about me.
Everything's gonna be just fine. But thank you,
Frodeon. Thank you, robot mentality for the one dollar.
Thank you, Kinky
Lil Poo Poo for the five
dollars. I'm gonna...
I can't laugh at that. I don't know what that is.
I don't know what that means. What the fuck did I just read?
Thank you for the five dollars. Thank you, Keldos
for the one dollar.
I swear this is not a gnome.
It's a Vinesauce animated thing.
Clip it.
That's a Vinny animated
geese. You wanna hear it again?
Alright, here's the whole video.
The video's like two minutes long.
I'm just kidding. But thank you for the video.
Thank you, Kinky
for the one dollar. I forgot to send a link
but I clipped the video of you killing a dog
and uploading it. What?
Oh, talking about in the game.
What the fuck?
This is like
a broken link. I can't even click this.
There's like five
spaces in here.
Why did you type W space W?
Why did you do all the spaces?
W space
W.
So what is this?
What the hell did you just give me as a link here?
You put a space between you
and two. You guys wanna know
what it was? What do you think it was?
Yeah.
That's like next level.
Alright, thank you for the dollar.
Thank you, Dr. Zoot Suit for the one dollar.
Jeremiah, I finished drawing female you.
I have sinned.
Thank you for the one dollar. Thank you, Lord Muffins for the one dollar.
Hey Jeremiah, I've been a fan for 25 years.
I would love it if you
would light by...
I'm not doing either of those things. Thank you for the one dollar,
Lord Muffin. Wizard Ribbit,
thanks for the one dollar. I need to wear Gunner Optics
to avoid gamer headache.
No, that's not what it is.
Thank you, though. Thank you, Jess, for the one dollar.
I've been keeping a library of all the sounds you've made
since the start of the year.
I was gonna keep it all...
I was gonna keep it up all year, but it's actually way more than
I thought. I have 270 sounds.
That's too many sounds.
That's more sounds than are in
the Star Wars trilogy.
Dermatantrum, what is this?
Eugh! Eugh! Eugh!
Eugh! Eugh!
That was pretty fucking close. I haven't heard that
since the stream. That was really close. That was really
good. That was on the spot.
No practice.
But thank you, though, Jess. Thank you
something or other for the one dollar. EuroGerms,
I apologize. This one hasn't come up before.
Would you ever consider doing a Germa Rumble with
community submitted characters and bios?
Seems like a train wreck.
Um...
Probably not. Probably not like a community
rumble. Because that...
I think that would get a little messy.
Great Canadian FK Club, thanks for five more
community subs. On top of the
countless amount that you currently
have, thank you so much.
But a community rumble
would get messy for the same reasons
that I think a lot of stuff like that has a tendency to get
messy. Because
let's say that there was, you know, ten contestants
or like five, twenty contestants or something that
I would be accepting.
You know, not picking somebody's
if there's like hundreds of entries.
I don't
want to make it like a competition.
The emote contest was the last real
competition in quotes.
And it was
handled pretty well.
But I don't want to like make a whole
lot of competitions. Mod
Rumble. But it's an interesting
idea. But I don't want to have a
situation where it's like, you
picked this and not mine? What the fuck?
That one sucks! And then people get angry
and you're like, well, uh...
Stuff like that is hard to make
everybody happy. And I've learned a lot
over the years.
Trying to get them to do it, trying to get it to happen
the right way. And how would I want to do
stuff like that? I've done it a couple times.
But I do like the idea.
Just the execution would need to be done correctly.
But thank you.
Thank you to
Guido for the one dollar.
I used to get those headaches a bunch too. Went away
after I got these glasses that help the
eye strain. Maybe you should try
it. I mean, it's worth a shot.
I think a long time
ago when I was doing YouTube and sitting
in front of a screen for a long time,
it did help to wear, like,
to have, like, flux on or have,
like, optics on.
Maybe I'll go back to doing it again.
But I do appreciate it. Thank you.
Flying Sombrero, thanks for the one dollar.
Hey Jerma, I was talking with this girl I recently met
about our favorite YouTubers and streamers.
I mentioned that you were my favorite streamer and she
stopped talking to me. Thanks.
Well, good. Because that
wasn't a keeper.
You know what I'm saying? Thank you
for the one dollar. Thank you, Mom
the Peach for the one dollar. Sub
today and looking forward to the future. Hope your head feels better.
Thank you. Appreciate that.
I'm gonna take some Advil and just
relax. And we're gonna try again tomorrow.
Krusty Earwax, thanks for the one dollar.
I don't know if referencing Jojo's Bizarre Adventure
is still a joke, but you should play
one of the shitty Jojo games and then they
do like the, I don't know, but whatever.
There was one on Dreamcast that I
hovered over the purchase button and realized that it got
afforded. I'm not kidding.
Didn't buy it though.
Thank you, Awesome Stevie for the one dollar.
Okay, you are epic.
Thank you. Dr. Clay,
thanks for the one dollar. We talked about Joel
challenging me. I already accepted the challenge.
InvaderZ, thanks for the two bucks.
I was finally able to make a stream. Thank you
so much, Jerma. You're awesome and you always make me laugh.
Welcome to the stream.
Glad you made it. Sorry, it was a short one.
Thank you, Breenland for the one dollar.
Hey yo, are you gonna play Kingdom Hearts 1, 2, and 3?
I'd say all of them, but it'd never
finish.
No, that's like 6,000 hours.
I don't think I'm gonna play Kingdom Hearts 3
on stream or 1 or 2.
But I hope you enjoy it when it releases in
like less than 24 hours.
So, have a great playthrough of Kingdom Hearts 3.
I heard it's pretty good.
Thank you for the suggestion,
but probably not on this channel.
Hey Tingy, thanks for the two bucks. I see how this is
gonna happen. Sliding more bits under the table.
Will this do, Wink? You can't pay me to do
anything. Thank you, DoubleD for the one
dollar. Hey Jerma, could you please assist me in identifying
this man? He's been
tormenting me for months. He keeps
rambling on something about playing Army of Two with his
college. It's a picture of italics.
Thank you. Subwab,
thank you for the ten dollars.
Jerma, figuring out the
person I want to be in life has been difficult, but I want to let you
know you've been a huge inspiration.
You're a real hero to me, so thanks for all the good times.
If I can inspire somebody
to do anything positive,
then I'm
fucking honored. Thank you.
Thank you for even saying
that. I hope
you, whatever you take from
me, whatever that is,
hope you have it positively affect your
life. Seriously, thank you.
And thank you for the ten dollars.
Thank you Dr. Plato
for the one dollar. Don't know if you're
going to see this, but I've had constant headaches and migraines
recently. Currently in the Navy,
so it's straining. I get where you're
coming from and getting headaches every day is so hard to deal
with. I've gotten an MRI, but came back clean.
I honestly don't know what to do about it.
Yeah, for me,
they come in like strings.
Like I will go to bed with a headache, wake up
groggy and fucked up and feel like
slow and headache-y.
And then another day, like it's
like an eye pain headache, and then
like a back of the head headache, and then it's gone for
three months. It's weird.
I feel like I'm currently like in the
thick of that right now.
But I'm really sorry to hear about your struggles
there. Hopefully you can
figure out some kind of solution.
Because it sucks. It does. It's annoying.
I wish you the best. Thank you for the
one dollar. Only a few more
here. Thank you Solid Milk for the one dollar. Hey Jeremy,
I'm wondering, should I ask a girl I've been friend-
Should I try to ask a girl I've been friends with
out for a while? Wait, hold on.
Hold on, let me read this again.
I've been wondering if I should try to ask a girl I've
been friends with for a while.
But I don't want to ruin our friendship.
Oh, okay. So you ask a girl out
that you've been friends with for a while.
I don't know. I
can't give you an answer there. Because I have
no idea what your relationship is like.
I don't know how long you've known
this person. It's very different. Plus I'm terrible
with relationship advice.
I'm probably one of the- I'm definitely not somebody
good to ask stuff like
this. Don't- remember
to make sure not to tell her that you know me. That you like
not know me, but that you watch me.
You saw how well that goes.
But without being able to gauge kind of
the whole situation, it'd be really easy for
me to be like, yeah, go for it.
But I have no idea.
And I don't want to be the person that gives you the wrong
info. And then it's like,
why the fuck did Jerma tell me to do that?
So I'm not really that great with
relationship advice.
I do wish you luck
in your
romantic endeavors.
But remember, if somebody wants to just be friends,
if you figure that out,
and that's, you know, you-
I know people that have-
you gotta be careful because there- I've known
people before where they were friends for a long
time, and then somebody tried to
put the, you know, the line out there.
They're like, hey, let's-
maybe we could be more than just friends. And then it
makes it awkward and they-
you go apart. So
that's possible. I mean, it depends on what your friendship
is like, but you just have to be careful.
My Tinder
pick-up line is, hey, baby, you watch
Jerma985. He beat Demon
Souls, Dark Souls, and Dark Souls 3.
No, but I- I wish
I could give you better advice, but there are much
better resources than me.
But thank you, though. Good luck.
Thank you, UpQuark, for the one dollar.
Uh, sorry for a downer.
I wanted to share with you a picture of my dog and I. She recently
passed away and couldn't miss her more.
Please, everyone, pet
your pet whenever you can.
I'm really sorry to hear that.
It's really fucking impossible to
lose an animal.
I think you've got a picture here of
this is a photo of the dog.
Let's take a look.
Is it a Golden Retriever?
No, she's beautiful.
I'm really sorry to hear about that.
Bad as she was.
I'm really sorry to hear that.
Take care of yourself. Much love to you.
And, uh, I don't know what
your dog's name was, but
rest in peace, for sure.
Thank you for the one dollar, UpQuark.
Also, thank you to Chubby Funster for the one dollar.
Hey, Jerma, you're really cute and funny.
How come you don't grow out your beard?
You'd look really good with one, I think,
unless you got something against beards, which I don't think I could
support a beard-hating streamer if that were the case.
Love you lots.
Uh, no, my facial
hair doesn't grow out full.
It's bad. It looks like shit.
It's very patchy and scraggly.
It's not full, it looks bad.
That's why I never do it.
But thank you.
Thank you, Nebula Brand, for the fifteen dollars.
Fifteen.
Thank you.
Hey, Jerma, I just want to say that even though we've never met,
watching your streams always feels like hanging out with an old friend.
2018 was a hard year for me
for a lot of reasons.
But even when I only had twenty bucks in my bank account,
I couldn't unsub from you.
I don't know how I would have gotten through the second half of 2018
if I didn't have your streams to come home to
every other day.
Thank you for bringing so much laughter to my life.
And here's to a much happier 2019.
Hell yeah.
Here's to 2019.
Thank you so much, Nebula Brand.
I'm really sorry to hear about your
struggles. Much love to you.
Thank you for everything.
Thanks for sticking around. I hope you have
a solid 2019.
Thank you.
Thank you, Wizard Ribbit, for the two bucks.
Drink some brain fluid for a healthy
brain.
It probably gives you headaches.
Tinging thanks for the two bucks. Man, you're one tough customer.
Wait, I'm the customer.
What the hell's going on here? Fine, I'll just have them...
I'll just have to get them the good, old-fashioned
American way?
No.
Thank you, Dr. Zoot Suit for the one dollar.
I realize I didn't have the link.
What is this? The link of what?
Oh, oh, okay.
Alright, oh.
Right. Oh.
Well, alright.
There it is. Thank you, Dr. Zoot Suit
for the one dollar. You mean machine for the two bucks.
Solid Milk, one dollar.
I fucked up the grammar, but thanks.
I'll be sure to tell her I watched you.
Oh god.
Thank you for the one dollar, Solid Milk.
Good luck.
Thank you to...
Thank you, Django, for the five dollars.
You're a good guy, Jerma. Thanks for all the
streams. Have a good night. You as well.
Thank you so much for the five dollars.
Appreciate the kind words.
Double D, thanks for the one dollar. Please share this photo
with the stream and anyone who sees this must have to report
it's just...
It's Italics again.
What are you doing?
He's 1200 Jerma bucks
for the... Italics was last seen on the Vegas
strip with an extremely short streamer. That's
very, very... That's not probably more than me.
But there are plenty of other streamers
that this could be who are small.
Not me, though. I'm average small.
I'm small, but I'm small. I'm average.
Alright, I'm gonna get out of here. Thank you
Anonilus for the one dollar. Hey, I meant to say thanks
in the last... I meant to say this in the last donation.
Uh, come up with a dumb
name for my
black duckling.
Italics named one
Bloor Boolean, so make it something dumb.
Enjoy these bits.
Um, how about, uh...
How about something like...
Uh...
Like a duck.
Uh, um... Bilbo.
With two L's.
I'm sorry, but that's what you're gonna get tonight.
No, don't boo me.
But thank you for the one dollar, and
I look forward to the duck streams.
Thank you Tingy for the one dollar. Spent all the bits I had on one joke.
This is the last of them.
I'll need to buy more before tomorrow's stream. Don't worry about that.
But thank you
for the one dollar, Tingy.
And finally, quarter dime for the one dollar. Hey, Jerma, I know this might sound
weird, but I actually enjoy the
spam memes.
Can we just get a good five minutes
out of them before they get shut down?
What do you mean shut down?
Shut down?
No, there's no spam.
I'm not gonna encourage spam on this channel.
This is a PogChamp moment when I'm gonna say that on stream.
But here are the subs
and the resubs for tonight.
A ton of community subs, a ton of money.
I, again, just want to apologize
for another, like, five hour stream
or four hour
and then, you know, this part.
We'll come back. We'll try it again tomorrow.
Strong. If you're just joining us
I just got another one of those fucking
weird, like, tired headache
things. Last time
it just, I got, like, just sleepy.
But I'm actually feeling some,
like, pain and pressure here. So.
Annoying, but I have to deal with it.
I'm sorry. It's just the way it is.
See you guys tomorrow. Same
time. Much love to you.
Thank you.
Thank you. Double D just came in with another one dollar.
Goodnight gamers and goodnight Jerma.
Smiley face. And then they actually put a smiley face.
See you tomorrow.
Smiley face.
Yeah, there was, there was a
let me see how many community subs came in from earlier.
Somebody, there was, like, what, like 50
or something. For tonight.
Yeah.
The Olaf just
dropped an absolute missile.
So did Furt.
Great Canadian.
You guys are
significant. You have a significant
amount of subs come from a lot of
a lot of people that are here now. So thank you
guys. Dorkcube, thanks for the
one dollar DVD commentary for streams
joke. When?
You mean, like, re-stream a stream and then do
DVD commentary?
How many emotes slots do we have now?
It's probably so many.
Let me see.
At least another 10.
I already had, like, I had still had like five
or six that were still open.
Gonna have to come up with some more emotes.
See a doctor for the headaches?
I have, don't worry, I have seen a doctor.
I have. I actually was
I've been getting all kinds of checkups
and tests over the last three or four weeks.
So I'm in the process,
don't worry. Let's see the Bitcoin
doctor.
I don't think that's real.
If it is, that's pretty ridiculous.
But, take care
guys. I'm gonna go relax.
And we'll go again tomorrow.
Hopefully I can finish Resident
Evil 2 tomorrow. See you guys
very soon. Take care.
Much love. See you soon. Have a great night.
Goodbye.