Hello there, ladies and gentlemen. It's Grandpa here, and today I have some Hitman, the Blood Money.
And today I want to play this game because Hitman Absolution, the sequel to this, is coming out pretty soon.
So I want to just show you my special techniques and how I take out the bad guys.
So this is the Vineyard level, and this is the guy we're going to kill right here, right by the door.
So this is a good technique. What you want to do is you pull out the mine.
And who gives a shit about these people running around? You just want to drop it in...
Where is he? I think he's right here.
Drop the landmine, take a little stroll over here, pull out the detonator, and see you later, motherfuckers!
What an explosion that was!
This is the guy. Oh. Well, I killed him anyway, so if you don't kill him with the blast, then just... Jesus, that was rough.
Also, this game is all about stealth. You want to be really quiet, and you want to use a syringe to make sure you put the people to sleep and not kill them.
Hey! What are you doing? Don't shoot it!
Don't shoot it!
Okay, let's try this again. Pull out the mine, everybody run scared.
Yeah, yeah, get the fuck out of my way. I don't want to deal with every inch.
Drop the mine, come on, come on, come on! I've never done this before! Come on!
Yes! I did it! I actually did it! Okay, now I...
I don't know what to do now. That's the first time I've ever done that.
Oh, okay, pull out the machine gun.
I don't know what to do! I don't have any bullets left! This is stupid!
Okay, I just, um... think here, grandpa. Come on, think!
I'm going to just... Oh my God, grab a gun! Grab somebody's gun!
Seriously, what the fuck is going on here?
Okay, so I've come to the realization that you're not supposed to use the mine.
So I'm just going to drop it at the beginning of the level so nobody sees it and I don't get in any trouble.
And then... What? What? What?
Why did that guy just pick up the mine?
Hold on a second, what is this guy doing?
Excuse me, you just picked up a fucking mine!
So this is hands down one of the weirdest things that's ever goddamn happened to me in a video game.
So this guy has the mine, can I blow him up?
Can I detonate this guy in this entire goddamn room? Are you serious?
You know, typically I would laugh at something like this, but that was just sad.