Hey, I'm here. Yep. Sorry. I had to take a phone call.
I had a phone call. I had to take. I couldn't ignore it.
Sorry.
Okay. Sorry. I might have to clear my throat.
So today, hello. Hi.
What's up?
Welcome to the stream.
Hope you had a good week.
I did. I think I had a pretty good week.
Here on the weekend now.
To hang out with you.
And play video games.
Aren't you ready?
Uh, we have a few things to do this weekend.
Today, we're gonna play this game called Considerate.
It's a game kind of like WarioWare.
I'm really into the micro game stuff right now.
The only difference is the choices you make in this game
are based on how nice of a person you are.
How considerate you are.
And to get rated at the end of how considerate of a person you are.
Based on the micro games.
So I, it looks cool.
Resident Sleeper.
I was, oh wow, he's gonna scream.
One day I will do that.
One day I'm gonna see a Resident Sleeper and I'm gonna go
Just like scream into the fucking microphone.
So that person is, because they just pressed enter.
And now it's like, holy shit, I just did Resident Sleeper.
And this motherfucker screamed.
And I can see it scrolling up the chat.
So I was wrong.
I'm not, how do I delete my chat room?
Oh shit, you're right, thank you.
Is this the guy from Bloodwigs?
Wait, Bloodwigs, what?
Yeah, I'm the guy, I'm the guy that likes to work with Bloodwigs.
I'm just, I stream with like another room.
Let me tweet.
Okay, tweet is out.
Now I can talk about what we're doing.
Where's my tweet?
What the fuck?
Here we go, okay, see it.
All right, what about Deltarune?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hey, hold on, let me, let me move the clock.
I almost said the clock.
It's a microphone.
It's not a clock.
Let me move the clock.
Hold on, there.
Let me move the mic closer to my face so I don't have to lean in.
So we're going to play Considerate.
There's three of them.
I think they're both, the three of them are like an hour each.
Maybe Considering?
I don't know.
We're going to do them.
I'm going to get bored of them, or maybe not.
And if we do get bored, then we're going to move on to Roswell Agent,
which is the third person FBI game where you drive around and you're an agent.
And it's about an alien invasion.
And there's a car in it, so you know how we feel about those.
And then I was going to play Deltarune tomorrow,
but Deltarune is going to be next weekend,
because I want to play Chapter One,
because I think it's been a long time between chapters,
and I want to make sure I know what the fuck I'm talking about,
because I don't remember a goddamn thing.
The only thing I remember is I beat that clown.
I beat Jevil first try.
I don't know anything else, and I kind of want to refresh her.
So off stream, I'm going to play Deltarune Chapter One before next weekend,
and then obviously we'll do Chapter Two next weekend.
Also next weekend, we're finally going to do the Sims 3 modded hell.
I have like 10 game changing mods, just like I did in the fourth game.
Sims 4, you get the idea.
We'll do that next weekend as well.
So there's your Friday, Saturday for next weekend.
Friday, Saturday for this weekend, however, is going to be this game,
the FBI game, and then tomorrow we're going to probably play the pawn shop game.
No umbrellas allowed.
It's a pawn shop simulator.
I think it looks pretty fun.
You're going to play Diablo?
I'm not going to stream Diablo 2.
No, I streamed Diablo 2 earlier last year or the year before.
I don't need to do it again.
That's pretty based.
I just don't think I need to stream it.
It's going to be hard for me to even play Diablo 2.
There's a lot going on right now.
It's not like my days of yesteryear where I would stay up
till like four in the morning playing Diablo 2.
Like 10 hours.
Those days are probably long gone.
Especially now with all this kind of stuff going on.
Projects.
Maybe I'll talk about that at some point.
Yeah, let's go.
Let's go.
I got this game ready.
Toby Fox referenced you on the stream?
Yeah, I know.
It was pretty cool.
I didn't even...
It's weird.
It's weird when somebody that you think is like cool,
or like, holy shit, Undertale.
Toby Fox, that guy's fucking legendary.
Like, he said my name.
That's like Brad Pitt saying your name.
That's like going to the red carpet
and standing there with like a microphone
and like waiting for an interview.
And Brad Pitt walks by everybody else,
makes direct eye contact with you on the red carpet,
walks straight up to you and goes,
I know you, bro.
I know you.
And you're like, what the...
Hey, Brad Pitt.
Yeah.
Yeah, I do.
Hey, enjoy the movie.
And they fucking just keep walking.
It's like, holy shit, Brad Pitt.
How do you know who I am?
You're the worst streamer.
Ego Andy.
No, not Ego Andy.
You didn't even see the movements I was doing.
Do you understand the movements I was just making?
I was just going like...
Okay, I was going like this with the microphone in my hand.
Hey, hey, Brad Pitt, how are you?
That's not Ego Andy.
That's like holy shit, Andy.
You know what I mean?
That's not Ego Andy.
I was shaking.
Okay, I'll be honest.
When I first opened this,
I thought it was an iPhone game that I had to flip up like left.
I really thought this was like an iPhone.
My orientation is wrong.
But no, this is correct.
First, I was like, why is my resolution so wrong?
Okay, so I think we're ready.
I'm ready to play Consider It.
Good afternoon.
Go camera again.
You'll get it in waves.
All right, let's play.
Do you want to use the mouse?
I don't think I use the mouse.
This is a space where you are free to consider things as you like.
There is no one here to stop you from being as considerate as you, please.
Now what?
After considering the...
That was me holding a burp back.
After considering the situation, move the red object on the screen.
Sometimes there may be nothing to move.
Just do what you consider the appropriate action.
If you wish to stop playing, just push the escape key.
It's too bright.
I don't...
What am I...
I can't fix that.
All right, number one.
The first thing to consider.
Together.
Oh, okay.
I wasn't going to move for those people.
Elementary dominoes.
Let's set a world record.
Okay.
I feel like I'm doing like a psychology test.
Down, boy.
I did it.
The wobble filter hurts my head.
Yeah, how do I turn that off?
In Tokyo.
Oh, someone's behind us.
Yeah, you're going to move out of the way.
Somebody, you don't want to...
If you're going to stand there.
If somebody wants to walk up the escalator, you got to let them pass.
Okay, I'm going to go here.
Is it going to reveal you?
You're moderately considerate.
I did everything that anyone should do in those situations.
I'm incredibly considerate.
Wait, this is going to keep going.
Does this get harder?
Santa.
Oh, I had to put my head down.
Okay.
What?
Can I take your order?
I know this fucking wobble filter is freaking me out.
Cocktails.
I would want a...
Okay.
I'm going to rate these on a scale of one to ten.
Eight.
Okay, no, I don't want a white Russian.
Did I pick a white Russian?
What am I supposed to do?
I just pressed a button.
What button did I press?
A, B, C?
What happened?
A, B, A, B, B.
Am I not saying words?
How do I...
I visit space bar?
If I get this last pin, you'll go out with me.
Yeah, okay.
Wait, what?
That thing's on a fucking string.
That thing was pulled in some way or another considerate.
I didn't even do anything.
You didn't get on a date.
Well, I was supposed to knock the inconsiderate Andy.
I didn't do...
What did I do wrong?
How many levels are there?
Okay, cans and bottles.
I have to break these?
Oh, I can jump.
Is this considerate?
I'm destroying recycling, right?
Am I breaking it down?
I'm confused.
I am too.
Stand.
Oh, seat.
Okay, I did all three of them.
Is this a puzzle?
Let's go to the zoo.
Okay, me and girlfriend.
Sensor, the lines are...
Wait, oh, I probably...
I mean, you would do the same thing though, right?
There's no way anybody could tell me.
Hold on.
We got to talk about this.
Tap, tap.
There's a ghost.
If there are two lions having sex at the zoo,
what, are you going to leave?
Every single person is going to be like,
what the fuck?
Oh, wow.
What's going on?
You're going to like turn away and leave.
All right, I did the wave with everybody.
Moderately considerate.
Okay, there are like three buttons.
There's up, down, left, right, and space.
From what I'm understanding here.
You went right up to it.
So I guess it would be inconsiderate.
Oh, well.
Wait, what?
No, I was trying to walk with the character.
Was that considerate?
Why would putting your umbrella down
be considerate in the rain?
That's you getting rained on.
Oh man, I got to get off at the next stop.
Doki, doki.
Oh, great.
This is the final stop.
Carano Bus Terminal.
All right, so get off.
I got off.
What's boyfriend and girlfriend here?
Okay, I'm going to sit down.
What?
There was enough room.
Today is our date.
Okay, Robocon or RomCon.
Let's go to Robocon.
I think we both would enjoy that.
It's still our date.
Okay.
What am I supposed to do?
Oh, walk on this side.
So nobody splashes her?
I don't know.
And somewhere or another considerate.
What?
Did I not raise my hand to say I need to get off?
Robocon is...
Wait, what does that mean?
Does that mean something?
You have to do it based on Japanese culture?
Good morning.
Oh, shit, his head.
No, no, pick it up.
No, don't look.
Don't look.
You don't...
Japanese samurai is weaker than great elderly.
Okay.
Um...
They have no options to do anything.
Oh, I got to walk with her.
Don't walk too fast.
Why would I walk in front of her?
Today is another date.
I guess we could think of them as a couple now.
Okay.
They were heading towards an anime
when suddenly they turned towards a romance movie.
He seems really naive.
He builds up his courage and takes her hand.
It seems like they are really dating now.
Oh, what you don't know is when you looked over,
he was sleeping.
No, keep walking.
You don't just walk.
Just go by.
You don't have to sit there and stare at anybody.
In some way or another, consider it.
Yeah, but I don't even know...
I couldn't...
I pressed every button.
I couldn't like swing the sword at that guy.
You'll stare at the zoo animal.
Okay.
I want...
I want to take...
Hold on.
So you have...
So who have we got for the yellow ranger?
What's...
I don't get it.
Me?
Did I not have raised my hand?
Did I do it?
I got it.
What's the max grade?
I don't know.
Is that the guy from South Park?
Why is that the South Park Warcraft guy?
Okay.
Why is he so sweaty?
Hey, I got my personality test back.
You want to see?
Let's see what you got.
My personality is looking at animals?
How do I exit?
Wait, is that what's on my mind?
That's weird.
Turn right.
Okay.
I feel like that's not a good thing.
In some way or another.
There's probably like four letters or four grades.
This is me.
Barber or bar?
I don't have any hair.
Why would I go...
I don't have hair.
I missed.
I didn't know that's what I was supposed to do.
You know what really is really fucking inconsiderate?
Sliding a drink down a wet slippery bar
and expecting your friends to catch it.
So that was on him, not me.
That was inconsiderate on them.
Oh, fuck.
I struck out.
Wait, why is it...
Oh, wait.
I'm supposed to let him do that.
Down to my last ball.
This is my last chance.
Was I supposed to not block that?
Oh, he's catching me.
He's catching the monster.
In some way or another.
That means bad.
There's a lot...
Okay, 36.
We're just still going.
I didn't know what button jump was.
I pressed up and it wasn't that.
What do I do?
I don't know what that is.
I don't know what I'm supposed to be doing.
Why am I scheming?
He missed.
How do I move in those scenarios?
Is there another button I'm not pressing?
Okay, this guy...
Let him sleep on me.
But is it in...
Okay.
When I say you, clap your hands.
Did I get it?
And somewhere...
I think I'm missing a button.
I have up, down, left, right on the arrow keys.
And I have space.
And sometimes I can't move anybody.
Wait, am I supposed to be moving them?
I can't believe I'm actually going to meet AA in person.
I know I get it.
Okay, BB is nobody there.
But like I wanted to come...
I came here to see AA.
Oh, I don't have very much time.
Oh, you get that mushroom so you can get bigger.
Well, I didn't want you to...
Okay, we're good.
I got two lives now.
What if it was a poison mushroom?
No, take the picture.
I tried to press space.
It didn't do anything.
Some of these don't work.
Is it just me or is it cold in here?
Got it.
Temperature.
We'll turn the heat up a little.
And somewhere in there, consider it.
A little?
What do you mean?
30 Celsius, Jesus Christ, is what?
Is it 100 degrees?
Shit.
I have so much trouble with Celsius because like
one or two degrees is something completely different.
Am I trying to block this guy from reading?
Oh, okay.
If I lose, that's considerate.
Hey, I'm thirsty.
Okay, got it.
She's like burning up.
All right, give me a coffee.
All right, coffee.
I'll take one.
But that's a hot coffee.
Oh, I was trying to...
All right, first of all, I'll be honest.
I was trying to drop it on the floor.
I'll be honest.
TV special, witness the power.
Oh, that would be inconsiderate.
I'm just seeing what my options are.
I'm just trying to see what it's even possible.
Psycho, psycho, psycho.
No, okay, I'm sorry.
I have to really...
I'm going to have to defend myself on this here.
What am I doing?
Be looking at somebody?
What should we be looking at?
Straight ahead?
You need to know what your tools are capable of doing, okay?
Oh, look, we need a spot.
No, I was trying at first to get a spot.
Not me take a spot.
Speed.
I thought it was us walking.
Big bro, I'm so hungry.
Big bro has to do something.
Ghost leg competition final.
The winner gets all you can eat.
Bra or don't draw.
It's up to you.
The last line.
You, big bro, winner.
What?
How do I draw?
How do I do this?
Control?
Alt?
Enter?
Hold the mouse button down?
I can't draw anything.
You need to put a controller in?
I didn't have any controls.
I don't think you can even look at the control.
Keyboard and mouse?
Hey, why don't we check that personality test again?
Quick, hit escape.
Hit escape quick.
Why am I trying to hit escape?
What, did I have like a porn hub tab open?
I don't understand.
Why was I freaking out?
Are you even listening?
Yes, I am.
Do you think I've get-
No!
That's what I-
What?
Are you listening?
I'm listening.
I am.
I swear to God.
It'd be so much better to be on the other side.
I'm listening.
How do I stand the character up?
Turn the volume down.
Today is premium Friday.
Premium Friday.
Leave at 15.
Okay.
Leave.
Everybody leave.
Everybody fucking leave.
Leave.
You don't have to work anymore.
All of you leave.
It's time to go home.
How do I say go home?
You were here for like four extra hours.
Today is our date.
Why does she have-
Wait a second.
Am I dating a cow?
What was that?
Wait, that's beef?
I didn't-
I thought the sushi-
Okay.
Let me-
Hear me out.
I thought sushi was meat.
And I didn't know what the other thing was.
I was unconcerned.
I'm taking too much.
I get thrown out of the restaurant at this point.
You thought sushi was meat?
Sushi is meat.
I-
You just did it!
You can't change the rules.
What do you mean sushi is not meat?
What do you think it is?
Waiting for your bento to heat up.
Um, okay.
How much does it cost?
All right.
So you can go ahead of me because I'm waiting for my-
You can just go ahead of me.
Yeah.
That's what I do.
If I was like I could look,
I'm gonna be like probably another two minutes or so.
Yeah, that's considerate.
No buttons do anything.
Let me hear you make some noise.
Oh, okay.
I think I've given certain love and peace.
Yes, we cannot.
Cannot what?
I don't know what I'm agreeing to as a collective audience.
Today is our date.
Okay, this is a robot.
All right, we're gonna go to Robocon.
Is that what I should have done?
Mod-
Okay, that was better than last time.
Moderately considerate.
Gundam.
There we go.
Okay.
Moderately-
First in line.
Okay, please ride the robots in order.
I don't know-
What?
Oh, that one's broken.
Help!
Okay, help.
Ally.
Shut up.
Let him get it.
Yeah, like, look, I'm not gonna get in the middle of two, like, cowboys, okay?
Those are two Red Dead Redemption characters.
I'm gonna grab the drink in the middle.
That's not considerate.
That's called survival.
I'm just-
I'm not getting involved with that one.
You can do it.
Oh, close that.
Why is there no food in our pot?
We need to be patient.
Something will arrive.
Okay, how the fuck are you supposed to do?
I didn't want to eat that.
How are you supposed to do that?
I think-
Okay, I got what they were looking for.
This is not even considerate.
It's just remembering the routine.
I've got a date tomorrow.
Tomorrow's exam could affect my whole life.
Tomorrow's the big day.
Live at the Bucadab-
Buc-
Typhoon.
What?
Why would I-
Why would I have let that go?
It's always been my dream to be saved by a handsome prince riding on a horse.
Evil ca-
Wait.
What should I do?
Go to the race-
The race course?
No, wrong.
So I was going to just go into the evil castle.
Shouldn't I just go hang out and meet somebody at the horse track thing?
I'm going to go walk up to Bowser's castle, knock on the door, and be like,
I'm going to wait for Mario.
Why would I do that?
Well, I guess in the later games, in Mario games.
Isn't Bowser not even a factor anymore?
Is he still doing that?
Is Bowser still like-
No.
Pay attention.
Costume competition.
I won.
He's in the new game, Mario Odyssey.
Is he?
Okay.
Don't push me.
Stunt on a comedy show.
What the fuck is this?
Don't push me.
I'm not going to push you.
Okay.
I'm not-
What the fuck is going on?
Not even hot.
I have to like-
Oh, it's crazy.
It's-
I'm real hot here.
Eye witness.
Oh, okay.
Is it-
We're going to blur-
We have to blur her.
Don't try-
In some way or another, consider it.
Push him.
It's comedy.
Oh yeah.
Somebody's literally begging me not to push them in something.
Yeah, but comedy show.
What is that supposed to mean?
And for the celebrity first pitch, Miss BB.
That looked bad.
I'll be honest, I was trying to hit it out of the park.
I was trying to embarrass BB.
Here we go.
I got it.
Remember, you'd be bad at improv.
He's telling me not to.
No, this is how considerate are you?
And dumping somebody into like a burning hot cauldron is not-
I didn't know what the hell I was-
What are you talking about?
We have to be safe.
No, no, no.
Put it back down.
It's a comedy bit.
I didn't know I was on a comedy show
until five seconds into that.
Uh, did I do it too early?
It said comedy show on the bottom.
Textbook.
Should I not look?
I think that's like where my eyes are looking.
So I'm gonna like look over here.
Right?
No, you look at the book.
Yeah, all right.
I'm like looking over at like a poster.
Oh, seatbelt.
Why are people calling you psycho?
I don't know.
Anyone know the answer?
You do.
Oh, but look, there's a spaceship over there.
Don't be distracted.
Me and then a couple.
Oh, I like sacrifice myself to get abducted.
Or yes, hand up.
Or no, hand down.
Answer if don't want world destroyed.
What?
Answer if don't you is human?
Yes.
Answer if don't want world destroyed.
Yes or no?
Don't want the earth destroyed.
No, I don't want the earth destroyed.
But don't want the earth-
I don't no-
Don't not want the earth not destroyed.
Put the hand down.
Tomorrow of today's day before yesterday's three days ago.
I can't even put my hand back down.
You lose weight?
Yes, apparently.
You see here?
I can't put my hand down.
You secret keep?
You have itchy spots?
Yes, I don't know.
I can't put my hand down.
You hero, you save world?
Yes, I can't put my hand down.
Was it escape?
Telephone.
Help, save me.
What's happening?
Save me?
Oh, I had to look away because he was changing to turn into a superhero.
I get it.
Okay, so we're just talking.
Somebody wants to-
All right, somebody wants to get up.
Let them go.
Discussion, future of the band, break up or vocal solo debut?
Oh, shit.
Okay, that was just me walking by it.
Okay, consider it.
All right, we got an important announcement for all of you.
My grandma suddenly passed away.
Oh, that's not-
I don't-
I'm not gonna-
We're gonna break up after today.
Okay, we don't cheer.
And what else you got?
Oh, okay.
Well, I was waiting for the other one.
Oh, fuck.
I'm sorry.
What's considerate here?
I don't know.
How do I get you to get up?
That wasn't considerate.
Very vaguely considerate.
Top right corner.
Could I have clicked it with the mouse?
I couldn't move.
I couldn't walk around.
You're a horrible person.
And today, I'm definitely gonna get-
What?
I don't know what that said, but I would sit here if I had a choice.
I'm bored.
I guess I should go attack a planet or something.
Hero is away.
Hero is in.
Well, it'd be considerate to, like, if the hero's there,
that I would lose, but I could get, like, my fill of attacking a planet,
but I would lose and I could just do it again.
I would leave.
I wouldn't actually destroy it, right?
Yeah, you got me.
Jesus.
It's been a while, but you came.
I really wanted to see you.
Just hold my hand.
Brings back memories, huh?
You sent me photo of that ghost.
I said it as my background, you know.
It was fun going to see that band.
We even went on a date with that cow, right?
Now I'd be like, okay, what are you talking about?
I know all about it.
It would have been nice to stay with you longer.
This is fucking horrible.
Remember the giant monster?
I totally beat it.
Do you remember the first day we met?
You were so indecisive.
Anyway, forget about me.
Just go find someone new.
What the fuck?
Sorry, can't stop crying.
Is this a bad ending?
I'm sorry I couldn't be more considerate.
But I'm not strong enough.
Wait, this is me.
I'm on my deathbed.
You always look out for other people.
You're so kind.
I really loved that about you.
I think it's me.
Even the times you didn't need to.
Oops.
Thank you.
Bye.
I don't want to die.
What the fuck?
This is got...
We went from like taking seats on the subway
to like somebody dying in your arms.
That's quite the bad ending.
That's still going, okay?
Very vaguely considerate.
Oh, should you get out of the way
for people walking up the escalator?
This person's fucking dead.
And it's your fault.
Oh.
Ooh, okay.
Your sympathy is your best quality.
Eco tote bag level.
All right, so my sympathy...
Ability to fit in, sense of duty,
quick thinking, application, and determination.
Eco tote bag level.
That's really fucking funny.
Okay.
Inconsiderate mode.
Considerate extras, chapters, secrets.
Okay, that was cool.
Should we just go right on to the next one?
There's three of these.
There's literally one, two, and three.
Should we just do number two?
Do inconsiderate mode.
All right.
What does this mean?
No one's going to hold you back.
Go ahead and mess around to your heart's content.
Okay.
Please be inconsiderate and mess around.
There's no explanations.
Just go nuts.
Or you can escape if you don't want to play anymore.
All right.
Oh, okay.
That's very...
I get it.
You're just doing the opposite.
Nah, I wouldn't need to do this.
Let's do that.
Let's do the next one.
Yeah.
Let's do...
Let's just go right on to the second one.
We could probably just bang them all out in a row.
Put the next one on.
Here.
You can get the cam for like 15 seconds while I do this.
Exit application.
You can see my pores.
Whatever.
We all have them.
All right.
Let's play inconsiderate two.
This one's called considerate more.
Considerate more.
A new era.
It's not too loud.
Brace yourself.
It might be...
Let's mute it.
I think we're good.
Does that count?
Okay.
Let's do it.
Hey, there it is.
Yeah.
I'll check the controls on this one.
Should I even change the game title?
I mean, do I even really need to change the game title?
It's the same fucking game.
All right.
Press any button.
Options.
Video.
Let's make sure it's in the right resolution.
Yeah.
1920 by 1080.
Full screen.
That's all I can do.
All right.
How to play.
This is a space where you are free to consider things as you like.
There's no one here to stop you from being as considered as you please.
After considering the situation, move the red object on the screen.
Okay.
But how do I move on the screen?
I think it's just the arrow keys in space.
It didn't tell you anything.
All right.
Consider it.
Use a controller.
It's just arrows in space.
Okay.
All right.
Part two.
Keep the face cam on.
I'll do the face cam for consider it's free.
That's what I'm going to have to keep really in with the third sequel.
You know what I mean?
Number one.
The announcement of a new era.
And the new name, the new era will be called Rewa.
Bro.
I held it up the wrong way.
There we go.
Okay.
Should I move?
Oh, this is for a ride.
What am I doing?
Okay.
You guys can go first because you're together, right?
Because then you'll take up two cars.
Line drive.
Oh, let the kid get it.
That's not how I would do this, by the way.
I would be up there trying to catch it with the sole reason that
two of us trying to catch it for that kid is...
All right.
Walk.
Holy shit.
Don't walk.
Two of us trying to catch it for that kid is exponentially more statistics for that to happen.
All right.
This is a comedy show.
I'll do it.
I won't do it.
Because everybody laughs, right?
The previous five questions.
Very vaguely considerate.
Oh.
You catch it and you hand the ball to the kid
to have the chance the kid actually gets the ball higher.
Let's eat ramen.
Recommended.
Your salt.
Salt ramen.
I'll take this one here.
How is that inconsistent?
It's what I wanted to order at a restaurant.
Thanks for the meal.
Who's waiting for a seat, please?
Oh, people are waiting.
No, don't fucking get up.
Get up.
Okay.
Here we go.
Oh, they're trying to take a picture.
See, I really tried to photobomb that, but I got it wrong.
Tablet.
Here.
You always give two.
Always.
Because some people, they want more than one.
But they'll never ask for more than one.
You were part-time for a...
What the...
I didn't even read it.
Books.
I don't know.
I didn't even...
I could have the chance to read the thing.
Considerably...
All right.
That's...
I was pretty considerate.
Three words per minute reading Andy.
No, it's called like...
50 words a minute reading Andy.
But it's split evenly across two different screens reading your comments.
I'll let you have one bite.
Oh, one bite.
Right there.
Okay, that's pretty good.
Never eat the top.
Always just one little bite at the bottom.
And you leave the frosting and shit forever for them to enjoy.
50 words per minute is still awful.
Starting school today.
Ba-dump, ba-dump, ba-dump.
Okay.
Emperor.
Yep.
Here.
Oh, no.
I'm God.
That kid...
Wow.
Censored.
Quick, change the channel.
Get away from the lion sex.
There's only two channels on TV.
They're broadcasting this across every network.
I think that's very actually important to find out why.
Like, CBS, ABC, NBC.
They're all airing it.
Why?
Okay.
Yellow Fighter.
Oh, you got me.
Did I lose?
This isn't my stop.
Here we go.
That's the thing to do, but here's the thing.
That also seems kind of rude, doesn't it?
I don't know.
Part of me is like...
Everybody gets up and like...
What?
Something wrong with me?
You're just gonna get the fuck away from me as fast as possible?
Like, oh, wow.
You really hate sitting next to me so badly that
the second the seat came available, you ran the fuck away as soon as you could.
I know that's completely irrational, but I feel like somewhere in my brain I think that.
So moving one seat over...
Oh, shit.
That's right.
I did it wrong.
But one seat over is like...
You're barely offensive enough to me where one seat is fine.
Okay, so what are we doing?
Oh, we're gonna walk...
Oh, wait.
I have to go like this.
I wanna play this game.
That is cool.
One seat over is giving them space.
Five seats is you smell.
Yeah, that's fucked up.
I shouldn't have gone that far.
Um...
Can you fit?
They not want that?
Was I supposed to get out of the elevator?
Two.
Three.
Four.
My god.
Holy shit.
That would be terrifying.
Psycho.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Here.
Take my card?
It's a pleasure to meet you.
How do I give you the card?
Other person, you.
This pleasure is all mine.
What's...
Why am I look...
Where am I looking?
It's pulling up.
Okay.
Where...
I'm gonna stay here.
Look at her face.
I couldn't look at her face.
I could just look at her teeth.
I'm moderately considerate.
Because it was definitely pulling up, guys.
Oh, my stomach.
Sorry.
Last one.
Uh...
Ow, my stomach.
I'm gonna shit my pants.
I'm no longer thinking about...
I just got killed.
Thanks.
I'm no longer thinking about...
Where the...
Like, how the stall's situated.
That shit.
If I'm gonna, like, shit my pants,
I'm going...
I gotta get in one.
Oh, he's having his password in.
What am I supposed to not look at?
Just look at the doll?
Inconsiderate.
Both of those things could be weird.
Why are you staring at my computer?
Cafe moonbucks.
Outdoor...
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's hot out.
Oh, I...
Oh, God.
Why does it have a gun?
Was it...
Maybe it was put my hands up?
Oh, here we go again.
I'm a ghost.
Why are you guys question marking me?
Why are you guys saying that's inconsiderate?
Is it really?
Because they just got a picture of a fucking ghost.
They can sell that for hundreds of thousands of dollars.
I was trying to make them money.
It's considerate to get sucked up as, like, a boba ball?
Okay.
It was three minutes?
Big bro, I'm so hungry.
Hang on.
Big brother will earn some money.
Closer Trans Am quiz.
Person who answers correctly first will get the prize.
Mount Fuji is the tallest mountain in Japan.
I don't know.
Maybe?
Probably?
What does it say?
Oh, I gotta keep the spotlight.
And you, down to the front row.
Quit throwing popcorn.
That was good.
I know I voice cracked.
I know.
This is a natural sense.
It's not something that can be trained.
Okay.
Looks like I was right about this one.
Oh, put the glasses up.
Let's keep it up.
Keep the glasses up.
Just hold them on your face at this point.
Should I let them stay down?
Take this, our finishing move.
All right.
At this rate, it'll never end.
I'm dead?
All right, can I leave?
Is it from oil tycoon?
Oh, electric vehicle.
Let's get in the electric vehicle.
E.
It was from oil tycoon.
Well, look, look at it.
What do you mean it's an oil tycoon?
I don't know.
Yeah, I don't know.
About to use the hand dryer.
Put your hands.
No, put your hands underneath this.
I'm sorry.
I need to get this right.
Oh, whatever.
Fucking just go.
You never learned how gasoline is made?
I know.
But EV, I don't know.
I want to get in the EV car.
I don't care how considerate that is.
I don't even drive an EV car.
But I want to see what the inside looks like.
Oh, shit.
Oh, I just fucking killed that person.
Taking the train with your girlfriend.
Okay.
We're going to go over here.
Right here.
This looks good.
Want to sit down?
Yeah.
Your change is 3,201 yen.
Here.
What is the other person doing with their handout?
Is that the wrong customer?
Line up.
Attention.
Right.
What?
You just said right.
I'm the only one that listened.
No, stand up.
You okay?
Mr. A isn't feeling well.
The tallest mountain in Japan is Mount Fuji.
That's true.
I am a doll made of wood.
No, that's not a lie.
My whole body is made of metal.
That's a lie.
I wanted a group date.
I invented the light bulb.
This is all lies.
I'm Mario.
That's a lie.
I was the vote of the sexiest man again this year.
I'm Mickey.
That's a lie.
Same company.
I was just scouted by a professional soccer team.
That's a lie.
They insured my legs.
No, that's true.
I couldn't go any further.
I tried to go up higher and it gets stuck.
I could only go.
I could only move it one direction or the other.
I tried to move it longer like three or four times.
It didn't work.
Consider it to let you fight.
Yeah, I tried to make the nose longer.
It didn't work.
The controls in this game are fucking ass.
I have a date with my boyfriend today.
Prairie.
I don't know.
What's that mean?
Deers love prairies.
No smoking.
Put the cigarette down.
Get out of the way.
How do I put down the cigarette?
Smoking's not the inconsiderate part of this.
I mean, it is because there's a post-it sign there.
But walking in the way of the Olympian that's lighting the torch or whatever the fuck's going on
is that's like the ultimate inconsiderate thing.
Okay, here we go.
You ready?
All right.
Boring.
Take it.
That wasn't bad.
Okay.
Who do I?
What do I do?
That person's gonna die.
All right.
So then you get on here and you switch.
Here we go.
Move the cursor.
I'll move the cursor off the screen.
I'm not going to get that.
I could probably kick it.
No.
No, I try to put my foot up, but none of the buttons work.
I'm in charge of the paper ball.
The closer the timing, the better.
What?
I've been waiting.
I wanted to put my foot out and stop the can.
Okay.
All right then.
Again.
Oh!
I literally tried to put my foot out to stop the cannon.
None of the actions did anything.
That was fine.
I wish I had a bike.
Leave it to big bro.
Road race competition.
The winner of the race will get a brand new bicycle.
Okay.
Who will win the new bicycle?
This is the final stretch.
Um, I can't.
Wait, should I not be winning?
You're an asshole.
I'm trying to slow down.
If I couldn't, I couldn't stop.
He hates it.
I saw the can in the middle of the road and I was like, do I hit the can?
So I tried to run the can over.
The can didn't knock my bike over.
Am I the, who am I?
Am I the groom?
Ladies and gentlemen, please stand for the bride.
I should have just, I should have stayed seated.
Okay.
Um, what finger does it go on?
It goes on this one, right?
What, one, two, it goes on this finger.
It doesn't go on the middle finger.
Okay.
Hooray!
Yay!
Oh, time to catch it.
Oh, I missed it.
So you just pretend like you're going to go for it but you don't actually go for it.
Because I don't want to be lined up for like another hour taking photos
with like the photographer, videographer.
You pretend like you really want to catch it and then it's like,
oh no, I missed it.
Oh, congratulations.
I don't want to line up with like, oh, bring it over here in front of the cake.
Let's take five pictures.
No, just, I don't fucking want to do that.
Okay.
Uh, don't let go.
You better not let go.
Oh, I'm not letting go.
Look, I know like when the kid's riding the bike and it's like, did you let go?
Don't let go.
Did you let go?
I fucking didn't even pay attention.
Oops.
I denied my boss work.
I give her, all right, just give everybody fucking holidays.
Give everybody a holiday.
Wait, I just, what did I just do?
I think I denied, I think I just made everybody work.
Lunch with a girl in a dress.
I didn't even, it was too fast.
I don't know where to go.
It was on the screen for less than a tenth of a second.
I don't know where it was supposed to go.
The store featured recent releases.
Texas Hold'em.
Oh, I want this one.
What about anything else?
I just woke up on my own.
Um, okay.
It was, she wasn't really by the game.
Why are you bad at this?
Explain to me how a guy flying across the screen with his lips puckered
and I'm lying down.
How am I supposed to understand what I have to do there?
What are you talking about?
Yeah, so what?
I have to get kissed?
I didn't even do anything.
I would have to sit up to get a kiss?
I don't understand.
Yeah, if you need to get out, go.
I'm not going to like close you in.
Okay, something wrong.
All right, what's wrong?
Oh, okay, I moved.
All right, move out of the way.
Am I controlling the smoke?
How is a grill sentient?
How can I be considerate with a grill smoke?
All right, cold sake.
Press the button to stop.
The button, okay.
I'm going to, that's what you want.
No use, I'm so sleepy.
I've got to take a nap.
No, that's not considerate.
Your yearly physical exam came in.
We'll start with a urine test.
Please fill this cup up.
That's right to the brim.
It's just like a party cup too, by the way.
Not even in a tight, encloseable thing.
Why was it just a big solo cup?
I'll get our tickets to the soccer game.
Only three tickets left.
No, grandma wants to go to the soccer game.
There's three tickets left.
I'm going to go get a, I'm not going to just, no.
I'm sorry, okay?
The person that looks at this guy gets shot.
So I'm not doing that.
Well, just a fucking chug in his blood.
What's considerate in a pistol duel is, okay, he cheated.
He did that literally.
Like that was too quick.
I pressed left.
That's better.
Is it not better?
Was it too much?
No, you idiot.
What are you doing?
Why would you take it away?
I didn't want to take it away.
Wrong person.
Taking in the night scenery with your girlfriend.
This person's having sex in their car.
Okay, was that a taxi?
That looked like a taxi.
The family's calling.
Mom, dad, or girl.
It's always you go right to mom.
Every dog that's ever been in my family.
Every dog, it always goes to mom.
Always.
Make little one inch bigger.
How much bigger?
Is that good?
More?
I don't know how big you want me to make little one inch.
If I could make them too big.
Wait, why am I sneaking out?
I didn't read the text.
I was too busy looking at it over here.
Everybody yelling at me.
Yeah, I like this dance.
Ooh, nice, okay.
I saw the belly move.
Cool.
All right, I did that one perfectly.
Plainly considerate.
I don't know what the scale here is.
That was a good match.
Let's head home.
I hope I clean up.
I wouldn't be, I wouldn't do this at all, by the way.
I'm not touching somebody else's trash.
I'm going to make sure that my area is perfect.
So that was, wait, what is going on?
You see when and might as then as well, right?
Yep.
But said that.
Don't fall asleep.
Can you believe it?
Ha ha ha ha.
I know, I can't believe it.
It's crazy.
Let's cross at the crosswalk.
It's not ready yet.
Do I go?
Where's the light?
That person was sitting in the middle of the intersection.
I like had to go.
Making cold Chinese noodles.
I think I did it.
Did I?
Bro, look, it's a sea turtle.
Wow, for real.
She's here to lay her eggs.
Let's watch over them.
Absolutely.
He wants to become a hero.
What?
I don't get it.
What was I supposed to do?
You were part-time for a moving company.
I didn't even get to read this.
I can't read that fast.
I'm going to put dad's DVDs at somewhere.
And that's how you solve these formulas.
This will be on the test.
Make sure to take notes.
Okay, I had to put sunglasses on?
Move out of the way.
Get out of the way.
Dodge.
What the hell's going on?
January, New Year's Day.
Exorcism rituals.
Oh, I just got exorcised.
The evil Mr. Rogue was cast down into hell.
However, since he once saved a spider in the past,
the Buddha lowered a thread of spider silk down to him.
Seeing it, he went and started climbing the thread.
But also, others crowded around, seeking to climb up as well.
Everybody stay calm.
The thread will snap if we all try to climb.
He's so smart, so persuasive.
Make a line and we'll climb one at a time.
When you reach the top, call down for the next person.
So smart.
Wait, this is...
Okay, I'm going to snip the line and fucking...
I'm not going to...
No, I'm not going to cut the thread.
I gave that opportunity, so I'm just going to take it away.
Shake.
Those people were in hell.
So don't make the offer if you don't plan on going through with it.
Did I move?
What am I doing?
Shit.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know what I was supposed to be doing.
I don't get it.
Just stand still?
Did I miss?
I'm going to tell you, ask me for my daughter's hand.
Three, two, one.
No way.
What the fuck are you talking about?
This doesn't make any sense.
I don't even know what I'm supposed to be doing.
I pressed every button once in a lifetime opportunity.
All right, open your eyes now.
All right.
You can see it.
Look at it with your eyes.
You put sunglasses on.
Whatever you're supposed to do, the special ones.
You need to look at it with the special sunglasses.
Why did the door not close?
You had to hold it there?
I couldn't.
I was trying to.
Here, eat some.
I swear to God, half the time the input doesn't do anything.
Match the rhythm and kick the whatever it is.
Okay.
On the count of three.
Nice.
Here we go.
New year in five, four, three, two, one.
What the fuck?
I pressed happy new year.
Happy new year.
Now for the next song.
Get a controller.
I might just plug a controller in, but I feel like it's not going to do anything.
I don't even see controller support on this Steam page.
Okay, so it's time to walk.
All right, walk.
Fuck.
Hey, why press button to clap hands?
Hmm?
You said clap the...
You said clap hands.
You told me to clap my hands.
Do I hatch while the mom's here?
Or hatch...
No, no, I don't want to hatch with you here.
Get the fuck out of here.
Staff, congratulations on graduating.
So be our final homeroom together until the next game, which is coming up right now.
Just a quick roll call, then we're finished.
Be sure to answer when I call your name.
The really weird thing to see looking out your window is scrolling credits.
At that point, you're in a simulation, right?
Would that be enough for you to know?
Too fast?
What?
Oh, there.
And finally, you.
After today, you will each begin walking your own path.
From time to time, you will find yourselves in situations where you will need to be considerate of others.
However, being considerate all the time isn't always a good thing.
You need to also think of yourself.
Being considerate of others and knowing when to take care of yourself are both vital skills.
I want you to become strong adults.
There is something out this window.
Okay, everybody stand and bow.
Goodbye.
So what did I get for...
What's my personality like?
What happened?
I've realized how to walk.
I just know it.
He stood up.
Yep, get right in the camera.
Camera, get the camera.
What are you doing?
Come on, what are you doing?
He messed that up.
I didn't.
Okay, total.
Generally considerate and understanding mediator.
Detailed results.
Common sense versus specified knowledge.
Above average, common sense.
Commonly understood social manners and etiquette is the first step in becoming more considerate.
I'm above average.
All right, specified knowledge.
Specialized know-how that isn't commonly known.
Having a lot of knowledge is an essential weapon for being more considerate.
Average, that's fine.
Spatial awareness and group dynamics.
Average and above average for group dynamics.
The knowledge to understand the role others expect you to play in a group.
Your cooperative nature leads to smooth teamwork.
All right.
Look at this adulting shit though.
Look at that.
Ability to step back and take in the situation then assume the roles others don't want to do.
Allowing everyone to better enjoy themselves.
And my sympathy is pretty average.
Whether or not you can put yourself in another one's shoes and understand how they feel.
Information integration is above average.
The power to instantly find the right meaning from fragmented hints with no context.
My speed is average.
The ability to immediately make decisions in any situation.
The speed to understand and react to a situation.
My rhythm is above average.
Talent of following rhythm is instructed.
Being flexible with the ability to go with the flow will be useful in being considerate.
And then interval.
Good and bad intervals.
Whether or not you understand the best timing when enacting in a series of events.
I'm really good at adulting.
All right, cool.
We got one more of these to do.
We got one more to do.
Average Andy.
I got good and above average in like four things we're talking about.
All right, I want to play the last one.
This is not all we're doing today.
Those of you freaking out saying that this is the end of the stream in like 30 minutes.
No, you're completely inaccurate.
We're going to be playing Roswell Agent after this.
For the remainder of today's stream.
And where is it?
All right, considerate three.
More and more.
Father to son in this.
Hey, Billy Bob.
Thanks for the vibe.
Immunity subs.
Agent of Roswell.
Yeah, Roswell Agent.
Agent Roswell.
I don't know, whatever it is.
Why is my screen capture not picking it up?
Hello?
There it is.
All right, I promised a face cam for this one, so I'll keep it on.
Are you purple?
It's a white balance in this room.
You're so purple.
I didn't think I was purple until you just said that.
I don't, because the white balance is wrong.
There, this is like what it's actually like in this room right now.
I'm still purple?
Whatever, I'm fucking purple.
Who cares?
All right, this is it.
Press any button.
I think they all just control the same way.
All right, let's go.
Consider it with a face cam, I promised.
Free to consider things, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yep, yep, yep, yep.
All right, number one.
So I would grab onto right here.
Because I'm not going to just stand there.
That's dangerous.
You could get hurt.
That's it.
You look like a plum.
Welcome, you.
Glad you're here.
The world is an estate at the hands of the Demon King.
Okay.
Would you help save it?
Yeah.
Money?
Yes, I'll help.
This one's correct.
Store your mayonnaise upside down.
Store some of your, most of your condiments upside down.
Store your bread upside down.
The consider it mart.
I'm just going to go to the one that has less people.
Did I bumper?
Don't change the lines.
What do you mean don't change the lines?
That helps like the store stay efficient.
And yeah, you change lines.
Oh no, I'm late.
That's going to barrel through people.
Okay, big bro.
I'm so hungry.
Big bro has something to do.
Old made championship.
All right, don't get this wrong.
Final round.
Who will win the all you can eat sushi prize?
Did I what?
I don't know.
What was I supposed to do?
I'm going to take the picture.
All right, I gotta get in.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Right here.
Am I like shouting out something?
I'm doing an ad.
All right, movie feedback.
And then be pissed that they're taking so long.
I would not stand up.
Marathon.
We'll reach the goal together.
We sure will.
All right, I'm going to make this look good.
But I still want to win.
You know what I mean?
We're almost there.
Like I won.
It was close.
It was so close.
But I fucking win.
Yeah, remember we were like neck and neck.
Yeah, it could have been anybody's game.
But it was still me.
I can't believe I won.
What the fuck?
I know.
That's not what do you mean it's bad friend?
That's a planetary ego.
A planetary ego would just be to sprint.
Take both cups of water that they were handing both of us.
Drink them both.
Throw the cups on the ground and sprint to the finish.
I stayed with my friend.
I knew I was capable of winning the race.
But I stayed with my friend.
We talked about shit.
We were hanging out jogging and we did it on our own time.
But I got in first place.
I didn't.
Somebody said going easy is not considerate.
All right, I hope it reaches him.
What?
I was supposed to hit him in the head?
Why not?
What?
That was very unclear.
Is it going to roll over me?
I found a funny video.
Yeah, let's do it.
It's going to be the two...
I knew it.
It was going to be the two lions having sex.
And this is an ad.
Why is this an ad on YouTube?
I'm not...
I want...
Why?
I would be...
Fuck the considerate shit.
I would be so confused as to why that existed.
Next stop is your stop.
Announce it.
You can be considerate...
The fuck doesn't do that?
Who doesn't do that?
If you get one of those clickable mechanical pencils,
one of the first thing you're going to do that
until it all comes all the way out.
And then you're going to try to write with it
and to be really gentle and be like,
holy shit, can I do this?
And it's going to break in half
and you're going to go, fuck, whatever.
And then you're going to pick up the pieces.
You're going to unscrew the top of the thing,
put the pieces back in because it doesn't matter.
It's not like you have to throw it away.
Going like this and going like this,
you put the lead back, the graphite back in the top.
What are you guys talking about?
You just put it back in.
You can refill them?
Yeah.
Yes, you can.
What do you mean you can't refill them?
That's, I, where, what planet are you guys on?
You did, did, did, did, did, did the slider,
did, did, did, did, did the slider.
And you put the, the eraser comes off
and you put it inside where the eraser is.
Did you not know that?
Hold on, what do I have to do?
I, did I get it?
I got it.
That is confirmed stupid.
Oh, watch out for the, yeah, old lady.
You go ahead and sit down.
But like, holy shit, fucking hurry up.
The train is moving.
Okay, we're good.
I think that would be dangerous.
If you did that to a mechanical pencil,
we would no longer be friends.
Bye bye.
Reporting from the field.
That's it from me.
Wait, should I not be over here?
It's hot.
Open the window a little.
This is a waste collection truck.
Wait, what?
TVs.
No, I, but will the smelly, smelly air come up here?
What?
I'm trying to have the, this is a waste collection truck.
Okay, I know you're trying to pay attention,
but like, it's, that's, that's good.
The author feels, I don't know if it's okay that,
I opened the window and it said,
we're a garbage collection truck.
I don't know.
I figured they was going to go in there and smell.
Can you, are you going to do something about that?
I think I'm pretty considerate.
Come back.
What?
Is he muted?
Stand up.
Sit, no, don't sit.
Should I sit?
I feel like this is way more inconsiderate
than just standing and not leaning back like an asshole.
Come back up.
Uh, dude, I can't pull it back up.
I don't understand.
None of them worked.
I don't, I don't, I don't, what the fuck?
I'm a crab.
All right.
Should I get out of the way?
Go in the water.
I have to hold it?
I did.
I swear to God.
Good luck in Tokyo.
Yeah, I'll write to you.
Yeah.
Uh, that's fucking, that was creepy.
It's like, I'm making sure you're actually on the train in the seat.
For what?
For some reason.
Like, I got to make sure you're actually sitting down doing that
because I'm about to go this way real fast and, and do something.
It's weird.
Why would you need to, it's weird.
Psychotic behavior.
Hey, where are the dentists?
Raise your hand if you feel any pain.
We're almost done.
This hurts a little more.
It hurts.
You didn't give me an Innova can, you fucking monster doctor.
What are you doing?
It hurts.
Wait.
Oh no.
Okay.
I was like, where should I go?
Is it inconsiderate to say you're in pain?
That's what I'm saying.
Like what?
If a dentist is just drilling my mouth and it hurts, I'm going to go like this.
Right?
Wait, hold on.
Got it.
Nice.
Yeah.
You make an audible like.
If somebody's drilling inside your mouth, you do not want to make a bunch of movements.
Like if somebody has a drill sticking out of your fucking mouth,
I don't want to be like, oh, that hurt me.
Ouchies.
No, that they'll fuck.
No way.
You go like this.
And then they go, fuck.
Okay.
All right.
Turn the wind down.
And then when you hear the drill, power down.
They look at you.
Everything okay?
And then you go, oh, I hurt because he's still afraid something back it up.
Oh my God.
That was a lot of power.
I was not expecting that.
Dude, that's weird.
Am I supposed to be falling off?
No, I think I said to get it.
Downloading 27%.
How would it go backwards?
That made no sense.
I pressed to like, I was trying to.
Okay.
Look at this graph.
I was trying to fill it.
They made apps of fucking.
The guy's fly is done.
Broccoli broccoli.
And then the ketchup and then I don't.
What am I looking at here?
This food.
What the fuck?
Oh, I'm putting a condiment on my food.
I thought I was selecting what food I wanted to eat first in what order.
This cow is so cute.
Yeah, let's get some lunch.
I'm starving.
Why are we crying?
That was sad.
A comment.
Oh, I like this.
I liked this video.
I guess I have a date with my boyfriend today.
Okay.
I mean, it's fine.
Yeah, that's fine.
Going in the haunted house with your boyfriend.
It's scary.
Hold me.
What?
Why are we putting our hands up?
Why did he, why was he freaked out by that?
Next up, a roller coaster with my boyfriend.
Here we go.
We're going to have fun.
Whoa, that was crazy.
Did you have fun?
Oh, you, you listen to it too together.
That's always like a nice thing to do.
But unfortunately, it's like really impractical because if usually you'll forget, it's the,
it's really this far, right?
You don't have very much distance.
So, so one of the two will forget that it's in and just be like, oh, cool.
And go over here.
And it like essentially like fucking strangles the person and like rips out of their ear
and shit just simply by tilting your head like, like this.
It sucks.
I'm surprised they haven't made like just a quad earbud thing at this point.
Like to prevent this from happening.
Why not just have like a, I mean, you can get a splitter,
but why not make one that's just like four so we can both listen.
I have that wireless.
No, but I want to be connected.
Wireless means we can literally sit across the fucking room.
If you have a TV or something, or you have like a big iPad or phone,
I can like sit over here.
I want to be like close, but not constricted.
You understand?
Because then one of us can go like this.
You know, one of us can be like, oh, look at this.
And they're like, oh, that's cute.
That's the fuck.
Come on.
You guys don't know how to be cute.
Give me a break.
It's time to pay the bill.
Oh, no, no, it's okay.
All right, fine.
You can pay for it.
I got a date tomorrow.
Tomorrow's the field trip.
Tomorrow's the outdoor concert.
I'm not going to like attack with a fucking tornado.
There we go.
Just enough for me to drop the fucking energy beam, right?
There comes, there comes a monster attack.
What's today's date?
Oh shit.
No, I'll take, I'll take the one that's half off.
Thanks, demon weather god.
Hurry up, hurry up, hurry up, hurry up, hurry up.
Yeah, you can take that.
You can do it.
That's fine.
It really depends on how far away you are.
If, okay, if I can see you across the grocery store
and you're making your way here, I'm going in front of you.
If you are within like 10 to 15 feet, then yeah, I'll do that.
But I'm sorry, if you, if you're like across the whole store,
I don't know, you could be going to a different aisle.
I don't know.
And you're yelling, hurry up.
That was you and me talking about that.
I wouldn't, that, hold on.
First of all, what's going on?
Excuse me.
Pay attention.
Can I turn around and say like, watch where you're fucking going?
Camping experience tour.
Start a fire.
Get a fire going before I, should I put the sun out?
Get a fire going so I can go to bed.
Get a fire started.
They just suck.
Consider it.
The title is partially displayed.
Wait, are we playing the game?
Oh, consider it together.
We're going to play the co-op.
You became stranded.
Do I keep, I gotta keep him awake?
Could you get us some tea, please?
Sure.
Green tea.
That's what they wanted, right?
Okay, here you go.
What?
What'd I do?
Okay.
And you make mine a little sweet.
Got it.
One.
That's it.
People are weird about sugar in their coffee.
Some people take one sip of something with one sugar in it
and they like want to spit it out.
And some people want like 50 sugars in it
and they think it tastes bland.
I don't even know what the fuck they were just saying.
Heaven.
I don't do sugar for people.
Ever.
If somebody ever tells you,
oh yeah, you just put some sugar in it for me.
You go, no.
You bring over a few of sugars
or a few packets of whatever or like sweetener
and you just say, here you go.
I'm not responsible for that
because people don't like it.
Turtles are so slow.
Whoa, that's not true.
Wanna race me?
Sure.
They didn't tell me it was Mario Kart.
Oh, I just like killed the turtle and the bunny.
I win.
That's the most important part.
I'm trying to switch them.
Were we together?
Uh, just to come out of the snow?
What's considerate about that?
Oh shit, Darth Vader.
How long does it need to be?
Make it like a spear.
Okay.
Would you get us some tea, please?
Yes, I can.
How do I stop pouring?
There we go.
You hear that.
How do I stop pouring?
I don't know how to stop pouring.
I don't understand.
How do I stop?
Whoa, that's a little too much though.
That's not considerate.
Well, it didn't do the thing where you stand in front.
So you get them moving
and then you go into the front.
So you stand in front of them while they're going like this
and you go like, no, whoa!
When they get close
and you pretend like you got flew backwards from them.
You're not doing that.
That's inconsiderate.
All right.
Considerate.
Which considerate is this?
Three.
What was he talking about?
Do I have to explain that?
I'm a guide bot.
If you want to know where to go, just ask me.
People always force me to work.
I'll revenge you one day.
Lost kid.
Lost.
Go that way.
That way.
Going to the arcade with my boyfriend.
Punch.
Fight.
The boyfriend did it really well.
Should I go lower?
Way stronger.
All right.
That's all right.
Whatever.
It wasn't my fault,
but I have to apologize in the next three seconds.
What button is apologize?
It was left.
What is that?
I don't know what this is.
They put it out.
I don't know what that was.
It was a fireworks sparkler.
Why would I be holding it upside down?
Who holds it like this?
Like that.
What are you?
Out of your mind?
You became stranded again.
Buddy, you're a boy.
I can't do this.
Nobody can do that.
That's what I'm supposed to do.
Not even going to attempt.
I'm not doing another like singing thing
and get all fucked up from it.
Working from home today.
Some rest.
It was almost a funny number.
Uh-oh.
Not good.
Can't hold it in.
Can't hold who?
Oh, shit.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Okay.
Little flush.
What are you doing for your birthday?
Maybe I should start preparing something.
Now, if you want to hide,
you want to hide,
here's a pro tip for all of you.
If you want to hide
and you're like,
holy shit,
what am I going to do?
I'm in the bathroom right now.
I don't want them to hear me in the bathroom.
Okay.
Here's what you have to do.
You do a flush.
You hold that thing down.
You do a big fucking flush.
And when you hear the like,
go, go, go, go, go,
it going into the tank,
like down into the tube.
That's when you shit.
You should go, you shit right there.
The sound will,
it'll be masked.
It'll be sounding like the end of the toilet.
Like that.
Trust me.
If you time it right,
no one will fucking ever know what happened.
I'm eating.
Happy birthday.
Blow my candle up.
How cute.
Ha ha ha ha ha.
What?
I couldn't do it.
Oh, I'm the candle.
How do I go back up?
I can't.
I'm holding up arrow right now.
All I can do is hold down.
That was wicked fucked up.
The thing I just said,
but whatever.
It works.
Be careful.
Don't go too,
you got to be gentle.
You want more slices?
What kind of weirdo?
Okay.
Hello.
I'm ZZ,
the VTuber.
Just have to adjust a few settings.
Hold on a second.
Extra large.
I brought my own bottle.
All right.
That's enough.
You don't need to take the whole goddamn thing.
That's how I feel when you put the cam on.
Oh, get out of here.
Train your brain.
Guess how many people are left in the house?
One, two, three.
There could have been people in there before.
Three.
There's one person left.
I don't know.
Input your answer.
I, but it didn't,
I don't have all the info though.
Right?
Like there could be somebody actually in there still.
It could be somebody else's house.
Oh, 911.
I'm for the explosion scene.
I mean, it's everything with explosions.
There's only one chance.
You got it.
That was perfect.
Would you get us some tea, please?
Yes.
Water, milk.
How do I, how do I make tea?
There's no tea.
Is there tea bags?
Where's tea?
There's no tea.
I haven't lunch with a client today.
Okay.
We're going to go to the family diner.
The cabaret?
I see.
Please take care of it.
Understood.
It's like a chatter.
All right.
Watch out.
What do I do?
Um, oh, it's, I'm the bullet.
Nice job.
But like, I, the water is probably considerate, right?
I would think so.
Uh, catch this person.
I don't know if that was considered or not.
The end.
Oh, right.
No, but I, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look.
I, look at, look at me, look at me.
During the credits, what you do is you slowly start to get up.
You start to do the thing where everyone starts to stretch a little bit.
You get into the aisle.
What's the fuck is going, what?
Turn the cam off.
Um, anyways.
Everybody gets up and you slowly make your way into the aisle
and you just walk like one mile per hour.
You walk so slow.
What am I doing here?
Exit.
Oh, it was the kids wanted me to do that.
Okay.
That it?
That what I, I got my fingers all over the sauce.
All right, that's fucking disgusting.
I would actually be pissed about that.
What am I doing with my hands?
Why is it no like fork or chopsticks or utensil or what?
I don't understand.
Why would I be dipping sushi like that with my hands?
Fork?
I don't know.
I use chopsticks.
It's the traditional way.
What?
Eating sushi with your hand?
I'd never ask for a fork.
I always use chopsticks.
I know how to use them.
You eat sushi with your hands.
It's a hand food.
That's the traditional way.
Oh, prove it.
When we come back from break, after this game is done,
I'll, I'll go get chopsticks and I'll show you that I can use them.
Fine.
Fork works better.
I'm, don't say that.
Watch out.
I'm very, everyone's really upset about you for saying that.
Would it be, what am I doing?
I'm drinking a lot of drinks.
Only just drink two.
When it comes to men, there are just so many of them.
I'm sure there's someone out there, yeah, who can see me from where I am.
That's right.
Two drinks, no more than that.
Will you back me up?
I'm sorry, but like, get out of the fucking way.
I didn't mean to bump you, but like, I'm very clearly way ahead of you by now.
But get out of the fucking way.
You don't own the sidewalk, fuck off.
Am I waiting for somebody?
Am I waiting for someone?
It looked like she was waiting for somebody.
I'm going to set off the fireworks.
Timing is everything with fireworks.
I had a great time today.
Um, uh, shit, I have to fill it.
Please marry me.
I'm giving you material to work with.
Uh, sure.
This is weird.
Are we dancing?
What am I doing?
This is something that like really has to pee.
I don't understand what I'm supposed to be doing.
Oh, all right.
But let me, let me defend myself for the last thing I said.
So if you're taking up a whole sidewalk, like if you look, if you want to stop and,
oh, look at that.
Let's look, we're sightseeing.
That's fine.
That's great.
But like, if you're not going to take a picture, right?
If you're not taking, oh, hey, let me get a good photo of that.
Go over there.
Oh, cool.
Yeah.
How about right here?
Right?
You give people the space to like, okay, you can take a photo.
But if you're just sitting there standing in the middle of like, and blocking the whole way,
there's nothing in my, nothing I can do to make you leave or make you move.
Right?
So it's, it's, it's inconsiderate.
That's very inconsiderate.
If you are with somebody and there's people behind you that are just walking,
you go, oh, that's really cool.
Come over here for a sec.
Like you step kind of on the edge and like, oh, yeah, yeah, cool.
Good.
People are just walking by one, two, three.
All right.
We've got a gap of like this, like not a person for like another minute, two minutes.
Let's go back into the sidewalk and fucking look around.
There we are.
You got to be aware of people walking on the sidewalk.
Otherwise you get a situation with someone.
You don't know what somebody has to be.
Throw the sword out, defend thyself.
Okay, Mr. David.
There was an honest woodcutter.
One day he dropped his precious axe in a lake.
A goddess then returned it to him or maybe not.
What kind of axe did you drop?
A golden axe or a silver axe?
Or was it this?
I mean, this is, this is a lot.
I can't lie to like a goddess.
They'll know.
Now they give me the golden one because I was truthful.
That's how this works.
I'm going to sneeze.
Okay.
I don't know if I got it or not.
I might have.
Hopefully I got it.
Train your brain.
What do you see?
Answer in English.
Apple.
Carrie.
I really like that lion having sex joke.
Okay.
I'm pregnant.
So I'm going to sit down.
Oh, sit down.
Thank you.
Why are the animals in here?
You.
That was bizarre.
I don't know.
Very vaguely considerate.
Down to the last five.
What am I doing?
Whoa.
What?
I don't get it.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
I think I have to get this all the way across.
All right.
Got it.
Another one.
When should I wake?
Three?
What time do I wake?
I don't know when to wake it up.
Did I not have done that?
I don't know.
We're running like a schedule.
Okay.
We need a baby.
Everybody in the frame.
Everyone's looking.
Got it.
Well, you weren't that happy, but it's all right.
At least we're all looking in the right direction.
You woke the baby up at 3 a.m.
Hey, you.
My, how the time flies.
You're already three.
It seems that my time as a mother will pass in a flash.
Got nothing to say about this one.
I had a dream yesterday.
You say that's more like me.
That might be so.
I wonder if one day this child will be considerate too.
Nowadays, don't they say that being too considerate when it comes to others is a fault?
Since everyone's different, you need to be considerate.
You have...
Everybody, wait a minute.
He's going like...
I'm so...
I was fucking...
That was weird.
That was strange.
That was...
I...
That was fucking weird.
With somebody's leg?
Yeah, I know.
But like, it was fucking weird.
It was a weird spot.
That was in a weird spot.
All right.
Turn the page.
Dirty.
Oh, no.
I'm just saying like it was fucking jarring for a second.
I was just like...
So I thought it was like his arm down there.
But both of his arms are up here.
And there was another arm like coming up here.
It was a leg.
It was a knee.
All right.
Ban all conversations.
Just lock it down right now.
Lock it down right now.
Lock it down quick.
I've made...
I've ruined it.
But...
Lock it down.
Ban all conversations.
What do you mean?
Get over here.
How did we do?
Not that great with timing.
Okay.
Generally considerate, a kind-hearted hot pot maestro.
I want to see the detailed...
I couldn't even read the...
I hit tab.
It didn't do anything.
What?
Can I go...
Okay, here we go.
All right.
Whoa.
Disappointing in group dynamics in this one.
The knowledge to understand the role others expect you to play in a group.
I think so.
What about interval?
Good and bad intervals?
My spatial awareness is big.
Shut it down.
Not five minutes ago.
It was a scene.
It was lying down like this.
And there was a sensor bar down there covering me.
It was like a sensor thing on him.
And then it was like, oh, here's another photo of like,
dad or whatever.
Like going like this.
And I'm...
I have defenses here.
I have a defense.
What's wrong with you?
And nothing's wrong with me!
All right, so that was considerate.
That was considerate.
It was a really fun experience.
I had a great time.
There's nothing wrong with me.
I'm going to get chopsticks to prove to you that I can use them.
And then we're going to go from there.
We're going to play the Roswell game.
You failed every test.
I did not.
I got like a 70 on everything.
We're going to take a three-minute break.
I'm going to get some water.
I'm going to pee.
And we'll just switch to Roswell Agent, whatever it's called.
70 is a C.
That's fine.
I passed.
All right, I'll be right back.
See you guys in a minute.
We're going to play the Alien game.
That was considerate.
One, two, and three.
That was very fun.
It was very engaging.
I really liked it.
I thought it was really fun.
I think it's like 10 bucks for the whole series.
It might be like $12 for all three of those games.
So it's like, you know, get like a few hours of fun out of it.
Like 10 bucks.
Yeah, it was fun.
See you in a minute.