Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with Surgeon Simulator 2013, and if you're wondering why I'm already laughing in this video, it's because this game is absolutely insane.
It's one of the most hysterical games I've ever played in my life. I just did a trial run like two seconds ago to kind of know what I was getting myself into.
And, holy, everybody that has a PC, this game is free. It's for the Global Game Jam for this past week.
And holy shit, guys, you gotta go play this game right now. So let me try to explain what's going on here.
So what you have to do is you have to perform a heart surgery. Now, that might sound like a pretty standard game.
There's a lot of games like that within the surgery type genre. But this is unlike any other you've ever played in your life.
If you've ever played QWOP, this is just like the game QWOP. You are given a task to do, and the game just mulls it all up for you.
You have to, like, for instance, look at my left hand. My left hand is A-W-E-R space, and that's to move my fingers.
And then on my right hand, it's the mouse. So left mouse button lowers the hand, and right mouse button is going to rotate the hand, and the mouse, of course, moves my hand around.
So the goal here is you have to perform an open heart surgery on this dude. And I don't know how you can play, how you can do this without screwing it up.
But I'm going to show you right now. Here we go. Surgeon Simulator 2013, baby. Let's do it. Perform a heart transplant.
Okay, I got my fingers all in check, and let's go. Don't mind me, sir. I'm just going to, like, remove this off your body.
No, give me it. I'm having trouble getting the guy's, like, frigging, like, Jimmy cloth off, whatever the hell this thing is.
All right, I don't want to, like, mess up the desk. Hold on. Put this over here. Why is my arm rotated? It didn't even do anything.
All right. You know what? Just go. My tools. I need those tools. No, get over here.
Get this stupid drape off the goddamn table. I just threw, like, the radio down.
All right, success. I have moved the drape off the table. All right, we got to get to the guy's heart.
All right, let's go with the bone saw. Come here. No, I don't want to rotate my head.
No, that's the guy's heart. That's the second heart I have to put in. Can I not move this and get out of the way?
Seriously, get out of the freaking way. All right, I'm going to saw his bones off. We're going to get to his heart. Here we go.
This does not seem to be doing anything. You know what? Just throw it. Get rid of it. No, his heart.
He's going to sharp object him with his heart now. Let's go with the hammer. All right, I'm just breaking in.
Give me this. Give me the hammer. Come on. Give me the hammer. Oh, sorry, dude. I really do apologize about this.
Break it. Just break in. Just smash it. Get me into his heart. Get me into his lungs.
They need to rename this game like Lawsuit 2013 because if you were a doctor and you did this to somebody.
Oh, my God. Well, welcome to like a legal battle that you would be in for like six weeks. Oh, I got it. Nice.
All right. I OK. Got it. Roger that. The guy's OK. Just get out of the way. Get me. His bones are literally everywhere.
I feel so bad for this dude right now. Why is my middle fell? You know what? Oh, I got.
Hey, hey, buddy. Sorry. Middle finger, baby.
All right. That was really immature. Now my wrist is broken. All right. Let's go get this heart. I could wear my hands.
Got it. Under control. It's all under control.
Get his heart out of there. Get these friggin bones out. There we go.
All right. Here we go. Now I need my scalpel to cut them out. You know, just bring them all. Bring every scalpel in.
Oh, shit. Am I even gripping this correct? I don't even know what I'm trying to aim at right now.
Get down there. Slice open his ventricle. I can't even like get this thing to do what it's supposed to do.
Here we go. No, no, not quite. Not quite. Do I have to get rid of the bones? Oh, shit.
Well, I dropped that one in there, too. A-W-E-R. Here we go. All right.
Oh, man. This is the most awkward thing ever. This is literally so friggin awkward.
Hey, you need like a friggin... Let's take a look at your chart. Oh, no.
That was the heart. That was the heart I needed to replace. It's over.
Dude, I lost the game. I can't do anything now.
I just chucked the guy's transplant heart across the room.
Well, oh, there we go. I was supposed to turn my wrist. Well, you don't get a heart now, man. Sorry.
Sorry. Why is this not cutting? I feel like I'm like shit-faced.
All right, I got it. It's done. Pick it up. Pick it up. Just rip it out of him.
Hey, you know what? You know what I got to say about that? Get out of here. Yeah.
Well, I absolutely... I lost the game. I seriously cannot go get the heart that's over here, so I lose.
Well, that's Surgeon Simulator 2013, guys. If you can do this without destroying your everything...
Wow, that's kind of crazy I can do that.
Link is in the description for this game, guys. You have to go check it out. You have to go play it.
Anyways, thank you so much for watching. Everybody really do appreciate it.
And I'll see you guys all next time. And of course, take care, everybody. Out!