Everything is multiplied by 10. I've heard about this. I've seen people play it. It's supposed to be crazy. I'm going demo night. And here we go. Oh, I thought someone was gonna be right there. I got somebody. Retrieving server info. They're being short. I'm so scared. I just have no idea what I'm in store for here. All I know is it's nuts.
Ow. Who has the Jurati every three seconds? What is happening?
I'm gonna have the coolest intro ever.
I didn't even hit that guy.
I'm gonna be like, actually I'll just do it when I'm in the game and then I start recording.
This is gonna be funny.
I wonder how much health I can have as a demo night like this. And how fast I can run.
Oh man.
As a scout, the shortstop and pistol share the same ammo.
You can't even walk over there.
Be mindful of your ammo while you both have equipped. While you have both equipped well.
There's rockets launching in all directions.
You're in?
3, 2, 1.
Hey guys, what's going on? I'm playing TF2 because you guys were like, hey, playing with Jervis. So I'm like, okay, Jervis, you wanna play with TF2? And he's like, yeah, dude. And then we're playing TF2 so here we are.
Yeah, dude.
I was trying to do the impression.
I'm never gonna be able to get out of here and get stabbed.
I got a double kill.
Oh my god, I did it. Oh my god, dude.
Time for a rampage. It is time for a complete rampage.
Oh man.
It's time for a complete rampage.
Are you serious? I just don't want to get backstabbed.
This is insanity, man.
Nobody can kill me.
What the shit is happening right now?
I'm unkillable. I'm unkillable. I am legitimately unkillable.
How come?
Because I have this thing.
Shit.
No, I got backstabbed by a spy. Shit.
Did you get a lot of kills?
I did. I did.
I had just about 2,000.
I was still trying to...
Geez, what the why?
Why do you have so much health?
No, not anymore.
Wait, you're Demoman, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, it's right. You go...
It won't blow up.
And I'm right clicking.
I don't know.
That doesn't seem right.
Yeah, it doesn't. What the hell?
Look at all these explosions.
I see a letter.
You fell and died.
Ah, fuck.
Give me that kill.
Yeah, I have like so many of them and they won't...
Do I have to wait a while?
I'm in a really good position right now.
No, maybe it's because of that item.
Maybe. I don't know.
Ah, okay.
I got so...
Ah, geez, I just barely noticed this guy is trying to attack me.
Don't get away from me.
You got peed on.
Oh, dear.
This is bad.
This is bad for him.
Why do I have this much health?
This just seems so unbelievably ridiculous.
Oh, geez.
How did I not kill him?
All right, buddy.
You know what?
We're doing this.
I don't even have to disguise anymore.
I don't...
Come on, boy.
It doesn't matter.
I'm invincible.
You can't defeat me.
You're insane.
If you could only see the insanity that was just my screen.
I'll check out the video.
Oh, man.
Sorry.
You want to...
Just come and hit me.
Fine.
You know...
Oh, wow.
You're dead.
This guy's gonna die too.
I'm not dead.
Oh, not you.
These people.
I just don't want to get backstabbed.
I just see Devilman's like flying in the sky and shit.
I'm so confused.
As long as I do not get backstabbed, I will live forever.
Because I'm just going to face stab people and stuff.
Oh, man.
What is it?
Why does my gun glow?
I don't get this.
What is it?
My gun glows like neon blue, green, whatever.
Oh, I'm losing health.
Losing health quick.
No, I died.
Mini crits.
Oh, mini crits.
I don't know anything about this game.
I got switched.
I'm on.
I'm on red.
Where are we going?
We are going...
I forgot this map.
To A. Come with me to A. We are going to defend A by ourselves.
We're going to defend A by ourselves?
Yes.
Oh, boy.
We're going to defend A by ourselves, and we're going to stick a middle finger into the blue
team because they're going to get 150,000 crits.
Oh, dear, you can do that too.
Yeah, with the other one.
I'm going to have...
It's a vintage one.
Keep coming this way.
I have a...
I'm going to have a crits for you like every 15 seconds.
Follow me.
Follow me, Spoon.
Oh, you have to look at them.
I'm so dumb.
They come from here.
See, like up there?
All right, Spoon, over here, and do hold the button down and shoot a bunch of them into...
Shoot all those grenades into that door.
Oh, to the right.
To the right.
Oh, jeez.
They came out of the other one.
Are you ready?
Here we go.
Kill them.
Oh, they ubered.
Oh.
No.
Get back.
Crits won't save us now.
You don't know me like that.
Shoot them.
Get back.
You don't know me like that.
I'm actually not killing you.
Oh, demo.
I have so much health.
Demo Knight.
Random Demo Knight appeared.
Random Demo Knight.
No, no.
I had a crit too.
Ah.
Dude.
How much health was I healing you for?
I wasn't.
You were not dying.
All right.
Come on out.
I got a crits for you.
Damn it.
I can't believe they haven't capped B yet.
That's pretty surprising.
Because I'm working my ass off over here.
Oh, man.
It's just me.
No one else exists.
There we go.
Let's see how this works.
Kidding.
What on earth is this?
What is going?
What on earth?
Ah, I know.
He's just shooting me up in the air.
What a jerk.
He's just launching all over the place.
He's just spinning around.
Oh, what the beggar's bazooka.
I get it.